1
00:01:06,880 --> 00:01:09,130
傲骨之战

2
00:01:06,880 --> 00:01:09,130
第一季 第五集

3
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:06,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:06,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

5
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:06,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

6
00:00:01,500 --> 00:00:06,000
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

7
00:00:01,500 --> 00:00:06,000
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

8
00:00:01,500 --> 00:00:06,000
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

9
00:00:01,500 --> 00:00:06,000
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

10
00:00:01,500 --> 00:00:06,000
原创翻译  双语字幕

11
00:00:02,000 --> 00:00:06,000
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利

12
00:00:07,220 --> 00:00:37,730
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

13
00:00:06,720 --> 00:00:37,730
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

14
00:00:07,730 --> 00:00:12,730
翻译      Alex  秋乙一  Margaery  吃冰棒  dzysteven

15
00:00:12,730 --> 00:00:17,730
翻译      capitaljack  一点都不酷喵  charcie  半半子七

16
00:00:17,730 --> 00:00:22,730
校对      free维塔  某羽

17
00:00:22,730 --> 00:00:27,730
时间轴      风吹来的那片云

18
00:00:27,730 --> 00:00:32,730
后期      你是不是饿得慌

19
00:00:32,730 --> 00:00:37,730
总监      free维塔

20
00:01:09,820 --> 00:01:12,380
你能用这个洋娃娃示意下他都摸你哪里了
Can you show me on this doll where he touched you?

21
00:01:12,400 --> 00:01:13,720
全身上下
It was everywhere.

22
00:01:13,850 --> 00:01:15,140
全身...
It was...

23
00:01:15,960 --> 00:01:18,940
参议员泰德·韦勒竞选办公室
第五大街韦勒塔楼625号
11月8日星期二

24
00:01:20,240 --> 00:01:22,790
我没做过
I didn't do it.

25
00:01:23,270 --> 00:01:24,150
她在说谎
She's lying.

26
00:01:24,150 --> 00:01:26,260
那也要接受传票审讯  韦勒先生  所以
Well, we still need to answer the subpoena, Mr. Weller, so...

27
00:01:26,260 --> 00:01:28,090
好  我的回答是  去死吧
Yeah, well, I have the answer: go to hell.

28
00:01:28,570 --> 00:01:30,660
我没强奸任何人  我没性骚扰任何人
I didn't rape anyone, I didn't molest anyone.

29
00:01:29,600 --> 00:01:36,130
芝加哥电视剧禁播集

30
00:01:30,660 --> 00:01:31,900
我对这种事嗤之以鼻
It just makes me sick.

31
00:01:32,810 --> 00:01:34,900
是因为竞选  他们以为拿些事情抹黑我
It's this campaign, they think they can say anything about me

32
00:01:34,910 --> 00:01:36,130
就能让人觉得是真的
and make it stick.

33
00:01:37,250 --> 00:01:40,360
所以  我们现在成为反特朗普律所吗
So, what, are we the anti-Trump firm now?

34
00:01:40,360 --> 00:01:42,670
不是这个原因  这事关「宪法第一修正案」
That's not what this is about; that's a First Amendment issue.

35
00:01:40,360 --> 00:01:42,670
保护言论与信仰自由以及和平集会权

36
00:01:42,680 --> 00:01:44,450
这和「宪法第一修正案」有什么关系
How is it a First Amendment issue?

37
00:01:44,540 --> 00:01:46,630
我们说的可是一家电视台
We're talking about a-a TV network,

38
00:01:46,630 --> 00:01:49,270
不是美国政府  这事和「宪法第一修正案」没关系
not the U.S. Government; that is not a First Amendment issue.

39
00:01:49,270 --> 00:01:52,240
朱利叶斯  特朗普政府给电视台施压
Julius, the Trump administration is pressuring the TV network;

40
00:01:52,240 --> 00:01:52,890
这就涉及到「宪法第一修正案」了  朱利叶斯
that makes it a First Amendment issue, Julius.

41
00:01:52,890 --> 00:01:55,070
他们如何给电视台施压
How are they pressuring the TV networks?

42
00:01:55,070 --> 00:01:56,290
我们说的是一家电视台
We're talking about a network

43
00:01:56,290 --> 00:01:58,190
拍了一集电视剧最后决定不播了
that shot an episode and chose not to air it.

44
00:01:58,190 --> 00:01:59,790
说个简单的事实  你给那个男人投了票
Simple matter of the fact, you voted for the man.

45
00:01:59,800 --> 00:02:01,790
-就是这个原因  -总算说到重点了
- That's what this is about. - Oh, there it is! There he is.

46
00:02:01,790 --> 00:02:03,620
一个给特朗普投票的黑人
The black man who voted for Trump.

47
00:02:03,630 --> 00:02:04,690
你给他投的票  我可没有
You voted for him, not me.

48
00:02:04,690 --> 00:02:06,640
拜托  消停点  先生们
Wait, gentlemen, please,

49
00:02:06,640 --> 00:02:09,900
我们问题的焦点在于要不要接这个案子
the only question before us is whether we take this case.

50
00:02:09,900 --> 00:02:10,900
不好意思
Uh, I'm sorry.

51
00:02:11,310 --> 00:02:12,090
什么案子
What is the case?

52
00:02:12,090 --> 00:02:15,380
我认识的一个芝加哥电视系列的编剧
A writer I know is one of those Chicago shows.

53
00:02:15,570 --> 00:02:18,280
他写了一集从现实取材的电视剧
He wrote a ripped-from-the-headline episode

54
00:02:18,280 --> 00:02:19,250
主角是唐纳德·特朗普
about Donald Trump.

55
00:02:19,910 --> 00:02:21,010
一个虚构的特朗普
A fictional Trump.

56
00:02:21,010 --> 00:02:24,140
基于他曾强奸一名13岁孩子的指控
It's based on the accusation - that he raped a 13-year-old.

57
00:02:24,510 --> 00:02:26,020
根本没有指控
there was no accusation.

58
00:02:26,020 --> 00:02:27,540
诉讼被撤销了
The lawsuit was dropped,

59
00:02:27,550 --> 00:02:29,690
而且原告的名字也从未公布
and the accuser never even let her name go public.

60
00:02:29,700 --> 00:02:31,430
因为她不想与总统为敌
Because she didn't want to go up against the president.

61
00:02:31,430 --> 00:02:33,000
这个总统可是说过...
This is the same president that said...

62
00:02:33,000 --> 00:02:35,050
你听说这个男人曾经说过
Have you listened to anything the man said...

63
00:02:33,010 --> 00:02:35,050
如果是奥巴马或者克林顿
Oh, if it was Obama or Clinton,

64
00:02:35,050 --> 00:02:36,840
你就觉得没问题了
you would have been fine with that.

65
00:02:36,730 --> 00:02:39,840
反残疾人  反妇女
Anti-disabled people, anti-women.

66
00:02:37,020 --> 00:02:39,320
我们能不能回到主题上来
Can we please stay on topic?

67
00:02:40,330 --> 00:02:41,870
电视台延后了播期
The network delayed the broadcast,

68
00:02:41,870 --> 00:02:43,320
所以编剧把它放上网
so the writer put it online.

69
00:02:44,150 --> 00:02:46,010
电视台要以偷窃罪提起诉讼
And the network is suing for theft?

70
00:02:46,010 --> 00:02:48,200
没错  1200万
Yes, for $12 million.

71
00:02:48,700 --> 00:02:50,640
他担心电视网出于对总统的忌讳
He was afraid they weren't going to show the episode

72
00:02:50,650 --> 00:02:52,230
不会播出这一集
due to the fear of the president.

73
00:02:52,640 --> 00:02:53,620
他没有律师
He's lost his lawyer,

74
00:02:53,620 --> 00:02:55,460
所以他要我们来代理他
so he's asking us to represent him.

75
00:02:56,080 --> 00:02:58,510
拜托  此事无关政见
Hello! This is not about politics.

76
00:02:58,510 --> 00:03:01,190
-我知道啊  你和他说  -你准备怎么做
- I know that, tell him. - What's your strategy?

77
00:03:01,570 --> 00:03:03,910
你不能辩护盗窃罪  他以此为荣
You can't argue against the theft. He's proud of his crime.

78
00:03:03,910 --> 00:03:07,040
-他拿它吹嘘  -我没说我们要辩护盗窃罪
- He brags about it. - I'm not saying we should argue against theft.

79
00:03:07,060 --> 00:03:08,600
朱利叶斯  朱利叶斯
Julius, Julius,

80
00:03:08,600 --> 00:03:11,380
我是说我们可以用「告密法」
I'm saying we should use the Whistleblower Laws.

81
00:03:11,380 --> 00:03:12,790
不行  阿德里安  他没被解雇
Mm-mm, Adrian, he was not fired.

82
00:03:12,790 --> 00:03:14,700
没错  他没被解雇  阿德里安
Exactly, he wasn't fired, Adrian.

83
00:03:14,710 --> 00:03:16,420
你有什么法律策略
What's your legal strategy?

84
00:03:16,430 --> 00:03:19,020
如果我们接了这个案子  你总得有辩护点
If we take this case, you need to argue something.

85
00:03:19,270 --> 00:03:20,470
试试"正当使用"这点
Try fair use.

86
00:03:23,200 --> 00:03:24,310
怎么切入  戴安
In what way, Diane?

87
00:03:24,740 --> 00:03:27,110
出于批判的目的
Copyright material may be quoted verbatim

88
00:03:27,110 --> 00:03:29,160
可以对版权材料进行逐字引用
for purposes such as criticism.

89
00:03:29,620 --> 00:03:30,630
那是批判
That's criticism.

90
00:03:30,630 --> 00:03:32,320
我们的当事人引用作品
Our client is quoting the work

91
00:03:32,320 --> 00:03:34,350
来表明电视台所遭受的寒蝉效应
to show the chilling effect on his network.

92
00:03:32,320 --> 00:03:34,350
指害怕后果而不敢发表言论

93
00:03:34,350 --> 00:03:37,330
伙计们  这个论点不错
People, it's good. It's good.

94
00:03:39,210 --> 00:03:40,760
阿德里安  能和你谈谈吗
Adrian, do you have a minute?

95
00:03:42,790 --> 00:03:45,070
说吧  我们为什么要做这些
Okay, why are we doing this?

96
00:03:47,800 --> 00:03:49,370
芝加哥电视制片方
Chicago TV production.

97
00:03:50,420 --> 00:03:51,750
这可是个大新闻  芭芭拉
It's blowing up, Barbara.

98
00:03:51,750 --> 00:03:53,660
明年可能会出台更多的减税政策
And there'll be even more tax breaks next year.

99
00:03:53,670 --> 00:03:55,720
你想把业务扩展到娱乐圈
You want to expand into entertainment.

100
00:03:55,720 --> 00:03:58,270
作为专攻本地案件的芝加哥律所
I want to put us on the map more strongly as

101
00:03:58,270 --> 00:04:00,460
我想让我们的名声打得更响
a Chicago firm that handles local cases.

102
00:04:00,460 --> 00:04:03,340
拿电视台开刀怎么能算明智之举
Then why isn't it a mistake to go up against the studios,

103
00:04:03,340 --> 00:04:05,300
尤其还是场没有胜算的案子
especially on a case we're gonna lose?

104
00:04:05,300 --> 00:04:06,610
这是次试水
It's an audition.

105
00:04:06,710 --> 00:04:08,650
我们要他们律师知道  我们实力也不容小视
We show their lawyers we can give them a run for their money.

106
00:04:08,650 --> 00:04:09,660
我猜
My guess,

107
00:04:10,520 --> 00:04:12,850
他们宁愿让我们把枪头朝外
they'd much rather have us inside the tent pissing out

108
00:04:12,850 --> 00:04:14,710
也不想让我们把枪头朝里吧
than outside the tent pissing in.

109
00:04:16,160 --> 00:04:18,310
我们今天得找戴安谈谈
Oh, we need to talk to Diane today.

110
00:04:18,850 --> 00:04:19,700
就不能等一个礼拜吗
Hey, can that wait a week?

111
00:04:19,710 --> 00:04:21,590
如果我们想保持一视同仁的话
Not if we want to be consistent.

112
00:04:21,610 --> 00:04:23,340
我们总是让合伙人在一个月内
We've always insisted that equity partners

113
00:04:23,340 --> 00:04:25,580
交齐认购资本
have the capital contribution within a month.

114
00:04:25,580 --> 00:04:27,020
好  那你去做吧
Okay, I need you to do it.

115
00:04:27,070 --> 00:04:29,540
为什么这些麻烦事总是交给我
Well, how come I always have to do all the dirty work,

116
00:04:29,540 --> 00:04:31,390
而你却在外面法庭上春风得意
and you get to go and have fun in court?

117
00:04:31,390 --> 00:04:32,990
因为你处理麻烦事很有一手
'Cause you're so good at the dirty work.

118
00:04:32,990 --> 00:04:36,050
我讨厌你用骂人的话来夸人
I hate when you disguise curses as compliments.

119
00:04:37,910 --> 00:04:39,070
我得去法庭了
I'm going to court.

120
00:04:44,990 --> 00:04:47,070
我找玛娅·林德尔
Maia Rindell, please.

121
00:04:49,270 --> 00:04:51,080
林德尔女儿花35万购买珠宝

122
00:04:52,070 --> 00:04:54,200
这篇报道完全失实
This article is completely false.

123
00:04:54,200 --> 00:04:55,290
这不是真的
It is untrue.

124
00:04:55,620 --> 00:04:58,690
所以你是在你父母庞氏丑闻事发前买的珠宝吗
So you bought the jewelry before your parents' Ponzi scheme?

125
00:04:58,690 --> 00:05:00,830
没有  我从来没买过这件珠宝
No. I never bought the jewelry.

126
00:05:00,830 --> 00:05:02,680
那是...  礼物吗
Was it a... gift?

127
00:05:02,680 --> 00:05:04,460
不  我根本没这件珠宝
No. There is no jewelry.

128
00:05:04,460 --> 00:05:07,500
-这篇报道是假的  -有目击证人的话
- This article is false. - It quotes witnesses.

129
00:05:07,500 --> 00:05:08,160
这里说道
Here it says,

130
00:05:08,160 --> 00:05:10,430
鲁道夫夫人的古董珠宝店的老板
the owner of Madame Rudolph's Antique Jewelry

131
00:05:10,430 --> 00:05:12,720
说他们卖了你十件珠宝
said they sold you ten pieces?

132
00:05:12,720 --> 00:05:14,560
这纯属瞎编
And that is made up.

133
00:05:14,940 --> 00:05:15,800
你给店里打过电话吗
Did you try calling the store?

134
00:05:15,800 --> 00:05:17,670
你是说没有一个叫多莉·鲁道夫的人
So you're saying there is no Dolly Rudolph,

135
00:05:17,680 --> 00:05:20,120
鲁道夫夫人的古董珠宝店的老板
proprietor of Madame Rudolph's Antique Jewelry?

136
00:05:20,120 --> 00:05:22,400
我是说可能有一个叫多莉·鲁道夫的人
Oh, I'm saying there might be a Dolly Rudolph,

137
00:05:22,400 --> 00:05:23,480
但我从来没见过她
but I have never met her,

138
00:05:23,480 --> 00:05:25,640
我也从来没从她那儿买过珠宝
and I've never bought any jewelry from her.

139
00:05:28,730 --> 00:05:30,040
你给店里打过电话吗
Did you try calling the store?

140
00:05:30,040 --> 00:05:33,730
我不能理解这篇报道怎么会错的这么离谱
I just don't understand how this article could get so much wrong.

141
00:05:33,730 --> 00:05:35,050
她想说的是
What she's saying is

142
00:05:35,050 --> 00:05:37,710
这篇报道只是不实报道中的一篇
the article's a part of this trend in fake news.

143
00:05:37,710 --> 00:05:40,460
编造故事用来获取点击率
It makes up stories to encourage clickbait.

144
00:05:40,460 --> 00:05:44,310
没错 但这个报道不止一篇
Yes, but this isn't the only article.

145
00:05:45,010 --> 00:05:45,940
这儿
Here.

146
00:05:47,270 --> 00:05:49,070
还有12家不同的网站
These are 12 different Web sites,

147
00:05:49,070 --> 00:05:50,380
大部分很知名
a lot of them well-respected,

148
00:05:50,380 --> 00:05:53,300
他们都说你做了一模一样的事
all saying that you did the exact same thing.

149
00:05:53,970 --> 00:05:55,590
这你要怎么解释
So how do you account for that?

150
00:05:55,780 --> 00:05:59,300
我认为是假新闻被其他网站当真的来用了
I think the fake news was picked up by other Web sites as if it were real.

151
00:05:59,300 --> 00:06:00,990
他们为什么会这么做呢
And why would they do that?

152
00:06:01,630 --> 00:06:03,620
因为这故事有趣
Because the story is fun.

153
00:06:04,090 --> 00:06:06,210
它有明确的反派  也就是我
It has a clear villain...me.

154
00:06:06,210 --> 00:06:08,070
这我可不清楚  林德尔小姐
Oh, I don't know, Ms. Rindell.

155
00:06:08,070 --> 00:06:11,300
我不觉得这故事哪儿有趣
I don't think there's anything fun about this story.

156
00:06:12,150 --> 00:06:13,820
你给店里打过电话吗
Did you try calling the store?

157
00:06:13,820 --> 00:06:16,870
那另一篇你去探监的文章呢
What about this article about you visiting your father

158
00:06:16,870 --> 00:06:18,590
你父亲那时候还在候审
while he was awaiting trial?

159
00:06:18,590 --> 00:06:19,950
你们聊了什么
What did you guys talk about?

160
00:06:19,950 --> 00:06:21,640
那是私人探访
That was a personal visit.

161
00:06:21,860 --> 00:06:24,480
我和林德尔先生的律师都在场  所以
I was there as well as Mr. Rindell's attorney, so...

162
00:06:24,480 --> 00:06:26,490
不  不是那次
No, no, not that visit.

163
00:06:26,570 --> 00:06:29,140
我说的是另外两次
I'm talking about the other two visits,

164
00:06:29,140 --> 00:06:31,330
玛娅是自己去的
when Maia went by herself.

165
00:06:31,890 --> 00:06:34,500
那也是假新闻  根本没有其他探访
That's more fake news. There were no other visits.

166
00:06:34,500 --> 00:06:34,950
耶什
Yesha.

167
00:06:39,030 --> 00:06:42,300
我现在得中止这次询问
At this point, we'll interrupt the questioning

168
00:06:42,300 --> 00:06:43,640
我和玛娅得商量一下
so Maia and I can discuss.

169
00:06:46,960 --> 00:06:47,920
没问题
Sure.

170
00:06:49,460 --> 00:06:50,970
你们可以好好弄清楚
Why don't you figure out

171
00:06:51,420 --> 00:06:53,860
哪些是假新闻
which is fake news

172
00:06:54,990 --> 00:06:56,050
哪些不是
and which is not.

173
00:07:04,830 --> 00:07:05,750
出什么事了
What's wrong?

174
00:07:06,270 --> 00:07:07,180
什么
What?

175
00:07:07,430 --> 00:07:08,860
没什么事  为什么这么问
Uh, nothing, why?

176
00:07:08,930 --> 00:07:10,040
你一副有事的样子
You just have a look.

177
00:07:10,240 --> 00:07:12,760
科斯达夫人在找你  我们有麻烦了吗
Mrs. Kolstad wants to see you now. Are we in trouble?

178
00:07:13,310 --> 00:07:14,440
什么  没有
What? No.

179
00:07:14,780 --> 00:07:16,070
因为我需要这份工作
Because I need this job.

180
00:07:16,260 --> 00:07:17,650
我会记住的
Oh, I'll keep that in mind.

181
00:07:20,000 --> 00:07:22,540
我们得做一个艰难的决定
We've had to make a difficult decision here.

182
00:07:24,640 --> 00:07:25,550
怎么了
What?

183
00:07:26,490 --> 00:07:29,460
这是我们解雇律师的时候会对他们说的话
Well, that's what we tell associates when we release them.

184
00:07:30,330 --> 00:07:32,480
不完全是这样
Well, it's not quite that.

185
00:07:34,480 --> 00:07:36,140
是认购金的事
The capital contribution.

186
00:07:36,430 --> 00:07:39,790
我们知道你要从原来律所提认购金有困难
Yes, we know you're having trouble releasing it from your old firm.

187
00:07:39,790 --> 00:07:42,090
但我们坚持钱必须尽快到位
But we need to insist.

188
00:07:42,880 --> 00:07:44,410
没关系  我理解
No, I understand.

189
00:07:45,220 --> 00:07:46,590
合伙人已经投过票了
The partners voted.

190
00:07:46,930 --> 00:07:49,450
如果一周内收不到认购金
If we don't get the contribution in a week,

191
00:07:49,780 --> 00:07:52,540
我们得把你降为普通律师
we'll need to make you of counsel.

192
00:07:58,210 --> 00:07:59,110
好的
Okay.

193
00:08:03,480 --> 00:08:06,310
你可能会想给律所雇一名律师
Uh, you may want to think of getting a lawyer for the firm.

194
00:08:06,980 --> 00:08:09,900
迈克·克里斯特瓦刚在询问玛娅
Mike Kresteva was just questioning Maia.

195
00:08:16,970 --> 00:08:18,750
你又去见你父亲了吗
You went and saw your father again?

196
00:08:19,650 --> 00:08:20,570
是的
Yes.

197
00:08:21,170 --> 00:08:22,080
为什么
Why?

198
00:08:23,170 --> 00:08:26,230
他叫我从贾克斯叔叔的电脑上下份材料
He asked me to download, from my Uncle Jax's computer,

199
00:08:26,230 --> 00:08:29,570
是一份叫"鬼混名单"的客户名单
a list of clients called the "Schtup List."

200
00:08:29,930 --> 00:08:31,050
鬼混名单
"The Schtup List"?

201
00:08:31,900 --> 00:08:32,870
那是什么
What's that?

202
00:08:33,120 --> 00:08:35,040
里面是基金里几个贵宾客户
It's a list of VIP clients in the fund

203
00:08:35,040 --> 00:08:37,230
贾克斯给他们做了特殊服务
that Jax did special work for.

204
00:08:38,370 --> 00:08:40,160
为了避税把利润时间做得早一点
Oh, um, backdating profits for tax purposes,

205
00:08:40,160 --> 00:08:42,120
或者把基金转到其他账户里
transferring funds to other accounts.

206
00:08:42,120 --> 00:08:43,490
一些非法活动吗
Illegal activities?

207
00:08:43,910 --> 00:08:46,200
你父亲认为可以拿这些来对付你叔叔吗
And your father thought he could use this against your uncle?

208
00:08:47,380 --> 00:08:48,260
没错
Yes.

209
00:08:49,160 --> 00:08:53,240
你明白的吧  你这样做  帮助你父亲
So you do know, by doing this, by helping your father,

210
00:08:53,240 --> 00:08:55,370
就已经被牵扯进非法行为了
you've implicated yourself in wrongdoing?

211
00:08:55,580 --> 00:08:56,830
他是我父亲
He's my father.

212
00:08:57,480 --> 00:08:58,830
我还能做什么
What could I do?

213
00:08:59,180 --> 00:09:01,510
你能让自己不坐牢
You can keep yourself out of jail.

214
00:09:11,110 --> 00:09:12,420
谁来了  我律师吗
Who is it, my lawyer?

215
00:09:15,200 --> 00:09:16,420
林德尔先生
Mr. Rindell?

216
00:09:16,920 --> 00:09:17,860
你好
Hello.

217
00:09:18,110 --> 00:09:19,540
我是迈克·克里斯特瓦
I'm Mike Kresteva.

218
00:09:20,270 --> 00:09:21,190
好吧
Okay.

219
00:09:21,960 --> 00:09:23,000
我认识你吗
Do I know you?

220
00:09:25,950 --> 00:09:29,150
不认识  但我想我可以帮你
No, but I think I can help you.

221
00:09:30,550 --> 00:09:32,480
你好  法官阁下  你好
Hi, Your Honor. Hi.

222
00:09:32,240 --> 00:09:33,890
托马斯·格拉特法官

223
00:09:32,790 --> 00:09:33,860
你好
Hello?

224
00:09:34,580 --> 00:09:35,460
我是安珀
I'm Amber.

225
00:09:35,460 --> 00:09:37,960
我是汤姆  很高兴见到你
Tom. Nice to meet you.

226
00:09:37,960 --> 00:09:41,600
我说  这案件很简单  法官阁下
Can I just say, this is a very simple matter, Your Honor.

227
00:09:41,640 --> 00:09:42,640
这就是盗窃
It's stealing.

228
00:09:42,880 --> 00:09:44,910
不管是偷了钱包
It doesn't matter if it's a stolen purse,

229
00:09:44,910 --> 00:09:48,710
还是偷了一集电视剧  都应同样处理
or a stolen episode of TV, it should be treated the same way.

230
00:09:48,710 --> 00:09:50,720
但我们在民事法庭  法官阁下
And yet here we are in civil court, Your Honor,

231
00:09:50,720 --> 00:09:52,110
而不是刑事法庭
not criminal court.

232
00:09:52,600 --> 00:09:54,010
这说法有趣
That's a funny approach,

233
00:09:54,010 --> 00:09:56,330
抱怨我们对你的客户还不够狠
complaining that we're not going hard enough on your client.

234
00:09:56,330 --> 00:09:58,910
-我只是想指出卢茨女士  -伍德
- I'm simply pointing out that Ms. Lutz is... - Wood.

235
00:09:59,190 --> 00:10:00,300
伍德卢茨
Wood-Lutz.

236
00:10:01,110 --> 00:10:02,420
伍德卢茨女士
Ms. Wood-Lutz...

237
00:10:02,780 --> 00:10:05,380
没选择提出刑事诉讼
has elected not to press criminal charges here.

238
00:10:05,380 --> 00:10:08,140
若只是简单的盗窃案  她不会这样做
Something she would do if this were a simple matter of theft.

239
00:10:08,140 --> 00:10:12,180
但失窃的钱包一般也不会价值1200万
It's also true that stolen purses don't usually cost $12 million.

240
00:10:12,180 --> 00:10:14,840
法官阁下  我们会在这里的唯一原因
Your Honor, the only reason we are here is because

241
00:10:14,840 --> 00:10:16,350
是伍德卢茨女士的当事人
Ms. Wood-Lutz's client

242
00:10:16,350 --> 00:10:18,000
觉得联邦通信委员会找麻烦
has an issue in front of the FCC,

243
00:10:18,000 --> 00:10:20,270
同时他们在担心特朗普政府
and they're afraid that the Trump administration

244
00:10:20,270 --> 00:10:21,590
-天  不是  -会做出不利的决定
- Oh, my Gosh, no. - will decide against them.

245
00:10:21,590 --> 00:10:24,250
法官阁下  我认为我的当事人是替罪羊
I submit, Your Honor, my client is a scapegoat.

246
00:10:24,250 --> 00:10:25,690
不是这样  法官阁下  我能说话了吗
No, Your Honor. Can I speak, please?

247
00:10:25,690 --> 00:10:29,190
法官阁下  她的当事人得向政府证明自己足够强硬
Her client needs to prove themselves tough to this administration

248
00:10:29,200 --> 00:10:30,490
委员会在独立拥有运营的问题上
so they'll decide in their favor

249
00:10:30,490 --> 00:10:31,880
就会做出有利于他们的决定
on the O&Os, Your Honor.

250
00:10:31,880 --> 00:10:33,130
我都不知道那是什么
I don't even know what that means.

251
00:10:33,140 --> 00:10:34,610
我也不知道
Well, actually I don't either.

252
00:10:34,620 --> 00:10:36,710
独立拥有和运营的电视台  法官阁下
Owned and operated TV stations, Your Honor.

253
00:10:36,720 --> 00:10:38,010
好吧  我不明白
Right, so I don't understand,

254
00:10:38,010 --> 00:10:40,630
你是说你的当事人没把剧集发布在网上吗
are you saying that your client didn't post the episode online?

255
00:10:40,630 --> 00:10:41,950
他发了
No, he did.

256
00:10:41,950 --> 00:10:44,300
我不明白  法官阁下
I-I don't understand, Your Honor.

257
00:10:44,310 --> 00:10:45,180
辩护内容是什么
What's the defense?

258
00:10:45,180 --> 00:10:46,300
合理使用
Fair use.

259
00:10:50,160 --> 00:10:51,050
好吧
Okay.

260
00:10:51,440 --> 00:10:52,400
我有兴趣了
I'm game.

261
00:10:52,990 --> 00:10:53,960
听听看吧
Let's hear it.

262
00:10:54,330 --> 00:10:55,590
嗨  丹尼
Hi, Danny.

263
00:10:56,410 --> 00:10:57,600
没事  一切都好
No, no, everything's fine.

264
00:10:57,600 --> 00:11:01,120
是我公寓的事  我们讨论过
It's just that thing we talked about with my apartment.

265
00:11:01,710 --> 00:11:03,900
我觉得我是想找个不那么豪华的地方
I think I want to look for something not as grand.

266
00:11:05,440 --> 00:11:06,370
戴安
Diane?

267
00:11:06,380 --> 00:11:08,700
有人来见你  还带了礼物
Someone is here to see you and he has a present.

268
00:11:11,890 --> 00:11:13,410
丹尼  我能回头再打给你吗
Danny, can I call you back?

269
00:11:15,200 --> 00:11:16,480
好的
Okay, good.

270
00:11:19,640 --> 00:11:21,070
需要我留下来做记录吗
Do you want me to stay and take notes?

271
00:11:21,980 --> 00:11:23,010
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.

272
00:11:28,670 --> 00:11:31,020
她很...健谈
She's... chatty.

273
00:11:31,490 --> 00:11:32,570
确实
She is that.

274
00:11:33,820 --> 00:11:34,890
你还好吗
So how are you?

275
00:11:35,380 --> 00:11:36,450
挺好的  你呢
Good. You?

276
00:11:36,800 --> 00:11:37,690
很好
Good.

277
00:11:39,440 --> 00:11:40,480
你给我打电话了
You called?

278
00:11:43,380 --> 00:11:45,010
没有  什么时候
Uh, no. When?

279
00:11:45,270 --> 00:11:46,310
昨天晚上
Last night.

280
00:11:47,510 --> 00:11:50,230
我接了  但是你已经挂了
I picked up, but you hung up.

281
00:11:50,230 --> 00:11:51,150
不
No.

282
00:11:51,380 --> 00:11:53,550
不  那肯定是不小心拨出去的
No, that must've been an accidental dial.

283
00:11:53,550 --> 00:11:55,440
我...  估计我手机...
I'm a... think my phone is...

284
00:11:56,020 --> 00:11:57,990
不管怎样  对不起
Anyway, I'm sorry.

285
00:11:57,990 --> 00:11:59,680
反正我也要给你打电话的
Well, I was gonna call you anyway, um...

286
00:12:01,050 --> 00:12:02,300
我需要你帮个忙
I have a favor.

287
00:12:03,210 --> 00:12:06,610
我同意给警察协会做个弹道学的演讲
I've agreed to give a speech on ballistics to the police union.

288
00:12:06,800 --> 00:12:09,210
是吗  这可不像你的作风啊
Really? Well, that doesn't sound like you.

289
00:12:09,210 --> 00:12:10,640
确实不像
Yes, it isn't.

290
00:12:11,970 --> 00:12:14,660
我希望你能读一下
I was hoping that you could read it.

291
00:12:15,270 --> 00:12:16,210
当然
Sure.

292
00:12:16,550 --> 00:12:17,660
今晚可以吗
Is tonight Okay?

293
00:12:17,740 --> 00:12:19,660
可以  我明天才讲呢
Yes, I have to give it tomorrow.

294
00:12:20,540 --> 00:12:23,630
还有  谢谢你
And... thank you.

295
00:12:47,540 --> 00:12:50,180
所以你不相信电视台会播这集
So, you didn't believe the network would broadcast the episode?

296
00:12:50,180 --> 00:12:51,860
抱歉  我可以反对吗
Sorry. Can I object here?

297
00:12:51,860 --> 00:12:53,820
-引导证人推测  -不  反对无效
- Calls for speculation. - No. Overruled.

298
00:12:53,820 --> 00:12:55,980
谢谢  法官阁下  费斯克先生
Thank you, Your Honor. Mr. Fisk?

299
00:12:55,980 --> 00:12:57,660
他们一再修改播出日期
They kept changing the broadcast date.

300
00:12:57,660 --> 00:12:59,900
他们一直往后推  一而再  再而三
They kept pushing it back, over and over and over again.

301
00:12:59,900 --> 00:13:01,450
他们从来就没指望特朗普会赢
They never expected Trump would actually win.

302
00:13:01,450 --> 00:13:03,520
当他赢了的时候  他们就想毁掉这集剧
And then, when he did, they wanted to bury the episode.

303
00:13:03,520 --> 00:13:05,670
-那就是你把剧放到网上的原因  -是的
- So that's why you put the episode online? - Yes.

304
00:13:05,670 --> 00:13:08,240
制片厂和电视台都有了寒蝉效应
There's been a chilling effect at the studio and the network.

305
00:13:08,240 --> 00:13:11,130
他们怕特朗普怀恨在心
They're worried about the Donald holding grudges.

306
00:13:11,380 --> 00:13:13,040
天知道电视台的领导们
Who knew network execs

307
00:13:13,040 --> 00:13:14,900
会因为凌晨三点的酒醉推文而吓到失禁
shit their pants over 3:00 a.m. drunk tweets?

308
00:13:14,910 --> 00:13:16,330
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.

309
00:13:16,330 --> 00:13:17,410
能不骂人吗
Can we not swear?

310
00:13:17,410 --> 00:13:19,460
是的  可以  费斯克先生
Yes, we can not. Mr. Fisk.

311
00:13:19,460 --> 00:13:21,390
对不起  我发现
I'm sorry, I-I found the idea that

312
00:13:21,390 --> 00:13:23,640
他们会因为害怕特朗普而删减内容
they would censor themselves for Trump terrifying.

313
00:13:23,640 --> 00:13:24,560
我只是想指出来
And I wanted to point that out.

314
00:13:24,560 --> 00:13:27,090
所以你把剧集作为公共服务放到了网上
So you put the episode online as a public service?

315
00:13:27,090 --> 00:13:28,870
咱们还是别太过分了
Hey, look, let's not go overboard here.

316
00:13:28,870 --> 00:13:30,550
他又不是纳尔逊·曼德拉
He's not Nelson Mandela.

317
00:13:28,870 --> 00:13:30,550
南非前总统

318
00:13:30,560 --> 00:13:32,020
但是我明白你的意思
But I get your point.

319
00:13:32,240 --> 00:13:33,790
律师  你还有问题吗
Counselor, do you have anything?

320
00:13:33,790 --> 00:13:35,660
是的  我们看一下
Yes, uh, let's see.

321
00:13:35,660 --> 00:13:38,890
合理使用的定义是
The definition of fair use is that

322
00:13:38,890 --> 00:13:42,280
"对可使用的受版权保护的材料的简短摘录"
"Brief excerpts of copyrightable material may be used."

323
00:13:42,280 --> 00:13:44,120
是简短  那么
Brief. So,

324
00:13:44,380 --> 00:13:46,010
你编写的那集剧时长是多少
how long was that episode that you wrote?

325
00:13:46,010 --> 00:13:46,690
42分钟
42 minutes.

326
00:13:46,690 --> 00:13:49,280
你放到网上的摘录部分又是多长呢
And how long was the excerpt you put online?

327
00:13:49,290 --> 00:13:51,510
由于我构思剧集的方式
Because of the way I structured the episode,

328
00:13:51,710 --> 00:13:52,920
我需要把整集都展示出来
I needed to show the whole thing.

329
00:13:52,920 --> 00:13:53,680
-那是因为  -好了
- It was a matter of... - Okay.

330
00:13:53,680 --> 00:13:55,360
我知道你想谈论更多内容
I know you want to talk more,

331
00:13:55,370 --> 00:13:57,260
但是只需要回答问题就可以了
but just answer the question.

332
00:13:58,590 --> 00:13:59,950
我把整集都放到网上了
I put the whole thing online.

333
00:13:59,950 --> 00:14:01,090
那是证明我的观点的唯一方式
It was the only way to prove my point.

334
00:14:01,090 --> 00:14:02,140
为什么你无法用一小部分
Why couldn't you prove your point

335
00:14:02,140 --> 00:14:05,100
简短的部分来证明你的观点呢
by using a small part, a brief part?

336
00:14:07,280 --> 00:14:09,020
因为需要全局
Because it required the whole thing.

337
00:14:09,020 --> 00:14:10,010
好的
All right.

338
00:14:10,310 --> 00:14:11,590
没有问题了  法官阁下
Nothing more, Your Honor.

339
00:14:11,710 --> 00:14:12,960
请求再次质询  法官阁下
Redirect, Your Honor.

340
00:14:14,560 --> 00:14:16,820
通过上传剧集你赚了多少钱
How much did you make by uploading the episode?

341
00:14:16,820 --> 00:14:18,090
我赚了多少
How much did I make?

342
00:14:18,470 --> 00:14:19,480
一分都没赚
Nothing.

343
00:14:19,540 --> 00:14:21,020
因为这是政治行为
Because this was a political move?

344
00:14:21,020 --> 00:14:22,520
而不是经济行为吗
Not an economic one?

345
00:14:22,620 --> 00:14:23,550
正是
Exactly.

346
00:14:23,550 --> 00:14:25,250
好了  还有其他问题吗  各位律师
All right. Anything else, counselors?

347
00:14:25,250 --> 00:14:28,260
是的  我有一位快速反驳证人
Yes. I have a quick rebuttal witness.

348
00:14:28,260 --> 00:14:30,600
但是真的很简短
But it'll be really brief.

349
00:14:31,140 --> 00:14:32,650
我是沃恩·延科
I'm Vaughn Yenko.

350
00:14:32,660 --> 00:14:35,230
我是剧集的联合执行制片人
I am a co-executive producer on the show.

351
00:14:35,490 --> 00:14:37,810
也就是说你是编剧吗
Okay, so that means you're like a writer?

352
00:14:38,090 --> 00:14:39,020
不
No.

353
00:14:40,940 --> 00:14:43,020
但是  基本上也对
But... yeah, mostly.

354
00:14:43,560 --> 00:14:46,310
费斯克先生坚持声称他出于政治立场
Mr. Fisk insists that he put his episode online

355
00:14:46,310 --> 00:14:48,050
把剧集放到了网上
as a political statement.

356
00:14:48,190 --> 00:14:48,740
那是事实吗
Is that true?

357
00:14:48,740 --> 00:14:51,140
反对  法官阁下  传闻证据
Objection, Your Honor. Hearsay.

358
00:14:51,150 --> 00:14:53,950
我认为这属于传闻证据的例外  法官阁下
I think this is a hearsay exception, Your Honor.

359
00:14:53,960 --> 00:14:55,820
前后不符的陈述
Uh, prior inconsistent statements.

360
00:14:55,820 --> 00:14:57,970
是的  反对无效
Yep. Overruled.

361
00:14:58,550 --> 00:15:00,330
我应该回答吗  法官阁下
S-So I should answer, Your Honor?

362
00:15:00,330 --> 00:15:01,570
请吧
Oh, please.

363
00:15:02,310 --> 00:15:03,320
他出于政治原因
It's not true...

364
00:15:03,540 --> 00:15:07,500
把剧集放到网上不是事实
him putting the episode online for political reasons.

365
00:15:07,510 --> 00:15:10,460
费斯克认为这集剧是他最好的作品
Fisk thought this episode was his best work.

366
00:15:10,880 --> 00:15:12,640
他认为它能让他得艾美奖
And he thought it was going to win him an Emmy.

367
00:15:12,640 --> 00:15:15,440
-胡说  -你觉得自己可了不起了
- That's bullshit. - Oh, you think you're God's gift.

368
00:15:15,450 --> 00:15:16,920
-你就是嫉妒我  -先生们  先生们
- This is about you being jealous. - Gentlemen. Gentlemen.

369
00:15:16,920 --> 00:15:18,720
你他妈就是个愚蠢的耶鲁混蛋
You stupid fucking Yale asshole.

370
00:15:18,720 --> 00:15:20,080
耶鲁可比普林斯顿强多了
Yale is better than Princeton.

371
00:15:20,080 --> 00:15:21,240
先生们  别吵了  别吵了
Gentlemen! Stop, stop, stop.

372
00:15:22,420 --> 00:15:24,300
耶鲁可以给我擦屁股了  朋友
Yale can wipe my ass, my friend.

373
00:15:24,300 --> 00:15:25,860
-可以擦  -先生们  住嘴
- Can wipe it. - Gentlemen, stop.

374
00:15:26,730 --> 00:15:29,060
我像下面那位一样讨厌耶鲁
Now, look, I hate Yale as much as the next guy,

375
00:15:29,060 --> 00:15:32,400
但是这么吵下去对谁的案子都没任何帮助
but no one is helping their case by arguing here.

376
00:15:32,500 --> 00:15:34,430
行了吗  我明白你们的意思
Okay, I get it.

377
00:15:34,440 --> 00:15:35,360
对不起
I'm sorry.

378
00:15:35,630 --> 00:15:39,450
你的辩护是他出于职业发展而不是政治原因
Now, you're arguing that he posted online for career,

379
00:15:39,450 --> 00:15:41,030
把剧放到网上
not political reasons.

380
00:15:41,030 --> 00:15:43,670
我没有辩护  法官阁下  证据证明如此
I am not arguing, Your Honor. That's what the evidence proves.

381
00:15:43,680 --> 00:15:46,660
是啊  证据证明的事情多了去了
Yeah, well, the evidence proves a lot of things.

382
00:15:47,260 --> 00:15:48,820
好了  我的决定如下
All right, here's my decision.

383
00:15:49,450 --> 00:15:52,470
用合理使用辩护就是笑话  律师们
Fair use is a joke here, counselors.

384
00:15:52,470 --> 00:15:54,150
他可是把整个剧都放到网上了
I mean, he put the whole thing online.

385
00:15:54,820 --> 00:15:55,650
我认为你们双方
Now, I think the two of you

386
00:15:55,650 --> 00:15:57,870
可以一起商量赔偿金了
should get together and decide damages.

387
00:15:57,870 --> 00:16:00,090
因为  律师们  你们输了
Because, counselors, you lost.

388
00:16:00,120 --> 00:16:01,760
你们官司输定了
It's a loser case.

389
00:16:01,760 --> 00:16:02,840
谢谢  法官阁下
Thank you, Your Honor.

390
00:16:02,840 --> 00:16:06,040
这样说只会让我改变主意  律师
You could only make me change my mind, counselor.

391
00:16:06,370 --> 00:16:07,410
再见
Bye.

392
00:16:16,780 --> 00:16:18,070
就这样了  对吗
So I guess that's it, huh?

393
00:16:18,350 --> 00:16:19,140
他们会要我破产
They're gonna bankrupt me.

394
00:16:19,140 --> 00:16:22,280
不  为时尚早
No, that is far from it.

395
00:16:23,600 --> 00:16:25,060
我们才刚刚开始
We're just getting started.

396
00:16:27,430 --> 00:16:28,440
请我吧
Hire me.

397
00:16:28,440 --> 00:16:30,550
只要我还有一口气在就会为你们公司辩护到底
I'll defend your firm with my last breath.

398
00:16:31,150 --> 00:16:32,980
克里斯特瓦先生想
Mr. Kresteva wants to

399
00:16:32,980 --> 00:16:36,160
对我们公司一起提出几起诉讼
tie together several accusations against our firm.

400
00:16:36,220 --> 00:16:38,660
他不仅针对我们办理过的警察暴力案件
Not just our work on police brutality cases,

401
00:16:38,660 --> 00:16:41,060
还有我们和林德尔基金的关系
but also our connection to the Rindell Fund.

402
00:16:41,070 --> 00:16:43,070
所以我们需要一位代表我们整个公司的律师
So we need a lawyer for the whole firm.

403
00:16:43,470 --> 00:16:44,850
-我可以胜任  -好
- That's me. - Okay.

404
00:16:45,020 --> 00:16:46,220
那我们怎么为自己辩护
So how do we defend ourselves?

405
00:16:46,220 --> 00:16:49,100
我们斗争到底  这是个新的民事权利
Oh, we fight. It's a new civil rights.

406
00:16:49,920 --> 00:16:52,220
我会与你们一起并肩作战  兄弟们  
And I will march with you, my bros,

407
00:16:52,220 --> 00:16:53,370
只要我还有一口气在
until my dying breath.

408
00:16:55,960 --> 00:16:57,690
就像一首经典不朽的饶舌歌曲
It's like immortal technique rapped:

409
00:16:57,690 --> 00:17:00,340
哟  他妈的给我装满  装满锁好*
*Yo, load the fuck up, locked and loading

410
00:17:00,340 --> 00:17:03,080
记得条子来了把窗户打烂*
*Remember to break that window when the cop comes in

411
00:17:05,640 --> 00:17:07,740
把那些婊子养的一枪爆头*
*Blow that motherfucker's head off.

412
00:17:09,410 --> 00:17:10,720
我们就该这么干
So, that's what we need to do.

413
00:17:10,720 --> 00:17:13,200
把那些律师所都操翻  好吗
Blow their mofo heads off. Okay?

414
00:17:19,580 --> 00:17:20,540
我走开一下
Uh, excuse me.

415
00:17:20,580 --> 00:17:21,510
没问题
Yeah.

416
00:17:27,510 --> 00:17:29,320
告诉我你有其他人选
Tell me you have someone else in mind.

417
00:17:29,370 --> 00:17:30,250
什么
What?

418
00:17:30,730 --> 00:17:32,800
你还有理想人选吗
Do you have another lawyer in mind?

419
00:17:32,840 --> 00:17:34,350
-有  -谁
- Yes. - Who?

420
00:17:34,880 --> 00:17:37,020
一个不走寻常路的人
Someone... unorthodox.

421
00:17:38,070 --> 00:17:39,310
有多不寻常
How unorthodox?

422
00:17:39,900 --> 00:17:40,970
你有时间吗
Do you have a minute?

423
00:17:42,330 --> 00:17:43,320
有
Yeah.

424
00:17:44,440 --> 00:17:45,710
戴安·洛克哈特
Diane Lockhart.

425
00:17:49,280 --> 00:17:50,280
抱歉
Excuse me.

426
00:17:50,560 --> 00:17:52,620
格罗斯先生  最近过得怎么样
Mr. Gross, how are you?

427
00:17:52,620 --> 00:17:55,020
备受折磨  愤怒  忧虑
Oh, you know, harried, angry, worried.

428
00:17:55,030 --> 00:17:56,540
那可真是概括
Yeah, that just about sums it up.

429
00:17:56,540 --> 00:17:57,650
这些是我的律师们
These are my lawyers.

430
00:17:57,650 --> 00:17:59,390
他们要花我180亿美金
They want to spend my $18 billion.

431
00:17:59,390 --> 00:18:00,430
先生们  你们好
Hello, gentlemen.

432
00:18:00,630 --> 00:18:02,790
我听说你换公司了
And I-I heard you switched firms.

433
00:18:02,790 --> 00:18:04,050
是的  我之前考虑换个环境
Yes, I was thinking about changing.

434
00:18:04,050 --> 00:18:06,140
一个全是黑人的公司  对吗
An all-black firm. Right?

435
00:18:06,140 --> 00:18:07,260
雷迪克&科斯达...
Reddick, Kolstad...

436
00:18:07,260 --> 00:18:08,650
雷迪克&博斯曼&科斯达律所
Reddick, Boseman & Kolstad.

437
00:18:08,650 --> 00:18:10,090
对  对
Right, right.

438
00:18:10,640 --> 00:18:12,470
所以你不再是冠名合伙人了
So you're not a name partner anymore.

439
00:18:12,530 --> 00:18:14,590
对  压力太大了  要不断地证明... 
No, there's so much pressure to keep proving...

440
00:18:14,590 --> 00:18:17,220
天  我恨芝加哥  但我就在这里
God, I hate Chicago. But here I am.

441
00:18:17,220 --> 00:18:18,290
每个星期  
Every week,

442
00:18:18,290 --> 00:18:21,500
我都感觉在努力带领一群杀猪的走进21世纪
trying to bring the hog butcher into the 21st century.

443
00:18:22,380 --> 00:18:24,820
-很高兴见到你  格罗斯先生  -我也是
- Well, it's good to see you, Mr. Gross. - Yeah.

444
00:18:26,190 --> 00:18:28,000
我对现在的律所不是很满意
I'm not very happy with my firm.

445
00:18:28,160 --> 00:18:29,460
我想找一个有冲劲的公司
Looking for a fighter.

446
00:18:29,470 --> 00:18:30,670
什么时候能去你办公室看看
When can I come see your office?

447
00:18:32,600 --> 00:18:34,000
随时恭候您的大驾
Whenever you want.

448
00:18:35,090 --> 00:18:36,320
小小的乐趣*
*A little fun

449
00:18:36,320 --> 00:18:37,560
刷刷你的牙齿*
*You brush your teeth

450
00:18:39,230 --> 00:18:39,790
刷刷你的牙齿...*
*You brush your teeth...

451
00:18:39,790 --> 00:18:42,050
所以这位律师是一位兼职牙医吗
So this lawyer is a part-time dentist?

452
00:18:42,070 --> 00:18:45,010
不是  她可能觉得这里当办公室比较划算
No, just someone who finds good deals on offices.

453
00:18:45,890 --> 00:18:49,440
那这个人能对抗克里斯特瓦吗
Is this "someone" facing Kresteva?

454
00:18:49,440 --> 00:18:50,260
希望如此
That's the hope.

455
00:18:50,260 --> 00:18:51,940
你们可以进去了  奎恩女士
You can go in now, Ms. Quinn.

456
00:19:02,740 --> 00:19:05,270
这感觉就像「绿野仙踪」  卢卡
This is feeling like The Wizard of Oz, Lucca.

457
00:19:05,270 --> 00:19:07,060
-有人吗  -你好
- Hello? - Hello.

458
00:19:09,110 --> 00:19:10,680
卢卡·奎因
Lucca Quinn.

459
00:19:15,410 --> 00:19:16,470
你最近怎么样
How are you?

460
00:19:16,470 --> 00:19:18,300
很好  谢谢  埃尔斯贝特  你呢
I'm very well. Thanks, Elsbeth. How are you?

461
00:19:18,300 --> 00:19:20,930
很好  现在我出院了
Good, now that I'm out of the hospital.

462
00:19:20,930 --> 00:19:22,060
你之前生病了吗
Oh, were you sick?

463
00:19:22,060 --> 00:19:24,250
没有  也许
No. Maybe.

464
00:19:24,430 --> 00:19:26,320
可能有些争议
There was some disagreement about that.

465
00:19:30,140 --> 00:19:31,550
老天  你真高
God, you're tall.

466
00:19:32,290 --> 00:19:33,310
你是谁
Who are you?

467
00:19:34,240 --> 00:19:36,230
阿德里安·博斯曼  
Adrian... Boseman.

468
00:19:36,350 --> 00:19:37,720
他是我们律所的老板
He's the head of our firm.

469
00:19:38,870 --> 00:19:39,810
你还好吗
Oh. How do you do?

470
00:19:39,810 --> 00:19:40,960
挺好的  谢谢
I'm well. Thank you.

471
00:19:41,510 --> 00:19:42,670
麻烦让一下
Excuse me.

472
00:19:44,480 --> 00:19:45,560
你们两位有何贵干
What do you two need?

473
00:19:48,500 --> 00:19:50,160
我们律所需要一位律师
Uh, our firm needs a lawyer.

474
00:19:50,230 --> 00:19:53,340
艾丽西娅曾经给过我一个建议
And Alicia once gave me a piece of advice.

475
00:19:53,400 --> 00:19:55,450
有麻烦  就雇埃尔斯贝特
When in trouble, hire Elsbeth.

476
00:19:55,460 --> 00:19:56,650
艾丽西娅·福瑞克  
Alicia Florrick?

477
00:19:56,650 --> 00:19:58,330
我喜欢艾丽西娅  她怎么样了
I like Alicia. How is she?

478
00:19:58,330 --> 00:20:00,240
搜索中  艾丽西娅·凯斯[著名女歌手]
Searching... Alicia Keys.

479
00:20:00,240 --> 00:20:01,660
艾达  不用了
Uh, Ada, no.

480
00:20:02,060 --> 00:20:03,030
取消
Cancel.

481
00:20:04,450 --> 00:20:05,530
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.

482
00:20:05,790 --> 00:20:08,900
范塔西娅请了病假  所以我才用这个的
Um, Fantasia's out sick, so I have this thing.

483
00:20:09,090 --> 00:20:09,970
艾达
Uh, Ada?

484
00:20:09,970 --> 00:20:11,450
取消  艾达
Cancel, Ada!

485
00:20:11,780 --> 00:20:13,870
我觉得她还在识别我的声音
I think it's still trying to recognize my voice.

486
00:20:13,870 --> 00:20:15,540
-关小音量  -对了
- Volume down. - There.

487
00:20:16,530 --> 00:20:19,560
那么...  你们遇到了什么麻烦
So... what's the problem?

488
00:20:20,130 --> 00:20:22,210
迈克·克里斯特瓦  你认识他吗
Mike Kresteva. Do you know him?

489
00:20:22,500 --> 00:20:24,260
不认识  但没关系
No, but that doesn't mean anything.

490
00:20:24,260 --> 00:20:25,940
他现在带领了一支专案组
He's heading up a task force,

491
00:20:25,940 --> 00:20:28,240
把我们律所当成目标
and they seem to be targeting our firm.

492
00:20:28,360 --> 00:20:31,540
-为什么  -我们接了很多警察暴力案件
Why? - We take on a lot of police brutality cases,

493
00:20:31,540 --> 00:20:34,280
有些家伙觉得  我们赢了太多这种官司了
and there are certain folk who think - we win too many.

494
00:20:34,490 --> 00:20:37,030
克里斯特瓦给我们律所的大部分人都发了传票
Kresteva has subpoenaed most of our firm.

495
00:20:37,310 --> 00:20:40,920
他没发现什么  但他决心要找到我们的把柄
There's nothing there, but he's determined to find something.

496
00:20:40,920 --> 00:20:44,260
好吧  事实上你们知道你们已经知道...
Well, the fact that you know what you already know...

497
00:20:44,650 --> 00:20:47,180
这说明你们还有更多不知道的东西
Well, it means there is something more you don't know.

498
00:20:47,180 --> 00:20:53,040
那么  我们怎么才能发现你们不知道什么
So... how do we find out what you don't know?

499
00:20:59,010 --> 00:21:00,630
你是在问我们吗
Are you asking us?

500
00:21:01,500 --> 00:21:03,650
不是  这是我要思考的
No. That's my problem.

501
00:21:04,470 --> 00:21:07,000
我来想  看看我能为你们做些什么
Just me. Let me see what I can do.

502
00:21:07,180 --> 00:21:08,270
给我  
Give me,

503
00:21:10,180 --> 00:21:11,270
一天时间
...a day.

504
00:21:15,150 --> 00:21:16,110
好吧
Okay.

505
00:21:33,480 --> 00:21:34,420
爸
Dad.

506
00:21:39,300 --> 00:21:40,430
只是保释
It's only bail.

507
00:21:41,780 --> 00:21:42,760
我知道
I know.

508
00:21:46,990 --> 00:21:49,170
天  我以为我再也见不着这座房子了
God, I thought I'd never see this house again.

509
00:21:50,140 --> 00:21:52,310
你还好吗  你看起来瘦了好多
Mmm. You okay? You look thinner.

510
00:21:52,440 --> 00:21:53,400
我挺好的
I'm good.

511
00:21:54,090 --> 00:21:56,640
那里没什么吃的
The food... lacked.

512
00:21:57,400 --> 00:21:58,900
怎么回事  我是说
What happened? I mean,

513
00:21:58,900 --> 00:22:01,150
他们怎么突然在保释这件事上改变主意了
why did they change their mind about bail?

514
00:22:01,250 --> 00:22:04,640
我不知道  希望是因为案子搞不定了
I-I don't know. I'm hoping because their case is falling apart.

515
00:22:04,830 --> 00:22:05,900
什么  他们没说原因吗
What, they didn't say?

516
00:22:05,900 --> 00:22:06,940
是玛娅吗
Is that Maia?

517
00:22:06,940 --> 00:22:08,110
是的  我打电话叫她来的
Yes, I called her.

518
00:22:08,800 --> 00:22:10,020
玛娅
Maia.

519
00:22:12,700 --> 00:22:16,000
看看我们这一家  又团聚了
Look at this family. Back together again.

520
00:22:16,000 --> 00:22:17,260
就好像什么也没发生过
Like nothing happened.

521
00:22:17,610 --> 00:22:18,880
你这是在讽刺吗
You're being sarcastic?

522
00:22:18,960 --> 00:22:20,730
不  真的是这种感觉
No, it really feels that way.

523
00:22:21,880 --> 00:22:23,280
我们叫了披萨
We called for pizza.

524
00:22:23,460 --> 00:22:24,000
你今天留下来住吗
Can you stay?

525
00:22:24,000 --> 00:22:27,110
不  我最好还是回艾米那边
No, um, I... I'd better get back to Amy.

526
00:22:27,110 --> 00:22:28,150
或许明天吧
Maybe tomorrow.

527
00:22:29,120 --> 00:22:31,410
你爸爸明天要跟联调局会谈
Your dad's talking to the FBI tomorrow.

528
00:22:31,520 --> 00:22:32,560
谈什么
Oh, about what?

529
00:22:32,790 --> 00:22:34,210
你知道的  这的那的
Oh, you know, this and that.

530
00:22:34,920 --> 00:22:36,050
他们在试探消息
They're on a fishing expedition.

531
00:22:36,050 --> 00:22:37,550
因为我们什么也没做错
Because we've done nothing wrong.

532
00:22:37,550 --> 00:22:38,700
而他们知道这一点
And they know it.

533
00:22:39,430 --> 00:22:40,870
又是朋友打来的
That's more friends.

534
00:22:41,240 --> 00:22:42,360
虽然是些酒肉朋友
Fair-weather friends.

535
00:22:42,360 --> 00:22:44,670
但能身处酒池肉林也是好的
But it's good to be in fair weather.

536
00:22:47,820 --> 00:22:50,490
妈妈有没有跟你说些什么关于贾克斯叔叔的事
Did Mom say anything to you about Uncle Jax?

537
00:22:50,590 --> 00:22:53,300
-喂  -没  只说了贾克斯坚持他的谎言
- Hello. - No, just that Jax is sticking to his lies.

538
00:22:53,300 --> 00:22:55,280
你好  格蕾西  是的
Oh, hi, Gracie. Yes.

539
00:22:55,280 --> 00:22:59,860
爸  我有一天晚上回家发现贾克斯在家里
Dad, I came over here one night and Jax was here.

540
00:23:00,030 --> 00:23:01,010
和妈妈在一起
With Mom.

541
00:23:01,080 --> 00:23:02,950
-这事我知道  她说了  -她说了吗
- I know. She said. - She did?

542
00:23:03,070 --> 00:23:05,590
是的  她试图说服贾克斯翻供
Yes, she was trying to convince Jax to change his story,

543
00:23:05,590 --> 00:23:06,540
将真相和盘托出
to tell the truth.

544
00:23:06,540 --> 00:23:07,450
爸
Dad...

545
00:23:07,450 --> 00:23:09,130
不是这样的  远不止那样
no, it was more than that.

546
00:23:09,350 --> 00:23:11,180
家里就他们两个
It was just the two of them.

547
00:23:11,260 --> 00:23:12,770
别担心  宝贝
Oh, don't worry, honey.

548
00:23:13,290 --> 00:23:15,440
你妈妈跟我说了  没谈成
Mom told me. It didn't work.

549
00:23:16,280 --> 00:23:17,380
我爱你  甜心
I love you, sweetheart.

550
00:23:17,380 --> 00:23:18,760
是迈克尔一家
It's the Michaels.

551
00:23:18,850 --> 00:23:20,440
约翰想跟你说说话
John wants to talk to you.

552
00:23:21,810 --> 00:23:22,810
我们回头再聊
We'll talk.

553
00:23:23,390 --> 00:23:24,560
你看上去气色不错  玛娅
You look good, Maia.

554
00:23:24,710 --> 00:23:26,260
约翰尼  你最近可好
Johnny boy, how are you?

555
00:23:26,540 --> 00:23:27,980
是不是很棒
Isn't it wonderful?

556
00:23:28,150 --> 00:23:29,730
你爸回家了
Having your dad home.

557
00:23:30,670 --> 00:23:32,960
是的  我不知道贾克斯会怎么看这件事
Yeah, oh, I wonder what Jax thinks?

558
00:23:35,100 --> 00:23:37,110
我不知道  我最近没见过他
I don't know. I haven't seen him.

559
00:23:37,960 --> 00:23:39,480
明晚回来吃晚饭吧
Come to dinner tomorrow night.

560
00:23:39,480 --> 00:23:40,590
叫上艾米一起
And bring Amy.

561
00:23:42,670 --> 00:23:44,120
别皱眉头
Oh, unfurrow that brow.

562
00:23:44,720 --> 00:23:46,240
会长抬头纹的
It'll give you creases.

563
00:23:46,500 --> 00:23:47,460
那可不好
No.

564
00:23:48,040 --> 00:23:51,240
光之墅  售价150万欧元

565
00:23:54,530 --> 00:23:55,740
上班族的绝佳下榻居所  月租1500美元

566
00:23:55,940 --> 00:23:56,720
上城区一卧室招租  月租1800美元

567
00:23:56,850 --> 00:23:57,400
有充沛的储物空间的舒适公寓  月租2000美元

568
00:23:57,510 --> 00:23:58,160
市中心区域私人公寓  月租2500美元

569
00:23:58,280 --> 00:23:58,950
新更换过地毯的绝佳学生公寓  月租2600美元

570
00:23:59,110 --> 00:23:59,530
这就是完美的私人公寓  月租2000美元

571
00:24:01,190 --> 00:24:02,290
打死我也不住
Not happening.

572
00:24:26,330 --> 00:24:27,410
上帝啊
Oh, God...

573
00:24:33,750 --> 00:24:35,460
其实并没有看上去那么糟
It's not as bad as it looks.

574
00:24:35,560 --> 00:24:36,460
真的吗
Really?

575
00:24:38,320 --> 00:24:39,570
只是写得太专业了
It's just technical.

576
00:24:39,750 --> 00:24:41,200
你上庭作证也不是一次两次了
You testify in court all the time

577
00:24:41,200 --> 00:24:42,830
说的都让人挺容易理解啊
and you make it understandable.

578
00:24:42,880 --> 00:24:44,750
你说的那是质询
That's an interrogatory.

579
00:24:45,010 --> 00:24:46,150
只要面对12个人的陪审团
With a jury of 12.

580
00:24:46,150 --> 00:24:49,260
而我这次是要在500人面前演讲
This is me in front of 500 people.

581
00:24:49,290 --> 00:24:50,310
500人
500?

582
00:24:52,090 --> 00:24:53,000
好吧
Okay.

583
00:24:53,670 --> 00:24:58,650
演讲主题是弹道学中的三维技术运用
Well, the subject is 3D technology in ballistics.

584
00:24:58,660 --> 00:25:02,970
不  不  是干涉仪在三维渲染中的影响
No. No, the impact of interferometers on 3D renderings.

585
00:25:03,560 --> 00:25:06,630
主题就是弹道学中的三维技术运用
The subject is 3D technology in ballistics.

586
00:25:06,730 --> 00:25:08,230
而且就我看来
And as far as I can tell,

587
00:25:08,230 --> 00:25:11,130
这篇稿子是关于使用镭射激光来放大
this is about the use of lasers to magnify

588
00:25:11,140 --> 00:25:14,210
弹壳上的瑕疵的  对吗
imperfections on a bullet casing, right?

589
00:25:14,250 --> 00:25:18,080
是的  使用干涉仪来创建
Yeah, using an interferometer to create what is...

590
00:25:19,120 --> 00:25:20,050
好吧
Right.

591
00:25:20,050 --> 00:25:23,670
用这项技术你可以把弹壳放大到两微米级别
And you can magnify a bullet casing up to two microns?

592
00:25:23,670 --> 00:25:24,340
是的
Yes.

593
00:25:24,350 --> 00:25:25,720
好吧  那具体是多小呢
Okay, and how small is that?

594
00:25:25,720 --> 00:25:27,470
给我一个现实生活中的例子
Just give me a real-world example.

595
00:25:27,480 --> 00:25:29,790
就跟我说说  来吧  喝口酒
I mean, just talk to me. Come on, take a sip.

596
00:25:30,840 --> 00:25:32,620
然后告诉我两微米是多小
Tell me how small two microns are.

597
00:25:32,620 --> 00:25:36,620
两微米大约是
Two microns are about 1/50

598
00:25:36,620 --> 00:25:38,880
一根头发直径的五十分之一
of the width of a human hair.

599
00:25:38,880 --> 00:25:42,250
很好  你刚说的我能理解了  就这样继续
Good. You just said something I understand, so start there.

600
00:25:42,250 --> 00:25:44,080
我是说  就拿一根头发
I mean, just take a single human hair,

601
00:25:44,080 --> 00:25:45,210
然后想象你有一把刀
and imagine you had a knife

602
00:25:45,210 --> 00:25:48,280
可以把那根头发切成50片
that could cut that hair into 50 thin slices.

603
00:25:52,160 --> 00:25:53,080
然后呢
What else?

604
00:25:53,510 --> 00:25:54,750
你开车过来的吗
Did you drive here?

605
00:25:54,880 --> 00:25:56,230
不  打车来的
No, a cab.

606
00:25:57,060 --> 00:25:58,020
很好
Good.

607
00:25:59,010 --> 00:26:00,050
把这杯干掉
Drink up.

608
00:26:04,240 --> 00:26:06,200
这是我们制作本案中这集视频的成本费用
This is our cost for the episode in question,

609
00:26:06,200 --> 00:26:08,070
也是我们能做到的最后也是最大让步了
and this is our best and final offer.

610
00:26:08,070 --> 00:26:09,330
但我也可以直截了当告诉你们
But I can cut to the chase...

611
00:26:09,330 --> 00:26:11,180
我们愿意把赔偿金额降到六百万美元
we're willing to cut our ask to $6 million,

612
00:26:11,180 --> 00:26:12,830
但他必须进行公开道歉
but we want a public apology.

613
00:26:14,120 --> 00:26:15,320
好好考虑一下吧
Take your time with it.

614
00:26:17,110 --> 00:26:20,390
这个是  这个是我们的出价
This is our... this is our counter.

615
00:26:23,160 --> 00:26:26,460
如你所知  我们已经把原赔偿金额减半了
Just so you know, we already cut our ask in half.

616
00:26:26,460 --> 00:26:28,380
我们可不准备
We're not ready to entertain...

617
00:26:29,590 --> 00:26:30,850
好好考虑一下吧
Take your time with it.

618
00:26:33,010 --> 00:26:34,040
去你妈的
Fuck you.

619
00:26:41,440 --> 00:26:43,000
屎盆子大战要来了
Here come the shitstorm.

620
00:26:43,340 --> 00:26:44,170
法官阁下  抱歉
Your Honor, sorry,

621
00:26:44,180 --> 00:26:45,750
但我们已经将赔偿金额减半了
but we have cut our ask in half,

622
00:26:45,750 --> 00:26:46,740
而且他们欺负我
and they have bullied me...

623
00:26:46,740 --> 00:26:48,350
如果这是在开玩笑的话
If this is supposed to be a joke,

624
00:26:48,350 --> 00:26:49,630
律师  我一点都笑不出来
Counselor, I'm not laughing.

625
00:26:49,630 --> 00:26:52,460
法官阁下  他们要求我们为一集他们从未
Your Honor, they're asking us to pay damages on a TV show

626
00:26:52,460 --> 00:26:53,730
打算播出的电视节目支付赔偿
they never intended to broadcast.

627
00:26:53,730 --> 00:26:55,000
不  法官大人  很抱歉
No, Your Honor, I'm sorry,

628
00:26:55,000 --> 00:26:57,360
那这种说法不正确  这是个有价值的电视节目
but that's untrue. It's a valued show.

629
00:26:57,360 --> 00:26:59,340
他们第一回合赢了  法官阁下
Look, they won round one, Your Honor.

630
00:26:59,340 --> 00:27:01,840
我们的委托人把视频从网上撤下来了
Our client dropped the episode on the Internet.

631
00:27:01,840 --> 00:27:03,110
现在是第二回合
This is round two.

632
00:27:03,110 --> 00:27:03,610
他们的损失在哪里
What are the damages?

633
00:27:03,610 --> 00:27:05,660
而我们要争辩的就是没有任何损失
And we would argue there are no damages.

634
00:27:05,800 --> 00:27:07,370
唐纳德·特朗普当选总统后
When Donald Trump was elected president,

635
00:27:07,370 --> 00:27:09,250
电视台决定抛弃这集节目
the network decided to dump the episode.

636
00:27:09,250 --> 00:27:12,790
他们不能对没有价值的东西索赔
And they can't claim damages on something that is worthless.

637
00:27:12,790 --> 00:27:15,930
法官阁下  我惊呆了  都不知道怎么回了
Your Honor, I am stunned. I don't even know how to respond.

638
00:27:15,930 --> 00:27:18,240
我也是  我们还是听听证人怎么说吧
I don't, either. So let's hear from the witnesses.

639
00:27:18,240 --> 00:27:19,360
谢谢  法官阁下
Thank you, Your Honor.

640
00:27:22,610 --> 00:27:24,290
没错  但他会给我们提供名单
Yeah, but he's giving us the names.

641
00:27:24,290 --> 00:27:25,650
他在和我们合作
He's cooperating.

642
00:27:25,650 --> 00:27:28,460
而且我们只答应了让他保释
And we never agreed to anything other than his bail.

643
00:27:37,070 --> 00:27:40,030
我要  我们稍后再谈
I'll... let's deal with this later.

644
00:27:40,030 --> 00:27:42,350
好吗  很好  再见
Okay? Okay. Bye.

645
00:27:48,400 --> 00:27:50,650
你好  我认识你吗
Hello. Do I know you?

646
00:27:50,650 --> 00:27:53,590
不  应该不认识  但这很奇怪
No. I don't think so, which is weird

647
00:27:53,590 --> 00:27:56,480
毕竟我们已经在同一个圈子工作了很多年
because we've been moving in the same circles for years.

648
00:27:56,480 --> 00:27:58,990
好吧  你是谁
Okay. Who are you?

649
00:28:02,850 --> 00:28:04,680
埃尔斯贝特·塔肖尼
Elsbeth Tascioni.

650
00:28:05,700 --> 00:28:06,820
当然
Oh. Sure.

651
00:28:08,480 --> 00:28:09,900
我不喜欢自己吃饭  你呢
I don't like eating alone, do you?

652
00:28:09,900 --> 00:28:10,980
我其实挺喜欢的
I do, actually.

653
00:28:10,980 --> 00:28:12,790
会让我想到上学的时候
Reminds me of school.

654
00:28:13,030 --> 00:28:14,460
你的汤看起来不错  是什么汤啊
That soup looks good. What is it?

655
00:28:14,460 --> 00:28:16,590
我不知道  麻烦结账
I don't know. Check, please.

656
00:28:16,890 --> 00:28:19,470
好吧  这的服务可有点慢
Yeah. They're a little slow here,

657
00:28:19,550 --> 00:28:22,560
但这也让我们有更多时间熟悉一下
but that just gives us longer - to get acquainted.

658
00:28:22,560 --> 00:28:23,520
结账  麻烦快点
Check, please.

659
00:28:23,520 --> 00:28:26,260
我是雷迪克&博斯曼&科斯达律所的律师
I represent Reddick, Boseman & Koldstad.

660
00:28:28,240 --> 00:28:29,730
原来他们聘请了律师
Aha. So they hired someone.

661
00:28:30,660 --> 00:28:31,940
好吧  这对他们来说是件好事
Well, good for them.

662
00:28:32,700 --> 00:28:36,220
其实是这样的  现在是我午休的时间
Uh, look, here's the thing, um, this is my lunch break,

663
00:28:36,220 --> 00:28:37,120
"塔大尼"小姐
Ms. "Tanjoni".

664
00:28:37,120 --> 00:28:38,320
是塔肖尼
Oh. Tascioni.

665
00:28:38,320 --> 00:28:39,020
算了  无所谓
Yeah, whatever.

666
00:28:39,020 --> 00:28:41,610
你和亨利·林德尔达成了协议
So, you're making a deal with Henry Rindell.

667
00:28:41,700 --> 00:28:43,420
你听到我打电话了
You heard my phone call?

668
00:28:43,420 --> 00:28:47,780
是的  我也看到林德尔先生已经获得保释了
Yes, but I also saw that Mr. Rindell was released on bail.

669
00:28:48,010 --> 00:28:51,590
所以你一定在司法部有很大的影响力
You must have some sway in the Department of Justice.

670
00:28:51,590 --> 00:28:54,730
没错  但我从没听说过你
I do, and I've never heard of you.

671
00:28:55,000 --> 00:28:56,970
因为我只是个小律师而已
That's because I'm just little old me.

672
00:28:56,970 --> 00:28:59,070
会跟踪别人
"Little old me" who follows people

673
00:28:59,070 --> 00:29:00,420
还会偷听电话的"小律师"
and listens to their phone calls.

674
00:29:00,420 --> 00:29:01,360
你的账单来了
Oh, your check came.

675
00:29:01,360 --> 00:29:03,530
-我请客吧  -不用了  我自己付
- Let me treat. - No, no. I got it.

676
00:29:03,530 --> 00:29:04,790
老实说吧
Here's the thing, uh...

677
00:29:05,740 --> 00:29:07,180
-埃尔斯贝特  -埃尔斯贝特
- Oh, Elsbeth. - ...Elsbeth,

678
00:29:07,180 --> 00:29:09,590
我确实在司法部有些影响力
I do have some sway at the DoJ,

679
00:29:09,590 --> 00:29:12,630
而且你会发现我是一个相当强劲的对手
and I think you'll find that I'm a pretty tough foe.

680
00:29:13,100 --> 00:29:16,950
你工作上找我麻烦  我就让你生活不痛快
You go after me professionally, I'll go after you personally.

681
00:29:18,770 --> 00:29:20,170
而且我往往都会赢
And I tend to win.

682
00:29:21,800 --> 00:29:24,430
天啊  听起来好吓人
Yikes. That sounds scary.

683
00:29:24,430 --> 00:29:26,100
不  我只是在陈述事实
No. Just telling the truth.

684
00:29:26,830 --> 00:29:27,900
别再跟着我
Don't follow me.

685
00:29:27,970 --> 00:29:29,560
别再偷听我打电话
Don't listen to my phone calls.

686
00:29:34,990 --> 00:29:37,960
辩方要求传唤莫里斯·温特莱布先生作证
The defense calls Mr. Maurice Weintraub to the stand.

687
00:29:37,960 --> 00:29:39,550
反对  法官阁下
Objection. Your Honor,

688
00:29:39,550 --> 00:29:42,710
抱歉  但温特莱布先生不在辩方证人名单上
I'm sorry, but Mr. Weintraub isn't on the defense witness list.

689
00:29:42,710 --> 00:29:44,930
我们是将他作为反驳证人传唤的  法官阁下
We're calling him as a rebuttal witness, Your Honor.

690
00:29:44,930 --> 00:29:47,550
温特莱布先生是在原告证人名单上的
Mr. Weintraub was on the plaintiff's list.

691
00:29:47,550 --> 00:29:49,950
好吧  他反正是在某个名单上的
Well, then he's on a list somewhere.

692
00:29:49,950 --> 00:29:51,060
让他出庭作证吧
Let's get him here.

693
00:29:58,430 --> 00:29:59,660
温特莱布先生
Mr. Weintraub,

694
00:29:59,700 --> 00:30:02,610
你们电视台计划什么时候播出费斯克先生的剧集
when did your network plan to air Mr. Fisk's episode?

695
00:30:02,620 --> 00:30:03,820
先更正一下
A quick correction.

696
00:30:03,820 --> 00:30:06,930
-这并不是他的剧集  -他写的那一集
- It's not his episode. - The episode he wrote.

697
00:30:07,080 --> 00:30:10,920
不  从版权角度来说  是我们写了那一集
No, for the purpose of copyright, we wrote the episode.

698
00:30:11,520 --> 00:30:13,290
我们制片厂和电视台
The studio and the network,

699
00:30:13,310 --> 00:30:16,330
聘用了费斯克先生  也给了他报酬
we paid Mr. Fisk - for a work for hire.

700
00:30:16,600 --> 00:30:19,530
好吧  那我们就来讨论一下你们写的剧集
Okay. Then let's discuss the episode you wrote.

701
00:30:19,530 --> 00:30:21,730
面对没字的白纸一定很艰难吧  先生
It must've been hard facing that blank page, sir.

702
00:30:21,730 --> 00:30:22,930
海明威是怎么说的来着
What did Hemingway call it?

703
00:30:22,940 --> 00:30:24,350
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.

704
00:30:24,350 --> 00:30:27,030
我想这应该算嘲讽性纠缠证人了
I guess I'd call it sarcastic badgering.

705
00:30:27,030 --> 00:30:28,980
我不带嘲讽地说  反对有效
Sustained. Unsarcastically.

706
00:30:28,980 --> 00:30:30,480
好吧  那我换个问题
Okay, then let's try this.

707
00:30:30,480 --> 00:30:32,730
你决定什么时候播出这一集呢
When did you decide to air this episode?

708
00:30:32,740 --> 00:30:33,820
本想五月份左右
Sometime in May,

709
00:30:33,820 --> 00:30:35,040
但现在它已经被放上网了
but now it's been online,

710
00:30:35,040 --> 00:30:36,510
所以没有必要再这么做了
there's no value in doing so.

711
00:30:36,510 --> 00:30:38,060
那你们公司每年会播出这个节目
And how many episodes of this show

712
00:30:38,060 --> 00:30:40,350
-多少集呢  -22集
- does your network air every year? - 22.

713
00:30:40,350 --> 00:30:42,730
但你今年不是订了23集吗  先生
Didn't you order 23 episodes this year, sir?

714
00:30:42,730 --> 00:30:43,530
是的  没错
Yes, that's true.

715
00:30:43,530 --> 00:30:45,310
而且你并不是像往常一样在年初
And didn't you order 23 episodes

716
00:30:45,310 --> 00:30:47,560
就预订了23集节目  而是在你决定
not at the beginning of the year, as you usually do,

717
00:30:47,560 --> 00:30:50,720
不能播出费斯克先生的剧集之后才定的
but after you decided you couldn't air Mr. Fisk's episode?

718
00:30:50,720 --> 00:30:51,820
是的  没错
Yes, that's right.

719
00:30:51,820 --> 00:30:54,740
我们发现费斯克先生私自放出了剧集之后
When we realized Mr. Fisk had put the episode online,

720
00:30:54,740 --> 00:30:56,690
我们认为我们需要多追加一集
we knew we needed an additional episode.

721
00:30:56,690 --> 00:31:00,470
没错  但这在他放出那集之前就发生了
Yeah, but this happened before he put the episode online.

722
00:31:01,500 --> 00:31:03,500
反对  律师自证
Objection. Counselor is testifying.

723
00:31:05,140 --> 00:31:06,200
反对有效
Sustained.

724
00:31:06,450 --> 00:31:09,270
好吧  这有一份写给
Okay, well, here is a memo

725
00:31:09,760 --> 00:31:11,800
节目编剧成员的备忘录
to the show's writing staff,

726
00:31:11,800 --> 00:31:14,510
上面写着要求追加新的一集
asking for an additional episode.

727
00:31:14,510 --> 00:31:16,570
你能读出这上面的日期吗
Could you read the date there?

728
00:31:26,050 --> 00:31:27,990
2016年11月18日
November 18, 2016.

729
00:31:28,190 --> 00:31:30,990
我的客户那时不是还没有放出剧集吗
Wasn't that before my client put the episode online?

730
00:31:31,820 --> 00:31:33,560
反对  超范围提问
Objection. Beyond the scope.

731
00:31:34,100 --> 00:31:35,170
反对有效
Sustained.

732
00:31:37,290 --> 00:31:40,240
难道不是因为特朗普上台之后
Isn't it true, sir, that after Trump won the presidency,

733
00:31:40,240 --> 00:31:42,230
你担心那一集节目会冒犯到他
you were worried the episode would offend him,

734
00:31:42,230 --> 00:31:43,830
所以才决定不播出那一集
so you decided not to show it,

735
00:31:43,830 --> 00:31:46,050
所以才要求追加第23集吗
and that's why you needed a 23rd episode?

736
00:31:46,050 --> 00:31:48,260
不是的  有时我们只是
No, sometimes we just...

737
00:31:49,230 --> 00:31:50,680
这个节目很受欢迎
it's a popular show.

738
00:31:51,370 --> 00:31:53,360
有时我们会预订更多的集数
Sometimes we order more episodes.

739
00:31:53,850 --> 00:31:56,280
很好  我没有其它问题了
Okay. Nothing further.

740
00:32:01,250 --> 00:32:02,810
博斯曼先生  来聊两句
Mr. Boseman, a word.

741
00:32:07,080 --> 00:32:08,920
我听说你们律所在寻求
I hear your firm is looking to branch out

742
00:32:08,920 --> 00:32:10,970
向其它专业领域拓展业务
into other areas of expertise.

743
00:32:11,530 --> 00:32:13,460
我们一直都在寻找机会
We're always looking for opportunities.

744
00:32:13,460 --> 00:32:15,550
如果你不介意的话  我给你点忠告
Well, if you don't mind some unsolicited advice...

745
00:32:15,550 --> 00:32:16,550
是免费的吗
Is it free?

746
00:32:16,550 --> 00:32:19,850
你会发现娱乐法这里是个非常小的圈子
You'll find that entertainment law is an extremely small pond.

747
00:32:19,920 --> 00:32:21,170
你们使出的那些小伎俩
This little performance you're putting on

748
00:32:21,170 --> 00:32:23,000
只会让你们尝到一点甜头
will only help you up to a point.

749
00:32:23,320 --> 00:32:25,220
但如果你让温特莱布先生这样的人难堪
When you embarrass men like Mr. Weintraub,

750
00:32:25,220 --> 00:32:26,890
那你就什么都得不到了
you've passed that point.

751
00:32:27,860 --> 00:32:29,350
你还真是会扫兴啊
You are a real kick.

752
00:32:29,350 --> 00:32:30,320
没错
Yep.

753
00:32:30,380 --> 00:32:32,510
而且只要你不留神  我还会让你更扫兴呢
And I'll kick your ass if you're not careful.

754
00:32:34,620 --> 00:32:35,810
我可真期待
Oh. I can't wait.

755
00:32:38,850 --> 00:32:39,960
你表现得不差嘛
You're not bad.

756
00:32:41,380 --> 00:32:42,920
是啊  我很棒
No, I'm good.

757
00:32:43,370 --> 00:32:44,970
好吧  但语气可能有一点嘲讽
Well, a little sarcastic, maybe.

758
00:32:44,970 --> 00:32:46,030
法官可不喜欢那样
Judges don't like that.

759
00:32:46,030 --> 00:32:48,740
你的评判真是对我大有裨益  谢谢
This is so helpful, being graded. Thank you.

760
00:32:48,830 --> 00:32:50,260
我觉得有人在讽刺我啊
I think we have a sarcasm problem here.

761
00:32:50,260 --> 00:32:52,230
你来这里有什么事吗
Is there some reason why you're here?

762
00:32:52,290 --> 00:32:55,590
有  我帮你们所
Yes. I spoke to the assistant attorney general

763
00:32:55,590 --> 00:32:57,050
和助理总检察长谈过了
on your firm's behalf.

764
00:32:57,050 --> 00:32:59,250
我觉得你们不会有什么麻烦了
I don't think you'll be having any problems anymore.

765
00:33:03,080 --> 00:33:05,670
常规回答是谢谢
The usual response is thank you.

766
00:33:05,680 --> 00:33:07,720
好  谢谢
Yes. Thank you.

767
00:33:07,720 --> 00:33:09,870
他现在对我们律所和林德尔基金
He's now coming after our firm for our connection

768
00:33:09,870 --> 00:33:11,170
的关联紧盯不放
to the Rindell Fund.

769
00:33:11,500 --> 00:33:14,280
我们不得不雇佣一个代理整个律所的律师
We've had to hire a firm-wide lawyer.

770
00:33:14,650 --> 00:33:15,910
-什么  -是的
- What? - Yeah.

771
00:33:16,520 --> 00:33:17,650
谢谢
Thank you.

772
00:33:17,820 --> 00:33:20,660
好吧  现在我很生气
Okay. Okay, now I'm pissed.

773
00:33:20,660 --> 00:33:22,810
你看起来是挺生气的
Yeah, you look it.

774
00:33:23,570 --> 00:33:24,580
谢谢
Thanks.

775
00:33:33,310 --> 00:33:35,870
太棒了  你们太棒了
It was fantastic. You were fantastic.

776
00:33:36,040 --> 00:33:38,270
你们看到让他读日期的时候他的表情了吗
Did you, did you see his face when you made him read the date?

777
00:33:38,270 --> 00:33:39,990
你们让他读出来了  真是太棒了
You made him read it. It was classic.

778
00:33:39,990 --> 00:33:41,860
-就像「佩里·梅森」里演的一样  -是的
- It was like Perry Mason. - Yep.

779
00:33:39,990 --> 00:33:41,860
老牌律政剧

780
00:33:42,030 --> 00:33:44,970
我认为我们做的已经很好了
I think we've taken this as far as we can,

781
00:33:44,970 --> 00:33:47,490
所以我们应该要考虑和对方达成协议了
so we should think about a possible deal.

782
00:33:50,170 --> 00:33:51,100
什么
What?

783
00:33:52,150 --> 00:33:55,610
抱歉  我  我们赢面很大  不是吗
I'm sorry, I... we have them on the run now, right?

784
00:33:55,640 --> 00:33:57,070
我们没有确凿证据
We don't have a smoking gun.

785
00:33:57,520 --> 00:33:58,500
没有确凿证据的话
Without that,

786
00:33:58,990 --> 00:34:01,630
就得假设我们在实体审讯阶段会输掉
we have to assume we're gonna lose the case on the merits.

787
00:34:01,690 --> 00:34:03,590
基思  我们现在能做的就是争取让电视台
What we're left with, Keith, is trying to get the network

788
00:34:03,590 --> 00:34:05,840
同意把金额限制在你能忍受的范围内
to agree to a dollar amount you can live with.

789
00:34:06,190 --> 00:34:07,300
抱歉  失陪一下
If you'll excuse me.

790
00:34:13,810 --> 00:34:15,480
所以  我们来谈谈你的财产
So, we should talk about your assets.

791
00:34:15,740 --> 00:34:16,890
这会毁了我的
It'll ruin me.

792
00:34:18,070 --> 00:34:20,000
他们不会拿走我的普锐斯汽车吧
You don't think they'll take my Prius, do you?

793
00:34:20,410 --> 00:34:22,540
不  你好  戴安
No. Oh, hi there, Diane.

794
00:34:22,540 --> 00:34:25,020
-格罗斯先生  -看看这地方
- Mr. Gross. - But look at this place.

795
00:34:25,050 --> 00:34:26,820
一个真正的非裔美国人的律所
A real African-American law firm.

796
00:34:26,820 --> 00:34:27,790
我爱这里
I love it.

797
00:34:28,490 --> 00:34:29,650
目之所及的每个地方
Everywhere you look.

798
00:34:29,680 --> 00:34:31,690
除了这里  三个白人
Except here. White, white, white.

799
00:34:31,720 --> 00:34:33,270
-梅丽莎  -我要走了
- Marissa. - Yep. I'm leaving.

800
00:34:33,270 --> 00:34:35,150
不用  等等  留下来
Oh, no, no. Wait, stay.

801
00:34:35,270 --> 00:34:36,290
做点记录什么的
Take some notes or something.

802
00:34:36,290 --> 00:34:38,320
没问题  我就坐在这里
Sure. I'll just sit right here.

803
00:34:40,400 --> 00:34:43,940
戴安  我正在考虑让贵所加入处理
So, Diane, I am thinking of adding your firm

804
00:34:43,940 --> 00:34:45,180
我在中西部的业务
to my Midwest business.

805
00:34:45,180 --> 00:34:45,980
你觉得怎么样
What do you say about that?

806
00:34:45,980 --> 00:34:48,020
-我觉得这主意很不错  -好的
- I say that's a great idea. - Good.

807
00:34:48,790 --> 00:34:51,170
我公司的法务部要有点冲劲
Yeah, we could use a little fight in our legal department.

808
00:34:51,170 --> 00:34:53,080
这你放心  我们就是为抗争而生的
Oh, you'll get that here. Fighting is in our blood.

809
00:34:53,080 --> 00:34:54,900
我知道  你们知道我是怎么知道的吗
Oh, I know. You know how I know that?

810
00:34:54,900 --> 00:34:55,770
说实话  不知道
No, actually, no.

811
00:34:55,770 --> 00:34:57,810
你们对抗拍特朗普马屁的电视台
This case you're bringing against the networks

812
00:34:57,810 --> 00:34:59,960
-那个案子  -我知道  那不是棒吗
- for sucking up to Trump. - I know. Isn't that great?

813
00:34:59,960 --> 00:35:01,050
别的律所都不接这个案子
No other firm would take it.

814
00:35:01,050 --> 00:35:03,440
没错  每个人都害怕那个家伙
Exactly. Everybody's so afraid of that guy.

815
00:35:03,440 --> 00:35:05,070
但共和党对奥巴马做了什么
But I say we do to Trump

816
00:35:05,070 --> 00:35:07,400
我们就要对特朗普做同样的事情
the same thing the Republicans did to Obama.

817
00:35:07,400 --> 00:35:09,490
不要和解  不要谈判
Don't settle, don't negotiate,

818
00:35:09,870 --> 00:35:11,090
也不要让步
and don't back down.

819
00:35:11,330 --> 00:35:14,020
你等着瞧他们怎么在法庭上打败那家电视台吧
Well, wait till you see the way they go after the network in court.

820
00:35:14,390 --> 00:35:16,730
这就是我来这里的原因  戴安
See that? This is why I'm here, Diane.

821
00:35:17,060 --> 00:35:20,200
我这只有一群白人老家伙
I just have a bunch of old-fart, white guys

822
00:35:20,200 --> 00:35:21,310
我们不知道如何抗争
who don't know how to fight.

823
00:35:21,310 --> 00:35:22,910
所以我才想来这里
That's why I'm thinking about coming here.

824
00:35:22,980 --> 00:35:24,310
你们知道如何抗争
You guys know how to fight.

825
00:35:24,430 --> 00:35:26,190
-那就让我们一起抗争吧  -当然
- So let's fight. - Indeed.

826
00:35:27,610 --> 00:35:30,040
可以给我一点时间吗  格罗斯先生
Um, could you just give me one minute, Mr. Gross?

827
00:35:35,640 --> 00:35:38,170
塔肖尼女士  我担心的是
Here's my worry, Ms. Tascioni.

828
00:35:38,410 --> 00:35:40,280
玛娅和我之间有律师与当事人保密特权  而且
Maia and I have attorney/client privilege and...

829
00:35:40,280 --> 00:35:41,720
是的  我们之间也有
Yes, and so do we,

830
00:35:41,720 --> 00:35:43,380
因为我代理整个律所
because I represent the firm.

831
00:35:43,840 --> 00:35:47,160
是  但是有些事情只和玛娅有关
Y-Yes, but some of these issues are only Maia's.

832
00:35:48,110 --> 00:35:49,200
那她应该离开律所
Hmm, then she should quit the firm

833
00:35:49,200 --> 00:35:51,830
因为她的个人问题会损害律所的利益
because her issues are hurting the firm's interests.

834
00:35:51,830 --> 00:35:53,010
不  我认为这不是
No, I-I don't think that's what...

835
00:35:53,010 --> 00:35:54,140
你想知道什么
What do you want to know?

836
00:35:54,750 --> 00:35:57,420
你父亲为什么会被保释
Why is your dad out on bail?

837
00:35:59,090 --> 00:36:00,180
我不知道
I don't know.

838
00:36:01,020 --> 00:36:03,760
他可能给克里斯特瓦先生提供了哪些名字
What names might he have given to Mr. Kresteva?

839
00:36:03,760 --> 00:36:05,550
玛娅  我认为你不应该回答这问题  你
Maia, I don't think you should answer that. You...

840
00:36:07,250 --> 00:36:10,230
我父亲让我下载一份名单并交给他
My dad had me download and give to him a list

841
00:36:10,230 --> 00:36:13,670
名单上是基金为其进行非法活动的重要客户
of all the VIP clients that the fund did illegal work for.

842
00:36:13,890 --> 00:36:16,300
你认为他把这些名字提供给他们了
And you think he gave them those names?

843
00:36:16,480 --> 00:36:17,440
是的
Yes.

844
00:36:17,600 --> 00:36:18,900
你看过那份名单了吗
Did you look at the list?

845
00:36:19,250 --> 00:36:20,260
看了
Yes.

846
00:36:20,300 --> 00:36:22,480
有没有与这家律所有关的人的名字
Were there any names connected to this firm?

847
00:36:22,480 --> 00:36:23,970
没有  我全都查过了
No. No, I looked them all up.

848
00:36:23,970 --> 00:36:26,800
没有律所的客户或律师的名字
There are no clients, no lawyers from this firm.

849
00:36:26,800 --> 00:36:28,010
你确定吗
Are you sure?

850
00:36:28,080 --> 00:36:31,240
因为他找到了某个人
Because he found someone...

851
00:36:31,240 --> 00:36:33,150
我喜欢这个唇膏
I like that lipstick.

852
00:36:33,640 --> 00:36:34,710
颜色很漂亮
That's a good color.

853
00:36:36,090 --> 00:36:37,070
谢谢
Thank you.

854
00:36:37,370 --> 00:36:38,540
会是什么呢
What is it?

855
00:36:40,420 --> 00:36:41,990
迪奥  红色
Dior. - Rouge. -

856
00:36:42,270 --> 00:36:43,410
我是说  也可能是香奈儿
Well, I mean, it could be Chanel.

857
00:36:43,410 --> 00:36:46,830
不  有一个雷迪克&博斯曼律所的律师
No. There is a Reddick, Boseman lawyer

858
00:36:46,840 --> 00:36:48,940
和那个重要客户名单有关联
connected to that VIP list.

859
00:36:49,420 --> 00:36:50,700
-谁  -你
- Who? - You.

860
00:36:50,930 --> 00:36:53,870
你下载了那份名单并把它交给了你父亲
You implicated yourself by downloading that list

861
00:36:53,870 --> 00:36:55,600
这就把你自己卷入了这件事
and getting it to your father,

862
00:36:55,600 --> 00:36:58,580
但前提是你父亲出卖你
but that would require your father turning on you,

863
00:36:58,580 --> 00:37:00,550
他不会出卖你的  对吧
and he wouldn't turn on you, would he?

864
00:37:05,250 --> 00:37:08,990
好吧  我们就到这里吧
Okay, let's leave this here.

865
00:37:10,170 --> 00:37:13,640
我会试着找到更多线索的
And I will try to find out something more.

866
00:37:15,770 --> 00:37:16,670
另外
Oh, and...

867
00:37:17,530 --> 00:37:19,910
如果你父亲再向你要求什么事  玛娅
if your dad asks anything more of you, Maia,

868
00:37:19,910 --> 00:37:22,110
我强烈要求你拒绝
I urge you to say no.

869
00:37:22,820 --> 00:37:25,430
他可能会为了减刑
He might be doing something at Mr. Kresteva's bidding

870
00:37:25,430 --> 00:37:27,570
而按照克里斯特瓦先生的指示做事
in order to lighten his sentence.

871
00:37:27,570 --> 00:37:29,960
他可能还会把你们的对话录音
He might also be recording your conversations.

872
00:37:29,960 --> 00:37:31,500
我不想这么说  但是
I hate to talk that way, but...

873
00:37:32,190 --> 00:37:34,690
你们花钱雇我就是让我来怀疑一切的
you pay me to be suspicious.

874
00:37:40,710 --> 00:37:41,670
好的
Okay.

875
00:37:42,450 --> 00:37:43,650
我要走了  再见
I'm going. Bye.

876
00:37:51,390 --> 00:37:53,290
弹道学中的三维技术

877
00:37:59,830 --> 00:38:00,810
你感觉如何
How do you feel?

878
00:38:01,570 --> 00:38:02,510
你不用过来的
You didn't have to come.

879
00:38:02,510 --> 00:38:03,990
我知道我不用过来的
I know I didn't have to come.

880
00:38:04,370 --> 00:38:05,370
谢谢
Thank you.

881
00:38:05,870 --> 00:38:07,420
这是我最后一次做这种事了
It's the last time I'm doing this.

882
00:38:07,660 --> 00:38:09,320
把观众都想象成是裸体的就行
Just picture them all naked.

883
00:38:13,130 --> 00:38:14,600
即使我搞砸了你也会爱我吗
You'll like me even if I fuck up?

884
00:38:14,600 --> 00:38:16,770
会  祝演讲成功
I will. Break a leg.

885
00:38:26,720 --> 00:38:27,660
晚上好
Good evening.

886
00:38:31,180 --> 00:38:32,750
取一根头发
Take a hair from your head.

887
00:38:33,140 --> 00:38:35,690
在想象中把它劈开
Now imagine that you can split that hair

888
00:38:35,690 --> 00:38:38,800
不只一  两次
down the middle not once, not twice,

889
00:38:38,810 --> 00:38:40,060
而是分50次
but 50 times.

890
00:38:40,090 --> 00:38:42,750
这五十分之一的头发就是两微米
That is the equivalent of two microns.

891
00:38:47,820 --> 00:38:49,680
要在弹道学上取得成效
To be effective at ballistics,

892
00:38:49,690 --> 00:38:52,420
就得讨论其具体方法
that is the measure that we need to be discussing.

893
00:38:52,850 --> 00:38:54,300
感谢莅临  谢谢
Thanks for coming. Thank you.

894
00:38:55,350 --> 00:38:56,290
谢谢
Thank you.

895
00:38:58,750 --> 00:39:01,030
很棒  讲得不急不慌
Great. I mean, you didn't rush.

896
00:39:01,030 --> 00:39:03,320
易于理解  清清楚楚
You made all your points comprehensible.

897
00:39:03,320 --> 00:39:04,230
我...
I'm...

898
00:39:08,610 --> 00:39:11,240
林德尔还是不愿说出她的名字
Rindell's still reluctant to give up her name.

899
00:39:11,990 --> 00:39:15,820
不  只是再强势一些而已
No, just a more aggressive posture, that's all.

900
00:39:16,910 --> 00:39:19,770
好  我到家了
Yeah. Okay, I'm home.

901
00:39:20,650 --> 00:39:21,540
再见
Bye.

902
00:39:21,560 --> 00:39:23,900
迪  一切可好
Say, D. What's happening?

903
00:39:23,900 --> 00:39:25,390
-人呢  -在这儿
- Where are you? - Back here.

904
00:39:27,700 --> 00:39:28,790
对了  冰激凌
Oh... the ice cream.

905
00:39:28,820 --> 00:39:30,800
彻底忘了  我乐意再出去买
I totally forgot. I'm happy to go back out.

906
00:39:30,800 --> 00:39:32,650
不用了  有了
No, no, no, we got some.

907
00:39:33,270 --> 00:39:35,530
听上去你已经开喝了
Sounds like you've been drinking already.

908
00:39:36,110 --> 00:39:37,620
迈克  你回来晚了
Mike, you're late.

909
00:39:39,230 --> 00:39:40,320
你还好吗
Are you all right?

910
00:39:41,190 --> 00:39:44,150
当然
Yeah. Uh, yeah.

911
00:39:44,810 --> 00:39:48,700
没想到会见到...
I just wasn't expecting to see...

912
00:39:48,700 --> 00:39:50,330
你同事
Your friend from work.

913
00:39:50,680 --> 00:39:52,480
你怎么从没向我介绍过
How come you've never introduced us?

914
00:39:52,480 --> 00:39:54,190
我也是这么说的
I said the same thing.

915
00:39:54,580 --> 00:39:56,300
迈克在同事面前不透露私生活
Mike is so private at work.

916
00:39:56,620 --> 00:39:58,290
我在乔之商贸城购物
I was shopping at Trader Joe's

917
00:39:58,290 --> 00:40:00,780
埃尔斯贝特听到我的姓  于是攀谈起来
when Elsbeth heard my last name and we started talking.

918
00:40:00,780 --> 00:40:04,340
聊起在夏威夷裸泳
About you skinny-dipping in Hawaii.

919
00:40:04,340 --> 00:40:05,720
她问起来我就说了
She got that out of me.

920
00:40:05,820 --> 00:40:06,990
我俩都晒伤了  我的天
We were so sunburned. Oh, my God.

921
00:40:06,990 --> 00:40:09,090
她就不请自来了
And she invited herself over?

922
00:40:09,100 --> 00:40:10,750
不  是我请她来的
No, I invited her.

923
00:40:10,750 --> 00:40:12,150
我不想独自喝酒
I didn't want to drink alone.

924
00:40:12,340 --> 00:40:14,260
然后埃尔斯贝特说帮我写
But then Elsbeth offered to help me address

925
00:40:14,260 --> 00:40:16,800
咱们结婚纪念日的致谢卡片
all of the thank you notes for our anniversary.

926
00:40:16,800 --> 00:40:18,670
这是我的荣幸
It was my pleasure.

927
00:40:19,550 --> 00:40:22,110
话说  我超爱你家厨房设计
I just love this kitchen, by the way.

928
00:40:22,110 --> 00:40:23,260
你人真好
You are so sweet.

929
00:40:23,260 --> 00:40:24,430
还有书房
And the study.

930
00:40:24,920 --> 00:40:26,490
没错  很喜欢你的书房
Oh, yes, I love your study.

931
00:40:26,490 --> 00:40:28,740
整体设计得很协调
The way you make the-the whole thing work together.

932
00:40:28,750 --> 00:40:30,950
-你...  -我不懂颜色搭配
- You were... - I'm terrible with colors.

933
00:40:30,960 --> 00:40:32,320
进了我书房
...in my study?

934
00:40:32,880 --> 00:40:34,910
是  去洗手间时顺便参观的
Yeah, on my way to the bathroom.

935
00:40:35,680 --> 00:40:36,730
是么
I see.

936
00:40:36,930 --> 00:40:39,230
迈克  来  亲一下
Mike, come on. Give me a kiss.

937
00:40:39,750 --> 00:40:42,520
埃尔斯贝特刚还在说你在办公室特有趣
Elsbeth was just saying how fun you are at the office.

938
00:40:42,600 --> 00:40:43,650
的确
He is.

939
00:40:45,990 --> 00:40:47,210
我马上回来
I'll be right back.

940
00:41:05,370 --> 00:41:07,190
埃尔斯贝特·塔肖尼

941
00:41:08,620 --> 00:41:10,960
大学时  迈克是啦啦队员
In college, Mike was a cheerleader.

942
00:41:11,600 --> 00:41:13,220
而我内向腼腆
And I was the shy girl.

943
00:41:13,510 --> 00:41:15,340
-你一点都不  -当时的确
- You weren't shy. - I was.

944
00:41:15,340 --> 00:41:18,100
不可能  看你现在如此开朗
No. The way you are now?

945
00:41:18,100 --> 00:41:19,740
那是因为喝了酒
That's because I'm drinking.

946
00:41:20,100 --> 00:41:22,420
但迈克解放了我的天性  是吧
But Mike really pulled me out of my shell, didn't you?

947
00:41:22,970 --> 00:41:26,030
是  谢谢你来看我们
Yeah. Thanks for dropping by.

948
00:41:27,980 --> 00:41:30,210
是哦  我该走了
Oh, yes. I guess I should go.

949
00:41:30,210 --> 00:41:31,460
别走  留下吃晚饭
No, no, stay for dinner.

950
00:41:31,470 --> 00:41:33,560
不了  也许...
No, no, no. Maybe, uh...

951
00:41:33,600 --> 00:41:35,440
-再找时间吧  -对了
- Maybe some other time. - Yes.

952
00:41:35,440 --> 00:41:36,890
咱们还约好去吃午饭呢
And we have that lunch date.

953
00:41:36,890 --> 00:41:39,470
是吗  什么时候
Oh, yeah? When's that?

954
00:41:39,480 --> 00:41:40,470
下周  对吧
Next week, right?

955
00:41:40,470 --> 00:41:42,080
是  我请客哦
Right. I'm treating.

956
00:41:42,080 --> 00:41:43,550
不  我请
No, I'm treating.

957
00:41:44,430 --> 00:41:45,410
我送你出去
I'll walk you out.

958
00:41:45,410 --> 00:41:46,600
不麻烦了  迈克
Oh, don't bother, Mike.

959
00:41:46,600 --> 00:41:48,490
不麻烦
Oh, it's no bother.

960
00:41:50,840 --> 00:41:53,930
你这样做  我可以吊销你的律师执照
I could have you disbarred for doing something like that.

961
00:41:54,330 --> 00:41:55,500
我进我家...
You come to my home...

962
00:41:55,500 --> 00:41:56,990
是人家邀请我来的
I was invited into your home.

963
00:41:56,990 --> 00:41:58,310
翻我办公桌
Go through my desk,

964
00:41:58,310 --> 00:42:00,260
还要挟我老婆诈取信息
shake down my wife for information.

965
00:42:00,260 --> 00:42:02,260
我绝不会要挟迪尔德拉
I would never shake down Diedre.

966
00:42:02,260 --> 00:42:03,350
她太可爱了
She's too lovely.

967
00:42:03,350 --> 00:42:05,860
等着听吊销律师资格委员会的人怎么说吧
Yeah, well, let's see what a disbarment committee says.

968
00:42:05,860 --> 00:42:07,010
注意安全
Get home safe.

969
00:42:10,120 --> 00:42:12,160
是啊  听听他们怎么说
Yeah, let's see what they say.

970
00:42:12,160 --> 00:42:13,870
你当时说什么来着
What was your quote? Um...

971
00:42:14,620 --> 00:42:17,400
"你工作上找我麻烦
"When you go after me professionally,

972
00:42:17,400 --> 00:42:19,980
我就让你生活不痛快"
I go after you personally."

973
00:42:20,010 --> 00:42:22,690
-我从没这么说过  -你说过
- I never said that. - Yes, you did.

974
00:42:22,780 --> 00:42:23,860
在餐厅
At the diner.

975
00:42:24,220 --> 00:42:25,410
胡说
That's a lie.

976
00:42:27,100 --> 00:42:28,870
你工作上找我麻烦
You go after me professionally,

977
00:42:28,970 --> 00:42:30,840
我就让你生活不痛快
I'll go after you personally.

978
00:42:31,530 --> 00:42:33,230
这是非法录音
It's an illegal recording.

979
00:42:33,730 --> 00:42:37,070
是  除非用于反驳谎言
Yes, unless it's used to contradict a lie.

980
00:42:37,240 --> 00:42:38,540
一切都好吗
Is everything all right?

981
00:42:38,540 --> 00:42:40,380
很好  在聊些公事
Oh, yeah, just something at work.

982
00:42:43,490 --> 00:42:44,540
再见
Bye!

983
00:42:54,460 --> 00:42:56,660
我们国家百分之九十的媒体
90% of the media in this country

984
00:42:56,660 --> 00:42:59,570
被六大集团控制  法官阁下
is controlled by six corporations, Your Honor.

985
00:43:00,130 --> 00:43:01,250
想想吧
Think about that.

986
00:43:02,080 --> 00:43:03,010
想想
Think.

987
00:43:04,340 --> 00:43:07,970
就像  天安门广场一排坦克
A column of tanks in Tiananmen Square, for instance,

988
00:43:07,970 --> 00:43:11,500
是控制人们所见所听所想的一种方式
is one way of controlling what people see, hear,

989
00:43:11,500 --> 00:43:14,560
但并非唯一方式  法官阁下
but it is not the only way, Your Honor.

990
00:43:15,070 --> 00:43:16,560
不是准备协商和解了吗
I thought we were negotiating.

991
00:43:16,640 --> 00:43:18,400
阿德里安觉得结果可以更好
Adrian thinks we can do better.

992
00:43:19,030 --> 00:43:22,690
政府打算遏制自由思想
A government intent on stifling the free flow of ideas

993
00:43:22,690 --> 00:43:26,940
只需遏制六大集团
need only stifle these six corporations.

994
00:43:27,690 --> 00:43:32,350
法官阁下  如今此地正如天安门广场
Your Honor, we are living in Tiananmen Square right here.

995
00:43:33,450 --> 00:43:36,840
这位年轻人  因在某网站上发布电视剧集
And this young man, by putting an episode of television

996
00:43:36,840 --> 00:43:40,020
就被那些坦克瞄准了
on a Web site, stood in front of those tanks.

997
00:43:40,200 --> 00:43:42,720
我今天请求法庭
And I am asking this court today

998
00:43:43,160 --> 00:43:45,730
不要让那些坦克粉碎这位年轻人的思想精神
to stop those tanks from crushing this young man's spirit

999
00:43:45,730 --> 00:43:46,980
和他的反抗意识
and his defiance.

1000
00:43:47,840 --> 00:43:48,800
好吧
Okay.

1001
00:43:50,390 --> 00:43:51,520
说得不错
Good speech.

1002
00:43:53,360 --> 00:43:54,920
我能下判决了吗
Now can I make my decision?

1003
00:43:55,070 --> 00:43:55,650
老天 赶紧吧
Oh, God, please.

1004
00:43:55,650 --> 00:43:58,920
法官阁下  我们刚得到新证据
Your Honor, we have new evidence just come to our attention.

1005
00:43:58,920 --> 00:44:01,580
法官阁下  您正要下判决呢
Your Honor, you were just about to decide.

1006
00:44:01,580 --> 00:44:02,890
法官阁下  我们相信这一证据
Your Honor, we believe this evidence

1007
00:44:02,890 --> 00:44:05,630
关乎「第一修正案」
touches upon your First Amendment concern.

1008
00:44:05,630 --> 00:44:06,620
是什么
What is it?

1009
00:44:07,580 --> 00:44:09,910
今天早上总统发了推特  法官阁下
The president just tweeted this morning, Your Honor.

1010
00:44:10,610 --> 00:44:12,760
"祝贺温特劳布成功抵御
"Congrats to Weintraub for standing up

1011
00:44:12,760 --> 00:44:15,310
一个好莱坞的爱哭鬼
to another Hollywood crybaby."

1012
00:44:16,260 --> 00:44:19,370
是时候调查那个他们雇来的写手了"
Time to look into who they hire to write."

1013
00:44:20,910 --> 00:44:23,570
那条推特初步表明政府的行为
That tweet is prima facie government action

1014
00:44:23,570 --> 00:44:25,800
触及了「第一修正案」的规定
that triggers a First Amendment defense.

1015
00:44:26,150 --> 00:44:27,300
法官阁下  今天上午您说
You said this morning, Your Honor,

1016
00:44:27,300 --> 00:44:29,500
这不是一桩涉及「第一修正案」的案件
this is not a First Amendment case.

1017
00:44:29,690 --> 00:44:32,510
但是恕我冒昧  我认为
But I submit, in all due respect,

1018
00:44:34,210 --> 00:44:35,250
如今它是了
now it is.

1019
00:44:45,140 --> 00:44:47,530
你们公开道个歉  我们就扯平了
A public apology and we'll call it even.

1020
00:44:48,560 --> 00:44:49,580
不
No.

1021
00:44:50,030 --> 00:44:51,860
什么  你还想向我们索赔吗
What, you want us to pay you?

1022
00:44:53,260 --> 00:44:55,590
不用公开道歉  我们就扯平了
No public apology, and we'll call it even.

1023
00:44:56,670 --> 00:44:58,110
我会去和我当事人说的
I'll talk to my clients.

1024
00:44:58,630 --> 00:44:59,840
我希望你们这么做真的值
I hope that was worth it to you,

1025
00:44:59,840 --> 00:45:01,880
因为这对你们的生意没好处
because it won't do much for your business.

1026
00:45:04,350 --> 00:45:05,650
我们值得吗
Is it worth it to us?

1027
00:45:06,740 --> 00:45:07,740
等着瞧吧
We'll see.

1028
00:45:16,840 --> 00:45:18,680
你不喜欢多说你自己的事  对吗
You don't like talking about yourself much, do you?

1029
00:45:19,580 --> 00:45:20,650
我只是在散步而已
I'm just walking.

1030
00:45:21,260 --> 00:45:23,170
不  我们谈过所有关于我的事
No, we've talked everything about me.

1031
00:45:23,170 --> 00:45:26,400
我专制的家庭  我妹妹的跳伞纪录
My overbearing family, my sister's parachuting record,

1032
00:45:26,400 --> 00:45:27,460
我的戒瘾之路
my struggle with addiction.

1033
00:45:27,460 --> 00:45:29,810
健怡可乐可不算瘾
Yeah, Diet Coke doesn't really count.

1034
00:45:29,820 --> 00:45:31,570
但我们没谈过任何关于你的事
But nothing about you.

1035
00:45:32,230 --> 00:45:33,480
我没什么好说的
There is nothing about me.

1036
00:45:33,480 --> 00:45:35,450
你父母喜欢你当律师吗
Are your parents happy that you're a lawyer?

1037
00:45:37,030 --> 00:45:38,670
-也许吧  -天哪
- I guess. - Oh, my God,

1038
00:45:38,670 --> 00:45:40,710
这就像是在盘问一样
it's like a cross-examination.

1039
00:45:41,130 --> 00:45:42,950
-他们都还在世吗  -是的
- Are they both still alive? - Yes.

1040
00:45:43,340 --> 00:45:44,500
你最好的朋友是谁
Who's your best friend?

1041
00:45:45,080 --> 00:45:46,310
我没有朋友
I don't have a friend.

1042
00:45:46,730 --> 00:45:48,920
停下  看着我
Stop. Look at me.

1043
00:45:49,690 --> 00:45:50,280
再说一遍
Say it again.

1044
00:45:50,280 --> 00:45:53,420
我没有朋友
I don't have a friend.

1045
00:45:56,220 --> 00:45:57,400
我不相信
I don't believe you.

1046
00:45:57,830 --> 00:45:58,980
这是你的权利
That's your right.

1047
00:46:01,740 --> 00:46:02,720
怎么了
What?

1048
00:46:03,870 --> 00:46:05,740
请不要说你要拯救我
Please don't say you're gonna save me.

1049
00:46:06,460 --> 00:46:09,510
-不  我要吻你  -那好
- No, I'm gonna kiss you. - Okay.

1050
00:46:15,730 --> 00:46:17,150
然后我会拯救你
Then I'm gonna save you.

1051
00:46:39,930 --> 00:46:41,160
我曾经有过最好的朋友
I had a best friend.

1052
00:46:45,410 --> 00:46:46,370
是谁
Who?

1053
00:46:46,600 --> 00:46:47,710
一个同事
A co-worker.

1054
00:46:49,400 --> 00:46:50,370
男的还是女的
He or she?

1055
00:46:50,370 --> 00:46:51,370
女的
She.

1056
00:46:53,460 --> 00:46:54,400
曾经有过
Had?

1057
00:46:54,630 --> 00:46:56,110
她不再是你的朋友了吗
She's not a friend anymore?

1058
00:46:56,230 --> 00:46:57,340
我觉得她还是的
I think she is.

1059
00:46:58,270 --> 00:46:59,710
我不轻易交朋友
I don't make friends easily.

1060
00:47:02,110 --> 00:47:03,200
为什么
Why not?

1061
00:47:05,530 --> 00:47:06,930
我不想受伤
I don't like to get hurt.

1062
00:47:09,540 --> 00:47:11,060
你害怕我会伤害你
You afraid I'm gonna hurt you?

1063
00:47:13,120 --> 00:47:14,960
不  男孩子伤不了我
No, I don't get hurt by boys.

1064
00:47:18,750 --> 00:47:19,960
让你不开心了吗
Are you offended?

1065
00:47:21,000 --> 00:47:22,050
我不知道
I don't know.

1066
00:47:22,160 --> 00:47:23,470
我甚至都不明白
I don't even understand it.

1067
00:47:26,610 --> 00:47:28,280
你会让我疯狂
You're gonna make me act crazy.

1068
00:47:29,810 --> 00:47:32,430
-是吗  -是的  你把事搞砸了
- I am? - Oh, yeah. You fucked up.

1069
00:47:33,010 --> 00:47:34,360
让我很感兴趣
You got me interested.

1070
00:47:43,020 --> 00:47:44,260
完美的房间  月租2000美元

1071
00:47:44,510 --> 00:47:45,220
机会不容错过  月租1000美元

1072
00:47:45,300 --> 00:47:45,920
机会不容错过  月租850美元

1073
00:47:54,090 --> 00:47:55,070
早上好
Good morning.

1074
00:47:57,720 --> 00:47:59,140
风之城[芝加哥别称]

1075
00:47:59,410 --> 00:48:00,650
那些箱子里装的什么
What's with the boxes?

1076
00:48:02,820 --> 00:48:04,330
我在找新的住所
I'm looking for a new place.

1077
00:48:05,120 --> 00:48:06,040
为什么
Why?

1078
00:48:08,310 --> 00:48:09,480
只是想改变一下
Just for a change.

1079
00:48:10,610 --> 00:48:11,740
变成什么样
Change to what?

1080
00:48:12,730 --> 00:48:13,820
找个新地方
A new place.

1081
00:48:25,050 --> 00:48:26,480
你想搬到我这里来吗
Do you want to move in together?

1082
00:48:33,330 --> 00:48:34,210
不想
No.

1083
00:48:37,250 --> 00:48:38,210
为什么
Why not?

1084
00:48:42,590 --> 00:48:43,790
这是我的问题
It's my problem.

1085
00:48:57,170 --> 00:48:58,370
我要去工作了
I have to get to work.

1086
00:48:59,780 --> 00:49:00,700
戴安
Diane...

1087
00:49:02,170 --> 00:49:03,220
让我来帮你
let me help.

1088
00:49:06,800 --> 00:49:08,130
库尔特  昨夜很美好
Kurt, last night was great,

1089
00:49:08,130 --> 00:49:10,550
但我要去工作了
but I have to get to work.

1090
00:49:21,010 --> 00:49:23,140
让你干脏活  那是什么
Makes you do the dirty work... what is that?

1091
00:49:23,780 --> 00:49:25,020
-进来  -戴安
- Come in. - Diane.

1092
00:49:25,250 --> 00:49:27,350
-是好消息吗  -我想是的
- Good news? - I think so.

1093
00:49:28,520 --> 00:49:30,240
尼尔·格罗斯知道我们赢了案子
Neil Gross saw that we won the case.

1094
00:49:30,680 --> 00:49:32,950
-他想签我们  -真好
- He wants to come on board. - Yes!

1095
00:49:33,240 --> 00:49:35,010
每年5800万美元
$58 million a year!

1096
00:49:35,010 --> 00:49:36,870
这还是生意不好的收入
And that's in a slow year.

1097
00:49:36,930 --> 00:49:38,010
等等  等等
Wait, wait.

1098
00:49:38,440 --> 00:49:40,060
我想你还有别的话要说
I think I'm seeing a caveat here.

1099
00:49:41,120 --> 00:49:42,060
一点小事
A small one.

1100
00:49:42,060 --> 00:49:43,020
什么
What?

1101
00:49:45,070 --> 00:49:46,380
我很喜欢这家律所
I like this firm a lot.

1102
00:49:46,560 --> 00:49:48,040
我觉得它的未来无可限量
I think it's got a great future.

1103
00:49:48,610 --> 00:49:49,740
但是凭良心讲
But in good conscience,

1104
00:49:49,750 --> 00:49:51,730
我并不太想要尼尔·格罗斯加入
I can't encourage Neil Gross to come here

1105
00:49:51,740 --> 00:49:53,740
如果我只是一名普通律师的话
if I'm only of counsel.

1106
00:49:54,840 --> 00:49:56,580
你在搞笑吗  戴安
You're fucking kidding me, Diane.

1107
00:49:56,580 --> 00:49:59,150
为什么戴安会是普通律师
Why is Diane going to be - of counsel?

1108
00:49:59,150 --> 00:50:00,740
她不会是普通律师
She isn't going to be of counsel

1109
00:50:00,740 --> 00:50:02,630
如果她拿得出认购金的话
if we get her capital contribution.

1110
00:50:02,630 --> 00:50:04,110
戴安  我们可以之后再解决这个
Diane, we can figure this out later.

1111
00:50:04,110 --> 00:50:06,150
不  我想我们现在就该解决
No, I think we should figure this out now.

1112
00:50:08,610 --> 00:50:09,750
你想怎么样
What do you want?

1113
00:50:11,140 --> 00:50:13,410
我想直接用查查网的聘金
I want my capital contribution to come directly

1114
00:50:13,410 --> 00:50:14,920
来出资入股
from the Chumhum retainer.

1115
00:50:15,720 --> 00:50:17,750
并且我想成为冠名合伙人
And I want to be made a name partner.

1116
00:50:20,230 --> 00:50:22,550
我们需要征求合伙人委员会的同意
We'll have to run that by the partnership committee.

1117
00:50:22,550 --> 00:50:23,470
真要这样吗
Seriously?

1118
00:50:23,480 --> 00:50:25,590
我们会征求合伙人委员会的意见的
We will run it by the partnership committee,

1119
00:50:27,540 --> 00:50:30,410
但是结果一定是肯定的
but the answer is yes.

1120
00:50:30,660 --> 00:50:34,090
祝贺你  戴安·洛哈特  正式合伙人
Congratulations, Diane Lockhart, full partner.

1121
00:50:34,660 --> 00:50:35,670
谢谢
Thank you.

1122
00:50:36,370 --> 00:50:37,730
你们愿意要我我很开心
It's good to be wanted.

1123
00:50:45,930 --> 00:50:47,690
她会是个麻烦
She's gonna be trouble.

