1
00:00:11,020 --> 00:00:12,240
你在看我吗
Are you watching me?

2
00:00:14,370 --> 00:00:15,760
我看起来精神抖擞吗
Do I look dashing?

3
00:00:15,760 --> 00:00:17,280
谁会说自己精神抖擞啊
Nobody says dashing.

4
00:00:17,510 --> 00:00:19,160
詹姆斯·邦德就这么说
James Bond says dashing.

5
00:00:19,250 --> 00:00:20,450
你以为你是詹姆斯·邦德
You think you're James Bond?

6
00:00:20,560 --> 00:00:21,980
我挺像詹姆斯·邦德的
I could be James Bond.

7
00:00:22,650 --> 00:00:25,070
我有康纳利般矫健的步伐
I've got Connery's swagger...

8
00:00:22,650 --> 00:00:25,070
肖恩·康纳利: 詹姆斯·邦德的首位扮演者

9
00:00:25,340 --> 00:00:28,120
我有丹尼尔·克雷格的体型
Definitely Daniel Craig's physique...

10
00:00:25,340 --> 00:00:28,120
丹尼尔·克雷格: 詹姆斯·邦德的第六任扮演者

11
00:00:28,640 --> 00:00:30,280
还有拉赞贝的...
Lazenby's...

12
00:00:28,640 --> 00:00:30,280
乔治·拉赞贝: 詹姆斯·邦德的第二任扮演者

13
00:00:30,700 --> 00:00:32,450
我不知道他有什么特点
I have no idea what he's known for.

14
00:00:34,810 --> 00:00:35,970
你没事吧
You okay?

15
00:00:37,480 --> 00:00:41,530
昨晚  路易对我说了些挺有意思的话
I had an interesting conversation with Louis last night.

16
00:00:42,490 --> 00:00:44,750
他说我应该小心你和瑞秋的关系
He said I should be careful of you and Rachel.

17
00:00:45,960 --> 00:00:47,610
你们俩之间有什么吗
Do I have anything to worry about?

18
00:00:47,800 --> 00:00:48,690
没有
No.

19
00:00:48,960 --> 00:00:52,690
他看我不顺眼  所以想借你来伤害我
He hates me, and he's just trying to get to me through you.

20
00:00:53,240 --> 00:00:54,440
那你们俩从来都没...
So you never--

21
00:00:55,380 --> 00:00:56,260
没有
No.

22
00:00:56,960 --> 00:00:58,280
你不需要担心我们俩
You got nothing to worry about.

23
00:00:58,280 --> 00:00:59,520
我们只是普通朋友
She's just a friend.

24
00:00:59,970 --> 00:01:02,090
-好吧  -我迟到了
- Okay. - And I'm late.

25
00:01:03,750 --> 00:01:04,490
我会打给你
I'll call.

26
00:01:04,490 --> 00:01:05,740
-好  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.

27
00:01:08,910 --> 00:01:10,250
我们应该出去
We should go out.

28
00:01:12,050 --> 00:01:13,680
我这就是要出门
Uh, this is going out.

29
00:01:13,720 --> 00:01:17,330
不  我的意思是你  我  还有瑞秋
No, I mean you and me and Rachel

30
00:01:17,330 --> 00:01:18,540
应该搞个四人约会
should go on a double date.

31
00:01:18,540 --> 00:01:20,400
她有男朋友吗
Does she have a-a boyfriend?

32
00:01:20,680 --> 00:01:22,730
我  不知道
I, uh, don't know.

33
00:01:22,730 --> 00:01:23,500
不要吧
No.

34
00:01:23,500 --> 00:01:25,380
和同事一起搞四人约会
Going on a double date with somebody from work

35
00:01:25,380 --> 00:01:27,310
会很奇怪的
might be kind of weird.

36
00:01:27,310 --> 00:01:29,350
如果我能了解她  我就不会担心了
If I get to know her, then I won't worry.

37
00:01:29,400 --> 00:01:30,680
会很有意思的
It'll be fun.

38
00:01:30,720 --> 00:01:33,540
只不过是几个朋友一起出去玩  不是吗
Just a couple friends going out. Right?

39
00:01:34,810 --> 00:01:35,960
好极了
Awesome.

40
00:02:04,740 --> 00:02:06,690
你怎么坐出租车  自行车被人偷了吗
Cab? Someone steal your bike?

41
00:02:06,690 --> 00:02:08,620
我现在脑子很乱  骑车怕出危险
I have a lot on my mind. It's a safety issue.

42
00:02:08,620 --> 00:02:09,540
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?

43
00:02:09,540 --> 00:02:11,650
路易跟珍妮说了我和瑞秋的事情
Louis told Jenny about Rachel and me.

44
00:02:11,650 --> 00:02:13,270
只不过是一个吻  还是她主动的
It was one kiss, and she kissed me.

45
00:02:13,270 --> 00:02:15,670
标准的肥皂剧情节  把文件给我
Okay, soap opera, just give me my documents.

46
00:02:15,870 --> 00:02:16,970
哈维
Harvey.

47
00:02:18,980 --> 00:02:20,050
卡梅隆
Cameron.

48
00:02:20,790 --> 00:02:21,990
你好吗
How the hell are you?

49
00:02:22,570 --> 00:02:23,940
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.

50
00:02:24,590 --> 00:02:25,630
太久没见了
Too damn long.

51
00:02:25,770 --> 00:02:27,320
这位是卡梅隆·丹尼斯  检察官
Cameron Dennis, district attorney,

52
00:02:27,320 --> 00:02:28,650
这是迈克·罗斯  我的助理
Meet Mike Ross, my associate.

53
00:02:28,650 --> 00:02:29,340
你好
Hi.

54
00:02:29,580 --> 00:02:31,540
我猜你就是他的哈维
I guess that makes you his Harvey.

55
00:02:32,300 --> 00:02:34,270
-抱歉  -哈维曾是我的助理
- Sorry? - Harvey was my associate.

56
00:02:34,270 --> 00:02:35,500
他的本事都是我教的
I taught him everything he knows.

57
00:02:35,500 --> 00:02:38,710
继我之后  他是最出色的检察官助理
Best A.D.A. to come up since me.

58
00:02:38,980 --> 00:02:42,570
-你教他的  -"绝不上庭"
- You taught him? - "Never go to court."

59
00:02:42,590 --> 00:02:43,190
那就是我说的
That's me.

60
00:02:43,190 --> 00:02:45,120
"无关同情  只看输赢"
"It's not about caring. It's about winning."

61
00:02:45,580 --> 00:02:46,090
还是我说的
Me.

62
00:02:46,090 --> 00:02:47,700
不是吧  你是哈维的哈维
No way. Harvey's Harvey.

63
00:02:47,700 --> 00:02:49,230
没错
Yeah, exactly.

64
00:02:50,340 --> 00:02:53,080
我们应该叙叙旧  一起吃个午饭
We should, uh, catch up, have lunch.

65
00:02:53,150 --> 00:02:54,430
这也太巧了
Hey, you know what? This is crazy.

66
00:02:54,430 --> 00:02:55,580
我今晚正好没事
I'm free for dinner tonight.

67
00:02:55,650 --> 00:02:57,010
你把行程都取消吧
Just cancel whatever you have,

68
00:02:57,010 --> 00:03:00,320
告诉杰西卡我强烈要求你腾出时间陪我
and tell Jessica I demanded that you clear your schedule.

69
00:03:00,740 --> 00:03:02,370
共进晚餐吗  好的
Dinner it is. It'd be nice.

70
00:03:03,360 --> 00:03:04,230
真乖
That's my boy.

71
00:03:05,260 --> 00:03:07,590
你知道去哪儿找我  晚上八点见
All right, you know where to find me, 8:00.

72
00:03:07,620 --> 00:03:08,860
真高兴碰到了你  哈维
Glad I ran into you, Harvey.

73
00:03:18,870 --> 00:03:20,500
罗斯  你还在这里工作吗
Ross, you still work here?

74
00:03:20,640 --> 00:03:21,060
真好笑
Funny.

75
00:03:21,060 --> 00:03:22,250
我以为被我打败之后...
Yeah, 'cause I thought after I beat you--

76
00:03:22,250 --> 00:03:23,250
我知道你想说什么
Yeah, I got it.

77
00:03:23,910 --> 00:03:25,560
-辛苦你赶工了  -不客气
- Thanks for expediting. - Yeah.

78
00:03:34,870 --> 00:03:36,220
你有什么需要吗
Do you need something?

79
00:03:36,560 --> 00:03:38,920
你知道哈维曾经是检察官吗
Did you know that Harvey, uh, was a prosecutor?

80
00:03:38,920 --> 00:03:41,000
-不  他没做过  -不  他曾经是
- No, he wasn't. - Yeah, he was.

81
00:03:41,000 --> 00:03:42,060
我看过公司所有人的简历
I've read every bio at the firm.

82
00:03:42,060 --> 00:03:43,730
凡是在地方检查院工作过的  都会写在简历里
People work for the D.A.'s office, it's on their bio.

83
00:03:43,730 --> 00:03:45,410
今天早上我们遇到了卡梅隆·丹尼斯
Well, we ran into Cameron Dennis this morning.

84
00:03:45,410 --> 00:03:46,840
-那个地方检察官  -对
- The D.A.? - Yeah.

85
00:03:47,050 --> 00:03:49,620
他说哈维是他最得力的助理
He says that Harvey's the best A.D.A. he's ever had.

86
00:03:50,170 --> 00:03:51,360
不可能  跟我来
No. Come here.

87
00:03:52,410 --> 00:03:54,420
看见没  没有做过检察官的记录
See? Nothing about being a prosecutor.

88
00:03:54,420 --> 00:03:55,160
是啊
Yeah.

89
00:03:55,520 --> 00:03:57,690
你得跟我和珍妮搞个四人约会
I need you to go on a double date with me and Jenny.

90
00:03:58,320 --> 00:03:59,600
不可能的
Yeah, not gonna happen.

91
00:03:59,600 --> 00:04:01,430
你一定要来  听我说
You have to. Listen to me.

92
00:04:02,080 --> 00:04:04,160
路易警告她要小心咱俩的关系
Louis warned her about you and me.

93
00:04:04,390 --> 00:04:05,090
什...
Wha--

94
00:04:05,650 --> 00:04:06,760
他怎么知...
How did he even get--

95
00:04:06,790 --> 00:04:07,730
你知道的
You know how.

96
00:04:07,800 --> 00:04:09,900
因为你吻过我之后  他正好走了进来
'Cause he walked in right after you kissed me.

97
00:04:09,900 --> 00:04:10,660
如果你拒绝
If you say no,

98
00:04:10,660 --> 00:04:12,780
那她会以为我们之间有问题
she's gonna think something's going on between us.

99
00:04:13,100 --> 00:04:15,420
好吧  我去
Okay. I'll go.

100
00:04:15,830 --> 00:04:17,900
-谢谢  -讨厌的路易
- Thank you. - Freakin' Louis.

101
00:04:18,380 --> 00:04:20,760
这是哈维吗
Oh, is this Harvey?

102
00:04:21,260 --> 00:04:23,600
没错  你一定要把这张照片发给我
Okay, you are definitely sending me that photo.

103
00:04:23,590 --> 00:04:25,690
年轻律师为恐怖"幽灵"辩护

104
00:04:23,600 --> 00:04:25,790
西法在众多案件中将他列为
Westlaw lists him as prosecutor of record

105
00:04:25,790 --> 00:04:28,390
记录在案的检察官
on pages and pages of cases.

106
00:04:28,390 --> 00:04:29,960
-我就说吧  -我真不明白
- I told you. - I don't get it.

107
00:04:29,960 --> 00:04:31,150
他为什么不把这些写进个人简历
Why wouldn't he have this on his bio?

108
00:04:31,150 --> 00:04:32,170
因为
Because.

109
00:04:32,350 --> 00:04:33,810
哈维想要隐瞒些什么
Harvey's got something to hide.

110
00:04:36,110 --> 00:04:40,110
■

111
00:04:36,110 --> 00:04:40,110
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
 更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

112
00:04:40,110 --> 00:04:45,110
翻译：马蒂 米苏 草草 媛媛 费列罗西瓜

113
00:04:40,110 --> 00:04:45,110
■

114
00:04:45,110 --> 00:04:50,110
时间轴：小怡子 潘叔 迟迟 校对：饿得慌 桃乐

115
00:04:45,110 --> 00:04:50,110
■

116
00:04:50,110 --> 00:04:55,110
后期：飞飞是菇凉  总监：丢丢

117
00:04:50,110 --> 00:04:55,110
■

118
00:05:01,900 --> 00:05:04,070
诉 讼 双 雄

119
00:05:01,900 --> 00:05:04,070
第一季 第十一集

120
00:05:11,310 --> 00:05:13,620
它能碰触到你灵魂深处的理想之境
It touches some idealistic core of your being,

121
00:05:13,620 --> 00:05:16,670
使最愤世嫉俗的人也不曾放弃希望
where even the greatest cynic has not given up hope.

122
00:05:17,130 --> 00:05:18,720
这就是我们听音乐的原因
That's why we listen to music.

123
00:05:18,720 --> 00:05:20,310
太动人了  路易
Oh, that's beautiful, Louis.

124
00:05:20,310 --> 00:05:21,160
真的吗
Really?

125
00:05:21,220 --> 00:05:22,880
我觉得你决定退出法律界
And I think your decision to leave law

126
00:05:22,880 --> 00:05:24,290
去做一名音乐评论家
to become a music critic

127
00:05:24,340 --> 00:05:25,650
会得到所有人的祝福
is in everyone's best interests.

128
00:05:25,650 --> 00:05:27,480
行了  我在引用彼得·谢勒的话
Okay, I was quoting Peter Sellars.

129
00:05:25,650 --> 00:05:27,480
彼得·谢勒: 英国当代最优秀的喜剧演员之一

130
00:05:27,480 --> 00:05:30,720
我刚拿到《尼克松在中国》的票  一千元一张
I just got $1,000-a-head tickets to Nixon in China.

131
00:05:27,480 --> 00:05:30,720
歌剧

132
00:05:30,720 --> 00:05:32,670
你们俩在约会吗  我是不是该待会再来
Are you two dating now? Should I come back?

133
00:05:33,880 --> 00:05:35,170
坐吧  哈维
Sit down, Harvey.

134
00:05:35,310 --> 00:05:38,550
真喜欢你这种语气  像我三年级的柯尔老师
Love it when you talk to me like my third grade teacher, Mrs. Coe.

135
00:05:40,620 --> 00:05:41,620
先生们
Gentlemen.

136
00:05:43,000 --> 00:05:44,640
马尔科姆·普莱斯上周去世了
Malcolm Price died last week.

137
00:05:44,640 --> 00:05:46,110
真是人道主义的巨大损失
Truly great loss for humanity.

138
00:05:46,110 --> 00:05:48,320
你想嘲笑死人吗  可以
You want to mock the dead? Fine.

139
00:05:48,520 --> 00:05:49,770
但他的小报
But his tabloid,

140
00:05:49,770 --> 00:05:52,140
《真相至上》为我们带来了可观的收入
Nothing But The Truth, has made us a fortune.

141
00:05:52,700 --> 00:05:56,060
普莱斯将他的不动产  十家公司
Price has left his estate, ten companies,

142
00:05:56,060 --> 00:05:58,470
包括报社  留给了他的两个女儿
including the tabloid, to his two daughters,

143
00:05:58,540 --> 00:05:59,730
麦迪森和凯尔茜
Madison and Kelsey.

144
00:05:59,900 --> 00:06:02,270
我们受到委托  要公平分配所有财产
We have been asked to divide the assets up fairly.

145
00:06:02,270 --> 00:06:03,640
那为什么要找我过来
And I'm here why?

146
00:06:03,640 --> 00:06:05,060
因为她们关系不和
Because they hate each other.

147
00:06:05,060 --> 00:06:07,560
马尔科姆想借由遗嘱让她们和解
Malcolm structured the will to bring them back together.

148
00:06:07,560 --> 00:06:10,650
你有能力让敌对的双方
You have a knack for bringing parties together

149
00:06:10,650 --> 00:06:12,080
化干戈为玉帛
who don't see eye to eye.

150
00:06:12,180 --> 00:06:13,260
那为什么要找他
So why is he here?

151
00:06:13,260 --> 00:06:15,420
因为麦迪森·普莱斯点名要他
Because Madison Price requested him.

152
00:06:15,580 --> 00:06:17,830
你确定她没把我俩搞混吗
You sure she's not mixing him up with me?

153
00:06:17,830 --> 00:06:19,350
哈德曼几年前曾经让我帮她
Hardman had me do some contract work

154
00:06:19,350 --> 00:06:20,320
处理过一些合同事宜
for her a couple years back,

155
00:06:20,320 --> 00:06:22,560
-可能是当时给她留下了好印象吧  -行了
- so I guess I made an impression. - Right.

156
00:06:23,230 --> 00:06:24,570
一人负责一位
So you each get a sister.

157
00:06:24,700 --> 00:06:26,300
你认为让我俩为敌对的双方效力
You think pitting us against each other

158
00:06:26,300 --> 00:06:28,320
对路易的委托人公平吗
is fair to Louis' client?

159
00:06:28,320 --> 00:06:30,100
拜托  财产分割
Please. Dividing financial assets?

160
00:06:30,100 --> 00:06:32,410
-给我擦鞋你都不配  -你该找个人擦
- You couldn't shine my shoes. - Someone should.

161
00:06:32,410 --> 00:06:34,100
其实  我都是自己擦鞋
Well, actually, I personally shine my own shoes,

162
00:06:34,100 --> 00:06:34,830
不必担心
so there you go.

163
00:06:34,830 --> 00:06:37,100
-他们真走运  -你怎么总是问唐娜
- Oh, lucky them. - How come you always ask Donna,

164
00:06:37,100 --> 00:06:37,870
"唐娜  顺便问一句
"Donna, by the way,

165
00:06:37,870 --> 00:06:39,420
路易穿的那双鞋很不错吧"
those are really nice shoes that Louis has on"?

166
00:06:39,420 --> 00:06:40,390
先生们
Gentlemen.

167
00:06:41,650 --> 00:06:42,990
我们是一伙的
We're on the same side.

168
00:06:44,520 --> 00:06:47,540
尽管我也不愿意选你们一同跟进此案
And although I would not choose to have you both on this,

169
00:06:48,000 --> 00:06:49,080
但现在只能这样
that is how it fell.

170
00:06:49,080 --> 00:06:53,710
所以我希望你们能尽弃前嫌
So I expect you to put your differences aside

171
00:06:53,920 --> 00:06:55,780
共同合作
and work together on this

172
00:06:56,040 --> 00:06:57,840
这样才能皆大欢喜
So that everyone can be happy.

173
00:06:58,060 --> 00:07:00,660
你们这次能做到吗
Can you manage that this time?

174
00:07:05,540 --> 00:07:06,870
她一直恨我
She's always hated me.

175
00:07:07,130 --> 00:07:09,480
也许这是个冰释前嫌的机会
Maybe this is a chance to put all that behind you.

176
00:07:09,480 --> 00:07:11,640
我也想  真的很想
I'd like that. Really, I would.

177
00:07:11,680 --> 00:07:14,090
但是我觉得麦迪她做不到
But Maddie? I don't think so.

178
00:07:14,320 --> 00:07:15,480
也许她会出乎你意料
Maybe she'll surprise you.

179
00:07:15,480 --> 00:07:16,900
凯尔茜是个贱人
Kelsey's a bitch.

180
00:07:17,010 --> 00:07:18,610
她没资格分到财产
She doesn't deserve any of it.

181
00:07:18,610 --> 00:07:22,260
恐怕你父亲不这么认为
Well, I'm afraid your father didn't share that point of view.

182
00:07:22,920 --> 00:07:25,420
根据他的遗嘱  我们要...
According to his will, we were meant...

183
00:07:25,420 --> 00:07:27,270
制定一个分配公司的合理方案
To find a division of these companies

184
00:07:27,270 --> 00:07:28,660
让你们双方都满意
that makes both of you happy.

185
00:07:28,660 --> 00:07:29,520
但是我要保证
But I want to make sure...

186
00:07:29,520 --> 00:07:30,700
让你满意
That you're happy.

187
00:07:30,720 --> 00:07:32,180
你想知道怎样才能让我满意吗
You want to know what will make me happy?

188
00:07:32,180 --> 00:07:33,800
只要让她痛苦就行
Whatever makes her miserable.

189
00:07:33,800 --> 00:07:34,600
很简单
It's simple.

190
00:07:34,600 --> 00:07:36,260
我想要《真相至上》
I want Nothing But The Truth.

191
00:07:36,870 --> 00:07:39,530
父亲和我共同奋斗了这么多年
My father and I worked together on it for years, and...

192
00:07:39,530 --> 00:07:40,870
快要逼疯我了
It made me crazy.

193
00:07:41,050 --> 00:07:44,310
他们俩自以为那份小报算得上是文学作品
The two of them pretending that tabloid was literature.

194
00:07:44,310 --> 00:07:45,790
它对我来说至关重要
It means everything to me.

195
00:07:45,980 --> 00:07:47,140
我想要
All I want...

196
00:07:47,180 --> 00:07:48,780
卖掉那份垃圾报纸
Is to sell off that piece of garbage

197
00:07:48,780 --> 00:07:50,550
让她分到越少越好
and for her to get as little as possible.

198
00:07:50,580 --> 00:07:52,010
她为什么那么生你的气
What made her so mad at you?

199
00:07:52,010 --> 00:07:54,690
爸爸和她妈离了婚  然后娶了我妈
She blames me for our dad leaving her mother

200
00:07:54,690 --> 00:07:56,030
她把这事怪罪于我
and marrying mine.

201
00:07:56,170 --> 00:07:57,700
她怎么会觉得那是你的错
How can she think that's your fault?

202
00:07:57,700 --> 00:07:59,980
因为她妈怀孕了
Because her mother got pregnant

203
00:07:59,980 --> 00:08:01,870
并以此套牢了我爸
and used it to rope in my dad.

204
00:08:02,110 --> 00:08:05,250
然后小凯尔茜就成为了他生活的焦点
And then little Kelsey became the center of his universe.

205
00:08:05,250 --> 00:08:07,760
你知道有人纯粹因为嫉妒而恨你
Do you know what it's like to have someone hate you

206
00:08:07,760 --> 00:08:08,940
是什么感觉吗
out of pure jealousy?

207
00:08:09,530 --> 00:08:10,700
我们会帮你拿下报社的
We'll get you the paper.

208
00:08:10,700 --> 00:08:13,230
我明知自己比她强好几倍  
Do you know what it's like

209
00:08:13,230 --> 00:08:15,110
还要眼看着她成为宠儿
to watch someone else get all the attention

210
00:08:15,110 --> 00:08:17,610
你知道那是种什么感觉吗
when you know that you're twice the person they are?

211
00:08:18,780 --> 00:08:20,400
她不会得到那家报社的
She's not getting that paper.

212
00:08:23,150 --> 00:08:24,680
-麦迪  -凯尔茜
- Maddie. - Kelsey.

213
00:08:24,710 --> 00:08:26,180
-路易  -哈维
- Louis. - Harvey.

214
00:08:26,220 --> 00:08:27,560
二位
Doctor, doctor.

215
00:08:28,370 --> 00:08:29,590
-继续跟进  -好的
- Chevy. - Nice.

216
00:08:30,120 --> 00:08:30,970
顺利吗
Good meeting?

217
00:08:30,970 --> 00:08:32,200
是的  我们谈得很融洽  你呢
Yeah, we connected. You?

218
00:08:32,450 --> 00:08:33,580
彼此彼此
We're on the same page.

219
00:08:34,500 --> 00:08:36,340
凯尔茜想得到什么
What was Kelsey looking for?

220
00:08:36,750 --> 00:08:38,310
不知道  去问问珍妮吧
I don't know. Why don't you ask jenny?

221
00:08:38,310 --> 00:08:39,570
你貌似挺爱跟她聊天的
You seem to like talking to her.

222
00:08:45,490 --> 00:08:47,590
没用的  迈克  你不会让我分心
No, Mike, that's not distracting.

223
00:08:47,850 --> 00:08:48,980
我只是在等
I was just waiting.

224
00:08:49,140 --> 00:08:50,000
等什么
For what?

225
00:08:50,060 --> 00:08:51,310
等你不分心
To not be distracting.

226
00:08:54,400 --> 00:08:55,460
在检察院工作的事  
How come Harvey doesn't talk about

227
00:08:55,460 --> 00:08:56,980
哈维为什么提都不提
working for the D.A.'s office?

228
00:08:58,350 --> 00:08:58,910
谁告诉你的  
Who told you that?

229
00:08:58,920 --> 00:08:59,980
卡梅隆·丹尼斯
Cameron Dennis.

230
00:09:00,130 --> 00:09:01,610
今早碰到他了
We ran into him this morning.

231
00:09:01,760 --> 00:09:02,810
他们还要一起吃晚餐
They're having dinner.

232
00:09:03,000 --> 00:09:04,730
难怪他不告诉我今天的行程
So that's why he wouldn't tell me where he was going.

233
00:09:04,730 --> 00:09:05,920
到底怎么回事  唐娜
What's going on, Donna?

234
00:09:07,060 --> 00:09:08,070
别管这事
Let it go.

235
00:09:08,360 --> 00:09:09,910
也别去问哈维
Don't ask Harvey about this.

236
00:09:10,260 --> 00:09:11,140
到底有什么秘密
What's the big secret?

237
00:09:11,140 --> 00:09:12,290
没有秘密  反正
It's no secret. Just...

238
00:09:13,780 --> 00:09:14,590
别问
Don't.

239
00:09:16,460 --> 00:09:18,210
在聊什么呢
And what are we talking about?

240
00:09:18,230 --> 00:09:19,150
普莱斯家两姐妹
The Price sisters.

241
00:09:19,730 --> 00:09:21,270
麻烦的女孩们
Those girls.

242
00:09:26,510 --> 00:09:28,410
我们非得给路易好脸色看吗
Do we really have to play nice with Louis?

243
00:09:28,410 --> 00:09:29,510
我想给他点颜色瞧瞧
I wanna crush him.

244
00:09:29,510 --> 00:09:30,480
想给他点颜色吗
You wanna crush him?

245
00:09:30,770 --> 00:09:32,490
去那家报社亲自跑一趟
Get over to the paper, kick the tires,

246
00:09:32,490 --> 00:09:33,550
看看它到底值多少钱
and figure out what it's worth.

247
00:09:33,550 --> 00:09:35,670
我还以为我们该进行独立评估
I thought we were supposed to use the independent valuations.

248
00:09:35,670 --> 00:09:37,930
什么  你以为他会按常理出牌吗
What, you think he's gonna play by the rules?

249
00:09:37,990 --> 00:09:38,910
我知道他不会
I know he won't.

250
00:09:38,910 --> 00:09:40,620
所以你得快他三步才行
That's why you better be three steps ahead of him,

251
00:09:40,620 --> 00:09:41,850
因为我敢保证
because I can guarantee you

252
00:09:41,850 --> 00:09:43,260
路易会快你两步的
Louis'll be two steps ahead of you.

253
00:09:43,290 --> 00:09:44,560
说曹操  曹操到
Speak of the devil,

254
00:09:44,790 --> 00:09:46,080
路易女王驾到
Her majesty's here to see you.

255
00:09:46,080 --> 00:09:47,670
-我听到了  -我故意的
- I heard that. - You were meant to.

256
00:09:47,670 --> 00:09:48,790
-各位  -是的  陛下
- Gentlemen. - Your highness.

257
00:09:48,790 --> 00:09:49,660
好吧  告诉你们  
Okay, you know what?

258
00:09:49,990 --> 00:09:51,070
这就是我过来的原因
That's exactly why I'm here.

259
00:09:51,070 --> 00:09:51,940
让我们嘲笑你吗
To be mocked?

260
00:09:52,370 --> 00:09:53,610
不  制定基本原则
No, to set clear ground rules,

261
00:09:53,610 --> 00:09:55,110
使谈判公开化
to keep the negotiation above board.

262
00:09:55,110 --> 00:09:55,870
当然
Absolutely.

263
00:09:55,870 --> 00:09:58,040
不准踢人  咬人  打后脑勺
No kicking, no biting, and no rabbit punches.

264
00:09:58,040 --> 00:09:59,210
你是在嘲笑基本原则吗
And now you're mocking the ground rules.

265
00:09:59,210 --> 00:10:00,480
没有  我只是在嘲笑你
No, I'm just mocking you.

266
00:10:00,630 --> 00:10:01,650
第一
Point one.

267
00:10:01,850 --> 00:10:04,100
我们都要进行独立评估
We both agree to use the independent valuations.

268
00:10:04,100 --> 00:10:06,340
当然  说得好
Absolutely. Good point.

269
00:10:06,360 --> 00:10:07,260
第二
Point two.

270
00:10:07,630 --> 00:10:09,410
不准找杰西卡出面调和
You do not call Jessica in to mediate.

271
00:10:09,750 --> 00:10:10,850
这是你我之间的较量
This is you and me.

272
00:10:10,900 --> 00:10:12,620
你是害怕她会帮我吧
You afraid mom's gonna take my side?

273
00:10:12,620 --> 00:10:14,390
不  我知道她会帮你的
No, I know mom's gonna take your side.

274
00:10:14,390 --> 00:10:16,190
-因为我是对的  -第三
- Because I'd be right. - Point three.

275
00:10:16,190 --> 00:10:17,120
界限分明
Chinese wall.

276
00:10:17,120 --> 00:10:19,660
不准动用我的内部文件
You can't access any internal documents that I create.

277
00:10:19,660 --> 00:10:20,870
让杰西卡看看我们的实力
Let's make Jessica proud.

278
00:10:20,870 --> 00:10:23,020
我们处理得当的话  就能皆大欢喜
We do this right, everyone walks away happy.

279
00:10:23,020 --> 00:10:23,930
很好
Wonderful.

280
00:10:24,740 --> 00:10:26,010
别担心  他斗不过我们
Don't worry. We'll still crush him.

281
00:10:26,010 --> 00:10:27,540
-我听到了  -我故意的
- I heard that. - You were meant to.

282
00:10:33,770 --> 00:10:34,780
打个赌怎么样
Care to make a wager?

283
00:10:34,780 --> 00:10:36,540
我们的职责是让姐妹俩都满意而归
Our job is to make both sisters happy.

284
00:10:36,540 --> 00:10:37,720
怎样知道谁赢了呢
How do we know who wins?

285
00:10:38,120 --> 00:10:39,020
到时候就知道了
We'll know.

286
00:10:39,850 --> 00:10:41,280
-赌金照旧吗  -不
- Usual amount? - No.

287
00:10:41,300 --> 00:10:42,660
我这次想换赌注
I think we should change it up this time.

288
00:10:43,360 --> 00:10:44,950
我赢了  迈克归我
I win, I get Mike.

289
00:10:45,420 --> 00:10:47,790
我又不是动产  凭什么拿我当赌注
You can't bet me like I'm chattel, Louis.

290
00:10:47,960 --> 00:10:49,130
反正他也赢不了
It's not like he's gonna win.

291
00:10:49,230 --> 00:10:50,940
-一个月  -十天
- One month. - Ten days.

292
00:10:50,940 --> 00:10:52,180
-哈维  -两周
- Harvey. - Two weeks.

293
00:10:52,180 --> 00:10:53,300
-九天  -哈维
- Nine days. - Harvey!

294
00:10:53,300 --> 00:10:55,460
好吧  就这样  十天
All right, you know what? Fine. Ten days.

295
00:10:55,670 --> 00:10:56,770
你赢了想要什么
And in return?

296
00:10:57,920 --> 00:10:59,490
这不好办啊  你的东西
Well, that's tough because anything you have

297
00:10:59,490 --> 00:11:00,340
我都看不上眼
I wouldn't want.

298
00:11:01,710 --> 00:11:03,980
什么  你拿我当赌注  却什么都不要吗
What? You're gonna bet me for nothing?

299
00:11:18,620 --> 00:11:19,590
哈维
Harvey?

300
00:11:20,960 --> 00:11:22,290
哈维·斯佩克特
Harvey specter.

301
00:11:23,320 --> 00:11:24,790
亚利桑德拉·利兹
Alexandra Leeds.

302
00:11:24,870 --> 00:11:26,890
听说你在检察院上班
I hear you're working for the Attorney General's office.

303
00:11:26,890 --> 00:11:28,770
而你在为专制资本家奋战
And you're fighting for the oppressive capitalists.

304
00:11:28,910 --> 00:11:30,540
是为专制资本家打赢官司
Winning for the oppressive capitalists.

305
00:11:30,540 --> 00:11:32,530
不错嘛  我们有必要吃个饭
Good for you. We should have lunch.

306
00:11:32,930 --> 00:11:33,950
聊一聊
Catch up.

307
00:11:35,730 --> 00:11:37,420
谁告诉你我今晚会过来
Who told you I was coming here tonight?

308
00:11:37,470 --> 00:11:38,390
没人告诉我
No one.

309
00:11:39,510 --> 00:11:41,070
我们五年没见面了
I haven't seen you in five years.

310
00:11:41,070 --> 00:11:42,110
你只想聊一聊吗
You wanna catch up?

311
00:11:42,420 --> 00:11:44,740
你是有求于我吧  不止一顿饭那么简单
You want something from me, and it isn't lunch.

312
00:11:45,280 --> 00:11:47,420
我想和你聊聊卡梅隆·丹尼斯
I want to talk about Cameron Dennis.

313
00:11:48,100 --> 00:11:50,470
一米八二  双鱼座  卷发
Six feet, Pisces, wavy hair.

314
00:11:50,470 --> 00:11:51,740
我是认真的
I'm serious.

315
00:11:52,680 --> 00:11:54,480
我已经十多年没和他共事了
I haven't worked for Cameron in over a decade.

316
00:11:54,480 --> 00:11:55,340
有什么好聊的
What's there to talk about?

317
00:11:55,680 --> 00:11:58,060
总检察长在调查一项指控
The Attorney General is investigating allegations

318
00:11:58,060 --> 00:12:01,130
查到他为了给被告定罪  故意隐瞒证据
that he systematically buried evidence to get convictions.

319
00:12:01,570 --> 00:12:04,030
那就去找他的同事聊吧
So talk to people who actually work with the guy.

320
00:12:04,040 --> 00:12:06,250
不  问题就在此  他是上级
No, that's the problem. He's still their boss.

321
00:12:06,380 --> 00:12:07,550
没人敢多说什么
Nobody's talking.

322
00:12:07,570 --> 00:12:08,490
我也是
Neither am I.

323
00:12:08,490 --> 00:12:11,320
吃饭还是走人  请便  祝你好运
Over lunch or anywhere else. So best of luck.

324
00:12:11,820 --> 00:12:12,800
哈维
Harvey.

325
00:12:13,730 --> 00:12:15,380
我本来只想和你吃个饭
I was hoping for some lunch.

326
00:12:18,620 --> 00:12:20,040
在大陪审团裁定前
I'm having you subpoenaed

327
00:12:20,040 --> 00:12:21,740
我会给你发来作证传票的
to testify before a grand jury.

328
00:12:21,740 --> 00:12:22,870
好好享用晚餐
Enjoy your dinner.

329
00:12:23,020 --> 00:12:24,250
代我向卡梅隆问好
Give Cameron my best.

330
00:12:36,460 --> 00:12:37,380
哈维
Harvey.

331
00:12:37,630 --> 00:12:39,120
很高兴你能来  你好吗
Glad you could make it. How are you?

332
00:12:39,340 --> 00:12:41,640
今早的"偶遇"  你打的是什么算盘
Tell me about the bullshit run-in that you staged this morning.

333
00:12:41,640 --> 00:12:42,590
你等了多久
How long did you have to wait

334
00:12:42,590 --> 00:12:44,580
才"偶遇"到我的
so that you could pretend to be surprised to see me?

335
00:12:45,660 --> 00:12:46,690
十分钟
Ten minutes.

336
00:12:47,110 --> 00:12:49,610
你从不早到  但我不想太冒险
You're never early, but I didn't want to cut it too close.

337
00:12:49,610 --> 00:12:52,460
我刚才也"偶遇"了亚利桑德拉·利兹
I also just had another little run-in with Alexandra Leeds.

338
00:12:54,530 --> 00:12:55,990
你打算拖我下水吗
You really want to drag me into this?

339
00:12:56,130 --> 00:12:57,170
别激动  哈维
Calm down, Harvey.

340
00:12:57,170 --> 00:12:58,920
我不会拖你下水的
I'm not dragging you into anything.

341
00:12:59,710 --> 00:13:01,100
他们倒是想把我拖下水
They're dragging me into this.

342
00:13:01,100 --> 00:13:03,560
借口说是因为换届选举  我想提醒你一下
It's election year nonsense, and I wanted to warn you.

343
00:13:03,710 --> 00:13:05,560
你把我叫来是为了提醒我吗
So you asked me here to warn me?

344
00:13:06,070 --> 00:13:09,050
是啊  还要确认一下你是站在我这边的
Yeah, and to reassure myself that you've got my back.

345
00:13:09,850 --> 00:13:11,110
情况有多糟
How bad is it?

346
00:13:11,590 --> 00:13:13,880
我倒是能招架得住  但还是很高兴有你在
It's nothing I can't handle, but I'm glad you're here.

347
00:13:14,700 --> 00:13:16,010
听着  哈维
Look, Harvey.

348
00:13:16,220 --> 00:13:17,920
虽说我们之间有很多不同之处
Whatever differences we had,

349
00:13:18,000 --> 00:13:19,320
但我们曾并肩奋战
we were a good team.

350
00:13:19,750 --> 00:13:21,050
事实是
The truth is that...

351
00:13:22,790 --> 00:13:25,350
若有证据证明我们之前判错了案子
If anything taints the work that we did,

352
00:13:26,120 --> 00:13:27,590
对我们都不利
It'll be bad for both of us.

353
00:13:27,590 --> 00:13:28,360
你在威胁我吗
Is that a threat?

354
00:13:28,770 --> 00:13:30,380
当然不是  这只是事实
Not at all. It's just reality.

355
00:13:31,140 --> 00:13:32,780
我们将罪犯绳之以法了  哈维
We put away bad people, Harvey.

356
00:13:32,780 --> 00:13:34,790
我们历经千辛  最终打赢了官司
We fought tough battles, and we won.

357
00:13:34,790 --> 00:13:36,250
是我教你怎么赢的
I taught you how to win.

358
00:13:36,450 --> 00:13:37,790
那不是你所教我的
That's not exactly what you taught me.

359
00:13:37,790 --> 00:13:40,640
我知道你不赞成我们打赢官司的方式
I know that you didn't always approve of the means,

360
00:13:40,640 --> 00:13:43,440
但我们都清楚  结果是对的
but we both know that the end result was always right.

361
00:13:44,500 --> 00:13:46,410
你说话还是这么有信服力
You're still the best smooth-talker I know.

362
00:13:46,620 --> 00:13:48,660
就用你的说话技巧脱身
Use it now. Talk your way out of this.

363
00:13:48,660 --> 00:13:50,600
摆平此事  如果闹上法庭
Settle. 'cause if this goes to court,

364
00:13:50,600 --> 00:13:52,370
你的丑事会被抖出来的
there are skeletons to be found.

365
00:13:52,980 --> 00:13:54,160
他们查不到的
They won't find them.

366
00:13:54,560 --> 00:13:56,010
你这么认为吗
You wanna bank on that?

367
00:13:56,220 --> 00:13:57,740
我站在你这边
I have your back.

368
00:13:57,790 --> 00:13:59,440
但我不会主动帮你
I am not volunteering anything.

369
00:13:59,530 --> 00:14:00,700
即使迫不得已
But if push comes to shove,

370
00:14:00,700 --> 00:14:02,290
我也不会为自己作伪证
I won't perjure myself.

371
00:14:03,290 --> 00:14:04,640
为了你也不行
Not even for you.

372
00:14:19,820 --> 00:14:21,950
与反基督徒共进晚餐  感觉如何
How was dinner with the antichrist?

373
00:14:25,290 --> 00:14:26,640
有你的传票
Subpoena came for you.

374
00:14:29,620 --> 00:14:30,580
准备怎么办
What are you gonna do?

375
00:14:31,320 --> 00:14:32,300
如果是你会怎么做
What would you do?

376
00:14:33,380 --> 00:14:35,940
抱歉  你没事吧
I'm sorry. Are you feeling okay?

377
00:14:36,300 --> 00:14:37,740
竟然询问我的意见
You just asked my advice.

378
00:14:37,740 --> 00:14:38,560
这么多年来  
All these years--

379
00:14:38,560 --> 00:14:39,960
还是头一次吧
Yeah, I think that's a first.

380
00:14:40,000 --> 00:14:41,390
你也在场  你会怎么做
You were there. What would you do?

381
00:14:41,590 --> 00:14:42,760
我会把实情都说出来
I'd tell them everything.

382
00:14:43,530 --> 00:14:45,300
眼看卡梅隆垮掉
I'd watch Cameron go down.

383
00:14:45,390 --> 00:14:47,180
然后办场聚会  喝点香槟
I'd throw a party. I'd drink champagne.

384
00:14:47,180 --> 00:14:50,020
再美美地睡上一觉
I'd go to bed, and I'd sleep like a baby after I did it.

385
00:14:50,310 --> 00:14:51,510
是吗  正面回答我的问题
Really? Don't equivocate.

386
00:14:51,510 --> 00:14:53,090
他是个祸害  哈维
He's poison, Harvey.

387
00:14:53,160 --> 00:14:54,610
离开他是明智的
Leaving there was huge.

388
00:14:54,740 --> 00:14:56,240
不然你的前途就完了
You could've gone down a dark road.

389
00:14:56,240 --> 00:14:58,180
如果换做是我  也会离开他的
And I'm telling you, I would not have followed.

390
00:14:58,180 --> 00:14:59,940
我刚从报社回来
I just got back from the paper.

391
00:15:00,070 --> 00:15:02,240
那地方不错  有增值的潜力
Nice place. It's a growing asset.

392
00:15:02,240 --> 00:15:04,150
还可以进行扩建
There's opportunity for expansion.

393
00:15:04,300 --> 00:15:05,840
如果我们帮凯尔茜打赢案子
If we get this thing for Kelsey,

394
00:15:05,840 --> 00:15:07,070
她这辈子都不用愁了
I think she's set.

395
00:15:09,030 --> 00:15:10,820
我在那里见到艾维斯了
I saw Elvis there.

396
00:15:10,820 --> 00:15:11,680
很好
Great.

397
00:15:12,370 --> 00:15:13,290
激动人心啊
Exciting.

398
00:15:14,190 --> 00:15:15,660
我是不是打扰你们谈话了
Am I interrupting something, or...?

399
00:15:17,230 --> 00:15:18,410
晚餐吃得不开心吗
Dinner didn't go well?

400
00:15:18,560 --> 00:15:20,550
还行  叙了叙旧
It was okay. Old times.

401
00:15:21,130 --> 00:15:22,760
你觉得没事就好
If that's how you want to play it.

402
00:15:23,010 --> 00:15:25,030
讨论一下给路易的提案吧
Let's talk about this proposal for Louis.

403
00:15:25,780 --> 00:15:27,320
这样吧  这案子由你来接手
You know what? Why don't you take a run at it?

404
00:15:27,320 --> 00:15:28,680
努力达成最佳协议
Get the best deal you can.

405
00:15:28,720 --> 00:15:30,960
你拿我当赌注  现在又撒手不管了  
You bet me, and now you're hanging me out to dry?

406
00:15:32,210 --> 00:15:33,380
好吧  我自己搞定
That's fine. I'll do it.

407
00:15:33,380 --> 00:15:34,230
我会赢的
And I'll win.

408
00:15:35,410 --> 00:15:38,270
等我赢了之后  你想好要什么东西了吗
Did you decide what you want him to pay you when I win?

409
00:15:38,280 --> 00:15:40,190
问他要《尼克松在中国》的票
His tickets to Nixon in China.

410
00:15:40,390 --> 00:15:41,780
你想去看歌剧吗
You want to go to the opera.

411
00:15:41,890 --> 00:15:43,000
不  但路易想
No, but Louis does,

412
00:15:43,000 --> 00:15:44,550
我就希望他看不成
and making him miss it would be amusing.

413
00:15:44,650 --> 00:15:45,740
意思是你什么都不想要吗
So you get nothing.

414
00:15:45,970 --> 00:15:47,680
你拿我当赌注却什么都不想要
You are betting me for nothing.

415
00:15:47,680 --> 00:15:48,720
你还杵在这儿干嘛
Are you still talking?

416
00:15:56,110 --> 00:15:58,360
找到今晚一起吃饭的男伴了吗
So did you find a date for tonight?

417
00:15:58,480 --> 00:15:59,170
是的
Yep.

418
00:16:01,140 --> 00:16:01,970
然后呢
And?

419
00:16:02,710 --> 00:16:03,780
我们到时见
And we'll see you there.

420
00:16:04,630 --> 00:16:05,400
怎么了
What?

421
00:16:05,910 --> 00:16:07,470
这不是你想要的吗
I thought that's what you said you wanted.

422
00:16:07,470 --> 00:16:08,780
跟你和珍妮坐在一起
To sit with you and Jenny

423
00:16:08,780 --> 00:16:11,300
让她能自始至终看清我内心的想法
and have her seeing into my brain the whole time?

424
00:16:11,600 --> 00:16:13,080
看什么
Seeing what?

425
00:16:14,270 --> 00:16:16,570
你记得我们接吻了吧
You do remember that we kissed, right?

426
00:16:16,570 --> 00:16:17,730
记忆犹新
I remember.

427
00:16:19,390 --> 00:16:20,850
不会有事的
It'll be okay.

428
00:16:36,400 --> 00:16:39,240
现在能谈谈分割财产的事吗
Hi. Uh, is this a good time to talk about division of assets?

429
00:16:39,240 --> 00:16:40,050
没空
No.

430
00:16:42,220 --> 00:16:44,130
那什么时候可以
Is there a better time?

431
00:16:44,130 --> 00:16:46,080
等到哈维有空的时候
Yes. When Harvey's available.

432
00:16:46,970 --> 00:16:48,530
哈维让我来接手了
Harvey asked me to handle it.

433
00:16:50,730 --> 00:16:51,720
他觉得你能打败我吗
He thinks you can beat me?

434
00:16:51,720 --> 00:16:52,630
那你就证明他错了
Prove him wrong.

435
00:16:52,710 --> 00:16:53,620
有什么好担心的
What's there to lose?

436
00:16:53,620 --> 00:16:56,260
当然了  除了《尼克松在中国》的门票
Ex--except for Nixon in China, of course.

437
00:16:57,280 --> 00:16:58,140
你开了什么条件
What do you have for me?

438
00:16:58,620 --> 00:17:00,710
共有十家公司
Okay, so there are ten companies.

439
00:17:01,320 --> 00:17:03,310
我们的提议是凯尔茜继承
We propose that Kelsey takes

440
00:17:03,310 --> 00:17:06,640
一号  三号  七号和九号公司
companies one, three, seven, and nine.

441
00:17:07,160 --> 00:17:08,780
那样我们就分到了...
So that gives us...

442
00:17:08,780 --> 00:17:10,760
52.3%的资产
52.3% of the assets.

443
00:17:10,890 --> 00:17:12,080
挺大方  不过不行
Hm, generous, but no.

444
00:17:13,600 --> 00:17:16,040
那么备选方案
Uh, alternatively,

445
00:17:16,040 --> 00:17:17,260
是凯尔茜继承
we propose that Kelsey takes

446
00:17:17,260 --> 00:17:20,340
一号  二号  四号和八号公司
companies one, two, four, and eight.

447
00:17:20,340 --> 00:17:21,260
那样你们就分到了...
That gives you--

448
00:17:21,260 --> 00:17:23,070
54.6%
54.6%.

449
00:17:23,160 --> 00:17:23,850
不行
No.

450
00:17:24,590 --> 00:17:26,480
-你有自己的提议吗  -没有
- Do you have a counterproposal, or-- - No.

451
00:17:27,180 --> 00:17:30,630
好吧  凯尔茜继承一号  七号
Okay, uh, Kelsey takes companies one, seven,

452
00:17:30,630 --> 00:17:32,150
-八号和九号公司  -不行
- eight, and nine. - no.

453
00:17:32,350 --> 00:17:34,250
路易  那样你们就分到60%的资产了
Louis, that gives you 60% of the assets.

454
00:17:34,250 --> 00:17:36,360
是的  但不行
Yes. But no.

455
00:17:37,950 --> 00:17:39,540
你的委托人到底想要什么
What is it your client wants?

456
00:17:42,500 --> 00:17:45,220
你的提议已经表明了
Well, your offer makes it infinitely clear

457
00:17:45,220 --> 00:17:46,530
你的委托人想要什么
what your client wants.

458
00:17:47,000 --> 00:17:48,240
报社
The tabloid.

459
00:17:48,630 --> 00:17:51,070
而我委托人想要的就是
And what my client wants is for your client

460
00:17:51,100 --> 00:17:52,140
不让你的委托人得逞
to not get what she wants,

461
00:17:52,140 --> 00:17:53,890
所以你们别想分到报社
so you can't have the tabloid, period.

462
00:17:54,720 --> 00:17:57,660
你有法律义务把这些提案拿给你委托人看的
You're legally required to take these offers to your client.

463
00:17:57,660 --> 00:17:59,260
那就告我不守职业道德
So bring me up on ethics charges.

464
00:17:59,340 --> 00:18:01,550
或者去向你的主管报告
Or report me to your supervisor.

465
00:18:01,550 --> 00:18:03,760
等等  见鬼  我就是你的主管
Oh, wait, shit. I am your supervisor.

466
00:18:04,070 --> 00:18:05,150
稍等片刻
Hold on one second.

467
00:18:10,200 --> 00:18:11,050
说吧
Go ahead.

468
00:18:11,970 --> 00:18:12,990
你有什么要投诉的
What are your complaints?

469
00:18:13,560 --> 00:18:15,100
有吗  没有吗  真的吗
Have any? No? Really?

470
00:18:19,940 --> 00:18:22,420
我们该找到公正公平的和解方案  路易
We're supposed to find a fair and equitable settlement, Louis.

471
00:18:22,420 --> 00:18:24,240
好啊  去跟杰西卡打小报告吧
Okay, you go run and tell Jessica.

472
00:18:24,590 --> 00:18:26,470
等等  那就违反约定了
Oh, wait, that would be breaking the rules,

473
00:18:26,470 --> 00:18:27,660
你就得来给我干活
and then you've have to come work for me.

474
00:18:27,660 --> 00:18:29,400
所以你还是滚去把哈维找来
So why don't you run along now and get Harvey

475
00:18:29,400 --> 00:18:32,530
让他赶快过来参与谈判
and tell him to get off his ass and join the negotiations.

476
00:18:32,530 --> 00:18:34,020
因为你已经失败了
Because you just failed.

477
00:18:36,280 --> 00:18:38,070
你离开地方检察官办公室时
When you left the D.A.'s office,

478
00:18:38,410 --> 00:18:40,620
你说你不想干了  学够了
you said you were done, you had learned enough,

479
00:18:40,660 --> 00:18:42,050
你想继续干别的了
and that you were ready to move on.

480
00:18:42,050 --> 00:18:43,470
那都是屁话吗
Was that just bullshit?

481
00:18:43,470 --> 00:18:45,610
是你想让我长些庭审经验
You were the one who wanted me to have trial experience.

482
00:18:45,610 --> 00:18:48,170
你说只有卡梅隆值得我学习
You said that Cameron was the only one that I should learn from.

483
00:18:48,170 --> 00:18:50,070
那他到底教了你什么
And what exactly did he teach you?

484
00:18:50,180 --> 00:18:52,940
哈维  你当时为什么离开了
Harvey, why did you leave?

485
00:18:53,960 --> 00:18:55,280
他有个案子
He had a case.

486
00:18:55,560 --> 00:18:57,630
我发现他隐藏了一件关键证物
I caught him burying a key piece of evidence

487
00:18:57,630 --> 00:18:59,080
他本来应该上交的
he was obligated to turn over.

488
00:18:59,080 --> 00:19:00,270
被告是有罪的
The guy was guilty.

489
00:19:00,270 --> 00:19:02,590
辩方律师用那证物可以给他脱罪
The defense would've used it to let him walk.

490
00:19:03,550 --> 00:19:05,010
好吧  你陷得有多深
All right, what kind of exposure do you have?

491
00:19:05,010 --> 00:19:06,650
我让他别这么做  他不听
I told him no, but he didn't listen.

492
00:19:06,650 --> 00:19:08,060
那你有义务举报他的
Then you were obligated to report him.

493
00:19:08,060 --> 00:19:09,370
所以我才离开了
Which is why I left.

494
00:19:09,370 --> 00:19:11,020
那你当时怎么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me this at the time?

495
00:19:11,020 --> 00:19:13,320
因为是你让我去受教育的  杰西卡
Because you put me there, Jessica, to be mentored.

496
00:19:13,320 --> 00:19:14,820
我当时以为
Okay? And it occurred to me,

497
00:19:15,020 --> 00:19:17,260
或许这正是你想让我学到的东西
that might've been exactly what you wanted me to learn.

498
00:19:18,490 --> 00:19:21,230
我声明一下  我没那个意思
For the record, it wasn't.

499
00:19:22,210 --> 00:19:24,220
你出庭作证时我会做你的律师
I'm gonna represent you at this deposition.

500
00:19:24,420 --> 00:19:26,400
我会尽量不让你说话
I'm gonna try to keep you from talking.

501
00:19:28,750 --> 00:19:30,050
不过我觉得你该说
But I think you should.

502
00:19:32,100 --> 00:19:33,290
他是我的导师
He was my mentor.

503
00:19:33,290 --> 00:19:34,590
他是名公务员
He is a public servant.

504
00:19:34,590 --> 00:19:35,660
他是我的导师
He was my mentor.

505
00:19:35,660 --> 00:19:37,290
法理大于人情
The standards are higher.

506
00:19:37,290 --> 00:19:38,790
他是我的导师
He was my mentor.

507
00:19:38,870 --> 00:19:41,110
我不会去揭发他
And I am not gonna be the one to expose him,

508
00:19:41,110 --> 00:19:43,470
就像我永远不会背叛你
any more than I'd ever turn on you.

509
00:19:55,920 --> 00:19:58,970
最糟的约会史  跟双胞胎
Worst dating story-- identical twins.

510
00:19:58,990 --> 00:20:00,990
我成了他们社会实验的小白鼠
I was a lab rat for their social experiment.

511
00:20:00,990 --> 00:20:03,220
他们想要证明女人很肤浅
They were trying to prove that women were shallow

512
00:20:03,220 --> 00:20:04,740
只能看到表象
and can't see beyond the surface.

513
00:20:04,740 --> 00:20:06,000
他们还想骗你上床吧
And they wanted to get laid.

514
00:20:06,150 --> 00:20:07,460
没错
Yes, that too.

515
00:20:07,750 --> 00:20:08,760
真不错啊
Good times.

516
00:20:09,450 --> 00:20:10,930
那你跟他们都上床了吗
So you slept with them both.

517
00:20:11,610 --> 00:20:12,660
险些
Almost.

518
00:20:13,060 --> 00:20:15,580
我发现他们也不是完全一样的
Turns out they weren't identical after all.

519
00:20:17,720 --> 00:20:20,390
不好意思  我得去趟洗手间
Excuse me, I am just going to run to the ladies' room.

520
00:20:20,390 --> 00:20:21,260
我们一起去吧
Oh, I'll go with you.

521
00:20:21,400 --> 00:20:22,120
好啊
Okay.

522
00:20:28,220 --> 00:20:29,470
怎么了  迈克
What's wrong, Mikey?

523
00:20:29,900 --> 00:20:31,000
今天工作不顺利吗
Tough day at the office?

524
00:20:31,180 --> 00:20:32,930
幸好没撞见你  要不更难捱
Didn't see you. It could've been worse.

525
00:20:33,080 --> 00:20:33,980
说得好啊
That's good.

526
00:20:34,320 --> 00:20:35,360
你和瑞秋
So you and Rachel.

527
00:20:35,680 --> 00:20:37,150
你们约会多久了
How long have you guys been dating?

528
00:20:37,170 --> 00:20:39,630
你知道律师和委托人在庭审过程中
You know how lawyers and clients work close

529
00:20:39,630 --> 00:20:41,120
会亲密地合作
over the course of a trial.

530
00:20:41,410 --> 00:20:43,670
在模拟法庭打得你落花流水那次
When we kicked your ass in the mock trial,

531
00:20:43,950 --> 00:20:46,350
我们  挺来电的
we, uh, bonded.

532
00:20:47,760 --> 00:20:48,880
要知道  在现实生活中
You know in the real world

533
00:20:48,880 --> 00:20:51,280
和委托人约会是有违职业道德的
dating clients is a violation of ethics, right?

534
00:20:51,480 --> 00:20:53,000
幸好不是真正的委托人
Good thing it's not the real world.

535
00:20:53,030 --> 00:20:57,150
我还打算违反职业道德一整晚呢
'Cause I intend to violate those ethics all night.

536
00:20:57,590 --> 00:20:58,800
你知道好笑的是
You know the funny thing?

537
00:20:59,500 --> 00:21:02,050
我总以为你会先上她
I always thought you'd get there first.

538
00:21:02,880 --> 00:21:03,790
我会告诉你她怎么样
I'll tell you how she is.

539
00:21:03,930 --> 00:21:04,710
别说了  凯尔
Shut up, Kyle.

540
00:21:04,900 --> 00:21:06,230
人家会以为你眼红了
Someone might think you're jealous.

541
00:21:06,410 --> 00:21:07,860
人家会以为你是个混蛋
Someone might think you're a dick.

542
00:21:08,280 --> 00:21:09,640
等等  已经有人这么想了
Oh, wait. Somebody already does.

543
00:21:10,930 --> 00:21:12,530
说得好  你该写下来
That's good. You should write that one down.

544
00:21:12,530 --> 00:21:13,560
你会把这些话记到日记里吗
Do you keep a journal of these things?

545
00:21:13,750 --> 00:21:14,540
吃你的豆腐吧
Finish your tofu.

546
00:21:14,730 --> 00:21:15,870
你们是怎么认识的
So how did you two meet?

547
00:21:19,070 --> 00:21:21,390
我之前跟他好朋友谈过恋爱
I dated his best friend.

548
00:21:22,210 --> 00:21:23,700
我知道  这不太好
I know, it's awful.

549
00:21:23,890 --> 00:21:26,670
但他不是个好人  我却没看出来
But he was a bad guy, and I didn't see it.

550
00:21:28,280 --> 00:21:29,200
迈克让我看清了他
Mike showed me.

551
00:21:30,510 --> 00:21:31,440
实际上...
The truth is, I--

552
00:21:32,080 --> 00:21:33,940
我觉得我们之间一直有种微妙的感觉
I think there was always something there with us.

553
00:21:34,150 --> 00:21:36,250
但是我和特雷弗彻底结束前
But nothing happened until Trevor and I

554
00:21:36,250 --> 00:21:37,150
我们之间什么都没发生
were totally done.

555
00:21:37,320 --> 00:21:38,150
一点都没有吗
Never?

556
00:21:39,550 --> 00:21:41,140
我们接过一次吻
Well, we did kiss once.

557
00:21:47,910 --> 00:21:49,100
开心吗
Hey, having fun?

558
00:21:49,400 --> 00:21:50,890
可开心了  是不是  迈克
Loads. Right, Mike?

559
00:21:50,890 --> 00:21:51,860
我想我们该走了
I think we're gonna go.

560
00:21:52,040 --> 00:21:53,100
什么  别啊  我们多开心啊
What? No. We're having fun.

561
00:21:53,290 --> 00:21:54,640
别走啊  别破坏气氛
Come on, you don't want to ruin this.

562
00:21:54,780 --> 00:21:56,250
-是啊  -凯尔  别...
- Yeah. - Kyle, really, just--

563
00:21:56,550 --> 00:21:57,560
凯尔  别...
Okay, Kyle, just--

564
00:21:57,740 --> 00:21:59,170
怎么了  有什么问题
What? What's the problem?

565
00:21:59,370 --> 00:22:00,600
别动手动脚  她不喜欢这样
Stop it. She doesn't like it.

566
00:22:11,400 --> 00:22:13,080
天啊  那家伙真是个混蛋
God, that guy is such a tool.

567
00:22:13,280 --> 00:22:14,740
那又如何  他又不是跟你约会
So what? He's not your date.

568
00:22:15,400 --> 00:22:16,670
话虽如此  可我要跟他共事呢
Yeah, well, I have to work with him.

569
00:22:16,850 --> 00:22:17,970
你才不是为这个烦心呢
That's not why it bothers you.

570
00:22:18,150 --> 00:22:19,680
是因为他跟瑞秋在一起  你心里清楚
It's because he's with Rachel, and you know it.

571
00:22:19,870 --> 00:22:21,540
天呐  珍妮  这我们不是谈过了吗
Oh, my God, Jenny. We have been over this.

572
00:22:21,720 --> 00:22:22,730
我看到了你看她的眼神
I've seen the way you look at her.

573
00:22:24,490 --> 00:22:25,710
我以前见过那种眼神
I've seen it before.

574
00:22:28,000 --> 00:22:30,390
我和特雷弗在一起的时你就是那么看我的
It's the way you used to look at me when I was with Trevor.

575
00:22:31,140 --> 00:22:31,730
珍妮
Jenny--

576
00:22:31,900 --> 00:22:32,970
我要回家了  迈克
I'm going home, Mike.

577
00:22:34,100 --> 00:22:37,400
你自己决定  要不要跟我在一起
Decide what you want. In or out.

578
00:22:37,570 --> 00:22:38,510
我喜欢你
I like you.

579
00:22:40,320 --> 00:22:41,390
很喜欢你
A lot.

580
00:22:44,520 --> 00:22:46,000
但鱼和熊掌不可兼得
But you can't have both.

581
00:22:54,930 --> 00:22:56,780
我以地方检察官助理的身份
I worked as an assistant district attorney

582
00:22:56,960 --> 00:22:58,740
在纽约地区工作了两年
for the county of New york for two years.

583
00:22:59,140 --> 00:23:01,170
说说你跟卡梅隆·丹尼斯的关系
Tell me about your relationship with Cameron Dennis.

584
00:23:01,170 --> 00:23:02,270
措辞含糊
Vague.

585
00:23:03,030 --> 00:23:06,280
你和地方检察官卡梅隆·丹尼斯
Did you and district attorney Cameron Dennis

586
00:23:06,500 --> 00:23:08,050
合作很亲密吗
work closely together?

587
00:23:08,320 --> 00:23:10,240
他是我的上司  他监督我所有的案子
He was my boss. He supervised all my cases.

588
00:23:10,590 --> 00:23:12,160
你们私下关系好吗
And were you personally close?

589
00:23:12,350 --> 00:23:14,450
-主观臆断  -法官会允许的
- Subjective. - A judge would allow it.

590
00:23:14,650 --> 00:23:16,760
可现在没法官
And yet there's not one here.

591
00:23:17,200 --> 00:23:19,620
你真的以为让他出庭作证
Do you really think by deposing him on the stand

592
00:23:19,800 --> 00:23:21,060
就能吓倒他吗
you're going to intimidate him?

593
00:23:21,260 --> 00:23:23,050
我觉得让他在这里作证  会让他明白
I think deposing him here will let him know

594
00:23:23,230 --> 00:23:24,710
如果这个证据搬上庭审
what it will be like if this evidence

595
00:23:24,890 --> 00:23:26,270
会是个什么样子
is brought forward at trial.

596
00:23:26,480 --> 00:23:27,780
你进行不到庭审
You're not getting to trial.

597
00:23:28,230 --> 00:23:30,430
如果你的委托人不在这里作伪证
If your client doesn't perjure himself right now,

598
00:23:30,620 --> 00:23:31,710
我确实不必
I won't have to.

599
00:23:32,310 --> 00:23:35,490
你和卡梅隆·丹尼斯私下里是否关系亲密
Were you and Cameron Dennis close personally?

600
00:23:35,670 --> 00:23:36,900
他是我的导师
He was my mentor.

601
00:23:37,420 --> 00:23:39,010
很难给这种关系下定义
It's a hard relationship to define.

602
00:23:39,200 --> 00:23:40,360
请问下一个问题  律师
Moving on, counselor.

603
00:23:40,520 --> 00:23:41,480
好吧
All right.

604
00:23:41,710 --> 00:23:44,720
我们可以不谈丹尼斯先生
We don't have to talk about Mr. Dennis.

605
00:23:45,520 --> 00:23:47,260
我们谈谈你吧  斯佩克特先生
Let's talk about you, Mr. Specter.

606
00:23:47,870 --> 00:23:52,980
在那两年里  你经手案件达18362件
In two years, you handled 18,362 cases.

607
00:23:53,170 --> 00:23:54,550
平均每天36件
36 cases a day.

608
00:23:54,740 --> 00:23:56,250
这非常惊人
That's beyond impressive.

609
00:23:56,470 --> 00:23:57,370
多谢夸奖
Thank you.

610
00:23:57,560 --> 00:24:00,050
你的庭审案件为147件  全部胜诉
You took 147 to trial, winning them all.

611
00:24:00,250 --> 00:24:01,620
赢不了  就不上庭
Don't go to trial if you're not gonna win.

612
00:24:03,040 --> 00:24:04,060
那你为什么离开了
Why'd you leave?

613
00:24:04,630 --> 00:24:06,790
一位名叫杰西卡·皮尔逊的律师
An attorney by the name of Jessica Pearson

614
00:24:06,980 --> 00:24:08,410
资助我上了法学院
helped me get through law school,

615
00:24:08,690 --> 00:24:12,230
她当时认为我该积攒些庭审经验
and she felt that I could use trial experience.

616
00:24:12,430 --> 00:24:16,330
但我一直计划着回到她的公司
But I always planned on ending up at her firm

617
00:24:16,520 --> 00:24:18,750
并为其赚取高额和解金
and paying her back by earning that firm

618
00:24:18,950 --> 00:24:20,460
以报答她的好意
outrageous settlements.

619
00:24:20,670 --> 00:24:21,750
我表现如何
How am I doing?

620
00:24:21,950 --> 00:24:22,920
还可以更好些
You could do better.

621
00:24:23,110 --> 00:24:24,610
你们俩当这是儿戏吗
You two think that this is a joke.

622
00:24:24,900 --> 00:24:26,090
值得争议
Argumentative.

623
00:24:26,270 --> 00:24:27,730
没错  的确值得争议
You're damn right it's argumentative.

624
00:24:27,940 --> 00:24:29,350
因为他明知这是违法的
Because he knows that laws have been broken,

625
00:24:29,540 --> 00:24:31,550
而且他有义务举报
and he has an obligation to report it.

626
00:24:31,790 --> 00:24:32,460
利兹女士
Ms. Leeds

627
00:24:32,650 --> 00:24:33,830
但既然你如此不配合
But if this is the way you want to play it,

628
00:24:34,030 --> 00:24:34,990
我会用总检察长赋予我的职权
the Attorney General has given me

629
00:24:35,180 --> 00:24:37,620
去调查事情的真相
a broad mandate to uncover what went on.

630
00:24:37,830 --> 00:24:40,150
这调查将不仅限于丹尼斯先生一人
And it need not be limited to Mr. Dennis.

631
00:24:40,660 --> 00:24:42,700
你是否也牵连其中呢  斯佩克特先生
Were you part of the problem, Mr. Specter?

632
00:24:43,400 --> 00:24:44,180
措辞含糊
Vague.

633
00:24:44,370 --> 00:24:45,440
我换个问法
I'll rephrase.

634
00:24:46,190 --> 00:24:48,410
在你担任纽约区
In your capacity as Assistant District Attorney

635
00:24:48,610 --> 00:24:49,790
地方检察官助理的期间
in the county of New York,

636
00:24:49,980 --> 00:24:51,590
你是否蓄意隐瞒证据
did you knowingly suppress evidence

637
00:24:51,770 --> 00:24:54,150
从而违反了美国职业协会道德准则
in violation of the A.V.A. Rules of Conduct,

638
00:24:54,350 --> 00:24:55,350
全国地方检察官行为规范
the N.D.A.A. Standards,

639
00:24:55,550 --> 00:24:58,360
以及纽约州律师协会条例  第8.4条第3款
and the New York State Bar Rule 8.4, Section C?

640
00:24:59,580 --> 00:25:00,730
根据第五修正案
My client would like to exercise

641
00:25:00,730 --> 00:25:02,830
我的委托人有权拒绝自证其罪
his Fifth-Amendment rights at this time.

642
00:25:09,680 --> 00:25:10,810
听说你提出了对我方不利的条件
I hear you botched a settlement

643
00:25:10,810 --> 00:25:12,670
把和解给搞砸了
by negotiating against yourself.

644
00:25:12,860 --> 00:25:13,700
我没有...
I didn't--

645
00:25:13,900 --> 00:25:15,080
你让路易知道了
You let Louis know the one thing

646
00:25:15,300 --> 00:25:16,730
我方委托人最在乎的东西
that was most important to our client.

647
00:25:16,930 --> 00:25:18,040
好吧  是的  我犯了个错误
Okay, yes, I made a mistake.

648
00:25:18,220 --> 00:25:19,540
但路易也失误了
But Louis made one too.

649
00:25:19,720 --> 00:25:20,740
他可没说
Well, he didn't mention that.

650
00:25:20,930 --> 00:25:22,300
没错  他知道了我们的委托人想要什么
Yes, he knows what our client wants,

651
00:25:22,470 --> 00:25:24,520
但我们也知道了他的委托人最想要什么
but now we know the one thing his client wants.

652
00:25:24,720 --> 00:25:26,170
她根本不在乎输赢  哈维
She doesn't care about winning, Harvey.

653
00:25:26,370 --> 00:25:27,990
她只想要我们的委托人失败
She just wants our client to lose.

654
00:25:28,960 --> 00:25:31,480
好的  很好  然后呢
Okay, well, that's good. So what's next?

655
00:25:31,670 --> 00:25:32,320
我们就败给她看
We lose.

656
00:25:32,520 --> 00:25:33,360
我们把报社给她
We give her the tabloid.

657
00:25:33,550 --> 00:25:34,750
那样就能让我们的委托人高兴吗
Well, how does that make our client happy?

658
00:25:34,950 --> 00:25:36,290
我们让麦迪森继承报社
We let Madison have the paper,

659
00:25:36,470 --> 00:25:37,890
然后带走所有的员工
and then we take everyone who works there,

660
00:25:38,070 --> 00:25:39,150
成立一个新的报社
and we start a new one.

661
00:25:39,470 --> 00:25:40,490
他们都喜欢凯尔茜
They all love Kelsey.

662
00:25:40,670 --> 00:25:42,540
《真相至上》只是块招牌
Nothing But The Truth is just a name.

663
00:25:42,720 --> 00:25:43,810
就让麦迪森拿去
We let Madison have it.

664
00:25:44,220 --> 00:25:45,550
我没白教你
I have taught you a thing or two.

665
00:25:46,880 --> 00:25:49,280
看来最新的情况你都知道了
Well, I see that you're up to speed.

666
00:25:49,880 --> 00:25:50,670
我也知道
Well, as am I.

667
00:25:50,840 --> 00:25:53,500
我注意到报社面临着员工的去留问题
Um, I noticed that there were some employee issues at the tabloid.

668
00:25:53,590 --> 00:25:54,830
合同即将到期之类的
You know, contracts about to expire.

669
00:25:55,050 --> 00:25:56,390
所以我想让你们知道
So I just want to let you guys know

670
00:25:56,580 --> 00:25:59,020
我索性把所有主力员工都续约了
that I went ahead and locked up all the key employees,

671
00:25:59,550 --> 00:26:00,560
以防不测
just to protect us,

672
00:26:01,120 --> 00:26:04,910
因为我们双方在同一战线  对吧
since we're all working on this together, right?

673
00:26:05,700 --> 00:26:06,400
很好
Good.

674
00:26:10,800 --> 00:26:11,850
-他知道了  -不可能
- He knows. - He can't.

675
00:26:12,030 --> 00:26:13,090
-他已经知道了  -我一向谨慎
- He does. - I was careful.

676
00:26:13,310 --> 00:26:14,520
那台服务器上的所有文件我都删了
I deleted every file from the server.

677
00:26:14,520 --> 00:26:17,100
除了我给凯尔茜发传真的时候拿出来过
The only time any paper trail left my locked desk

678
00:26:17,270 --> 00:26:18,770
所有文件都一直锁在我办公桌里
is when I faxed it to Kelsey.

679
00:26:18,770 --> 00:26:19,600
你传真了
You faxed it.

680
00:26:19,790 --> 00:26:22,560
你居然用了一台能储存任何经手信息的机器
From the large machine that stores all the information you put in it

681
00:26:22,560 --> 00:26:24,620
而且只要有你的代码  就能把信息打印出来
to be printed back later by anyone who has your code?

682
00:26:24,620 --> 00:26:25,490
他不能这么做
He can't do that.

683
00:26:25,690 --> 00:26:28,450
我们说好了界限分明的
We have a Chinese wall thing.

684
00:26:28,640 --> 00:26:30,010
天啊  他要打败我们了  是吧
Oh, god, he's gonna beat us, isn't he?

685
00:26:30,200 --> 00:26:31,150
他知道我们想要什么
Look, he knows what we're up to,

686
00:26:31,370 --> 00:26:33,330
但是他就喜欢炫耀自己的战术
but he couldn't keep his tactics to himself.

687
00:26:33,800 --> 00:26:34,980
我们可以利用这一点反败为胜
So we can use that against him.

688
00:26:35,240 --> 00:26:36,840
没错  这才是消灭路易之道
And that's how we'll crush Louis.

689
00:26:37,660 --> 00:26:39,130
我再重申一次  哈维
Refresher course, Harvey.

690
00:26:39,320 --> 00:26:40,940
在这件案子上  你和路易并非对手
You and Louis aren't opponents on this one.

691
00:26:41,120 --> 00:26:42,270
你们得鼎力合作
You're working together.

692
00:26:42,800 --> 00:26:44,120
像船长和塔妮尔一样
Like Captain & Tennille?

693
00:26:42,800 --> 00:26:44,120
船长和塔妮尔  美国1970年代的夫妻音乐搭档

694
00:26:44,580 --> 00:26:46,070
那么  他是塔妮尔
Well, if so, he's tennille.

695
00:26:46,260 --> 00:26:47,210
谁
Who?

696
00:26:49,440 --> 00:26:51,230
你得跟我来一下
You need to come with me.

697
00:26:51,550 --> 00:26:52,320
怎么  我遇上麻烦了吗
What, am I in trouble?

698
00:26:52,720 --> 00:26:54,610
没错  哈维  麻烦大了
Yeah, Harvey. You are.

699
00:27:05,520 --> 00:27:07,280
收拾我之前想买酒先犒劳我吗
Gonna buy me a drink before you screw me?

700
00:27:07,480 --> 00:27:08,580
坐下  哈维
Sit down, Harvey.

701
00:27:08,800 --> 00:27:10,060
听听她要说什么
Listen to what she has to say.

702
00:27:11,810 --> 00:27:13,240
你吓得我双腿发抖
You got me trembling in my boots.

703
00:27:16,580 --> 00:27:17,300
你不过是条小鱼
You're a small fish,

704
00:27:17,300 --> 00:27:19,000
而且你现在都不属于这个池子了
and you don't even swim in the pond anymore.

705
00:27:19,000 --> 00:27:21,610
但如果非得把你活吞  才能扳倒卡梅隆·丹尼斯
But if I have to eat you alive to get to Cameron Dennis,

706
00:27:21,810 --> 00:27:22,780
我在所不惜
I will.

707
00:27:24,180 --> 00:27:25,730
这是我告他的案宗
This is my case against him.

708
00:27:25,920 --> 00:27:27,750
伪造DNA测试
Falsifying DNA tests,

709
00:27:27,940 --> 00:27:29,270
逼供
coerced confessions,

710
00:27:29,450 --> 00:27:30,610
隐瞒证词
testimony buried.

711
00:27:31,000 --> 00:27:32,690
你既然掌握了这些证据  为何还需要我
You have all this. Why do you need me?

712
00:27:34,960 --> 00:27:36,790
因为这只是间接证据
Because this is circumstantial.

713
00:27:36,980 --> 00:27:37,760
你掌握了罪行
You have the crimes,

714
00:27:37,940 --> 00:27:39,430
但无法直接证明是卡梅隆干的
but you can't physically tie them to Cameron.

715
00:27:39,630 --> 00:27:41,110
他是个行为不端的公务员
He's a dirty public servant,

716
00:27:41,310 --> 00:27:42,770
我认为你是因为这个才离开的
and I think it's why you left.

717
00:27:43,330 --> 00:27:45,550
你干得风头正劲  不可能随便走人
Your record was too good to just walk away.

718
00:27:45,740 --> 00:27:46,640
也许我变贪婪了
Maybe I got greedy.

719
00:27:46,830 --> 00:27:48,290
-哈维  -我不会去作证
- Harvey. - I'm not testifying.

720
00:27:48,480 --> 00:27:49,250
你太固执了
You're being stubborn.

721
00:27:49,440 --> 00:27:51,460
这件事不是你说了算
And this isn't one where you get to make the call.

722
00:27:53,090 --> 00:27:54,010
抱歉
I'm sorry.

723
00:27:56,360 --> 00:27:57,310
我已经尽力了
I've done all I can.

724
00:27:58,380 --> 00:28:00,330
他不仅为自己的案子徇私舞弊
It wasn't just his cases he cheated on.

725
00:28:01,160 --> 00:28:02,170
赫克特·阿维拉
Hector Avila.

726
00:28:02,590 --> 00:28:03,510
你看看
Take a look.

727
00:28:04,040 --> 00:28:05,460
你觉得你真有那么伟大吗
You think you were really that great?

728
00:28:05,730 --> 00:28:07,340
你觉得你一向出色的成绩
You think your great track record

729
00:28:07,530 --> 00:28:08,870
是因为你技艺超群吗
was because of your skill?

730
00:28:09,980 --> 00:28:11,710
我有两种揣测  哈维
I got two theories here, Harvey.

731
00:28:12,350 --> 00:28:14,300
要么你在浪费时间保护一个
Either you're wasting your time protecting a man

732
00:28:14,510 --> 00:28:15,690
一开始就把你蒙在鼓里的人
who screwed you from the beginning,

733
00:28:15,890 --> 00:28:17,880
要么你不仅纵容了他的行为
or you didn't just know he did this,

734
00:28:18,190 --> 00:28:19,330
还亲身参与其中
you participated,

735
00:28:19,550 --> 00:28:21,370
如果是这样  你的律师资格会被吊销
in which case I'll have you disbarred.

736
00:28:32,070 --> 00:28:34,020
快点  快点
Come on. Come on.

737
00:28:34,020 --> 00:28:34,860
见鬼
Damn it.

738
00:28:36,250 --> 00:28:36,900
你在做什么
What are you doing?

739
00:28:37,080 --> 00:28:38,120
没做什么
Uh, nothing.

740
00:28:38,290 --> 00:28:39,620
我只是发几封传真
I'm just sending some faxes.

741
00:28:41,940 --> 00:28:42,850
闪开
Stand down.

742
00:28:44,610 --> 00:28:46,590
它们卡在里面  唐娜  你又能怎样
They're stuck, Donna. What are you gonna do?

743
00:28:47,520 --> 00:28:49,070
我可是传真机语者
I'm the fax whisperer.

744
00:28:50,300 --> 00:28:52,270
好吧  很好笑  行了吧
Okay, that's ridiculous, all right?

745
00:28:52,450 --> 00:28:53,110
我都试过了
I've tried everything.

746
00:28:53,300 --> 00:28:54,440
我按了...我已经试过了
I've hit-- I've already done that.

747
00:28:54,630 --> 00:28:55,490
它没反应...
And it didn't--

748
00:28:57,260 --> 00:28:58,270
你赢了
Whatever.

749
00:28:58,680 --> 00:29:00,420
联合国际报想要购买《真相至上》吗
United International wants to buy the tabloid?

750
00:29:00,590 --> 00:29:03,130
不管怎样  都不准告诉路易
Uh, whatever you do, don't say anything to Louis.

751
00:29:03,300 --> 00:29:05,260
凯尔茜·普莱斯不想出售
Kelsey Price does not want to sell.

752
00:29:05,850 --> 00:29:06,900
守口如瓶
Not a word.

753
00:29:07,210 --> 00:29:08,160
谢谢
Thanks.

754
00:29:22,580 --> 00:29:25,380
你这儿发生爆炸了吗
Whoa. Something explode in here?

755
00:29:26,250 --> 00:29:28,040
就是查点资料
Just doing some research.

756
00:29:28,250 --> 00:29:31,080
没错  你总是亲自动手查资料
Yeah, 'cause you always do your own research.

757
00:29:32,790 --> 00:29:36,330
好吧  先是和唐娜  和杰西卡开闭门会议
Okay, closed-door meeting with Donna, with Jessica,

758
00:29:36,750 --> 00:29:39,270
又和你以前从没提起过的地方检察官共进晚餐
dinner with some D.A. you've never even mentioned before.

759
00:29:39,450 --> 00:29:43,000
这些都是卡梅隆·丹尼斯教你的吧
Is this all something Cameron Dennis taught you?

760
00:29:43,200 --> 00:29:44,840
瞒着所有人  因为你如此出色
Keep secrets from everyone because you're so good,

761
00:29:45,030 --> 00:29:45,880
不需要任何人的帮助
you don't need anyone's help?

762
00:29:46,360 --> 00:29:49,050
有人在做有关证据篡改的调查
There's an investigation into evidence tampering.

763
00:29:49,250 --> 00:29:51,520
想让我上庭供出前任上司的不端行为
I've been asked to testify against my old boss...

764
00:29:52,930 --> 00:29:54,610
不然我就将面临指控
or face charges myself.

765
00:29:56,220 --> 00:29:57,560
你会被吊销律师执照
You could be disbarred.

766
00:30:00,250 --> 00:30:01,350
如果他们能认定我有罪
If I'm found guilty.

767
00:30:02,820 --> 00:30:03,790
你有罪吗
Are you guilty?

768
00:30:04,820 --> 00:30:06,450
至少没有篡改证据
Not of evidence tampering.

769
00:30:06,780 --> 00:30:07,840
我绝不会那么做
I would never do that.

770
00:30:08,040 --> 00:30:08,990
其它事情呢
Of anything else?

771
00:30:09,310 --> 00:30:09,980
我做过的任何事情
Anything I ever did,

772
00:30:10,160 --> 00:30:12,120
如果让一位公正的法官判定
you put me in front of an unbiased judge,

773
00:30:12,320 --> 00:30:13,330
我就是清白的
I walk away clean.

774
00:30:13,510 --> 00:30:15,470
如果上法庭交由大陪审团判定
You put me in a courtroom with a grand jury,

775
00:30:16,580 --> 00:30:17,710
那就说不准了
anything can happen.

776
00:30:18,110 --> 00:30:19,940
那你会去作证吗
So are you gonna testify?

777
00:30:20,140 --> 00:30:21,510
现在看起来没得选了
I'm not sure what choice I have.

778
00:30:21,970 --> 00:30:24,520
曾经有个混蛋告诉我说
Well, some dickhead once told me

779
00:30:24,700 --> 00:30:27,570
你脑袋被枪顶着的时候
that when they put a gun to your head,

780
00:30:27,760 --> 00:30:29,800
并非只有屈服和被杀两条出路
it's not just give in or be killed.

781
00:30:29,980 --> 00:30:32,400
还有146个其他选择
There are 146 other options.

782
00:30:34,630 --> 00:30:35,880
你会想出办法的
You'll figure something out.

783
00:30:38,360 --> 00:30:40,120
明早你们会看到我的提案
I'll have a proposal for you in the morning,

784
00:30:40,300 --> 00:30:41,680
我想双方都会满意的
And I think we'll all be happy.

785
00:30:42,140 --> 00:30:43,020
好吗
All right?

786
00:30:43,690 --> 00:30:44,730
晚安
Night.

787
00:30:47,410 --> 00:30:48,290
他上钩了
He took the bait?

788
00:30:48,800 --> 00:30:50,170
如同瓮中捉鳖啊
Like shooting a fish in a barrel.

789
00:30:50,790 --> 00:30:51,800
干得不错
Good work.

790
00:30:55,560 --> 00:30:56,350
你要去哪儿
Where you going?

791
00:30:57,080 --> 00:30:58,690
我决定采纳你的建议
I just might take your advice.

792
00:31:19,690 --> 00:31:20,820
大局已变
The tides are turning.

793
00:31:21,390 --> 00:31:22,670
你要跟着一起变吗  哈维
You turning with them, Harvey?

794
00:31:23,090 --> 00:31:23,840
你动摇了吗
They turn you?

795
00:31:25,090 --> 00:31:26,330
赫克特·阿维拉
Hector Avila.

796
00:31:28,170 --> 00:31:29,240
你甚至都不知道  是不是
You don't even know, do you?

797
00:31:29,890 --> 00:31:31,210
这是什么旧案子吗
Is this some old case?

798
00:31:31,420 --> 00:31:33,860
是我的旧案子  但你隐瞒了证据
It's my old case, and you buried evidence.

799
00:31:34,380 --> 00:31:35,240
你带窃听器了吗  哈维
You wearing a wire, Harvey?

800
00:31:38,320 --> 00:31:39,230
不  你没有
No, you're not.

801
00:31:40,210 --> 00:31:41,010
我能看出来
I can tell.

802
00:31:41,510 --> 00:31:43,510
我不再那么容易被看穿了  卡梅隆
I'm not that easy to read anymore, Cameron.

803
00:31:43,700 --> 00:31:44,810
对我来说  你还是很浅显
You are to me.

804
00:31:45,180 --> 00:31:46,410
赫克特·阿维拉
Hector Avila.

805
00:31:46,590 --> 00:31:47,880
不管他是谁  他有罪吗
Was he guilty, whoever he was?

806
00:31:48,060 --> 00:31:49,890
-那是我的案子  -有罪就是有罪
- He was my case. - Guilty is guilty.

807
00:31:50,080 --> 00:31:51,060
体制不允许你这么胡来
That's not the way the system works.

808
00:31:51,240 --> 00:31:53,170
体制早就腐坏了  这你也知道
The system is broken, and you know it.

809
00:31:53,340 --> 00:31:54,490
那并非合理怀疑
It's not reasonable doubt.

810
00:31:54,680 --> 00:31:56,890
陪审团想要百分之百地确定
Juries want to be sure without a shadow of a doubt.

811
00:31:57,070 --> 00:31:58,200
那是我的案子
It was my case.

812
00:31:58,380 --> 00:31:59,660
你是为我工作的
You worked for me.

813
00:31:59,830 --> 00:32:01,570
那些都是我的案子
They were all my cases.

814
00:32:03,370 --> 00:32:04,610
你太令我失望了
You're a disappointment.

815
00:32:04,850 --> 00:32:05,780
不
No.

816
00:32:06,060 --> 00:32:07,350
是你令我失望
You're the disappointment.

817
00:32:07,530 --> 00:32:08,930
你本可以成为一名优秀的地方检察官
You could've been D.A. yourself.

818
00:32:09,100 --> 00:32:11,430
你比那些排着队来指控我的蠢货律师
You are twice the lawyer than any of the pricks lined up

819
00:32:11,610 --> 00:32:13,450
要好上几倍  但你出卖了自己
to run against me. But you sold out.

820
00:32:13,630 --> 00:32:15,930
当了有钱人的奴隶  只是奴隶而已
You help rich people keep their money. That's all you do.

821
00:32:16,110 --> 00:32:20,630
我对于社会的价值比你高得多
I stack my value to society against yours, and I win by a mile.

822
00:32:23,990 --> 00:32:25,130
你要出卖我吗
So you're selling me out?

823
00:32:25,320 --> 00:32:26,830
你我都知道  他们不是要让你坐牢
We both know they don't want to put you in jail.

824
00:32:27,000 --> 00:32:28,300
那不是他们的目的
That's not what this is about.

825
00:32:29,380 --> 00:32:31,090
脱身吧  卡梅隆  跟他们达成协议
Walk away, Cameron. Make a deal.

826
00:32:31,480 --> 00:32:34,820
让别人当检察官  就什么事也没有了
Let someone else be D.A., and all of this, it goes away.

827
00:32:35,010 --> 00:32:36,030
否则呢
Otherwise?

828
00:32:36,240 --> 00:32:37,680
知道如果你多嘴的话会怎么样吗
You know what happens if you talk.

829
00:32:37,900 --> 00:32:39,600
他们会复查案件
They start reopening cases.

830
00:32:39,800 --> 00:32:41,450
也许赫克特·阿维拉就逍遥法外了
Maybe Hector Avila walks away.

831
00:32:41,650 --> 00:32:42,940
他杀过一次人  就难免再犯
He murdered once. He'll murder again.

832
00:32:43,570 --> 00:32:44,780
你还记得他啊
You do remember him, don't you?

833
00:32:44,950 --> 00:32:46,040
他们我全都记得
Oh, I remember 'em all.

834
00:32:46,230 --> 00:32:47,020
麦斯威尔·兰金
Maxwell Rankin?

835
00:32:47,200 --> 00:32:50,340
他干了什么来着  强奸了34还是35个女人
What was it, uh, 34 or 35 women that he raped?

836
00:32:50,710 --> 00:32:52,620
阿伯托·普兰克  记得吗
Alberto Plank? You remember him?

837
00:32:52,640 --> 00:32:54,650
他活活烧死了自己的孩子
He burned his children alive.

838
00:32:54,780 --> 00:32:56,010
到时候会一发不可收拾的  哈维
You'll open the floodgates, Harvey.

839
00:32:56,180 --> 00:32:57,040
你想让自己的良心受到谴责吗
Do you want that on your conscience?

840
00:32:57,240 --> 00:32:58,600
那就去达成协议
Then make a deal.

841
00:32:58,750 --> 00:33:00,920
是否继续监禁他们  决定权在你
It's on you to keep them in jail.

842
00:33:02,760 --> 00:33:03,690
好吧
Okay.

843
00:33:06,660 --> 00:33:08,660
好吧  哈维
Okay, Harvey.

844
00:33:09,630 --> 00:33:10,740
你赢了
You win.

845
00:33:11,140 --> 00:33:12,100
这算不上是赢
This isn't winning.

846
00:33:15,170 --> 00:33:16,130
见到你真高兴  哈维
Good to see you, Harvey.

847
00:33:16,340 --> 00:33:17,460
有空再来啊
Let's do it again soon.

848
00:33:25,740 --> 00:33:27,600
所以说你的委托人真的愿意
So your client's really willing to give Madison

849
00:33:27,780 --> 00:33:28,770
把《真相至上》给麦迪森吗
Nothing But The Truth?

850
00:33:29,440 --> 00:33:31,500
你都摆明了这不容商量
You made it clear it was non-negotiable.

851
00:33:31,960 --> 00:33:33,750
我已经说服了我的委托人进行和解
I convinced my client to settle.

852
00:33:35,160 --> 00:33:36,020
她希望向前看
She wants to move on.

853
00:33:36,610 --> 00:33:39,820
你确定没有其它信息需要披露了吗
You're sure there isn't anything that you want to, uh, disclose?

854
00:33:41,250 --> 00:33:41,950
没了
Nope.

855
00:33:42,150 --> 00:33:43,220
我们没什么问题了
I think we're good.

856
00:33:45,880 --> 00:33:46,760
那我们也没问题了
Then we're good.

857
00:33:51,580 --> 00:33:55,710
皆大欢喜  笑得合不拢嘴
Everybody's happy as clams.

858
00:34:00,020 --> 00:34:01,320
谢谢  路易
Thank you, Louis.

859
00:34:02,630 --> 00:34:05,630
你  对协议满意吗
You, um... happy with the deal?

860
00:34:06,860 --> 00:34:08,080
是的  我确实很满意
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I am.

861
00:34:08,610 --> 00:34:09,630
你呢
You?

862
00:34:13,960 --> 00:34:15,360
满意得你难以想象
You don't even know the half of it.

863
00:34:15,740 --> 00:34:16,760
是吗
Don't I?

864
00:34:17,610 --> 00:34:19,190
你满意的是你的委托人得到了报社
Are you happy that your client got the paper

865
00:34:19,390 --> 00:34:21,260
还是你一转身就把它卖了
or that you turned around and sold it?

866
00:34:23,480 --> 00:34:25,050
你以为我不知道  是吧
Oh, you didn't think I knew about that, did you?

867
00:34:26,930 --> 00:34:28,370
想知道我为什么满意吗  路易
Want to know why I'm happy, Louis?

868
00:34:29,660 --> 00:34:31,070
我满意是因为你看到的那份
I'm happy because when you read over that offer

869
00:34:31,260 --> 00:34:32,860
从联合国际报发来的报价
from united international,

870
00:34:33,530 --> 00:34:34,710
是我故意想让你看到的
I wanted you to read that.

871
00:34:35,750 --> 00:34:37,760
我就是想让你卖给他们
I wanted you to sell to them.

872
00:34:38,240 --> 00:34:39,700
因为你有所不知的是
Because the thing you didn't know

873
00:34:40,000 --> 00:34:43,680
昨天凯尔茜·普莱斯收购了联合国际报
is that yesterday Kelsey Price bought United International.

874
00:34:45,410 --> 00:34:47,920
你不该在别人背后搞鬼  路易
You shouldn't go behind people's backs, Louis.

875
00:34:48,110 --> 00:34:51,800
你不该试图获取与你无关的信息
You shouldn't try and access information that's none of your business.

876
00:34:52,000 --> 00:34:52,760
会让你弄巧成拙
It could backfire.

877
00:34:59,030 --> 00:35:00,800
我们得和哈维谈谈
I think we need to talk to Harvey.

878
00:35:03,230 --> 00:35:04,080
对不起  哈维
I'm sorry, Harvey.

879
00:35:04,250 --> 00:35:05,180
你算计了我
You set me up.

880
00:35:05,790 --> 00:35:07,460
不  路易  是你搬起石头砸自己的脚
No, louis. You set yourself up.

881
00:35:07,790 --> 00:35:10,840
那份报价要不是被你看到  原本毫无意义
The sales offer was meaningless until you read it.

882
00:35:11,180 --> 00:35:12,280
这是作弊
This is cheating.

883
00:35:13,700 --> 00:35:15,310
是你作弊  路易
You cheated, Louis.

884
00:35:15,760 --> 00:35:18,330
你犯了规  就得付出代价
You broke the rules, and you have to pay the price.

885
00:35:18,520 --> 00:35:20,900
人们也许以为律师什么事都肯做
People may think that lawyers will do anything,

886
00:35:21,090 --> 00:35:22,330
且无所不能
that they can do anything.

887
00:35:22,520 --> 00:35:24,250
现在我不买账了
Now, I'm not willing to accept that, okay?

888
00:35:24,450 --> 00:35:27,170
你不能自己打完擦边球 
You can't go skirting the rules and justify it

889
00:35:27,170 --> 00:35:29,650
回头又去指责别人犯规
because you think someone else broke the rules, okay?

890
00:35:29,850 --> 00:35:32,410
你作弊  而且你输了
You cheated! And you lost!

891
00:35:32,620 --> 00:35:33,670
就这么简单
End of story.

892
00:35:41,250 --> 00:35:43,790
哈维  我赢了
Harvey, I won.

893
00:35:46,060 --> 00:35:50,080
他在传真机旁的表演太明显了
His playacting by the fax machine was so obvious.

894
00:35:50,260 --> 00:35:52,300
我发现凯尔茜取得了联合国际报的所有权
I found out Kelsey owned United International,

895
00:35:52,480 --> 00:35:54,280
我想既然他们那么想要那家报社
and I thought if they wanted the paper so badly,

896
00:35:54,460 --> 00:35:55,840
他们肯溢价多少收购呢
how much would they overpay for it?

897
00:35:56,340 --> 00:35:57,400
50%
50%.

898
00:35:59,730 --> 00:36:01,570
哈维  你溢价50%收购的生意
Harvey, you overpaid 50% for a business

899
00:36:01,750 --> 00:36:04,940
被高额的员工续约费用所拖累
so buried in expenses from the employee deals that I made,

900
00:36:05,220 --> 00:36:06,340
只能勉强维持经营
it can barely stay afloat.

901
00:36:06,780 --> 00:36:09,390
我只需说服麦迪森袖手旁观
And then all I had to do was convince Madison to sit back,

902
00:36:09,770 --> 00:36:11,830
好好看着她的妹妹惨败就行了
have fun, watch her sister fail miserably.

903
00:36:12,010 --> 00:36:12,960
我赢了
I won.

904
00:36:13,430 --> 00:36:15,320
你委托人的目的达到了
Your client got what she wanted.

905
00:36:15,680 --> 00:36:16,720
我委托人的也是
So did ours.

906
00:36:16,900 --> 00:36:18,110
杰西卡要求皆大欢喜
Jessica asked to make everyone happy.

907
00:36:18,310 --> 00:36:19,600
现在打成平局  皆大欢喜了
Everyone's happy. It's a draw.

908
00:36:21,740 --> 00:36:24,650
等一下  你现在跟我老实说
Just hold on a second. You tell me the truth right now.

909
00:36:26,070 --> 00:36:27,030
这对你来说算是赢了吗
Is this a win to you?

910
00:36:27,830 --> 00:36:29,260
好  路易  你赢了
Fine, Louis. You win.

911
00:36:29,560 --> 00:36:32,360
你领先一步  迈克归你  十天
You were a step ahead. You got Mike. Ten days.

912
00:36:32,570 --> 00:36:33,680
你觉得现在我想要他吗
You think I'd want him now?

913
00:36:35,490 --> 00:36:36,900
我刚把他打了个落花流水
I just wiped the floor with him.

914
00:36:50,470 --> 00:36:51,380
有什么可以帮到你
How can I help you?

915
00:36:52,180 --> 00:36:54,150
我绝不让他替那个混蛋背黑锅
I'm not gonna let him take the fall for that asshole.

916
00:36:55,960 --> 00:36:56,970
请坐
Have a seat.

917
00:37:03,390 --> 00:37:04,980
哈维没想那么远
Harvey didn't see it for a long time.

918
00:37:05,680 --> 00:37:07,430
卡梅隆随时可以脱身
I mean, Cameron's good when he wants to be.

919
00:37:07,770 --> 00:37:09,490
知道我怎么判断一个人的性格吗
You know how I judge a man's character?

920
00:37:11,040 --> 00:37:12,480
不是看他怎么对待自己平级的人
Not by how he treats his equals,

921
00:37:12,660 --> 00:37:14,410
而是看他怎么对待自己的下属
but by how he treats the underlings.

922
00:37:15,950 --> 00:37:17,270
尤其是最底层的员工
Lowest rungs on the ladder.

923
00:37:18,880 --> 00:37:20,750
在这方面我一直很钦佩你
You always impressed me in that regard.

924
00:37:22,730 --> 00:37:23,720
谢谢
Thank you.

925
00:37:25,950 --> 00:37:27,340
哈维绝对不会用这个
Harvey would never use this,

926
00:37:27,530 --> 00:37:29,200
他要是知道我有  一定会要我的命
and he'd kill me if he knew I had it.

927
00:37:29,600 --> 00:37:30,810
但是你能帮他吗
But can you help him?

928
00:37:33,520 --> 00:37:35,820
你能用这些帮他吗
Can you use this to help him?

929
00:37:50,140 --> 00:37:51,970
哈维在罚你吗
Is Harvey punishing you for something?

930
00:37:52,370 --> 00:37:53,460
是路易
Louis.

931
00:37:53,640 --> 00:37:55,170
不是吧  你输了吗
No! You lost?

932
00:37:55,370 --> 00:37:56,320
你得为他工作吗
You have to work for him?

933
00:37:56,520 --> 00:37:58,630
我输了  然后他说不想要我
I lost, and then he said he didn't want me.

934
00:37:58,930 --> 00:38:00,020
就把我承包给别人了
He farmed me out.

935
00:38:00,210 --> 00:38:01,460
真遗憾
Oh, I'm so sorry.

936
00:38:01,670 --> 00:38:02,990
有什么能帮你的吗
Is there anything I can do to help?

937
00:38:06,340 --> 00:38:07,410
怎么
What?

938
00:38:09,220 --> 00:38:10,380
你的手
That.

939
00:38:11,070 --> 00:38:12,160
你这是什么意思
What are you talking about?

940
00:38:17,580 --> 00:38:20,830
我曾喜欢你很久  瑞秋  我跟你调情
I wanted you for months. Rachel, I flirted.

941
00:38:21,030 --> 00:38:23,060
我还计划过我们的婚后生活
I-I-I made up some scheme where we were married.

942
00:38:23,260 --> 00:38:27,700
结果等到我开始和别人约会了  你才跟我说
And you made it clear you don't date anyone from the office.

943
00:38:27,700 --> 00:38:28,990
你不跟公司里的人约会
Until I start seeing someone else.

944
00:38:28,990 --> 00:38:30,380
你想太多了
Okay, you're delusional.

945
00:38:31,630 --> 00:38:33,150
那天约会你为什么带凯尔来
Why did you bring Kyle on that date?

946
00:38:33,750 --> 00:38:34,880
因为事发突然
Because it was last-minute

947
00:38:34,880 --> 00:38:37,900
你又要我帮你说服女友你不喜欢我
and because you needed me to help convince your girlfriend that you don't like me.

948
00:38:38,160 --> 00:38:39,630
你这么做是为了气我
You did it to get to me.

949
00:38:39,930 --> 00:38:41,310
你太过分了  真蠢
This is crazy. It's just stupid.

950
00:38:41,520 --> 00:38:43,190
你根本就不喜欢他  瑞秋
You don't even like the guy, Rachel.

951
00:38:44,200 --> 00:38:47,470
珍妮帮我把西装送到公司来  而你做了什么
Jenny comes to drop off a suit at the office, and what do you do?

952
00:38:48,210 --> 00:38:49,170
你吻了我
You kiss me.

953
00:38:49,350 --> 00:38:51,640
我好像记得你也吻了我
You know, I seem to recall you kissing me too.

954
00:38:51,830 --> 00:38:52,650
对  这就是问题
Yeah, that's the problem.

955
00:38:52,860 --> 00:38:54,190
我是吻了你  感觉也很好
I did. And it was great.

956
00:38:54,580 --> 00:38:57,950
但太晚了  你太晚了
But it's too late. You were too late.

957
00:38:58,150 --> 00:38:59,140
我不能这样了
And I can't do any of this.

958
00:38:59,340 --> 00:39:00,410
-不能怎样  -这样  这样
-Do what? - This, this.

959
00:39:00,610 --> 00:39:03,200
你拿自己的第一次说笑
This you joking about your first time or--

960
00:39:03,420 --> 00:39:05,810
或者拍我的肩膀  摸我的手臂
or rubbing my shoulders or--or touching my arm.

961
00:39:06,910 --> 00:39:08,710
你只是跟我玩玩  你明明知道
You're playing with me, and you know it.

962
00:39:08,920 --> 00:39:10,800
据我所知  你也是跟我玩玩
What I know is you're playing with me too.

963
00:39:11,100 --> 00:39:14,180
你在跟她在一起很久之后  还一直跟我调情
You kept flirting with me long after you started dating her.

964
00:39:15,040 --> 00:39:16,080
好吧  那就到此为止
Yeah, well, that's gonna stop.

965
00:39:17,580 --> 00:39:18,600
好啊
Good.

966
00:39:19,570 --> 00:39:20,710
以后你办案子的时候
You know, and while you're at it,

967
00:39:21,040 --> 00:39:23,350
别再跑来找我帮忙
no more running to me for favors or asking me for help.

968
00:39:23,540 --> 00:39:25,200
去找别的律师助理吧
How 'bout you find yourself some other paralegal?

969
00:39:25,410 --> 00:39:27,040
我不想和你有任何瓜葛了
Because as far as I'm concerned, we're done.

970
00:39:38,340 --> 00:39:39,510
能让我们单独谈一下吗
Uh, can you give us a minute?

971
00:39:44,760 --> 00:39:46,160
杰西卡
Well, Jessica.

972
00:39:48,320 --> 00:39:50,260
我跟亚利桑德拉·利兹谈过了
I've spoken to Alexandra Leeds.

973
00:39:51,000 --> 00:39:52,650
她跟我说了你们达成的协议
She told me about the deal you cut.

974
00:39:53,540 --> 00:39:54,440
我能说什么
What do you want me to say?

975
00:39:58,910 --> 00:39:59,830
这是副本
This is a copy.

976
00:40:01,270 --> 00:40:04,350
我现在开车去总检察长的办公室
I'm driving over to the Attorney General's office right now

977
00:40:05,630 --> 00:40:06,540
如果我到了之后
if she doesn't tell me

978
00:40:06,540 --> 00:40:08,650
她告诉我  你们还没达成新协议的话
you've cut a new deal by the time I get there,

979
00:40:09,240 --> 00:40:13,430
她就会拿到原件  然后我会把证据给她
she gets the original. And then I give her the proof.

980
00:40:16,150 --> 00:40:18,010
你没有证据
You don't have the proof.

981
00:40:18,630 --> 00:40:20,030
是吗
Don't I?

982
00:40:22,660 --> 00:40:23,970
去谈个新协议
Cut a new deal.

983
00:40:25,740 --> 00:40:27,830
你要是敢再动我的人
And if you ever mess with one of mine again,

984
00:40:29,260 --> 00:40:31,040
亚利桑德拉也会拿到原件
Alexandra gets that anyway.

985
00:40:48,010 --> 00:40:52,770
你不用出庭作证了  他们不需要你了
You don't have to testify. They don't need you anymore.

986
00:40:54,080 --> 00:40:55,240
卡梅隆达成协议了吗
Cameron made a deal?

987
00:40:55,440 --> 00:40:58,290
他达成的协议是要出卖你
He made a deal to sell you out.

988
00:40:59,400 --> 00:41:00,680
但我去另外谈了个协议
But I made my own deal.

989
00:41:01,330 --> 00:41:05,300
他会下台  享受天伦之乐
He'll be stepping down, spending some quality time with his family.

990
00:41:05,480 --> 00:41:06,950
你到底怎么做到的
How exactly did you manage that?

991
00:41:07,150 --> 00:41:09,850
与你无关  但你可以清静了  哈维
Not your concern. But you're in the clear, Harvey.

992
00:41:13,420 --> 00:41:15,820
一般人听到这个消息会很高兴的
Some people would be happy with that news.

993
00:41:16,810 --> 00:41:18,320
那个狗娘养的
That son of a bitch.

994
00:41:19,080 --> 00:41:21,140
克利福德·丹纳当时18岁
Clifford Danner was 18.

995
00:41:21,140 --> 00:41:23,030
12年前  我控他入狱
I put him in jail 12 years ago.

996
00:41:23,220 --> 00:41:25,980
这孩子这辈子都毁在监狱里了
Kid's been rotting in prison his whole adult life.

997
00:41:27,460 --> 00:41:28,530
然后呢
And?

998
00:41:29,620 --> 00:41:30,920
他是清白的
He's innocent.

999
00:41:32,720 --> 00:41:34,410
卡梅隆掩盖了证据
Cameron buried the evidence.

1000
00:41:34,840 --> 00:41:35,840
我若是有证据的话
If I'd had it...

1001
00:41:36,930 --> 00:41:38,280
足够翻案吗
Do you have enough to overturn?

1002
00:41:39,230 --> 00:41:40,440
不知道
I don't know.

1003
00:41:46,320 --> 00:41:47,500
那你打算怎么办
So what are you going to do?

1004
00:41:52,360 --> 00:41:53,670
我要救他出来
I'm gonna get him out.

