1
00:07:15,430 --> 00:07:20,430
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:07:15,430 --> 00:07:20,430
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:07:15,430 --> 00:07:20,430
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:07:15,430 --> 00:07:20,430
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:07:15,430 --> 00:07:20,430
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:07:20,430 --> 00:07:24,430
{\an8}翻译：草草  猫咪赐我速死  CS漫画家小明  杳杳君  潇湘月影

7
00:07:24,430 --> 00:07:29,430
{\an8}翻译：王大可  feilixiaozi  油炸电风扇  校对：油炸电风扇   潇湘月影

8
00:07:29,430 --> 00:07:34,430
{\an8}时间轴：阿丹    猫   今    芒果树叶

9
00:07:34,430 --> 00:07:39,430
{\an8}后期：斯人&加森      精校总监：某羽

10
00:07:41,290 --> 00:07:43,420
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

11
00:07:41,290 --> 00:07:43,420
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第八集

12
00:00:00,980 --> 00:00:02,640
{\pos(189,213)}《诉讼双雄》前情提要

13
00:00:02,850 --> 00:00:03,970
你真的很了解他
You really know him.

14
00:00:03,990 --> 00:00:05,470
确实
I really do.

15
00:00:05,660 --> 00:00:06,540
从来没吗
Never?

16
00:00:06,600 --> 00:00:07,340
没有
No.

17
00:00:07,560 --> 00:00:08,660
为什么
Why not?

18
00:00:09,310 --> 00:00:10,940
因为你就再也回不到从前了
Because you can never go back.

19
00:00:11,210 --> 00:00:12,950
傅滋曼坚持要我
Forstman's insisting that I run the money

20
00:00:12,950 --> 00:00:14,410
在钱流向对方之前
through Switzerland and the Caymans

21
00:00:14,410 --> 00:00:15,830
通过瑞士和开曼群岛进行管理
before it comes out on the other side.

22
00:00:15,830 --> 00:00:17,110
你有义务举报这件事
You're obligated to report it.

23
00:00:17,110 --> 00:00:18,810
我没举报  也不会去
I didn't, and I'm not going to.

24
00:00:18,810 --> 00:00:19,820
你胡说些什么啊
What are you talking about?

25
00:00:19,820 --> 00:00:21,140
-瑞秋  -洛根跟我接吻了
- Rachel, hey-- - Logan and I kissed.

26
00:00:21,320 --> 00:00:22,550
迈克  不  求你了
Mike, no, please.

27
00:00:24,010 --> 00:00:25,250
我昨天说  只要有你
And when I said that it didn't matter

28
00:00:25,250 --> 00:00:27,300
下一步做什么都无关紧要
what I'd do next because I have you?

29
00:00:27,310 --> 00:00:28,010
我错了
I was wrong.

30
00:00:28,190 --> 00:00:29,220
因为我们完了
Because we're done.

31
00:00:29,870 --> 00:00:32,280
这是你完成这笔交易的酬金
That's your fee for putting this deal together.

32
00:00:32,280 --> 00:00:32,900
你这个混蛋
Son of a bitch.

33
00:00:32,900 --> 00:00:34,610
你让我来不是为了让你签字
You didn't bring me here for you to sign on the arrows.

34
00:00:34,610 --> 00:00:36,450
而是为了让我签字
You brought me here for me to sign on the arrows.

35
00:00:36,750 --> 00:00:37,370
没错
Yep.

36
00:00:37,440 --> 00:00:39,300
你不能和那个人一起工作
You cannot take a job with that man.

37
00:00:39,610 --> 00:00:40,700
你又能做什么
What are you gonna do about it?

38
00:00:40,700 --> 00:00:42,630
我重新雇佣了迈克·罗斯
I hired Mike Ross back at the firm.

39
00:00:42,760 --> 00:00:43,520
什么
What?

40
00:00:43,520 --> 00:00:44,620
你真的要放弃我吗
You're really gonna drop me?

41
00:00:44,620 --> 00:00:45,700
当然了
You're damn right I am.

42
00:00:45,700 --> 00:00:47,060
我再也不想见到你了
I never want to see you again.

43
00:00:49,190 --> 00:00:50,360
你要回来了吗
Are you back here?

44
00:00:50,480 --> 00:00:54,410
不  我会在其它地方待一段时间
No, I'm going to stay somewhere for a while.

45
00:00:54,420 --> 00:00:56,170
-迈克  -瑞秋  不管你想说什么
- Mike-- - Rachel, whatever you're going to say,

46
00:00:56,170 --> 00:00:57,610
现在都不是说的时候
now is not the time to say it.

47
00:00:58,300 --> 00:00:59,880
我明天就回去上班了
I'm coming back to work tomorrow.

48
00:01:00,460 --> 00:01:01,550
如果你不能接受的话
If you can't accept that,

49
00:01:01,550 --> 00:01:03,200
不管你想和我说什么
then whatever you were going to say to me

50
00:01:04,800 --> 00:01:05,650
都不重要了
won't matter.

51
00:02:08,170 --> 00:02:09,430
我觉得你可能需要这个
Thought you might need this.

52
00:02:10,310 --> 00:02:11,550
谢谢
Thank you.

53
00:02:11,770 --> 00:02:14,980
依我看  你有三个选择
So, the way I see it, you've got three options.

54
00:02:15,810 --> 00:02:19,110
直接穿昨天穿的衣服
You can wear what you were wearing last night,

55
00:02:19,230 --> 00:02:20,910
回家换衣服
you can go back to your place and change,

56
00:02:20,910 --> 00:02:24,110
或者  去我衣柜挑  随便挑
or you can grab anything you want from my closet.

57
00:02:25,280 --> 00:02:27,830
不选吗  我还坚信你会扑上去...
Nothing? I thought for sure you would leap at the chance--

58
00:02:27,830 --> 00:02:29,590
迈克今天要回去工作了
Mike's coming back to work today.

59
00:02:30,610 --> 00:02:31,510
我知道
I know.

60
00:02:31,840 --> 00:02:33,340
-我怎么办  -继续做你从
- What am I gonna do? - You're gonna do

61
00:02:33,340 --> 00:02:35,380
迈克走了之后就一直在做的事
what you've been doing since the day Mike left.

62
00:02:35,880 --> 00:02:38,390
挺胸抬头地走进哈维的办公室
You're gonna walk into Harvey's office with your head held high,

63
00:02:38,390 --> 00:02:39,570
做好你的工作
and you're gonna do your job.

64
00:02:39,570 --> 00:02:40,690
-那是迈克的工作  -瑞秋
- Mike's job. - Rachel--

65
00:02:40,690 --> 00:02:44,690
我不知道要怎么靠近他又跟他保持距离
I don't know how to be near him without being near him.

66
00:02:45,330 --> 00:02:46,480
我告诉你
I'll tell you how. 

67
00:02:47,820 --> 00:02:48,680
给他空间
Give him space.

68
00:02:48,680 --> 00:02:50,150
我不想给他空间
I don't want to give him space.

69
00:02:50,310 --> 00:02:52,390
我想跑向他
I want to run to him

70
00:02:52,390 --> 00:02:54,660
抱住他  告诉他我爱他
and hold him and tell him that I love him.

71
00:02:54,660 --> 00:02:55,460
我知道  瑞秋
I know, but, Rachel,

72
00:02:55,460 --> 00:02:57,250
但如果你现在想拉近他
if you try to pull him towards you right now,

73
00:02:57,250 --> 00:02:59,230
就只会把他推远
all you're gonna do is push him away.

74
00:02:59,270 --> 00:03:01,540
相信我  别强求
Trust me. Let things be.

75
00:03:01,540 --> 00:03:02,900
事情终会如愿的
They'll turn out the way they're supposed to.

76
00:03:02,900 --> 00:03:04,270
这你说不好
You don't know that.

77
00:03:06,290 --> 00:03:07,770
我确定
I do know that.

78
00:03:10,760 --> 00:03:11,620
好吧
Okay.

79
00:03:13,180 --> 00:03:15,390
瑞秋  我要告诉你一件我以前没告诉过你的事
Rachel, I'm gonna tell you something I've never told you.

80
00:03:20,030 --> 00:03:21,300
我跟哈维上过床
I slept with Harvey.

81
00:03:23,520 --> 00:03:24,870
天呐
Oh, my god.

82
00:03:27,630 --> 00:03:28,640
但你说...
But you told me that--

83
00:03:28,640 --> 00:03:30,050
我知道我跟你怎么说的
I know what I told you.

84
00:03:30,770 --> 00:03:32,540
就那一次  如果我们当时还是同事
It was once, and I never would have done it

85
00:03:32,540 --> 00:03:34,080
我绝不会那么做的
if we were still working together.

86
00:03:35,120 --> 00:03:36,970
但后来他离开了地检官办公室
But then, he left the D.A.'s office,

87
00:03:36,970 --> 00:03:38,240
我们就...
and...

88
00:03:39,540 --> 00:03:40,750
那个了
it happened.

89
00:03:41,750 --> 00:03:43,050
然后我再见他的时候
And then, the next time I saw him,

90
00:03:43,050 --> 00:03:44,610
他要我跟他一起来律所
he wanted me to come with him to the firm,

91
00:03:44,610 --> 00:03:46,300
我就同意了  我们也到此为止了
and I did, and that was that.

92
00:03:46,300 --> 00:03:47,970
你想跟他在一起吗
Would you have wanted a relationship with him?

93
00:03:47,970 --> 00:03:49,400
我愿意试试
I would have wanted to try,

94
00:03:50,620 --> 00:03:51,850
但他当时没准备好
but he wasn't ready.

95
00:03:53,990 --> 00:03:56,900
如果我逼他
And if I had pushed him to be ready,

96
00:03:56,900 --> 00:03:58,750
我今天就会是跟别人
I would be sitting here talking to somebody else

97
00:03:58,750 --> 00:04:02,100
谈一个我很久以前的同事了
about somebody I used to work with a long time ago.

98
00:04:02,770 --> 00:04:03,900
你什么意思
What are you saying?

99
00:04:04,700 --> 00:04:07,110
一切终会水到渠成
I'm saying everything turned out the way it was supposed to.

100
00:04:07,110 --> 00:04:08,630
但你说
But you said the reason

101
00:04:08,630 --> 00:04:13,420
你们之所以没有...是因为那样就回不去了
that you two never--is because you can never go back.

102
00:04:15,820 --> 00:04:16,940
我撒谎了
I lied.

103
00:04:23,650 --> 00:04:25,350
我很想让你先走
Oh, I'd let you go,

104
00:04:25,350 --> 00:04:27,190
但毕竟是我先来的
but I was here first.

105
00:04:27,300 --> 00:04:28,510
哈维·斯佩克特
Words to live by

106
00:04:28,510 --> 00:04:30,950
世界第一自私鬼的金句良言
by Harvey Specter, the most selfish man in the world.

107
00:04:31,770 --> 00:04:33,080
那我不客气了
Don't mind if I do.

108
00:04:33,150 --> 00:04:34,190
等等
Wait a second.

109
00:04:35,390 --> 00:04:36,930
你怎么来这么早
What are you doing here so early?

110
00:04:36,930 --> 00:04:38,060
我一向这么早来
I always get in this early.

111
00:04:38,060 --> 00:04:40,830
你从不这么早来  我很确定
You never get in this early, and I know that for a fact

112
00:04:40,830 --> 00:04:43,840
因为我每天都这时候来
because this is the time I get in every single day.

113
00:04:43,860 --> 00:04:45,070
你该偶尔多睡会儿
You should sleep in once in a while.

114
00:04:45,070 --> 00:04:46,280
对你有好处  相信我
It's good for you. Trust me.

115
00:04:46,280 --> 00:04:48,040
我每天都这样
I do it every single day.

116
00:04:48,180 --> 00:04:51,000
巧的是我今早有工作
It just so happens that this morning, i have work to do.

117
00:04:51,280 --> 00:04:52,400
什么工作
What work?

118
00:04:53,340 --> 00:04:55,060
施姆金斯堡简报
The schmoolkinsberg brief.

119
00:04:55,690 --> 00:04:57,560
施姆金斯堡简报
The schmoolkinsberg brief?

120
00:04:58,170 --> 00:04:59,430
你就编这种借口
That's what you're going with?

121
00:04:59,470 --> 00:05:00,590
反正它又不会自己写出来
It's not gonna write itself.

122
00:05:00,590 --> 00:05:02,280
我要解除你的命名合伙人地位了
I'm taking your name off the wall.

123
00:05:02,700 --> 00:05:04,790
说真的  我是为了东京市场的事而来
Seriously, I'm here for the Tokyo markets.

124
00:05:05,120 --> 00:05:06,920
你倒说一个出来
Name one Tokyo market.

125
00:05:06,920 --> 00:05:09,090
-日经指数  -再说一个
- The Nikkei. - Name another.

126
00:05:09,090 --> 00:05:12,450
本田  丰田  起亚
Honda, Toyota, Kia.

127
00:05:12,480 --> 00:05:13,520
起亚是韩国的
Kia's Korean.

128
00:05:13,520 --> 00:05:15,440
反正是一个时区的
Yeah, but they're in the same time zone.

129
00:05:15,440 --> 00:05:16,810
那里现在正是晚上
Where it is currently dinner.

130
00:05:17,750 --> 00:05:19,510
我受够你的审问了
I'm a tired of this inquisition.

131
00:05:19,510 --> 00:05:21,540
我就是因为这个从不早来
This is exactly why I don't come in this early.

132
00:05:21,540 --> 00:05:24,480
而你今早这么早来
And the reason that you're here this early this morning

133
00:05:24,480 --> 00:05:27,030
是因为这是迈克·罗斯第一天回来
is because it's Mike Ross' first day back.

134
00:05:27,030 --> 00:05:27,830
是吗
Is it?

135
00:05:37,170 --> 00:05:39,400
路易  你怎么这么早就来了
Louis, why are you here so early?

136
00:05:39,400 --> 00:05:41,000
我要把傅滋曼的文件
I am taking this Forstman document,

137
00:05:41,000 --> 00:05:45,480
埋在这堆文件的肚子里
and I am burying it in the bowels of these files.

138
00:05:45,950 --> 00:05:48,070
然后我要把这堆文件
And then, I am putting these files

139
00:05:48,480 --> 00:05:51,670
深埋在我们仓库的肚子里
deep in the bowels of our storage.

140
00:05:51,670 --> 00:05:52,980
路易  别再说肚子了
Louis, please stop saying bowels.

141
00:05:52,980 --> 00:05:54,650
卡特里娜  我没时间管肚子不肚子的
Katrina, I don't have time to give a shit about bowels,

142
00:05:54,650 --> 00:05:56,360
今天之后  我们要重新开始
'cause after this, we are starting fresh.

143
00:05:56,360 --> 00:05:58,700
我再也不想听到吉利斯工业  肖恩·卡荷尔
and I don't want to hear about Gillis industries, Sean Cahill,

144
00:05:58,700 --> 00:06:00,110
或是查尔斯·傅滋曼了
Charles Forstman ever again.

145
00:06:06,690 --> 00:06:10,980
瞧瞧是谁啊  雌雄大盗
Well, look who it is, Bonnie and Clyde.

146
00:06:10,980 --> 00:06:12,540
我正想找你们
Just the people I wanted to see.

147
00:06:12,540 --> 00:06:13,880
你想干什么  肖恩
What do you want, Sean?

148
00:06:13,880 --> 00:06:15,790
给你们这个
To serve you with this.

149
00:06:15,790 --> 00:06:16,940
那是什么
What the hell is that?

150
00:06:19,620 --> 00:06:22,480
他要所有跟吉利斯工业收购相关的文件
He wants all files relating to the Gillis industries takeover.

151
00:06:22,480 --> 00:06:23,600
我不是想要
Oh, I don't want the files.

152
00:06:23,600 --> 00:06:25,440
-我是必须拿走  -胡扯
- I'm taking them. - Bullshit.

153
00:06:25,440 --> 00:06:27,920
我们有60天时间上诉或配合
We have 60 days to fight that or comply.

154
00:06:27,920 --> 00:06:29,200
你来告诉他还是我来
You want to tell him or should I?

155
00:06:29,200 --> 00:06:32,120
哈维  这不是传票  是搜查令
It's not a subpoena, Harvey. It's a search warrant.

156
00:06:32,120 --> 00:06:34,380
你要么给我全部文件
So you're gonna give me all the files,

157
00:06:34,380 --> 00:06:37,200
要么就跟他们走一趟
or you're gonna head downtown with these two fine gentlemen.

158
00:06:37,310 --> 00:06:38,430
好啊  肖恩
Okay, Sean.

159
00:06:38,830 --> 00:06:40,030
随你便吧
Have it your way.

160
00:06:40,590 --> 00:06:42,010
你从那边走
You're going to take that hall.

161
00:06:42,140 --> 00:06:43,650
然后你会遇到一个有点像
You're going to run into what appears

162
00:06:43,650 --> 00:06:45,910
木乃伊的法务秘书
to be the mummified remains of a legal secretary.

163
00:06:45,910 --> 00:06:47,610
-她叫诺玛  -是的
- Her name is Norma. - Mm-hmm.

164
00:06:47,610 --> 00:06:49,460
她会步履蹒跚的带你们去60层
She's gonna limp you up to the 60th floor

165
00:06:49,640 --> 00:06:52,260
那里存着三十年的档案
where you will find 30 years worth of files

166
00:06:52,260 --> 00:06:54,230
自从里根政府以来就没被整理过
that haven't been sorted since the Reagan administration.

167
00:06:54,230 --> 00:06:55,470
还是在56层来着
Or is it the 56th floor?

168
00:06:55,470 --> 00:06:57,300
据我所知也有可能是35层
It could be the 35th floor for all I know.

169
00:06:57,300 --> 00:06:58,540
重点是  在你试图
The point is, while you're trying

170
00:06:58,540 --> 00:06:59,660
找到消失的法柜时
to find the Ark of the Covenant,

171
00:06:59,830 --> 00:07:02,850
我们会在市中心法官面前取消掉这个东西
we'll be downtown in front of a judge blocking this bullshit.

172
00:07:02,850 --> 00:07:04,390
你认为在我找到想要的东西前搞定法官
You think the threat of you getting to a judge

173
00:07:04,390 --> 00:07:06,800
就能威胁我离开吗
before I find what I want is gonna get me to leave?

174
00:07:06,800 --> 00:07:07,940
那就留下
Then stay,

175
00:07:08,070 --> 00:07:10,190
但你认为谁的动作会快一点呢
But who do you think's gonna get the job done faster?

176
00:07:10,450 --> 00:07:15,180
你和这两个夹克男还是雌雄大盗呢
You and those two windbreakers or Bonnie and Clyde.

177
00:07:56,550 --> 00:07:57,900
欢迎回家  水手
Welcome home, Sailor.

178
00:07:59,700 --> 00:08:01,390
你这次出海走得够久啊
You were out to sea a long time.

179
00:08:01,390 --> 00:08:03,360
确实是  但现在我回来了
I was, but now I'm back.

180
00:08:03,360 --> 00:08:05,410
这个地方可是一点都没变啊
And this place hasn't changed a bit.

181
00:08:06,240 --> 00:08:07,490
也许变了
Maybe it has.

182
00:08:07,620 --> 00:08:08,760
这是斯宾纳的新专辑吗
Is this a new Spinner's album?

183
00:08:08,760 --> 00:08:10,320
不是  你也知道那不是新的
No, and you know it's not new.

184
00:08:10,320 --> 00:08:11,470
你和哈维还就此开过玩笑
You and harvey joked about it.

185
00:08:11,470 --> 00:08:12,910
我以为那是另外一张
I could have sworn that was a different one.

186
00:08:12,910 --> 00:08:14,540
你不是过目不忘吗
Said the man with the photographic memory.

187
00:08:14,540 --> 00:08:16,130
好吧  那也不等于我看过每一张唱片啊
Okay, that doesn't mean I've seen every album--

188
00:08:16,130 --> 00:08:17,580
你根本不知道该去哪是吧
You have no idea where to go, do you?

189
00:08:17,580 --> 00:08:19,370
-一点都不知道  -跟我来
- Not a clue. - Come with me.

190
00:08:23,690 --> 00:08:24,950
唐娜  我去了大办公室
Donna, I went to the bullpen.

191
00:08:24,950 --> 00:08:27,250
有个长小胡子的人坐了我的位置
Some guy with a soul patch was sitting at my desk.

192
00:08:27,320 --> 00:08:29,140
因为那不是你的位置了
That's because it's not your desk anymore,

193
00:08:29,140 --> 00:08:30,970
而且你也配不上小胡子
and you're not cool enough to pull off a soul patch.

194
00:08:30,970 --> 00:08:32,170
这我不同意
I dispute that.

195
00:08:32,230 --> 00:08:34,100
你能在下巴上长出那种胡子吗
Are you even capable of growing a soul patch?

196
00:08:34,100 --> 00:08:36,880
在我幻想中的大学二年级  我留过山羊胡
I had a goatee my sophomore year of never.

197
00:08:37,290 --> 00:08:38,630
听着  那不是你的位置了
Look, it's not your desk anymore

198
00:08:38,630 --> 00:08:40,200
因为你被换到大办公室的另一端了
because you're on the other side of the bullpen now.

199
00:08:40,200 --> 00:08:41,170
哪个另一端
Which other side?

200
00:08:41,480 --> 00:08:43,490
另一端  就是你不在的那一端
The other side. Like, not the side that you were on.

201
00:08:43,490 --> 00:08:45,010
离门近了还是远了
Towards the door or away from the door?

202
00:08:45,030 --> 00:08:45,790
你说哪扇门
Which door are you talking about?

203
00:08:45,790 --> 00:08:46,720
你说的是哪扇
Which door are you talking about?

204
00:08:46,720 --> 00:08:48,740
得了  闭嘴吧  跟我走就行了
You know what? Just shut up and keep walking.

205
00:08:48,980 --> 00:08:50,130
你才来不到五分钟
You're not here five minutes,

206
00:08:50,130 --> 00:08:51,560
就已经让我头疼了
and you're already a pain in my ass.

207
00:08:54,010 --> 00:08:56,630
这里就是那个另一端
This is the other side of the bullpen.

208
00:08:59,180 --> 00:09:00,620
-你是认真的吗  -我知道
- Are you serious? - I know.

209
00:09:00,690 --> 00:09:01,940
我也全力抗争过
I fought it tooth and nail.

210
00:09:01,940 --> 00:09:03,570
要是让我说  你就该坐在
I mean, if it were up to me, you'd be setting up shop

211
00:09:03,570 --> 00:09:04,630
档案室的角落办公
in the file room.

212
00:09:04,830 --> 00:09:06,260
你安排的对吧
You did this, didn't you?

213
00:09:06,430 --> 00:09:08,990
我没有不安排而已
Well, I didn't not do it.

214
00:09:09,400 --> 00:09:10,420
谢谢  唐娜
Thanks, Donna.

215
00:09:10,510 --> 00:09:11,980
很高兴你能回来  迈克
It's good to have you back, Mike.

216
00:09:14,140 --> 00:09:15,820
好吧  我们中的一个要干活了
Well, some of us have work to do,

217
00:09:15,820 --> 00:09:16,870
当然  那一个
and of course, by "Some of us,"

218
00:09:16,870 --> 00:09:17,900
是你
I mean you.

219
00:09:18,630 --> 00:09:20,490
你要回来的消息一传开
As soon as word got out that you were coming back,

220
00:09:20,490 --> 00:09:21,990
合伙人们就开始拿号排队
the partners started taking numbers

221
00:09:21,990 --> 00:09:23,560
给金童安排工作了
to give the boy wonder their work.

222
00:09:25,300 --> 00:09:27,510
-谢谢  唐娜  -你已经谢过我了
- Thanks, Donna. - You already thanked me.

223
00:09:27,510 --> 00:09:28,430
不是工作的事
Not for that.

224
00:09:29,810 --> 00:09:31,120
谢谢你没有提瑞秋
For not mentioning Rachel.

225
00:09:31,120 --> 00:09:31,850
-迈克  -得了吧
- Mike. - Come on.

226
00:09:31,850 --> 00:09:33,810
你以为我会相信你对此一无所知吗
You expect me to believe you don't know what's going on?

227
00:09:35,740 --> 00:09:38,130
我知道这是你跟她之间的事
I know enough to know that it's between you and her.

228
00:09:43,950 --> 00:09:46,780
你得给利点

229
00:09:50,260 --> 00:09:51,700
天哪
Shit.

230
00:09:51,930 --> 00:09:53,430
看看是谁回来了啊
Look who's back.

231
00:09:53,430 --> 00:09:56,510
天哪  看看谁还在这啊
Shit, look who's still here.

232
00:09:56,710 --> 00:09:58,260
你在华尔街捣乱的时候
Somebody had to pick up your slack

233
00:09:58,260 --> 00:10:00,090
总要有人留下来给你收拾烂摊子啊
while you were shiting the bed on Wall Street.

234
00:10:00,090 --> 00:10:01,650
就因为有你这样的烂律师
Which is why it's good to be back here

235
00:10:01,650 --> 00:10:03,250
衬托我的优秀
where there's a shity lawyer like you

236
00:10:03,250 --> 00:10:04,490
能回来上班才这么美好
to make me look good.

237
00:10:05,460 --> 00:10:06,490
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.

238
00:10:07,080 --> 00:10:08,110
谢谢  卡特里娜
Thanks, Katrina.

239
00:10:08,180 --> 00:10:10,090
别谢我  谢谢路易
Don't thank me. Thank Louis.

240
00:10:10,250 --> 00:10:12,350
他把我招回来的时候就谢过了
Oh, I did when he hired me back.

241
00:10:12,350 --> 00:10:13,360
我相信你谢过
I'm sure you did,

242
00:10:13,360 --> 00:10:15,540
我也相信他没告诉你这事
and I'm sure he would never tell you this,

243
00:10:15,540 --> 00:10:17,590
但是我想让你知道
but I wanted you to know

244
00:10:17,590 --> 00:10:19,260
他为了让你回来  放弃了什么
what he gave up to bring you back here.

245
00:10:19,860 --> 00:10:20,730
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

246
00:10:20,730 --> 00:10:22,460
在路易搞定傅滋曼时
Jessica gave Louis one wish

247
00:10:22,460 --> 00:10:23,850
杰西卡给了他一个愿望
when he closed Forstman,

248
00:10:23,850 --> 00:10:26,510
他计划重新安排工作时间表
and he had a whole plan to manage his work schedule

249
00:10:26,510 --> 00:10:28,740
以便能够与希拉重归于好
so he could try to reignite things with Sheila.

250
00:10:29,190 --> 00:10:32,080
但他放弃了那些  因为比起他自己
And he gave all that up because he cared more about you

251
00:10:32,080 --> 00:10:33,370
他更在意你
than he did about himself.

252
00:10:37,910 --> 00:10:39,540
-我不知道这件事  -就像我说的
- I didn't know that. - Well, like I said,

253
00:10:39,540 --> 00:10:40,460
我觉得你应该知道
I thought you should.

254
00:10:50,470 --> 00:10:51,760
欢迎回来
Welcome back.

255
00:11:05,970 --> 00:11:07,210
我十分钟之后要开庭
I have court in ten minutes.

256
00:11:07,210 --> 00:11:09,140
你们三个来这干嘛
Now, what are you three doing in front of my face?

257
00:11:09,140 --> 00:11:09,740
我们来这里
We're here

258
00:11:09,740 --> 00:11:11,300
是因为他今早带着一张搜查令
because he showed up at our offices this morning

259
00:11:11,300 --> 00:11:12,320
来了我们的办公室
with a search warrant.

260
00:11:12,320 --> 00:11:13,680
很抱歉  是一张你无权
A search warrant, I'm sorry to say,

261
00:11:13,680 --> 00:11:15,140
阻止的搜查令
you have no authority to stop.

262
00:11:15,140 --> 00:11:17,060
你有权  因为他故意
Yes, you do, because he deliberately

263
00:11:17,060 --> 00:11:18,820
跳过你的管辖权得到的这张搜查令
went outside your authority to get it.

264
00:11:18,820 --> 00:11:19,980
-什么  -法官大人
- What? - Your Honor,

265
00:11:19,980 --> 00:11:21,610
我之所以去找另一个法官
I went to a different judge because my office

266
00:11:21,610 --> 00:11:23,070
是因为我的办公室找您的时候您不在
tried to reach you, but you were unavailable.

267
00:11:23,070 --> 00:11:24,910
您可以去和秘书核实  有通话记录的
Check with your clerk. There's a record of the call.

268
00:11:24,910 --> 00:11:26,650
你是从富兰克林法官家打的电话吧
Did you make it from judge Franklin's house?

269
00:11:26,650 --> 00:11:29,550
他可是昨晚八点半签署的搜查令
Because he's the one who signed the warrant at 8:30 last night.

270
00:11:29,550 --> 00:11:31,980
他就是每周四跟你打高尔夫的那个法官
The same judge you play golf with every Thursday.

271
00:11:31,980 --> 00:11:34,500
巴拉克·奥巴马还和艾瑞克·霍德打篮球呢
And Barack Obama plays basketball with Eric Holder.

272
00:11:34,500 --> 00:11:35,710
把所有人都抓起来吧
Let's arrest everybody.

273
00:11:35,710 --> 00:11:37,590
我对所有人不感兴趣
I'm not interested in everybody.

274
00:11:37,590 --> 00:11:39,360
我只好奇你为什么绕过我
I'm interested in why you went around me.

275
00:11:39,360 --> 00:11:40,810
因为昨晚我需要一纸搜查令
Because I needed a warrant last night

276
00:11:40,810 --> 00:11:42,900
来阻止他们今早销毁证据
to stop them from destroying evidence this morning.

277
00:11:42,900 --> 00:11:45,360
除非哪天有罪推定变成原则
And the day someone's guilty until proven innocent

278
00:11:45,360 --> 00:11:48,080
你这种论调才稍微站得住脚[盛水]
is the day that argument holds an ounce of water.

279
00:11:48,080 --> 00:11:49,570
最好带着你的杯子  哈维
Better get your glass, Harvey.

280
00:11:49,570 --> 00:11:51,160
这一天比你预想的来得更快
That day's coming sooner than you think.

281
00:11:51,160 --> 00:11:52,530
反正不会是今天
Well, it's not today.

282
00:11:53,060 --> 00:11:54,570
在我们完成听证之前
I'm revoking your search warrant

283
00:11:54,570 --> 00:11:55,710
你的搜查令无效
until we can have a full hearing.

284
00:11:55,710 --> 00:11:56,940
-法官大人  -够了
- Your Honor-- - Now, that's enough.

285
00:11:56,940 --> 00:12:00,140
如果你要搜查一家律师所的文件
If you want to go rummaging around in a law firm's files,

286
00:12:00,140 --> 00:12:02,850
那最好带点比含沙射影有力点的证据来
you better come to me with more than innuendo.

287
00:12:06,800 --> 00:12:07,760
我还是走吧
I better get going.

288
00:12:07,760 --> 00:12:09,440
我还得查查"含沙射影"是什么意思
I have to look up the word "innuendo,"

289
00:12:09,440 --> 00:12:10,420
如果你们懂我的意思
if you know what I mean.

290
00:12:13,990 --> 00:12:16,530
哈维  我告诉你  那人不会罢手的
Harvey, I'm telling you, that man is not going to stop coming.

291
00:12:16,680 --> 00:12:19,110
我有个激进的办法
I'm going to suggest something radical here.

292
00:12:19,410 --> 00:12:20,350
什么办法
And what is that?

293
00:12:20,810 --> 00:12:22,780
他想要的  我们不如直接给他
We could just give him what he wants.

294
00:12:23,170 --> 00:12:24,880
事实上我们也没什么要隐瞒的
The fact is we've got nothing to hide.

295
00:12:24,880 --> 00:12:27,020
哈维  我不关心我们有什么事要隐瞒
Harvey, I don't care that we have nothing to hide.

296
00:12:27,020 --> 00:12:29,100
警察追一辆车够久
A police officer follows a car long enough,

297
00:12:29,100 --> 00:12:30,570
总会被他发现点毛病
he's gonna find a busted taillight.

298
00:12:30,570 --> 00:12:33,240
即使他没发现  他也会自己搞出事来的
And even if he doesn't, he's gonna bust it himself.

299
00:12:33,240 --> 00:12:34,450
那你觉得我们该怎么做
Well, what are you suggesting we do?

300
00:12:34,450 --> 00:12:36,290
我不知道  但这整个迫害活动都是因为
I don't know, but this whole witch hunt

301
00:12:36,290 --> 00:12:38,850
卡荷尔认为你和迈克·罗斯勾结
is about Cahill thinking you colluded with Mike Ross.

302
00:12:38,850 --> 00:12:40,050
所以既然他回来了
So now that he's back,

303
00:12:40,050 --> 00:12:41,700
你何不和那个骗子勾结勾结
why don't you collude with that fraud

304
00:12:41,700 --> 00:12:43,360
把这件事给解决了呢
and get us the hell out of this?

305
00:12:51,290 --> 00:12:53,180
看来你给自己搞了间办公室
See you got yourself an office.

306
00:12:53,890 --> 00:12:55,910
是啊  没我以前那间好  不过
Yeah, it's not as nice as the one I had, but--

307
00:12:55,910 --> 00:12:57,130
总归还是一个进步
It's still a step up.

308
00:12:57,130 --> 00:12:59,650
是因为房间更小了  还是视野更差了
You mean because it's smaller or because the view is worse?

309
00:12:59,650 --> 00:13:01,890
因为这是我以前的办公室
I mean because it's my old office.

310
00:13:02,850 --> 00:13:03,810
你在逗我
You're shiting me.

311
00:13:04,100 --> 00:13:05,530
看看你左边第一个抽屉
Look in the top left drawer.

312
00:13:12,000 --> 00:13:13,610
-你是说真的  -是的
- You're serious. - I am.

313
00:13:15,110 --> 00:13:16,520
唐娜说是她安排的
Donna said she did this.

314
00:13:16,520 --> 00:13:18,470
给你间办公室是她的主意
She had the idea to give you an office.

315
00:13:18,470 --> 00:13:20,300
给你这间办公室是我的主意
It was my idea to give you this office.

316
00:13:20,300 --> 00:13:21,740
它还刚好空出来了
And it just happened to be empty.

317
00:13:21,740 --> 00:13:22,720
差不多吧
Something like that.

318
00:13:22,720 --> 00:13:23,270
好吧
Right.

319
00:13:24,630 --> 00:13:26,240
能让你回到该回的地方真好
It's good to have you back where you belong.

320
00:13:27,660 --> 00:13:29,220
好了  闲话少说
Okay, enough fun.

321
00:13:29,390 --> 00:13:31,320
肖恩·卡荷尔想调查收购案的
Sean Cahill's trying to go through every file

322
00:13:31,320 --> 00:13:33,180
所有文件  有兴趣吗
we have on the takeover. You in?

323
00:13:33,180 --> 00:13:35,010
反正我很确定我对帮保罗·波特
I sure as hell don't want to do an amicus brief

324
00:13:35,010 --> 00:13:36,520
-写意见书没兴趣  -很好
- for Paul Porter. - Good.

325
00:13:36,520 --> 00:13:37,980
那就想个办法阻止卡荷尔
Then figure out a way to keep Cahill

326
00:13:37,980 --> 00:13:39,640
拿到我们的文件
from getting his hands on our documents,

327
00:13:39,640 --> 00:13:41,700
要快  我们没多少时间了
and do it fast because we don't have much time.

328
00:13:41,700 --> 00:13:43,520
哈维  你有没有想过
Harvey, have you considered

329
00:13:43,520 --> 00:13:45,560
其实他追查我们是因为认为我们有合谋罪
the fact that he's been going after us for collusion,

330
00:13:45,560 --> 00:13:47,910
-而其实我们没有  -所以呢
- and we didn't collude? - What are you getting at?

331
00:13:47,910 --> 00:13:49,790
我们何不直接把文件都给他
Why don't we just give him all the files?

332
00:13:50,050 --> 00:13:51,010
我们清清白白
We have nothing to hide,

333
00:13:51,010 --> 00:13:52,790
阻止他倒显得我们有罪了
and fighting him makes it look like we do.

334
00:13:52,790 --> 00:13:53,900
我也是这么和杰西卡说的
That's what I said to Jessica.

335
00:13:53,900 --> 00:13:55,040
你知道她怎么跟我说的吗
You know what she said to me?

336
00:13:55,040 --> 00:13:56,970
警察追一辆车够久
"A cop follows a car long enough,

337
00:13:56,970 --> 00:13:58,490
总会被他发现点毛病
"he's gonna find a busted taillight.

338
00:13:58,490 --> 00:14:01,090
即使他没发现  他也会自己搞出事来的
And even if he doesn't, he's gonna bust it himself."

339
00:14:03,620 --> 00:14:05,140
说到杰西卡
Speaking of Jessica,

340
00:14:06,040 --> 00:14:08,610
你还没告诉我  我回来她怎么想呢
you never told me how she felt about me coming back.

341
00:14:11,700 --> 00:14:14,330
想办法打败卡荷尔  再来问我这个
Find a way to beat Cahill, and then ask me that again.

342
00:14:21,130 --> 00:14:22,550
你就非得先去找他  是吧
You just had to get to him first, didn't you?

343
00:14:23,030 --> 00:14:24,190
怎么  给了他一绺你的头发吗
What, did you give him a lock of your hair?

344
00:14:24,190 --> 00:14:25,470
你想说什么  路易
What are you talking about, Louis?

345
00:14:25,470 --> 00:14:26,630
你以为我没发现你刚好
You think I didn't notice you conveniently

346
00:14:26,630 --> 00:14:27,890
把亨德森安排到了我的旧办公室
put Henderson in my old office

347
00:14:27,890 --> 00:14:29,170
好让迈克搬进你的旧办公室
so you can give Mike your old office?

348
00:14:29,170 --> 00:14:31,270
告诉你吧  路易
For your information, Louis,

349
00:14:31,270 --> 00:14:33,300
亨德森求我把你的旧办公室给他
Henderson begged for your old office

350
00:14:33,300 --> 00:14:35,270
因为他认为你是这世界上
because he thinks you're the best attorney

351
00:14:35,270 --> 00:14:36,800
最强的律师
that's ever walked the face of this earth.

352
00:14:36,800 --> 00:14:38,370
扯淡  真的吗
Oh, bull--really?

353
00:14:38,800 --> 00:14:39,970
千真万确
Absolutely.

354
00:14:42,760 --> 00:14:44,340
你说那些不是为了讨我欢心
So you're not just saying that to butter me up

355
00:14:44,340 --> 00:14:45,530
好让我就此罢休吧
so I'll let this go?

356
00:14:46,210 --> 00:14:47,200
对天发誓
Hand to god,

357
00:14:47,520 --> 00:14:48,980
或者像亨德森说的
or as Henderson would say,

358
00:14:49,510 --> 00:14:51,640
-对路易发誓  -那好吧
- "Hand to Louis." - Okay, then.

359
00:14:51,640 --> 00:14:53,710
只要你没骗我就好
Just as long as you're not trying to pull one over on me.

360
00:14:56,010 --> 00:14:57,410
那个亨德森真有前途
That Henderson is going places.

361
00:15:04,680 --> 00:15:05,870
别动
Don't move.

362
00:15:08,010 --> 00:15:09,410
你在干嘛
What are you doing?

363
00:15:09,720 --> 00:15:11,580
拍下此刻的记忆影像
Taking a mental picture of this moment.

364
00:15:12,030 --> 00:15:13,390
路易  那不是记忆
Louis, that's not a mental--

365
00:15:13,390 --> 00:15:15,780
迈克·罗斯  浪子回家了
Mike Ross, the prodigal son, returns.

366
00:15:16,310 --> 00:15:17,680
-谢谢  -不用谢
- Thanks. - You're very welcome.

367
00:15:17,680 --> 00:15:21,000
路易  我还要再谢谢你让我回来
And Louis, I want to thank you again for bringing me back.

368
00:15:22,240 --> 00:15:23,460
我永远不会忘记这份情
I'm never gonna forget it.

369
00:15:23,780 --> 00:15:26,290
如果有什么事情我可以报答你的话
And if there is every anything that I can do to repay you--

370
00:15:27,220 --> 00:15:28,260
迈克  别这样
Mike, please.

371
00:15:28,740 --> 00:15:29,830
不要侮辱我
Don't insult me.

372
00:15:29,830 --> 00:15:33,330
你不欠我的  如果你真的在乎我
You do not owe me, and if you really care about me,

373
00:15:33,330 --> 00:15:36,050
就永远不许再提报答我之类的话
you will never mention repaying me with a favor again.

374
00:15:37,370 --> 00:15:39,100
-真的很感谢  路易  -很好
- Really appreciate it, Louis. - Good.

375
00:15:39,480 --> 00:15:41,690
现在  我要你停下手头的事
Now, I need you to drop whatever it is you're doing--

376
00:15:41,690 --> 00:15:43,360
路易  我不能停下
Oh, Louis, I can't drop what I'm doing.

377
00:15:43,360 --> 00:15:44,430
哈维刚刚要我
Harvey just asked me to--

378
00:15:44,430 --> 00:15:45,750
你说你不能停下手头的事是什么意思
What do you mean you can't drop what you're doing?

379
00:15:45,750 --> 00:15:46,970
我才刚把你带回来  你欠我人情
I just brought you back here. You owe me.

380
00:15:46,970 --> 00:15:48,490
你刚刚说让我别提要报答你
You just told me never to mention that again.

381
00:15:48,490 --> 00:15:49,630
啥  你以为我说真的吗
What, do you think I meant that?

382
00:15:49,970 --> 00:15:51,300
我这么说是因为大家都这么说啊
I said that because that's what people say.

383
00:15:51,300 --> 00:15:52,540
你应该说的是
Now, what you say is,

384
00:15:52,540 --> 00:15:53,480
谁在乎哈维让我干什么
"Screw what harvey asked me to do.

385
00:15:53,480 --> 00:15:54,390
我一点都不在乎那个人
"I don't give a shit about him.

386
00:15:54,390 --> 00:15:55,690
我只在乎你  路易
I only give a shit about you, Louis."

387
00:15:55,690 --> 00:15:57,330
路易  这不只是为了哈维
Louis, this isn't just for Harvey.

388
00:15:57,330 --> 00:15:58,320
是为了律所  好吗
It's for the firm, okay?

389
00:15:58,320 --> 00:16:00,060
-肖恩·卡荷尔  -胡说
- Sean Cahill-- - Bullshit.

390
00:16:00,060 --> 00:16:01,410
那是指哈维一贯使用的...
That's just the kind of thing that Harvey--

391
00:16:01,410 --> 00:16:03,270
你刚说的是  刚说的是
Did you just--did you just--

392
00:16:03,270 --> 00:16:04,400
你刚说的是  肖恩·卡荷尔吗
Did you just say, "Sean Cahill"?

393
00:16:04,400 --> 00:16:05,410
对  他想拿到
Yeah. He's trying to get access

394
00:16:05,410 --> 00:16:07,000
我们关于吉利斯收购案的文件
to our files on the Gillis takeover.

395
00:16:07,000 --> 00:16:09,310
为什么不早说
Why didn't you say that in the first place?

396
00:16:09,310 --> 00:16:10,620
咱们得拼尽法律的全力
We need to fight this son of a bitch

397
00:16:10,620 --> 00:16:12,170
和那个孙子打到底  迈克
with the full force of the law, Mike.

398
00:16:12,170 --> 00:16:13,830
-我刚才就在这么做  -继续
- That's what I was doing. - Then, do it.

399
00:16:13,830 --> 00:16:15,070
你没时间管我这个案子
You don't have time to work on this case.

400
00:16:15,070 --> 00:16:16,350
我把这个案子给卡特里娜
I need to bring it to Katrina.

401
00:16:17,160 --> 00:16:19,650
-路易  你还好吗  -我不好
- Louis, are you okay? - No, I am not okay.

402
00:16:19,650 --> 00:16:21,160
迈克  这是针对我们律所的攻击
Mike, this is an attack on our firm,

403
00:16:21,160 --> 00:16:23,290
攻击一个人  就是攻击我们所有人
and an attack against one of us is an attack against all of us.

404
00:16:23,290 --> 00:16:24,310
赶紧开始干活
Get the hell to work.

405
00:16:28,980 --> 00:16:30,040
我们有麻烦了
We're in trouble.

406
00:16:30,410 --> 00:16:32,810
肖恩·卡荷尔想拿到吉利斯案的文件
Sean Cahill is trying to get the Gillis files.

407
00:16:32,810 --> 00:16:35,590
路易  你把那个文件埋起来了
Louis, you buried that document.

408
00:16:35,590 --> 00:16:36,540
你不明白
You don't understand.

409
00:16:36,540 --> 00:16:38,630
证监会会永远存档这些文件
The SEC is gonna have these files forever,

410
00:16:38,630 --> 00:16:40,090
最终  他们会发现
and eventually, they're gonna see the money

411
00:16:40,090 --> 00:16:41,800
那笔钱从一个地方转移到另一个地方
went in one place and came out the other,

412
00:16:41,800 --> 00:16:43,400
经手人是我
and I'm the person who did it.

413
00:16:45,980 --> 00:16:46,910
需要我做什么
What do you need me to do?

414
00:16:46,910 --> 00:16:49,190
尽全力掩盖我的痕迹
I want you to cover up my tracks as best you can.

415
00:16:49,390 --> 00:16:50,430
你要做什么
And what are you going to do?

416
00:16:50,430 --> 00:16:51,950
我去解决这件事
I'm going to try to fix it so the goddamn thing

417
00:16:51,950 --> 00:16:53,290
让这件事从没发生过
never happened in the first place.

418
00:17:02,060 --> 00:17:03,200
你来干什么
What are you doing here?

419
00:17:03,200 --> 00:17:05,770
我觉得咱们没什么好聊的了
I didn't think we had any further business to discuss.

420
00:17:05,770 --> 00:17:07,220
是没有  只是刚完成的那笔交易
We don't. We just have a problem

421
00:17:07,220 --> 00:17:08,790
出了一些问题
with the business we just did.

422
00:17:08,790 --> 00:17:10,630
你是要我给你更多的钱吗
Are you here to shake me down for more money?

423
00:17:10,630 --> 00:17:11,710
我是来退钱的
I'm here to give it all back.

424
00:17:11,710 --> 00:17:14,160
-路易  我跟你说了  -不  听我说好吗
- Louis, I told you-- - No, just listen to me, okay.

425
00:17:14,160 --> 00:17:17,050
证监会  他们正在努力拿到我们的文件
The SEC--they're trying to get access to our files.

426
00:17:17,050 --> 00:17:18,840
一旦拿到  他们就会发现
That happens, they see 

427
00:17:18,840 --> 00:17:20,470
你是绕经离岸银行付的款
that your payout was routed offshore

428
00:17:20,470 --> 00:17:21,590
而且没有付税
and you didn't pay taxes on it.

429
00:17:21,590 --> 00:17:23,970
他们会发现我还没有付税
They'll see I haven't paid taxes.

430
00:17:23,970 --> 00:17:26,400
我从前年秋天开始
I have until the third quarter of two years from now

431
00:17:26,400 --> 00:17:27,860
就没报税
to report that income,

432
00:17:27,860 --> 00:17:29,650
如果我需要的话  会报的
and if I need to, I will.

433
00:17:29,650 --> 00:17:30,850
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?

434
00:17:31,300 --> 00:17:32,540
他们可不傻
They're not idiots.

435
00:17:32,540 --> 00:17:36,090
把钱通过瑞士银行和开曼群岛的银行转账的人
Nobody has money wired through a Swiss bank and the Caymans

436
00:17:36,090 --> 00:17:37,930
没有一个打算向国税局报税的
if they're planning on reporting it to the IRS.

437
00:17:37,930 --> 00:17:40,150
证明不了什么
That's not proof of anything,

438
00:17:40,150 --> 00:17:42,840
如果他们检查这些文件  只会发现
and the only thing they'll definitely find if they get a look at those files

439
00:17:42,840 --> 00:17:44,230
你贪污受贿
is that you embezzled money.

440
00:17:44,230 --> 00:17:45,720
快滚出我的办公室
So get out of my office.

441
00:17:45,720 --> 00:17:46,870
听我说  该死的
Listen to me, goddamn it.

442
00:17:46,870 --> 00:17:49,240
我们得撤销这个交易
We need to undo this deal.

443
00:17:50,910 --> 00:17:52,150
听我说  路易
I tell you what, Louis.

444
00:17:54,100 --> 00:17:55,070
坐好
Have a seat.

445
00:17:57,860 --> 00:17:59,190
你希望得到内心的平静吗
You want peace of mind?

446
00:18:00,480 --> 00:18:03,240
重新起草我们已经签署的这份文件
Draw up the same paperwork we already signed.

447
00:18:03,920 --> 00:18:07,480
只不过这次  让哈维签字
Only this time, have Harvey sign it instead of you.

448
00:18:07,480 --> 00:18:08,110
什么
What?

449
00:18:08,110 --> 00:18:09,260
是你说的  你要穷极所能
You're the one who said you'd go to the ends

450
00:18:09,260 --> 00:18:10,640
和他对着干
of the earth to stick it to him.

451
00:18:10,640 --> 00:18:11,690
抢走他的客户是一码事
Taking his client is one thing.

452
00:18:11,690 --> 00:18:12,790
陷害他
Framing him for a felony?

453
00:18:12,790 --> 00:18:13,860
是另一码事
That's another.

454
00:18:13,860 --> 00:18:14,940
你自己决定
It's your call.

455
00:18:15,600 --> 00:18:17,270
把你的名字  换成他的  
Use your name, replace it with his,

456
00:18:17,270 --> 00:18:18,100
我根本不在乎
I don't give a shit.

457
00:18:18,760 --> 00:18:22,250
但这笔交易不会变
But the deal is staying in place.

458
00:18:39,670 --> 00:18:42,620
听说他们新雇佣了一个金牌律师
I heard they hired a new hotshot attorney,

459
00:18:42,620 --> 00:18:44,460
但他们没告诉我这个人有多帅
but they never said how handsome he was.

460
00:18:44,460 --> 00:18:46,190
瑞秋  我现在真的忙不过来
Look, Rachel, I'm really swamped right now.

461
00:18:46,190 --> 00:18:48,510
忙得连过来打个招呼都没时间吗
Too swamped to even stop by and say, "Hello"?

462
00:18:49,630 --> 00:18:51,640
打个招呼  接着就会说更多
Saying hello is just gonna lead to saying a lot more,

463
00:18:51,640 --> 00:18:53,690
但现在不是聊天的时候
and now is not the time to have it out.

464
00:18:55,690 --> 00:18:57,220
我不是来找你闲聊的
Well, I'm not here to have it out with you.

465
00:18:57,220 --> 00:19:00,380
我是来和你一起对抗肖恩·卡荷尔的
I am here to work with you on fighting off Sean Cahill.

466
00:19:00,380 --> 00:19:01,530
我不需要帮助
I don't need any help.

467
00:19:01,530 --> 00:19:02,720
但你刚说  你忙不过来了
But you just said you were swamped.

468
00:19:02,720 --> 00:19:04,960
因为我一直在努力不和你聊天
Because I'm trying to avoid having a conversation with you,

469
00:19:04,960 --> 00:19:06,460
很明显  没成功
which, obviously, isn't working.

470
00:19:08,180 --> 00:19:10,350
迈克  我现在是哈维的初级律师了
Well, Mike, I am Harvey's associate now.

471
00:19:10,350 --> 00:19:12,380
你忙他的案子  就得和我共事
So you working a case with him, you're working it with me.

472
00:19:12,380 --> 00:19:13,840
他可没告诉我
He didn't say anything to me about it.

473
00:19:13,840 --> 00:19:15,160
他告诉我了
Well, he said it to me.

474
00:19:15,600 --> 00:19:16,770
不然我为什么过来
Why do you think I'm here?

475
00:19:19,520 --> 00:19:21,460
我不管他说了什么  这不是好主意
I don't care what he said. It's not a good idea.

476
00:19:21,460 --> 00:19:23,890
为什么  我们俩同处一室都不行了吗
What isn't? For us to even be in the same room together?

477
00:19:23,890 --> 00:19:25,240
现在  不行
Not right now. No.

478
00:19:25,240 --> 00:19:27,460
是你自己选择回来的
You're the one who chose to come back here.

479
00:19:27,460 --> 00:19:28,470
那又怎样
So?

480
00:19:29,780 --> 00:19:31,060
所以你没理由
So you don't get

481
00:19:31,060 --> 00:19:33,510
为我也在这儿工作而表现得那么失望
to act disappointed that I work here too.

482
00:19:33,510 --> 00:19:34,760
瑞秋  听我说
Rachel. Listen to me.

483
00:19:34,760 --> 00:19:36,580
我告诉过你  我需要空间
I told you that I needed space.

484
00:19:36,580 --> 00:19:38,510
住在酒店还不算吗
What do you call staying in a hotel?

485
00:19:38,860 --> 00:19:40,250
从我们今天的谈话来看
Based on this conversation,

486
00:19:40,250 --> 00:19:41,370
我做的太对了
I call it a smart move.

487
00:19:41,370 --> 00:19:42,800
好了  迈克  对不起
Okay, Mike, I'm sorry.

488
00:19:43,420 --> 00:19:44,450
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?

489
00:19:44,450 --> 00:19:45,400
透透气
Get some air.

490
00:19:53,350 --> 00:19:55,650
你帮他们违法  他们雇你回去
They hire you back after helping them break the law,

491
00:19:55,650 --> 00:19:56,990
就让你午餐吃这个吗
and this is what they give you for lunch?

492
00:19:56,990 --> 00:19:58,480
如果你吃过这家的百吉饼
You wouldn't ask that if you'd ever had

493
00:19:58,480 --> 00:19:59,700
就不会这么说了
one of these bagels.

494
00:19:59,700 --> 00:20:01,690
或许吧  这么问吧
Maybe not, but let me ask you this.

495
00:20:01,920 --> 00:20:04,050
记得那个叫"做笔交易"的娱乐节目吗
You remember that game show called Let's Make a Deal?

496
00:20:05,600 --> 00:20:06,680
没兴趣
Not interested.

497
00:20:06,680 --> 00:20:08,230
你还没听听你会得到什么好处呢
You haven't heard what's in it for you.

498
00:20:08,230 --> 00:20:09,890
我不需要知道我会得到什么好处
I don't need to hear what's in it for me

499
00:20:09,890 --> 00:20:11,250
因为我知道你会得到什么好处
because I know what's in it for you.

500
00:20:12,120 --> 00:20:13,230
聪明的孩子
You're a smart kid.

501
00:20:13,640 --> 00:20:14,800
我明白他们为什么重新雇用你了
I see why they wanted you back.

502
00:20:14,800 --> 00:20:16,210
我要开始吃百吉饼了  看不到你的脸
I'm gonna get back to my bagel, which is gonna

503
00:20:16,210 --> 00:20:19,070
它的味道会更好
taste so much better when I'm not looking at you.

504
00:20:19,360 --> 00:20:22,180
在你开吃之前  考虑一下这个
All right, before you gobble that up, think about this.

505
00:20:23,410 --> 00:20:25,500
我会拿到那些文件  早晚的事
Sooner or later, I'm gonna get those files.

506
00:20:26,210 --> 00:20:28,220
但你也可以亲自交给我
But there's nothing to stop you from giving them to me

507
00:20:28,220 --> 00:20:29,630
没人拦着你
all on your own.

508
00:20:29,990 --> 00:20:30,870
如果你交给我
If you do that,

509
00:20:31,370 --> 00:20:33,320
那么文件中提及"迈克·罗斯"的所有地方
any of those files that say "Mike Ross",

510
00:20:33,730 --> 00:20:36,500
我都替换成"匿名前雇员"
I'll replace with "Anonymous former employee".

511
00:20:38,240 --> 00:20:39,110
很诱人啊  肖恩
That would be tempting, Sean,

512
00:20:39,110 --> 00:20:41,620
可前提是我真有什么不可见人的事
if I actually had something to hide.

513
00:20:47,660 --> 00:20:49,760
我还有一个问题
Oh, I do have one more question, though.

514
00:20:50,720 --> 00:20:53,420
-是哈维买单吗  -什么
- Is Harvey footing the bill? - What?

515
00:20:53,420 --> 00:20:55,750
你住的苏豪大酒店的房间
For your room at the Soho Grand.

516
00:20:56,500 --> 00:20:57,580
你现在住那个酒店  对吧
That's where you're staying, right?

517
00:20:58,530 --> 00:20:59,830
你应该吃一吃那的科布沙拉
You should try the Cobb salad.

518
00:20:59,830 --> 00:21:01,480
世间难得的美味
It's out of this world.

519
00:21:07,170 --> 00:21:08,400
猜猜刚才是谁得到了
Guess who just got propositioned

520
00:21:08,400 --> 00:21:09,900
惹眼的金发人的提议
by a striking blonde?

521
00:21:09,900 --> 00:21:11,640
告诉我你说的是凯特·阿普顿[金发女星]
Please tell me it was Kate Upton.

522
00:21:12,040 --> 00:21:13,420
她配你太年轻了吧
Isn't she a little young for you?

523
00:21:13,420 --> 00:21:15,250
昨晚她还跟我说我的年龄正好
Last night, she told me I was the perfect age.

524
00:21:15,250 --> 00:21:16,290
当她爸爸吗
To be her father.

525
00:21:16,290 --> 00:21:17,090
迈克  你什么时候才能明白
When are you gonna understand 

526
00:21:17,090 --> 00:21:18,440
他们都想要爸比
they all want a daddy, Mike?

527
00:21:18,440 --> 00:21:19,650
你想谈卡荷尔还是
You want to talk about Cahill or just

528
00:21:19,650 --> 00:21:21,530
继续吹虚那些莫须有的事
keep bragging about things that never actually happened.

529
00:21:21,530 --> 00:21:23,950
-卡荷尔想要什么  -不是他想要什么
- What did Cahill want? - It's not what he wanted.

530
00:21:23,950 --> 00:21:25,090
而是他想给我开价
It's what he gave me.

531
00:21:25,090 --> 00:21:26,160
说来听听吧
Well, let's have it.

532
00:21:26,160 --> 00:21:27,890
那孙子知道我现在住酒店
Son of a bitch knew I was staying at a hotel.

533
00:21:27,890 --> 00:21:29,280
-你想说什么  -你不是说过
- What are you getting at? - Didn't you say

534
00:21:29,280 --> 00:21:31,210
他绕开了霍普金斯法官去的搜查令
he sidestepped Judge Hopkins to get a search warrant

535
00:21:31,210 --> 00:21:32,270
想得到我们的文件吗
for our files?

536
00:21:32,270 --> 00:21:34,100
你觉得他绕开了霍普金斯
You're thinking he went around Hopkins

537
00:21:34,100 --> 00:21:35,480
拿到官方授权来纠缠我们吗
to get authorization to follow us?

538
00:21:35,480 --> 00:21:37,760
我觉得他从来没得到过官方授权
I'm thinking he never got authorization at all.

539
00:21:37,760 --> 00:21:39,030
那么最晚明天  我们必须拿到
Then we need to get a list

540
00:21:39,030 --> 00:21:41,670
证监会申请监控的名单
of the SEC's requests for surveillance by tomorrow.

541
00:21:41,670 --> 00:21:43,190
我有个司法部的朋友
I have a friend at Justice.

542
00:21:43,530 --> 00:21:44,510
什么时候有的
Since when?

543
00:21:45,090 --> 00:21:46,970
好吧  我没有  但是说出来很酷
Okay, I don't, but I thought it sounded cool.

544
00:21:46,970 --> 00:21:48,610
迈克  这不是儿戏
Mike, this is serious.

545
00:21:48,610 --> 00:21:50,620
我们需要这份名单  最晚明天
We need that list, and we need it by tomorrow.

546
00:21:50,620 --> 00:21:51,410
这就去办
On it.

547
00:22:00,170 --> 00:22:01,540
好消息  路易
Good news, Louis.

548
00:22:01,540 --> 00:22:06,340
我不仅把那份文档错误归类  错误归期
I not only misfiled and misdated that document,

549
00:22:06,340 --> 00:22:08,770
还放进了一万份看起来一样的文档里
I added in 10,000 others that look just like it.

550
00:22:09,090 --> 00:22:11,910
现在已经深埋地下了
That thing is as buried as it's ever going to be.

551
00:22:11,910 --> 00:22:13,020
你那么做管什么用
What the hell difference does it make?

552
00:22:13,060 --> 00:22:14,130
没用的
It's all for nothing.

553
00:22:15,540 --> 00:22:17,690
-傅滋曼那边出了什么事  -你说呢
- What happened with Forstman? - What do you think?

554
00:22:18,650 --> 00:22:19,850
他不买我的账
He didn't go for it.

555
00:22:19,850 --> 00:22:22,770
不  还有其他事  因为
No, something else happened because 

556
00:22:23,060 --> 00:22:25,820
如果只是他不买账  你不会这么郁闷
you wouldn't be this upset if he just turned you down.

557
00:22:25,820 --> 00:22:27,590
他不会撤回任何事情
He wouldn't undo anything,

558
00:22:27,950 --> 00:22:31,130
但他想要我把责任都嫁祸给哈维
but he is willing to let me pin the whole thing on Harvey.

559
00:22:31,130 --> 00:22:32,530
那要怎么做
How could you even do that?

560
00:22:32,530 --> 00:22:33,660
我也不知道
Oh, I don't know.

561
00:22:33,680 --> 00:22:36,120
做一份新文件  伪造他的签名
Make up a new document, forge his signature.

562
00:22:36,320 --> 00:22:38,040
不要紧  因为我不会那么做
Doesn't matter 'cause I'm not gonna do it.

563
00:22:38,050 --> 00:22:40,390
-路易  -卡特里娜  别说了
- Louis-- - Katrina, enough.

564
00:22:41,550 --> 00:22:43,820
你干得很好  但事实是
You did good work, but the truth is,

565
00:22:43,820 --> 00:22:45,390
如果我们必须上缴那些文件
if we have to turn over those files,

566
00:22:45,390 --> 00:22:46,410
他们就会发现那笔交易
they find that transaction.

567
00:22:46,410 --> 00:22:47,880
而我的结局就是坐牢
I'm gonna end up in prison.

568
00:22:52,580 --> 00:22:55,180
那么你和我
Then you and I 

569
00:22:55,890 --> 00:22:57,630
最好想办法确保
better figure out a way to make sure

570
00:22:57,630 --> 00:22:59,360
哈维能赢得那项动议
Harvey wins that motion.

571
00:23:05,340 --> 00:23:06,370
好吧
Okay.

572
00:23:10,210 --> 00:23:11,150
你给别人留空间的方法
Don't you have a funny way

573
00:23:11,150 --> 00:23:13,280
-也太搞笑了  -什么
- of giving someone space. - What?

574
00:23:13,280 --> 00:23:16,050
你不但做了我们说好决不许做的事
Not only did you do exactly what we talked about not doing,

575
00:23:16,050 --> 00:23:18,920
你还撒谎  用哈维的名义跑去见他
but you lied, and you used Harvey's name to do it.

576
00:23:18,930 --> 00:23:20,900
-对不起  -不  道歉可不够
- I am sorry. - No, sorry's not good enough.

577
00:23:20,900 --> 00:23:23,670
这已经是近期我们第二次谈这件事了
This is the second time we've had this conversation recently,

578
00:23:23,670 --> 00:23:25,900
我想知道为什么还要谈一次
and I want to know why the hell we're having it again.

579
00:23:27,290 --> 00:23:28,810
我没想撒谎
I didn't mean to lie.

580
00:23:28,810 --> 00:23:31,060
我只是去找迈克谈谈
I just--I went to Mike to talk--

581
00:23:31,060 --> 00:23:32,280
说的就是这个
That's my point.

582
00:23:32,440 --> 00:23:33,950
你一天都熬不住吗
You couldn't even make it through one day?

583
00:23:33,950 --> 00:23:35,230
我以为可以
I thought that I could.

584
00:23:35,230 --> 00:23:37,620
谁知我看到他坐在那  我就...
And then, I saw him sitting there, and I just--

585
00:23:37,620 --> 00:23:39,360
瑞秋  虽然很难
Rachel, just because something's hard to do

586
00:23:39,360 --> 00:23:40,930
也不是说你不能做到
doesn't mean that you can't do it.

587
00:23:40,930 --> 00:23:42,860
好吧  我不该把哈维卷进来
Okay. I shouldn't have brought Harvey into it.

588
00:23:42,860 --> 00:23:45,320
但我不会为跟迈克说话而道歉的
But I am not going to apologize for talking to Mike

589
00:23:45,320 --> 00:23:47,520
因为他和我  跟你和哈维完全不同
because he and I aren't the same as you and Harvey.

590
00:23:47,720 --> 00:23:48,810
你说什么
Excuse me?

591
00:23:49,550 --> 00:23:51,840
-我不是这个意思  -我跟你谈的这些
- That didn't come out that I-- - I did not tell you that 

592
00:23:51,840 --> 00:23:53,350
不是为了让你羞辱我
for you to just throw it back in my face.

593
00:23:53,350 --> 00:23:54,930
我不是想要羞辱你
I didn't mean to throw it in your face.

594
00:23:55,090 --> 00:23:58,190
我尊重你顺其自然的做法
I respect that you let things take their natural course.

595
00:23:59,420 --> 00:24:02,250
但我想主动行动  和迈克和好
But I want to make things work with Mike,

596
00:24:03,060 --> 00:24:05,240
而我所知道的唯一方法  就是去争取他
and the only way I know how to do that is to fight for him.

597
00:24:07,200 --> 00:24:08,620
去争取他吧
Fight for him all you want,

598
00:24:09,250 --> 00:24:11,020
但别再用哈维的名义撒谎了
but don't lie about Harvey ever again.

599
00:24:35,930 --> 00:24:37,570
已经开始怀念这里了吗
You're missing it in here already?

600
00:24:38,890 --> 00:24:40,140
只是路过
Just passing through.

601
00:24:41,660 --> 00:24:42,620
我骗了你
I lied to you. 

602
00:24:42,620 --> 00:24:44,280
-我知道你骗了我  -不是说那件事
- I know you lied to me-- - Not that.

603
00:24:46,110 --> 00:24:47,920
哈维没有派我负责你的案子
Harvey never assigned me to your case.

604
00:24:50,780 --> 00:24:53,530
我这么做是因为  你离开了家
I did it because you left our home,

605
00:24:53,530 --> 00:24:55,160
又来到了这儿
and you came here.

606
00:24:55,250 --> 00:24:58,610
每次看到你  我心里想的
And all I can think every time I look at you 

607
00:24:58,710 --> 00:25:00,550
就是非常抱歉
is how sorry I am.

608
00:25:06,990 --> 00:25:08,640
而我希望你别再来找我的原因
And the reason I want you to leave me alone

609
00:25:08,650 --> 00:25:10,980
是每当我看到你  我想到的
is all I can think when I look at you

610
00:25:12,150 --> 00:25:13,170
就是他
is him.

611
00:25:15,580 --> 00:25:17,220
那你为什么要回来
Then why did you come back?

612
00:25:18,570 --> 00:25:22,290
我快要淹死了  路易给了我一根救命稻草
I was drowning, and Louis threw me a lifeline.

613
00:25:22,290 --> 00:25:24,020
我也是你的救命稻草
I'm your lifeline, too.

614
00:25:24,470 --> 00:25:26,670
救命稻草  你是推我下水的那个人
A lifeline? You're the one that threw me overboard.

615
00:25:26,680 --> 00:25:28,740
-迈克  -为什么偏偏是他
- Mike-- - And why did it have to be him?

616
00:25:34,520 --> 00:25:36,830
我不需要你不停的跟我道歉
I don't need you to keep telling me that you're sorry

617
00:25:36,830 --> 00:25:39,610
释放魅力或者其他什么
or to be charming or anything else.

618
00:25:42,840 --> 00:25:45,260
我只是需要把那个场景从我脑中抹去
I just need to get that image out of my head.

619
00:26:12,140 --> 00:26:13,980
-拿到了吗  -没有
- Did you get it? - No.

620
00:26:14,270 --> 00:26:15,770
能先通知我一声也好吧
A little heads up would have been nice.

621
00:26:15,770 --> 00:26:17,000
我可没有后备计划
I don't exactly have a backup plan.

622
00:26:17,000 --> 00:26:18,680
好消息是我有
Well, good thing I do. 

623
00:26:18,960 --> 00:26:20,170
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?

624
00:26:20,170 --> 00:26:22,760
有没有证据证实我们的理论  并不重要
It doesn't matter whether we have proof of our theory or not.

625
00:26:22,770 --> 00:26:25,000
重要的是  我们的理论是不是真的
It just matters whether or not our theory is true.

626
00:26:25,000 --> 00:26:26,170
你打了一份假名单
You typed up a fake list.

627
00:26:26,170 --> 00:26:27,900
没错  聪明绝顶
Exactly. Brilliant.

628
00:26:27,900 --> 00:26:29,120
如果你不是最后一刻才赶到的话
It would have been a little more brilliant

629
00:26:29,120 --> 00:26:30,490
就更厉害了
if you didn't get here at the last second.

630
00:26:30,490 --> 00:26:33,280
不演得真一点就没用了  那需要时间
It wouldn't work if it doesn't look real, and that takes time.

631
00:26:33,280 --> 00:26:34,230
好了  快给我
Okay, just give it to me.

632
00:26:34,230 --> 00:26:35,900
我能搞定
I got it.

633
00:26:42,030 --> 00:26:43,630
快看呀
oh, well, well.

634
00:26:43,780 --> 00:26:45,060
这不是神奇双侠吗
If it isn't the Wonder Twins.

635
00:26:45,060 --> 00:26:46,980
一副混蛋样
Form of "Douche bag."

636
00:26:46,980 --> 00:26:48,930
是抓住你小辫子的样子
Shape of "Got you by the balls."

637
00:26:48,930 --> 00:26:50,360
不不不  必须是动物形态
no, no, no, no. It's got to be an animal.

638
00:26:50,360 --> 00:26:52,030
我才懒得管必须是什么呢
I don't care what it has to be.

639
00:26:52,330 --> 00:26:55,030
这个  是证监会过去三个月
What that is, is every surveillance request

640
00:26:55,030 --> 00:26:56,920
所有的监视请求
from the SEC in the last three months.

641
00:26:56,920 --> 00:26:58,730
迈克  你来告诉它上面有什么吧
Mike, why don't you tell him what's on there?

642
00:26:58,750 --> 00:27:01,200
他知道上面有什么  没有什么
Oh, he knows what's on there and what's not on there,

643
00:27:01,200 --> 00:27:03,240
不在上面的  有你和我
which would be me and you.

644
00:27:03,530 --> 00:27:05,470
等一下  这不是会使他
Wait a second, doesn't that make any evidence

645
00:27:05,470 --> 00:27:07,170
打算用的证据都不能采用吗
he's planning on using today inadmissible?

646
00:27:07,170 --> 00:27:09,720
我想是的
I believe it would.

647
00:27:10,000 --> 00:27:12,010
别自找难堪了  肖恩
Save yourself the embarrassment, Sean.

648
00:27:12,260 --> 00:27:14,070
撤销你对搜查令
Withdraw your request for a warrant, 

649
00:27:14,070 --> 00:27:15,820
传票或是其他什么的申请吧
a subpoena, or anything.

650
00:27:15,820 --> 00:27:18,290
好了  我们开始吧
All right. Let's get this thing going.

651
00:27:18,660 --> 00:27:20,420
你们俩在他桌边干嘛
What are you two doing at his table?

652
00:27:21,040 --> 00:27:22,560
你来告诉他还是我们来
You want to tell him or should we?

653
00:27:24,650 --> 00:27:27,550
法官大人  我正式撤销
Your Honor, I am formally withdrawing my request

654
00:27:27,550 --> 00:27:28,890
审查他们文件的请求
to go through their files.

655
00:27:28,890 --> 00:27:30,530
那我们在这儿干嘛
Then, why are we all here?

656
00:27:30,830 --> 00:27:32,610
我希望法庭记录在案
Because I want it to be on the record

657
00:27:32,620 --> 00:27:34,520
洛根·桑德斯请我代表他
that Logan Sanders requests The release 

658
00:27:34,520 --> 00:27:38,970
要求公开这两位之间的所有对话
of all communications between these two gentlemen on his behalf.

659
00:27:38,970 --> 00:27:40,450
-什么  -你听见了
- What? - You heard me.

660
00:27:40,450 --> 00:27:43,290
法官大人  我们怎么知道签名不是伪造的
Your Honor, how do we know that signature isn't fabricated?

661
00:27:43,730 --> 00:27:44,760
请
Go ahead.

662
00:27:44,800 --> 00:27:46,360
给桑德斯先生打个电话
Give Mr. Sanders a call.

663
00:27:46,560 --> 00:27:47,850
他会告诉你这是真的
He'll tell you it's true.

664
00:27:50,340 --> 00:27:52,120
因为他和你不同  他可是很乐意
Because unlike you, he was more than happy

665
00:27:52,120 --> 00:27:54,780
在申请上签字来换取豁免的
to sign the request in exchange for immunity.

666
00:27:56,960 --> 00:27:59,660
一旦签字被核实
Pending verification of this signature,

667
00:28:00,220 --> 00:28:03,420
你们必须立刻提供他所要的一切资料
you are to give him everything he asks for immediately.

668
00:28:04,270 --> 00:28:05,350
法官大人
Your Honor.

669
00:28:07,480 --> 00:28:09,730
告诉过你  我迟早会拿到那些文件的
I told you I'd get those files sooner or later.

670
00:28:10,250 --> 00:28:11,630
看来很快就能拿到了
Guess it's gonna be sooner.

671
00:28:20,610 --> 00:28:21,230
这是什么
What's that?

672
00:28:21,230 --> 00:28:23,610
五十种阻止肖恩·卡荷尔的办法
It's 50 different ways we can stop Sean Cahill in his tracks.

673
00:28:23,620 --> 00:28:25,110
-你为什么  -告诉过你了
- Why did you-- - I told you.

674
00:28:25,110 --> 00:28:27,460
攻击我们中的一个就是攻击我们所有人
An attack on one of us is an attack on all of us.

675
00:28:27,460 --> 00:28:29,750
哈维是我兄弟  如果卡荷尔找他麻烦
Harvey is my brother, and if Cahill's coming after him,

676
00:28:29,750 --> 00:28:32,080
-就是找我麻烦  -路易  没用的
- he is coming after me. - Louis, it doesn't matter.

677
00:28:32,080 --> 00:28:33,330
我们什么也做不了
There's nothing we can do about it.

678
00:28:33,330 --> 00:28:34,710
什么叫我们什么都做不了
What do you mean there's nothing we can do about it?

679
00:28:34,710 --> 00:28:36,270
洛根·桑德斯和卡荷尔达成了协议
Logan Sanders cut a deal with Cahill.

680
00:28:36,280 --> 00:28:38,170
我们必须公开我和哈维
We have to release all communications

681
00:28:38,170 --> 00:28:40,000
关于吉利斯工业的所有谈话
between me and Harvey on Gillis.

682
00:28:40,760 --> 00:28:42,260
只是你和哈维之间  就这样吗
Just between you and Harvey? That's it?

683
00:28:42,270 --> 00:28:43,300
没有傅滋曼的部分吗
None of the Forstman stuff?

684
00:28:43,300 --> 00:28:44,360
就这些
That's it.

685
00:28:44,770 --> 00:28:45,980
太好了  我们没问题了
Thank god. We're in the clear.

686
00:28:45,980 --> 00:28:48,140
路易  一秒前你才说攻击哈维
Louis, one second ago, you said that an attack on Harvey

687
00:28:48,140 --> 00:28:49,420
-就是攻击你  -是是是
- was an attack on you. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.

688
00:28:49,420 --> 00:28:50,590
但你说我们什么也做不了
And you just said there's nothing we can do about it.

689
00:28:50,590 --> 00:28:52,330
但这并不是件好事呀
But that doesn't make it a good thing.

690
00:28:52,580 --> 00:28:53,960
-不是吗  -你到底...
- Doesn't it? - What are you--

691
00:28:53,960 --> 00:28:55,850
迈克  你有没有和哈维串通
Mike, did you collude with Harvey or not?

692
00:28:56,060 --> 00:28:57,870
-当然没有  -我就是这个意思
- Of course I didn't. - That's exactly my point,

693
00:28:57,870 --> 00:28:59,930
在我看来  问题已经解决了
so as far as I'm concerned, this matter is done.

694
00:29:12,070 --> 00:29:12,920
猜这是什么
Guess what this is?

695
00:29:12,920 --> 00:29:14,930
路易  我不是星际迷航的粉丝
Louis, I was never really a Star Trek fan.

696
00:29:14,930 --> 00:29:17,320
这是一个幸福者的安静心率
It's the resting heart rate of a happy man.

697
00:29:19,260 --> 00:29:20,270
事情结束了吗
it's over?

698
00:29:20,710 --> 00:29:22,400
我们要给他们文件
We're sending them files,

699
00:29:22,400 --> 00:29:24,840
但不是我们的文件
but we're not sending them our files.

700
00:29:25,150 --> 00:29:26,180
我不明白
I don't understand.

701
00:29:26,180 --> 00:29:28,980
洛根·桑德斯签了个协议
Logan Sanders signed a deal,

702
00:29:29,330 --> 00:29:30,990
等等等等
blah, blah, blah.

703
00:29:31,160 --> 00:29:33,420
他们不会拿到傅滋曼的文件
They're not getting the Forstman document.

704
00:29:34,180 --> 00:29:36,120
这就结束了吗
And that's the end?

705
00:29:36,120 --> 00:29:38,550
-结束了  -恭喜你  路易
- That's the end. - Congratulations, Louis.

706
00:29:38,620 --> 00:29:39,830
谢谢  卡特里娜
Thank you, Katrina.

707
00:29:43,060 --> 00:29:44,120
不如这样
You know what,

708
00:29:44,420 --> 00:29:45,620
我们现在就下班
why don't take the rest of the day off and check out

709
00:29:45,630 --> 00:29:46,440
去看我之前跟你说的
that Mummenschanz retrospective 

710
00:29:46,440 --> 00:29:47,430
魔力无极限默剧团经典回顾
I've been telling you about.

711
00:29:47,430 --> 00:29:50,170
谢谢  路易  不过我可能会做点别的
Thank you, Louis, though I may do something else.

712
00:29:50,170 --> 00:29:51,330
随你便  不过我可告诉你
Suit yourself, but I'm telling you right now.

713
00:29:51,330 --> 00:29:52,390
表演棒极了
It's a game changer.

714
00:29:53,260 --> 00:29:54,270
他们...
They--

715
00:30:02,690 --> 00:30:05,200
这么说洛根·桑德斯放弃了保密特权
Am I to understand Logan Sanders waived privilege?

716
00:30:05,200 --> 00:30:07,240
-没错  他有这个权利  -该死  哈维
- Yeah, it's his right. - Goddamn it, Harvey.

717
00:30:07,240 --> 00:30:09,650
你就不该放弃他这个客户
You never should have cut that man loose as a client.

718
00:30:09,650 --> 00:30:11,130
我放弃他是因为我知道
Well, I cut him loose because I knew

719
00:30:11,130 --> 00:30:13,450
他会有之前那样的行为
he was the kind of person who would do what he just did.

720
00:30:13,450 --> 00:30:15,070
扯淡  你放弃他
bullshit. You cut him loose

721
00:30:15,070 --> 00:30:17,100
因为你知道迈克·罗斯要回来工作了
because you knew Mike Ross was coming back here.

722
00:30:17,100 --> 00:30:17,800
一点没错
Well, you're damn right I did.

723
00:30:17,800 --> 00:30:19,720
我可不会为此道歉
I'm not gonna apologize for it.

724
00:30:19,720 --> 00:30:21,630
你应该先跟我商量
You should have discussed it with me first.

725
00:30:21,630 --> 00:30:24,880
请求原谅比要求许可容易多了
Well, it's easier to ask for forgiveness than permission.

726
00:30:24,880 --> 00:30:26,380
原谅
Forgiveness?

727
00:30:26,580 --> 00:30:28,520
你刚说你不会为此道歉
You just said you're not going to apologize for it.

728
00:30:28,520 --> 00:30:29,860
是不会
You know what? I'm not,

729
00:30:29,860 --> 00:30:31,190
我可不想听
because I don't want to hear a lecture

730
00:30:31,190 --> 00:30:33,230
他的公司带来的收益的长篇大论
on the amount of billings his company brought in.

731
00:30:33,230 --> 00:30:36,470
你指过去二十年来的两千万收益
You mean the $20 million going back over two decades.

732
00:30:36,470 --> 00:30:38,380
盈利一亿我也不在乎
I don't give a shit if it's $100 million.

733
00:30:38,380 --> 00:30:40,660
你要是想跟我辩论该留什么样的客户
You want to have it out over which clients we keep,

734
00:30:40,660 --> 00:30:41,830
我奉陪到底
I'm happy to.

735
00:30:41,830 --> 00:30:43,590
但这次我做了决定
But in this case, I made a call,

736
00:30:43,590 --> 00:30:45,080
挺不挺我  随便你
and you're either gonna back me or you're not.

737
00:30:45,080 --> 00:30:46,540
不能再打下去了
We need to stop fighting.

738
00:30:46,700 --> 00:30:47,740
什么
Excuse me?

739
00:30:47,770 --> 00:30:49,360
-我们没打  -就是在打
- We're not fighting. - Yes, we are.

740
00:30:49,360 --> 00:30:50,910
我说的不是你俩
I'm not talking about you two.

741
00:30:50,920 --> 00:30:53,150
那你说的是什么
Then what the hell are you talking about?

742
00:30:53,150 --> 00:30:54,240
卡荷尔
Cahill.

743
00:30:54,810 --> 00:30:55,930
你要我们让步吗
You want us to give in?

744
00:30:55,930 --> 00:30:59,250
不  他想要全部文件
No. I'm saying he wants all the files,

745
00:30:59,560 --> 00:31:01,010
那就都给他
let's give him all the files.

746
00:31:19,960 --> 00:31:20,970
瑞秋  你来这儿做什么
Rachel, what are you doing here?

747
00:31:20,970 --> 00:31:22,530
我说了我需要时间
I told you needed some time.

748
00:31:22,530 --> 00:31:25,170
你还说你得努力忘掉
And then you told me that you needed to get that image 

749
00:31:25,170 --> 00:31:26,000
那幅画面
out of your head. 

750
00:31:26,000 --> 00:31:30,090
-所以我需要...  -不  不会的
- Which is why I need-- - No. No, it isn't.

751
00:31:30,710 --> 00:31:34,500
因为你永远忘不掉那幅画面
Because you'll never completely get it out of your head.

752
00:31:36,700 --> 00:31:39,390
-苔丝  -没错  苔丝
- Tess. - Yes, Tess.

753
00:31:40,920 --> 00:31:43,480
我那可不是想象出来的
And my image isn't made up, and... 

754
00:31:45,120 --> 00:31:47,300
也不是两个人在接吻
it wasn't of two people kissing.

755
00:31:47,650 --> 00:31:50,610
但我就算忘不掉也释怀了  因为...
But I got over it without getting rid of it because 

756
00:31:50,740 --> 00:31:52,870
原谅靠的不是遗忘
forgiveness doesn't work that way.

757
00:31:53,620 --> 00:31:55,290
你知道我对他的感觉
You knew how I felt about him.

758
00:31:58,660 --> 00:32:01,230
你知道我会怎么想  可你还是做了
You knew what it would do to me, and you did it anyway.

759
00:32:01,230 --> 00:32:05,030
我说了  我犯了个错误
And I told you I made a mistake.

760
00:32:06,400 --> 00:32:07,880
你想让我怎么做  瑞秋
What do you want from me, Rachel?

761
00:32:10,810 --> 00:32:12,310
我想让你决定
I want you to decide

762
00:32:12,310 --> 00:32:16,250
你对我的爱和对我行为的厌恶  哪个更深
if you love me more than you hate what I did.

763
00:32:17,490 --> 00:32:18,770
如果你恨我
And if you don't,

764
00:32:21,950 --> 00:32:23,580
我希望你亲口说分手
then I want you to tell me that it's over.

765
00:32:23,580 --> 00:32:24,990
如果你爱我
And if you do, 

766
00:32:26,200 --> 00:32:28,630
我希望你回家
then I want you to come home.

767
00:32:51,810 --> 00:32:52,940
下午好  肖恩
Afternoon, Sean.

768
00:32:53,220 --> 00:32:54,400
你一直在输
Well, you're in a good mood for a man 

769
00:32:54,410 --> 00:32:55,780
心情倒是不错
who keeps getting his ass kicked.

770
00:32:55,780 --> 00:32:58,350
有些时候  人们会厌倦争斗
Well, at a certain point, you get tired of fighting.

771
00:32:58,350 --> 00:32:59,400
我可不知道
Well, I wouldn't know,

772
00:32:59,400 --> 00:33:00,670
但这事结束后  我们倒是可以去喝一杯
but after this, we can grab a beer,

773
00:33:00,670 --> 00:33:02,530
你可以给我讲讲失败的滋味
and you can tell me what it's like to be a loser.

774
00:33:04,560 --> 00:33:05,640
法官大人
Your Honor.

775
00:33:05,940 --> 00:33:07,110
斯佩克特先生
Mr. Specter,

776
00:33:07,110 --> 00:33:09,990
你最好是来上交你客户的文件的
you better be here to hand over your clients files.

777
00:33:10,090 --> 00:33:11,990
我要做的不仅如此
I'm here to do more than that.

778
00:33:11,990 --> 00:33:14,500
我们要交出吉利斯工业
We're handing over all of the files

779
00:33:14,570 --> 00:33:16,300
收购案的全部文件
in the Gillis Industries takeover,

780
00:33:16,300 --> 00:33:19,400
但我希望法庭将全部文件登记在案
but I want the court to catalog every piece of paper in there

781
00:33:19,400 --> 00:33:21,840
以免肖恩"找到"什么
so Sean doesn't "Find one" 

782
00:33:21,840 --> 00:33:23,550
本不存在的文件
that was never there in the first place.

783
00:33:23,550 --> 00:33:27,180
你们从第一天开始  争论的不就是这事吗
Isn't this what you were arguing against from day one?

784
00:33:27,180 --> 00:33:29,940
我们改主意了  因为没什么好遮掩的
We changed our minds because we have nothing to hide.

785
00:33:29,940 --> 00:33:31,700
不  这是他的策略
No, no. This is a ploy.

786
00:33:31,700 --> 00:33:34,260
他是想证明我们拿到了全部文件
He's trying to get me on record stating that we have everything,

787
00:33:34,260 --> 00:33:35,950
如果我一无所获
and if I find nothing,

788
00:33:35,950 --> 00:33:38,250
他会以诬告起诉我
he's gonna file malicious prosecution charges.

789
00:33:38,250 --> 00:33:39,450
事实上  肖恩
Actually, Sean,

790
00:33:39,450 --> 00:33:41,680
我现在就要以诬告起诉你
I'm filing those charges right now.

791
00:33:41,680 --> 00:33:44,370
如果你在要求的文件中
And when you don't find anything in the contents

792
00:33:44,370 --> 00:33:45,860
找不到我们的把柄
of everything you ever asked for,

793
00:33:45,860 --> 00:33:48,130
这次扯淡的搜查就成了你诬告的头条证据
this bullshit search becomes Exhibit A.

794
00:33:48,130 --> 00:33:50,660
法官大人  他的起诉毫无根据
Your honor, he has no basis to file that action.

795
00:33:50,660 --> 00:33:52,380
这是你两天前来我这里
I can't stop the man from giving you

796
00:33:52,380 --> 00:33:56,300
要求的东西  我不能阻止他给你
exactly what you were in here asking me for two days ago.

797
00:33:56,510 --> 00:33:58,600
你到底要不要冒着
Now, are you gonna proceed under threat

798
00:33:58,600 --> 00:34:01,460
被控诬告的风险继续调查
the malicious prosecution or not?

799
00:34:03,380 --> 00:34:04,780
怎么了  肖恩
What's the matter, Sean?

800
00:34:04,780 --> 00:34:06,680
你怕你什么都找不到吗
Afraid you won't find anything?

801
00:34:06,980 --> 00:34:08,520
把文件给我
Just give me the files.

802
00:34:12,600 --> 00:34:13,850
你想见我吗
You wanted to see me?

803
00:34:14,940 --> 00:34:17,130
既然有功  就该嘉奖
I wanted to give credit where credit is due.

804
00:34:18,840 --> 00:34:19,820
卡荷尔上钩了
Cahill went for it.

805
00:34:19,820 --> 00:34:21,110
没错
Yes,

806
00:34:21,570 --> 00:34:24,520
等他一无所获  我们就摆脱他了
and when he finds nothing, we'll be done with him.

807
00:34:25,120 --> 00:34:26,330
做得不错
Good job.

808
00:34:26,330 --> 00:34:27,600
谢谢
Thank you.

809
00:34:29,710 --> 00:34:31,440
也谢谢你让我回来
And thank you for taking me back,

810
00:34:32,610 --> 00:34:34,360
我知道你不想让我回来
especially since I know you didn't want to.

811
00:34:34,360 --> 00:34:36,500
如果你是我  你愿意吗
Would you have wanted to if you were me?

812
00:34:36,500 --> 00:34:38,640
可我想出了补救事情的办法
I did just come up with that fix.

813
00:34:38,860 --> 00:34:42,870
解决卡荷尔抓你和哈维串通的把柄的事吗
A fix for Cahill coming after you for colluding with Harvey?

814
00:34:44,080 --> 00:34:45,210
如果我没遇见你
A problem I never would have had

815
00:34:45,210 --> 00:34:46,830
就根本不会有这样的问题
if I'd never met you.

816
00:34:49,260 --> 00:34:50,800
你叫我下来干什么
Why'd you call me down here?

817
00:34:50,800 --> 00:34:53,000
我想知道你到底为什么回来
I want to know why the hell you came back.

818
00:34:56,280 --> 00:34:57,950
有趣的是  如果你今早问我这个
You know, it's funny. If you'd asked me that this morning,

819
00:34:57,950 --> 00:35:00,340
我会说因为我没别处可去
I would have said because I had no place else to go.

820
00:35:00,340 --> 00:35:02,280
我今早没问你
I didn't ask you this morning.

821
00:35:02,570 --> 00:35:03,960
我是现在在问你
I'm asking you now.

822
00:35:05,790 --> 00:35:08,180
那我为什么回来就不重要了
Then it doesn't matter why I came back.

823
00:35:09,950 --> 00:35:11,890
重要的是我会留下来
What matters is that I'm staying

824
00:35:13,080 --> 00:35:14,850
因为我就属于这里
because this is where I belong.

825
00:35:25,270 --> 00:35:27,310
我正要找你
Hey, just the person I was looking for.

826
00:35:27,680 --> 00:35:28,390
你听说了
You heard? 

827
00:35:28,390 --> 00:35:29,740
我只知道
I heard that I just

828
00:35:29,740 --> 00:35:30,880
我刚刚定了一张去波士顿的机票
booked a plane ticket to Boston

829
00:35:30,890 --> 00:35:31,780
给希拉一个惊喜
to surprise Sheila,

830
00:35:31,780 --> 00:35:33,570
明天的麦克贝听证会就交给你了
and I need you to cover the McBain hearing tomorrow.

831
00:35:33,570 --> 00:35:38,160
路易  麦克贝的听证会已经算不上事了
Louis, the McBain hearing is the least of our worries.

832
00:35:38,160 --> 00:35:39,410
什么意思
What do you mean?

833
00:35:39,790 --> 00:35:41,230
今早哈维去了法院
Harvey went to court this morning

834
00:35:41,230 --> 00:35:42,800
同意交出一切
and agreed to hand over 

835
00:35:42,800 --> 00:35:45,410
关于吉利斯收购的文件
every single document on the Gillis takeover,

836
00:35:45,410 --> 00:35:46,910
包括傅滋曼的文件
including Forstman.

837
00:35:46,910 --> 00:35:49,380
什么  为什么...
What? Why would--

838
00:35:49,380 --> 00:35:52,220
因为他觉得我们没什么需要遮掩的
Because he thinks we have nothing to hide.

839
00:35:52,960 --> 00:35:57,010
该死  那我带着手铐
Shit. Then it's only a matter of time

840
00:35:57,010 --> 00:35:58,490
被警察带走只是时间问题了
before I'm marched out of here in handcuffs.

841
00:35:58,490 --> 00:35:59,640
我不会让事情发展到那一步的
I'm not gonna let it come to that.

842
00:35:59,640 --> 00:36:01,400
你能有什么办法阻止
Oh, how the hell are you gonna stop it?

843
00:36:01,400 --> 00:36:04,160
狸猫换太子
By replacing one document with another.

844
00:36:05,420 --> 00:36:07,290
我不会陷害哈维的
I am not framing Harvey.

845
00:36:07,330 --> 00:36:09,650
这不是陷害哈维
This isn't framing Harvey.

846
00:36:10,200 --> 00:36:12,720
-而是在拯救你  -什么意思
- It's freeing you. - What are you talking about?

847
00:36:12,720 --> 00:36:14,430
这份文件会表明傅滋曼的付款
This makes it look like Forstman's payment never

848
00:36:14,430 --> 00:36:16,290
从未经过任何离岸账户
went to any offshore accounts

849
00:36:16,460 --> 00:36:17,910
而且跟你毫无关系
and that you never took a piece of it.

850
00:36:17,910 --> 00:36:19,430
这可是伪造
No, that's forgery.

851
00:36:20,780 --> 00:36:23,610
那也比你犯下的罪行要轻
Which is less of a crime than what you did.

852
00:36:26,500 --> 00:36:28,010
我没让你做这些
I didn't ask you to do this.

853
00:36:28,010 --> 00:36:29,490
那就别用
Then don't use it,

854
00:36:30,630 --> 00:36:32,940
但你也说了  要是交出那些文件
but you're the one who said that if we give them those files,

855
00:36:32,940 --> 00:36:34,560
被抓只是时间问题
it's only a matter of time.

856
00:36:35,050 --> 00:36:38,950
路易  卡荷尔想抓的是哈维和迈克的把柄
Louis, Cahill's looking for dirt on Harvey and Mike,

857
00:36:38,950 --> 00:36:40,650
跟你和傅滋曼无关
not you and Forstman.

858
00:36:41,010 --> 00:36:42,650
他都不会多看一眼的
He won't even give this a second glance.

859
00:36:42,650 --> 00:36:44,450
但要是他注意到了  就把哈维推到火坑里了
But if he does, it puts Harvey in jeopardy,

860
00:36:44,450 --> 00:36:47,620
还是像傅滋曼希望的一样陷害了他
and I might as well frame him just like Forstman wanted me to.

861
00:36:49,370 --> 00:36:50,620
那你可要好好做个决定了
Then you have a decision to make

862
00:36:50,950 --> 00:36:53,680
因为明天一早就会上交文件了
because they're turning everything over first thing tomorrow.

863
00:37:11,590 --> 00:37:13,440
路易  没事吧
Louis, is everything okay?

864
00:37:15,960 --> 00:37:18,110
没事  迈克
Yeah, everything's fine, Mike.

865
00:37:30,620 --> 00:37:31,940
唐娜
Donna?

866
00:37:32,800 --> 00:37:34,220
需要我做什么  哈维
What can I do for you, Harvey?

867
00:37:34,320 --> 00:37:36,300
明天要上交的文件都准备好了吗
Everything taken care of for the file transfer tomorrow?

868
00:37:36,300 --> 00:37:38,560
二十分钟前就准备好了
It was taken care of 20 minutes before you asked for it.

869
00:37:38,560 --> 00:37:40,750
好  这些是霍华德  米勒和克莱恩的文件
Great. Here's Howard, Miller, and Klein.

870
00:37:40,750 --> 00:37:42,290
我现在就想要看看
I'd like to get a jump on these right now.

871
00:37:42,290 --> 00:37:44,260
已经很晚了  哈维  今天已经够忙了
Oh, it's late, Harvey. We've had a long day.

872
00:37:44,260 --> 00:37:45,740
-不如我们...  -来吧
- Maybe we can just-- - Come on.

873
00:37:45,740 --> 00:37:48,220
我们可以点你爱的那家破烂泰餐店的外卖
We can order from that shity Thai place you love.

874
00:37:48,220 --> 00:37:49,740
两小时把这些搞定
Knock this out in two hours.

875
00:37:49,740 --> 00:37:53,400
-这是命令还是请求  -什么意...
- Is that an order or a request? - What are you--

876
00:37:53,400 --> 00:37:54,910
我今晚有约  哈维
I have a date tonight, Harvey,

877
00:37:54,910 --> 00:37:56,440
所以除非你觉得我们保不住
So unless you think we're gonna lose

878
00:37:56,440 --> 00:37:58,130
霍华德  米勒和克莱恩了
Howard, Miller, or Klein,

879
00:37:58,130 --> 00:37:59,480
我就下班了
I'm leaving.

880
00:38:02,510 --> 00:38:03,910
今晚好好玩
Have a good night.

881
00:38:04,320 --> 00:38:05,650
谢谢  哈维
Thanks, Harvey.

882
00:38:07,480 --> 00:38:09,620
-别忘了保护措施...  -就此打住
- Don't forget to use protection-- - Stop right there.

883
00:38:09,620 --> 00:38:11,500
怎么我跟别人出去的时候
Oh, so when I go out with someone,

884
00:38:11,500 --> 00:38:12,640
你就可以给我乱七八糟的建议
you can give me all the shit in the world,

885
00:38:12,650 --> 00:38:15,580
-轮到你...  -没错  就是这么回事
- but when you do-- - Yep. That's exactly how it works.

886
00:38:15,870 --> 00:38:17,260
自己习惯去吧
Get used to it.

887
00:38:20,840 --> 00:38:22,850
你又怎么了  跟撞鬼了似的
What's wrong with you? You look like you just saw a ghost.

888
00:38:22,850 --> 00:38:24,240
差不多
I feel like I did.

889
00:38:24,470 --> 00:38:26,330
-我们好像有麻烦了  -什么意思
- I think we have a problem. - What do you mean?

890
00:38:26,330 --> 00:38:27,410
我们终于为摆脱
We just took step number one

891
00:38:27,410 --> 00:38:29,280
卡荷尔这个破事迈出了一步
to finally putting this Cahill bullshit behind us.

892
00:38:29,280 --> 00:38:31,830
我正要说这个  我们好像没摆脱掉它
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I don't think it is behind us.

893
00:38:31,830 --> 00:38:34,390
-什么意思  -我不知道路易做了什么
- What? - I don't know what Louis did,

894
00:38:34,390 --> 00:38:35,930
但他好像做错事了
but I think he did something wrong.

895
00:38:35,930 --> 00:38:37,090
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?

896
00:38:37,090 --> 00:38:39,550
他昨天来找我的时候  还咬牙切齿地
When he came to me yesterday, he was chomping at the bit

897
00:38:39,550 --> 00:38:41,500
-要帮忙对付卡荷尔呢  -路易不就这样吗
- to help fight Cahill. - That's Louis.

898
00:38:41,500 --> 00:38:43,220
为这家律所他可是奋不顾身
He'd take a bullet for this firm, you know that.

899
00:38:43,220 --> 00:38:44,890
那当我告诉他洛根只会交出
Then why did he immediately change his tune

900
00:38:44,890 --> 00:38:46,620
我方的通讯记录时
after I told him that 

901
00:38:46,620 --> 00:38:48,570
就突然改变态度了呢
Logan was only releasing our communications?

902
00:38:48,870 --> 00:38:49,920
他松了一口气吗
He seemed relieved?

903
00:38:49,920 --> 00:38:51,420
他乐疯了
He seemed ecstatic,

904
00:38:51,420 --> 00:38:51,950
而在此之前
And before that,

905
00:38:51,950 --> 00:38:53,940
在他发现我们是为了对付卡荷尔之前
he was pissed that I was working on your stuff

906
00:38:53,940 --> 00:38:56,290
他对我帮你忙这件事十分生气
until he found out it was to fight Cahill.

907
00:38:56,610 --> 00:38:58,750
你觉得他究竟做了什么
What exactly are you thinking he might have done?

908
00:38:58,750 --> 00:39:00,210
具体的我也不知道
I don't know exactly,

909
00:39:00,210 --> 00:39:04,100
但我觉得他应该是跟傅滋曼达成了什么协议
but I think he cut some sort of deal with Forstman.

910
00:39:04,100 --> 00:39:05,170
他的确跟傅滋曼达成协议了啊
He did cut a deal with Forstman.

911
00:39:05,170 --> 00:39:07,300
我指的是非法协议
I'm talking about an illegal deal.

912
00:39:07,460 --> 00:39:09,100
迈克  我知道傅滋曼很狡猾
Mike, I know Forstman's a snake,

913
00:39:09,100 --> 00:39:10,960
但我们说的可是路易
but this is Louis you're talking about.

914
00:39:10,960 --> 00:39:13,530
但你没看见他让我回来工作时的样子
I know, but you weren't there when he made me that offer.

915
00:39:13,530 --> 00:39:15,230
我从没见过他那样
I'd never seen him like that.

916
00:39:15,260 --> 00:39:18,350
他想方设法不让我为"那个人"工作
He was desperate to keep me from working for "That man."

917
00:39:18,350 --> 00:39:19,530
-迈克  -更重要的是
- Mike-- - And then on top of that,

918
00:39:19,530 --> 00:39:22,160
我又了解到他为了让我回来放弃了什么
I found out what he gave up to get me back here.

919
00:39:22,160 --> 00:39:23,450
希拉
Sheila.

920
00:39:24,860 --> 00:39:28,160
但他既然不关心我们的通讯记录
But why would he care about us handling over everything

921
00:39:28,160 --> 00:39:31,080
为什么又对交出所有文件耿耿于怀
if he didn't care about the communications between us?

922
00:39:31,990 --> 00:39:33,930
因为如果他真的跟傅滋曼达成了非法协议
Because if he did make a dirty deal with Forstman,

923
00:39:33,930 --> 00:39:35,630
证据不会在那些文件里
It wouldn't have been in those documents.

924
00:39:35,630 --> 00:39:37,740
而会在其他的文件当中
It would have been in the other documents.

925
00:39:39,090 --> 00:39:40,940
那些我们刚刚答应法院
The documents we just told the court

926
00:39:40,940 --> 00:39:42,640
愿意上交的文件里
we're happy to turn over.

927
00:39:43,570 --> 00:39:44,650
你想做什么
What are you gonna do?

928
00:39:44,650 --> 00:39:47,020
我要去查出路易究竟做了什么
I'm gonna find out what the hell Louis did.

929
00:39:50,350 --> 00:39:51,670
回家吧  迈克
Go home, Mike.

930
00:39:52,170 --> 00:39:53,730
你今晚什么也没法做
There's nothing you can do tonight.

931
00:41:58,310 --> 00:41:59,920
我犯了个大错
I made a huge mistake.

