1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:01,400
《訴訟雙雄》前情提要

2
00:00:01,400 --> 00:00:02,980
我和你爸可是同一戰壕里的
I'm bonding with your father here.

3
00:00:02,980 --> 00:00:03,970
說到這
Speaking of which--

4
00:00:03,970 --> 00:00:05,260
你是不會手下留情的吧
You're not taking it easy on me, are you?

5
00:00:05,260 --> 00:00:06,040
差不多吧
A little.

6
00:00:06,040 --> 00:00:07,960
你對我來說很重要
You mean something to me.

7
00:00:08,140 --> 00:00:09,600
一直都是
You've always meant something to me,

8
00:00:09,600 --> 00:00:12,000
以后也會是
and you always will mean something to me.

9
00:00:12,700 --> 00:00:14,250
你需要我幫你什么  哈維
What do you need, Harvey?

10
00:00:14,880 --> 00:00:16,110
艾娃·海辛頓
Ava Hessington.

11
00:00:16,110 --> 00:00:18,200
我不會輸給他的
I am not losing to him.

12
00:00:18,200 --> 00:00:20,830
你  跟你的夙仇
You...your blood feud

13
00:00:20,830 --> 00:00:23,150
我不知道你們之間有什么過節
or whatever it is you have with that man

14
00:00:23,150 --> 00:00:25,650
但我成了頭號受害者
is what put the target on my back in the first place.

15
00:00:25,650 --> 00:00:28,750
我留下的爛攤子  理應由我收拾
I made this mess. It's up to me to clear it up.

16
00:00:29,260 --> 00:00:31,470
哈維和卡梅隆達成協議要拿下你
Harvey and Cameron made a deal to take you down,

17
00:00:31,470 --> 00:00:32,840
協議的一部分就是
and part of that deal was that

18
00:00:32,840 --> 00:00:35,060
這一切必須由我來告訴你
I got to be the one to tell you about it.

19
00:00:35,060 --> 00:00:36,850
如果他沒有獲得本國的律師執業許可
And if he can't practice law in the country,

20
00:00:36,850 --> 00:00:38,620
他就不能在我們公司就職
he can't be a member of our firm.

21
00:00:38,620 --> 00:00:40,020
這一切都是你一手操辦的
You set this whole thing up.

22
00:00:40,030 --> 00:00:41,970
是杰西卡一手操辦的
Jessica set this whole thing up.

23
00:00:42,010 --> 00:00:42,910
另外  愛德華
And, Edward...

24
00:00:42,910 --> 00:00:44,410
看來我們得"離婚"了
we may be getting a divorce,

25
00:00:44,410 --> 00:00:47,420
但我還是打算保留房子的所有權
but I fully intend on keeping ownership of the house.

26
00:01:01,790 --> 00:01:03,660
拜托  我要早起不代表
Oh, come on, just because I have to wake up early

27
00:01:03,660 --> 00:01:05,250
你也要跟著受罪啊
doesn't mean you should suffer.

28
00:01:05,250 --> 00:01:06,240
聽說有這么個說法
Well, you know what they say.

29
00:01:06,240 --> 00:01:08,190
一起醒來的伴侶...
The couple that wakes together...

30
00:01:09,850 --> 00:01:11,130
是一起做早點的情侶
Bakes together?

31
00:01:11,130 --> 00:01:13,900
-長相廝守  -都不押韻
- Stays together. - Yeah, that doesn't rhyme.

32
00:01:14,080 --> 00:01:15,310
你真討厭
You're ridiculous.

33
00:01:18,840 --> 00:01:20,580
天吶  太好喝了
Oh, my God. That's amazing.

34
00:01:21,030 --> 00:01:21,990
我知道
I know.

35
00:01:22,650 --> 00:01:23,730
你真厲害
You're amazing.

36
00:01:23,840 --> 00:01:24,850
我知道
I know.

37
00:01:32,060 --> 00:01:34,420
你壓根沒想放我去上班  對吧
You have no intention of letting me go to work, do you?

38
00:01:34,420 --> 00:01:38,320
從前  楠塔基特島有個女孩
There once was a girl from Nantucket.

39
00:01:39,440 --> 00:01:41,180
我愛你
I love you.

40
00:01:41,740 --> 00:01:43,270
這話也不押韻哦
Oh, that doesn't rhyme, you know?

41
00:01:43,270 --> 00:01:44,930
怎么  你現在是押韻警察了嗎
What are you, the rhyming police now?

42
00:01:44,930 --> 00:01:47,120
-你先開始的  -那就由我結束
- You started it. - And I'm gonna finish it.

43
00:01:47,120 --> 00:01:48,590
我也愛你
I love you too.

44
00:02:00,730 --> 00:02:02,470
你比昨晚還開心
You look happier than you did last night.

45
00:02:02,480 --> 00:02:03,380
是的
I am.

46
00:02:06,320 --> 00:02:07,610
你來干什么
What are you doing here?

47
00:02:07,610 --> 00:02:09,030
載你一程
I was thinking I'd give you a ride.

48
00:02:09,450 --> 00:02:10,780
你昨晚才送過我
You just gave me a ride last night.

49
00:02:10,780 --> 00:02:12,390
這次我要跟你一起坐車
Yeah, this time I thought I'd join you.

50
00:02:13,090 --> 00:02:15,580
哈維  我們一天有十五個小時
Harvey, we put in 15-hour days

51
00:02:15,580 --> 00:02:16,560
離對方只有十二英尺[3.6米]
12 feet from each other.

52
00:02:16,560 --> 00:02:18,090
真的還要一起去上班嗎
You really want to go to work together?

53
00:02:18,200 --> 00:02:19,740
誰說要去上班了
Who said anything about work?

54
00:02:19,970 --> 00:02:21,350
我們去紐格汀吃早餐
We have breakfast at Nougatine

55
00:02:21,350 --> 00:02:23,660
再去愛馬仕看看
and an excursion to Hermes that may or may not

56
00:02:23,660 --> 00:02:25,040
有沒有新進什么手包
involve a new handbag.

57
00:02:26,150 --> 00:02:27,580
你一直在換新手包
You've been needing a new handbag.

58
00:02:27,580 --> 00:02:29,370
手包這種東西怎么都不嫌多
You can never have too many handbags.

59
00:02:29,380 --> 00:02:30,780
你真是我志趣相投的好閨蜜
You're a woman after my own heart.

60
00:02:30,790 --> 00:02:32,030
這樣的話...
Well, in that case...

61
00:02:35,690 --> 00:02:39,410
哈維  你為什么要這么做
Harvey... why are you doing this?

62
00:02:40,510 --> 00:02:42,230
唐娜  最近發生了很多事
Donna, we've all been through a lot.

63
00:02:42,710 --> 00:02:44,210
我們應該小小慶祝一番
We deserve a little celebration.

64
00:02:45,520 --> 00:02:48,000
你前段日子的確很煎熬
Well, in that case, you have had it pretty rough.

65
00:02:49,010 --> 00:02:51,040
買一個手包可不夠
We're gonna need to get you more than one handbag.

66
00:02:51,190 --> 00:02:52,830
必須的
I wouldn't have it any other way.

67
00:03:06,650 --> 00:03:07,770
杰西卡
Jessica.

68
00:03:08,400 --> 00:03:10,690
路易  有什么能幫你的嗎
Louis, what can I do for you?

69
00:03:10,920 --> 00:03:12,350
我不是為我自己來的
Actually, I'm not here about me.

70
00:03:12,350 --> 00:03:13,230
是為了你
I'm here about you.

71
00:03:13,230 --> 00:03:14,240
怎么說
How so?

72
00:03:20,660 --> 00:03:22,140
我想處理律所的解散合并案
I want to handle the dissolution.

73
00:03:22,590 --> 00:03:23,740
那你的確是為你自己來的
So this is about you.

74
00:03:23,740 --> 00:03:25,450
不  杰西卡
No. Jessica...

75
00:03:26,750 --> 00:03:28,540
你要幫艾娃脫罪  我就幫她脫罪
I got Ava out when you wanted her out.

76
00:03:28,920 --> 00:03:30,670
我證明了我會不惜一切代價
I proved that I will do whatever it takes.

77
00:03:30,670 --> 00:03:33,300
而且我知道達比的資源
And what's more, I know Darby's assets,

78
00:03:33,300 --> 00:03:35,230
你要的我都能幫你拿到
and I will get you everything that you have coming.

79
00:03:35,230 --> 00:03:36,800
我要的我自己都能拿到
I can get everything I have coming.

80
00:03:36,800 --> 00:03:38,680
也許吧  但史蒂芬·亨特利和愛德華·達比
Maybe, but after what Stephen Huntley

81
00:03:38,680 --> 00:03:41,280
做出那種事  你肯定想讓他們十倍奉還
and Edward Darby did, you want to exact a pound of flesh.

82
00:03:41,280 --> 00:03:42,490
你想殺了他倆
You want to kill them both.

83
00:03:44,970 --> 00:03:45,900
你什么意思
What's your point?

84
00:03:45,910 --> 00:03:47,890
我的意思是  你走進那間房時的怒氣
My point is, is that you go into that room angry,

85
00:03:47,890 --> 00:03:49,110
會蒙蔽你的雙眼
you're gonna have blinders on.

86
00:03:50,040 --> 00:03:52,130
就只能被他們牽著鼻子走了
And they're gonna lead you any way they want you to go.

87
00:03:52,130 --> 00:03:54,320
我鎮定自若地走進那間房
I get in that room, I'm cool as a cucumber,

88
00:03:54,500 --> 00:03:57,220
則能將他們牽著鼻子走
and I will lead whatever way you want to go.

89
00:03:58,220 --> 00:04:00,210
剛收到愛德華·達比提議的
We just got Edward Darby's proposed formula

90
00:04:00,210 --> 00:04:01,680
資產分配方案
for splitting our assets.

91
00:04:07,060 --> 00:04:08,610
-狗娘養的  -是啊
- Son of a bitch. - I know!

92
00:04:08,610 --> 00:04:10,860
他做出這種事還想跟我們談條件
He thinks he can dictate terms after what he's done?

93
00:04:10,860 --> 00:04:11,890
我們得擊垮他
We need to crush him.

94
00:04:11,890 --> 00:04:13,300
看到沒  蒙蔽了雙眼
See? Blinders.

95
00:04:13,320 --> 00:04:14,200
什么
What?

96
00:04:14,520 --> 00:04:17,190
路易剛提議由他接手談判
Louis was just suggesting that he run the negotiations.

97
00:04:17,200 --> 00:04:20,270
路易還提議律所收養一只獾作為吉祥物呢
Louis also suggested the firm adopt a badger as a mascot.

98
00:04:20,270 --> 00:04:21,900
獾是一種高貴而令人生畏的生物
The badger is a noble and fearsome creature,

99
00:04:21,900 --> 00:04:23,610
但這不是重點  我可以打敗他們
but that's not the point. I can beat them.

100
00:04:23,610 --> 00:04:25,290
華盛頓將軍隊還認為他們能打敗
And the Washington Generals think they can beat

101
00:04:25,290 --> 00:04:26,680
環球旅行者隊[皆為籃球隊]  但他們根本不是
the Globetrotters, but they're not even

102
00:04:26,680 --> 00:04:27,710
同一個聯盟的隊伍
in the same league.

103
00:04:27,710 --> 00:04:29,410
我爸是華盛頓將軍的球員
My father played for the Washington Generals.

104
00:04:29,600 --> 00:04:30,870
-看到沒  -你什么意思
- See? - So what are you saying?

105
00:04:30,870 --> 00:04:32,350
-我跟你不是一個級別的嗎  -我是說我倆
- I'm not in your league? - I'm saying you and I

106
00:04:32,350 --> 00:04:33,800
根本不是一卦的
don't even play the same sport.

107
00:04:33,810 --> 00:04:36,920
哈維  夠了  路易說得有理
Harvey...enough. And Louis has a point.

108
00:04:37,300 --> 00:04:38,830
你真在考慮他的建議
You seriously want to consider this?

109
00:04:38,830 --> 00:04:39,850
這就是個笑話
This is a joke.

110
00:04:40,500 --> 00:04:41,820
路易  能讓我們單獨談談嗎
Louis, will you give us a moment?

111
00:04:42,790 --> 00:04:43,850
拜托
Please?

112
00:04:47,730 --> 00:04:49,850
我不是笑話
I am not a joke.

113
00:04:55,920 --> 00:04:57,950
你不能再這樣了
You can't do that anymore.

114
00:04:58,120 --> 00:04:59,430
你是說逗弄路易嗎
You mean make fun of Louis?

115
00:04:59,430 --> 00:05:00,780
這可是我最大的人生樂趣之一
It's one of life's great pleasures.

116
00:05:00,790 --> 00:05:02,050
你倆還是同事時
When the two of you were colleagues,

117
00:05:02,050 --> 00:05:04,190
那還算公平  但你現在是掛名合伙人了
that's fair game, but you're a name partner now,

118
00:05:04,190 --> 00:05:05,850
你得尊重他一點
and you have to show him some respect.

119
00:05:05,850 --> 00:05:07,310
我很尊重他啊
I am showing him respect.

120
00:05:07,310 --> 00:05:09,000
我都當面嘲笑他了
I'm being dismissive to his face.

121
00:05:10,980 --> 00:05:13,460
哈維  記得克普曼嗎
Harvey, remember Kopelman?

122
00:05:13,660 --> 00:05:15,380
那樣的禿頂地中海可挺難忘的
Comb-overs like that are hard to forget.

123
00:05:15,380 --> 00:05:18,150
我剛來這里工作時  我們每天
When I first started here, he and I would fight

124
00:05:18,150 --> 00:05:20,960
就跟貓狗大戰似的  針鋒相對
like cats and dogs every day, toe-to-toe.

125
00:05:21,880 --> 00:05:23,060
有一天他太過分了
Then one day he went too far.

126
00:05:23,060 --> 00:05:25,320
越過了底線  我受夠了
He crossed a line, and I'd had enough,

127
00:05:25,320 --> 00:05:27,620
沖進去揍得他滿地找牙
and I went in, and I ripped him up.

128
00:05:28,770 --> 00:05:30,670
你知道我和丹尼爾接手這家律所的那天
You know what I did the day after Daniel and I

129
00:05:30,670 --> 00:05:31,810
我干什么了嗎
took over the firm?

130
00:05:32,750 --> 00:05:36,290
我告訴克普曼  我有多重視他
I went to Kopelman, and I told him how much I valued him.

131
00:05:38,330 --> 00:05:39,800
我認識他那段日子
Kopelman never voted against you

132
00:05:39,800 --> 00:05:41,160
他從沒給你投過反對票
the whole time I knew him.

133
00:05:42,280 --> 00:05:43,480
正是
Exactly.

134
00:05:43,580 --> 00:05:45,150
話說  路易說得對
And by the way, Louis is right.

135
00:05:45,220 --> 00:05:47,890
杰西卡  尊重路易是一回事
Jessica, it's one thing for me to show Louis respect.

136
00:05:48,320 --> 00:05:50,630
但要我旁觀他處理案子
But you want to put me on the sidelines for him?

137
00:05:50,630 --> 00:05:51,720
不
No.

138
00:05:52,290 --> 00:05:54,340
我要讓他做四分衛
I'm gonna put him in at quarterback,

139
00:05:54,860 --> 00:05:56,270
把球搶來給你
then snap the ball to you.

140
00:05:58,010 --> 00:06:01,010
人人影視
YYeTs.com

141
00:05:58,010 --> 00:06:01,010
原創翻譯  雙語字幕

142
00:05:58,010 --> 00:06:01,010
■

143
00:05:58,010 --> 00:06:01,010
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com

144
00:06:01,010 --> 00:06:06,010
 翻譯：愛卿遛小鳥  圈圈  reginamoon  王大可  絨布熊

145
00:06:01,010 --> 00:06:06,010
■

146
00:06:06,010 --> 00:06:11,010
時間軸：憑陵新月  sinagujia  校對：油炸電風扇

147
00:06:06,010 --> 00:06:11,010
■

148
00:06:11,010 --> 00:06:16,010
 翻譯：feilixiaozi  小飯   后期 & 特效：倉鼠sama     總監：swears

149
00:06:11,010 --> 00:06:16,010
■

150
00:06:22,670 --> 00:06:24,840
第三季 第九集

151
00:06:22,670 --> 00:06:24,840
訴 訟 雙 雄

152
00:06:28,420 --> 00:06:29,210
讓我把這事理清楚
So let me get this straight.

153
00:06:29,210 --> 00:06:30,540
你要追查他們的委托人
You want to go afte their clients

154
00:06:30,540 --> 00:06:32,160
以此估算他們的收入額
so we get to count those revenues.

155
00:06:32,160 --> 00:06:34,490
結案時  收入多的就能決定
Whoever has more revenue is gonna determine

156
00:06:34,490 --> 00:06:36,360
誰能拿到什么
who gets what at the time of closing.

157
00:06:36,360 --> 00:06:37,790
路易鎖定談判條件
Louis locks in the settlement terms

158
00:06:37,790 --> 00:06:39,440
同時我們提高我們的和解籌碼
while we tip the basis for the settlement.

159
00:06:39,440 --> 00:06:40,390
的確
Exactly.

160
00:06:40,940 --> 00:06:43,040
有人可能會說這是欺詐談判
Some might say that's negotiating in bad faith.

161
00:06:43,200 --> 00:06:45,910
我們合作時達比就并非光明正大
And I say Darby wasn't above board when we got married.

162
00:06:45,910 --> 00:06:48,340
難道我們分道揚鑣時需要嗎
Why should we be above board when we're getting divorced?

163
00:06:48,340 --> 00:06:49,620
除非和解完成
And until the settlement is done,

164
00:06:49,630 --> 00:06:51,140
否則就不是搶客戶
it's not stealing clients.

165
00:06:51,290 --> 00:06:53,150
這是改變記錄律師
It's shifting the attorney of record.

166
00:06:55,160 --> 00:06:56,730
等等  這些都是你一個人想到的嗎
Wait a minute. Did you think of this all by yourself?

167
00:06:57,230 --> 00:06:59,380
為什么不是我自己一個人想到的
Why wouldn't I think of this all by myself?

168
00:06:59,510 --> 00:07:00,510
是杰西卡對吧
It was Jessica, wasn't it?

169
00:07:00,520 --> 00:07:01,640
一切都是她想到的
She thought of it all by yourself.

170
00:07:01,640 --> 00:07:04,210
目前的當務之急是確定
The important thing right now is to decide

171
00:07:04,210 --> 00:07:05,080
我們應該找的客戶
which client to go after.

172
00:07:05,080 --> 00:07:07,100
你在回避我的問題  沒說到底是誰想出來的
And to avoid my question about whose idea it was.

173
00:07:07,100 --> 00:07:08,300
-正是  -好吧
- Exactly. - Okay.

174
00:07:08,770 --> 00:07:11,440
要想影響到和解計算分配
Well, if it's going to affect the settlement calculations,

175
00:07:11,440 --> 00:07:13,830
我們需要一個大客戶  并且是一個
we're gonna need a big client and we're gonna need a big one

176
00:07:13,830 --> 00:07:15,090
剛遭受損失的大客戶
who just took a loss.

177
00:07:15,100 --> 00:07:16,530
未必
Not necessarily.

178
00:07:17,080 --> 00:07:19,580
你知道美國小姐選美中誰的壓力最大嗎
You know who cries hardest in the Miss America pageant?

179
00:07:19,790 --> 00:07:21,310
-亞軍  -是冠軍
- The runner-up. - The winner...

180
00:07:21,430 --> 00:07:23,310
因為她知道她再也贏不了了
Because she knows she can't win again,

181
00:07:23,450 --> 00:07:25,640
但是贏的人往往會想繼續贏的
and winners always want to win more.

182
00:07:25,810 --> 00:07:27,860
對  但他們哭不是因為這個
Yeah. That's not why they cry.

183
00:07:27,860 --> 00:07:29,700
-你說這個干什么  -繼續聽
- What's wrong with you? - Stay with me.

184
00:07:29,820 --> 00:07:33,470
我們需要的是一家想要
What we need is a huge company that is still looking

185
00:07:33,470 --> 00:07:34,700
保住王冠的大公司
to keep the crown.

186
00:07:39,250 --> 00:07:40,120
三星
Samsung.

187
00:07:40,120 --> 00:07:41,260
-馬上去  -好
- Get it going. - Yeah.

188
00:07:42,390 --> 00:07:44,210
對了  你真的看
Wait. Do you-- you actually watch

189
00:07:44,210 --> 00:07:45,420
美國小姐選美大賽嗎
the Miss America pageant?

190
00:07:45,450 --> 00:07:47,310
不看  但我跟冠軍一起慶祝過
No, but I've celebrated with the winner.

191
00:07:47,350 --> 00:07:49,660
是德克薩斯  佛羅里達  還是紐約的
Texas, Florida, New York?

192
00:07:49,660 --> 00:07:50,630
加利福尼亞
California.

193
00:07:50,800 --> 00:07:52,750
終于有問題你不想回避了
Now, there's a question you didn't want to avoid.

194
00:07:53,170 --> 00:07:54,220
對
Exactly.

195
00:07:58,550 --> 00:07:59,410
你找我有事嗎
You wanted to see me?

196
00:07:59,410 --> 00:08:01,830
-對  有要事  -什么事
- Yes, and it's important. - What can I do for you?

197
00:08:02,250 --> 00:08:03,970
要調整我們新名片上的字體嗎
Adjust the font on the new business cards?

198
00:08:03,970 --> 00:08:06,400
-還是要筆用  -我也不知道
- Order some pens? - I don't know.

199
00:08:06,640 --> 00:08:07,530
如果我們沒有筆用了
If we don't have any pens,

200
00:08:07,530 --> 00:08:09,040
你要用什么來簽訂單呢
what would you sign the order with?

201
00:08:10,630 --> 00:08:11,430
你到底想怎樣  杰西卡
What do you want, Jessica?

202
00:08:11,430 --> 00:08:12,940
我只是跟你開個玩笑而已
I was just making a little joke.

203
00:08:13,080 --> 00:08:14,590
我還以為我是這里唯一的笑話呢
Oh, I thought I was the only joke around here.

204
00:08:15,540 --> 00:08:18,360
路易  你不是笑話
Louis, you are no joke.

205
00:08:18,400 --> 00:08:19,450
你說得對
And you're right.

206
00:08:19,780 --> 00:08:21,850
你冷板凳坐太久了
You have been on the sidelines far too long.

207
00:08:23,100 --> 00:08:25,120
我想讓你處理協商的事
I want you to handle the negotiations.

208
00:08:26,900 --> 00:08:28,010
你一定不會失望的
You won't be sorry.

209
00:08:28,710 --> 00:08:29,640
你想要一磅肉的話
You want a pound of flesh,

210
00:08:29,640 --> 00:08:30,770
我會把整具尸體都給你拿來
I'm gonna bring you the whole carcass.

211
00:08:30,770 --> 00:08:31,740
我知道你有這個能力
I believe you would,

212
00:08:31,740 --> 00:08:33,460
但我想讓你做點別的事
but I'm going to ask you to do something else.

213
00:08:33,460 --> 00:08:35,620
-悉聽尊便  -我需要你公正
- Anything you need. - I need you to be fair.

214
00:08:38,040 --> 00:08:40,730
-公正  -對  公正
- Fair? - Yes, fair.

215
00:08:42,010 --> 00:08:43,890
-這是一種方法  -是唯一的方法
- That's one way to go. - It's the way to go...

216
00:08:44,160 --> 00:08:46,190
因為我想讓他們以為我們不計前嫌了
Because I need them to think that we're moving on,

217
00:08:46,190 --> 00:08:48,370
但事實上  我們要去挖他們的客戶
when, in fact, we're going after their clients.

218
00:08:48,940 --> 00:08:51,810
天哪  天哪
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.

219
00:08:51,810 --> 00:08:53,260
你和哈維要讓我參與你們的任務嗎
You and Harvey are letting me in on one of your missions?

220
00:08:53,260 --> 00:08:55,810
-真是令人震驚啊  -路易  冷靜
- This is litt-tastic. - Louis, calm down.

221
00:08:55,810 --> 00:08:56,840
冷靜  不要
Calm down? No!

222
00:08:56,840 --> 00:08:58,380
這就跟《大逃亡》一樣
This is just like The Great Escape.

223
00:08:58,390 --> 00:09:00,320
你要招募我去敵人的陣營
You're recruiting me to go behind enemy lines.

224
00:09:00,320 --> 00:09:01,290
我就是史蒂夫·麥奎因啊
I'm Steve Mcqueen.

225
00:09:01,310 --> 00:09:02,710
-你知道《大逃亡》  -開什么玩笑
- You know The Great Escape? - Are you kidding?

226
00:09:02,710 --> 00:09:04,660
查爾斯·布朗森就是在我祖母的小村莊里長大的
Charles Bronson grew up in my grandmother's shtetl.

227
00:09:02,710 --> 00:09:04,660
《大逃亡》主演

228
00:09:04,670 --> 00:09:08,560
那你一定知道史蒂夫·麥奎因最最冷靜的人
Then you know Steve Mcqueen was the cooler king.

229
00:09:09,410 --> 00:09:12,830
路易  我需要你也保持冷靜
Louis, I need you to be my cooler king.

230
00:09:12,850 --> 00:09:14,060
好  沒問題
Yeah, I am cool.

231
00:09:15,070 --> 00:09:17,140
也就是說你授權我代你簽字
So you're authorizing me to sign on your behalf?

232
00:09:17,430 --> 00:09:20,410
對  但是你絕對不能
Yes, but under no circumstances

233
00:09:20,410 --> 00:09:22,770
鎖定現有的客戶分配
are you to lock in the existing client allocations.

234
00:09:22,850 --> 00:09:24,140
拜托  除非我死了
Please, I'd die before that happens.

235
00:09:24,140 --> 00:09:25,610
希望不會到那種地步
Let's hope it doesn't come to that.

236
00:09:28,610 --> 00:09:30,500
-那是椰汁嗎  -對
- Is that coconut water? - Yeah.

237
00:09:31,620 --> 00:09:32,310
抱歉
I'm sorry.

238
00:09:32,320 --> 00:09:33,500
今早我帶了一些
I took some with me this morning.

239
00:09:33,500 --> 00:09:34,320
希望你不要介意
I hope you don't mind.

240
00:09:34,320 --> 00:09:36,600
我為什么要介意  你需要補充水分
Why would I mind? You needed the hydration.

241
00:09:36,870 --> 00:09:38,470
是你讓我需要補充水分的
You made me need the hydration.

242
00:09:38,480 --> 00:09:39,650
不用謝
You're welcome.

243
00:09:46,850 --> 00:09:48,910
-怎么了  -沒事
- What? - Nothing.

244
00:09:48,910 --> 00:09:49,900
到底怎么了
What?

245
00:09:52,680 --> 00:09:54,970
我只是不喜歡你直接用
I just don't like when you drink

246
00:09:54,970 --> 00:09:56,680
從冰箱里拿出的瓶子來喝水
from the bottles in the refrigerator.

247
00:09:56,680 --> 00:09:59,320
-但那是我的瓶子  -我冰箱里的不是
- But it's my bottle. - The ones in my fridge aren't.

248
00:09:59,380 --> 00:10:00,390
也就是說你介意我拿了
So you do mind that I took it.

249
00:10:00,390 --> 00:10:03,410
不  我介意你用我冰箱里的瓶子直接喝
No, I mind that you drink from the bottles in my fridge.

250
00:10:05,660 --> 00:10:06,580
好吧
Okay.

251
00:10:06,790 --> 00:10:10,320
還有你又把你的咖啡杯留在水池上了
And that you left your coffee mug in the sink again.

252
00:10:11,340 --> 00:10:12,740
我應該把杯子放在水池里面是吧
I thought I was supposed to put the mug in the sink.

253
00:10:12,740 --> 00:10:14,810
對  放在右邊  左邊是用來沖洗的
Yes, on the right side. The left side is for rinsing.

254
00:10:14,810 --> 00:10:16,960
如果水池兩邊都有的話我就沒法洗了
I can't rinse if there are dishes piled on both sides.

255
00:10:17,030 --> 00:10:18,310
我會盡量記住的
I'll try and remember that.

256
00:10:18,500 --> 00:10:20,720
憑你的頭腦你不用盡量
You'd think a guy with your memory wouldn't have to try.

257
00:10:22,060 --> 00:10:24,130
-好吧  你說吧  -說什么
- All right, let's hear it. - Hear what?

258
00:10:24,130 --> 00:10:25,120
-列表啊  -什么列表
- The list. - What list?

259
00:10:25,120 --> 00:10:26,720
我做的惹你不高興的事
Of things I do that annoy you.

260
00:10:26,770 --> 00:10:28,360
-我沒有那種列表  -人人都有
- I don't have a list. - Everyone has a list.

261
00:10:28,360 --> 00:10:30,260
-你也有嗎  -我的列表不是重點
- Do you have a list? - This isn't about my list.

262
00:10:30,260 --> 00:10:31,510
重點是你的
This is about your list.

263
00:10:31,510 --> 00:10:33,390
不  重點就是你的  因為我已經
No, it's about yours because I just told you

264
00:10:33,390 --> 00:10:34,920
把我所有的都告訴你了
everything that's on mine.

265
00:10:35,080 --> 00:10:37,020
你是跟我說上西區最一絲不茍的女人
You're telling me that the most meticulous woman

266
00:10:37,020 --> 00:10:38,990
她只有一個兩件事的列表嗎
on the upper west side only has a list of two?

267
00:10:39,220 --> 00:10:40,860
-不公平  -不  不公平的是
- That's not fair. - No, what's not fair

268
00:10:40,860 --> 00:10:42,520
你是針對我的
is you making this all about me.

269
00:10:42,590 --> 00:10:44,910
我可能不夠完美  但你也是
I might not be perfect, but neither are you.

270
00:10:44,910 --> 00:10:46,900
所以失陪了  我還有更重要的事去做
So, excuse me, I have more important things to do

271
00:10:46,900 --> 00:10:48,780
沒工夫在這里談論要把咖啡杯放在哪里
than talk about where I left my coffee cup.

272
00:10:50,600 --> 00:10:52,350
-公正  -公正
- Fair? - Fair.

273
00:10:53,070 --> 00:10:55,600
-公正  -對  公正
- Fair? - Yes, fair.

274
00:10:56,150 --> 00:10:58,530
我玩沙坑的時候都不會公平
I didn't even like playing nice in the sandbox.

275
00:10:58,530 --> 00:10:59,580
要是有人有更好的沙子玩具
Someone has better sand toys,

276
00:10:59,580 --> 00:11:00,870
-你就搶走  -正是
- you take 'em. - Exactly.

277
00:11:00,930 --> 00:11:03,590
你不能去邀請芭蕾舞演員跳探戈
And you don't ask bolshoi ballerinas to dance the tango.

278
00:11:03,600 --> 00:11:05,080
那樣就真是褻瀆神明了
That would indeed be blasphemy.

279
00:11:05,120 --> 00:11:06,810
如果杰西卡想妥協
If Jessica wants compromise,

280
00:11:06,810 --> 00:11:09,070
她應該雇個調解員  而不是斗士
she should hire a mediator, not a gladiator.

281
00:11:09,710 --> 00:11:11,440
除非是杰西卡不想妥協
Except Jessica doesn't want compromise.

282
00:11:11,440 --> 00:11:13,960
她只想讓一個鐵石心腸的殺手去做一件事
She wants a stone-cold killer to do one thing and one thing only.

283
00:11:13,960 --> 00:11:14,810
什么事
And what is that?

284
00:11:14,810 --> 00:11:18,070
在哈維拿下三星前  不能鎖定客戶分配
Not to lock client allocations till Harvey lands Samsung.

285
00:11:18,170 --> 00:11:19,270
那就給我下命令吧
Then give me an order.

286
00:11:19,270 --> 00:11:22,370
你的命令是不要讓我內部的斗士
Your order is to not let my inner gladiator

287
00:11:22,370 --> 00:11:24,250
戰勝我外面的協商人員
get past my outer negotiator.

288
00:11:24,380 --> 00:11:25,820
這可不是件容易的事  路易
That's not gonna be easy, Louis.

289
00:11:26,120 --> 00:11:28,190
你就跟綠巨人一樣  一旦被激怒
You're like the Hulk-- once you get enraged,

290
00:11:28,190 --> 00:11:29,090
就沒有回路了
there's no going back.

291
00:11:29,090 --> 00:11:31,030
雖然你對我性情和體格的描述
Though your description of both my temperament

292
00:11:31,030 --> 00:11:33,090
是準確的  但是對我有利的一點是
and physique is accurate, the one thing that I have

293
00:11:33,090 --> 00:11:35,350
我跟對方沒有任何
on my side is that I have no personal animus

294
00:11:35,350 --> 00:11:36,380
個人恩怨
against the other side.

295
00:11:44,860 --> 00:11:45,850
奈斯比特
Nesbitt.

296
00:11:46,080 --> 00:11:47,260
利特
Litt.

297
00:11:48,850 --> 00:11:50,040
我看到你身穿格子西裝
I see you're wearing your checkered suit

298
00:11:50,050 --> 00:11:51,360
搭配深紅色領帶
with your crimson power tie.

299
00:11:51,890 --> 00:11:53,070
看的很對
You see correctly.

300
00:11:53,310 --> 00:11:54,570
看樣子你是要來硬的了
Looks like you came to play hardball.

301
00:11:54,570 --> 00:11:55,970
我不是來硬的
I didn't come to play anything.

302
00:11:55,970 --> 00:11:57,870
-我是來贏的  -可我不是來贏的
- I came to win. - Well, I'm not here to win.

303
00:11:57,880 --> 00:12:00,150
我來確保我們制定出一項公平的協議
I'm here to make sure we hammer out a fair agreement.

304
00:12:00,500 --> 00:12:01,670
為了幫助你達到這個目標
And to help you achieve that,

305
00:12:01,680 --> 00:12:03,900
我瞧見你把你的小仙女帶來了
I see you've brought along Tinker Bell.

306
00:12:04,240 --> 00:12:05,670
而你是如此的懼怕小仙女
And you were so scared of Tinker Bell,

307
00:12:05,670 --> 00:12:06,720
以至于你為了你的貓咪庭審
you sent her to Barcelona

308
00:12:06,720 --> 00:12:07,590
把她派到巴塞羅那去了
for your cat trial.

309
00:12:07,600 --> 00:12:08,220
就在那段時間
During which time,

310
00:12:08,220 --> 00:12:10,920
她和另一個高級合伙人親密共事
she worked closely with a different senior partner...

311
00:12:11,660 --> 00:12:14,150
一遍又一遍
Again and again.

312
00:12:16,050 --> 00:12:16,890
別擔心
Don't worry.

313
00:12:17,490 --> 00:12:19,300
班納博士今天可不會變身成綠巨人
Dr. Banner's not turning green today.

314
00:12:19,490 --> 00:12:20,240
看到了吧  所有你以為
See, whatever you thought

315
00:12:20,240 --> 00:12:22,110
會發生在我身上的事  都沒發生
was gonna happen to me here isn't.

316
00:12:22,230 --> 00:12:24,850
所以你大可繼續隨便嘲笑我
So go ahead, wind me up all you want,

317
00:12:24,850 --> 00:12:26,060
因為我是不會失去我的淡定冷靜的
'cause I ain't losing my cool.

318
00:12:26,060 --> 00:12:27,110
好吧
Fine.

319
00:12:28,290 --> 00:12:29,760
這是我的初步提案
This is my initial proposal.

320
00:12:35,430 --> 00:12:37,060
那些是我寫給米卡度的信
Those are letters I wrote to Mikado.

321
00:12:37,150 --> 00:12:38,220
未拆封的
Unopened.

322
00:12:39,620 --> 00:12:40,630
你從來沒有讀給她聽
You never read them to her?

323
00:12:40,630 --> 00:12:41,670
一個字也沒讀
Not a single word.

324
00:12:41,670 --> 00:12:43,040
你個狗娘養的
You son of a bitch.

325
00:12:43,050 --> 00:12:44,310
你以為你可以激怒我嗎
You think you can rattle me?

326
00:12:44,310 --> 00:12:45,660
我是不可激怒的
I'm un-rattleable.

327
00:12:45,730 --> 00:12:46,720
真的嗎
Really?

328
00:12:47,750 --> 00:12:50,590
這幅你送給她的肖像畫
This portrait that you sent her.

329
00:12:54,000 --> 00:12:54,960
出去
Get out!

330
00:12:54,990 --> 00:12:56,300
-路易  -我說了要你走開
- Louis-- - I said go.

331
00:13:02,910 --> 00:13:05,140
是的  我們倆要開戰了
Oh, yeah, you and I are going to war.

332
00:13:05,140 --> 00:13:07,090
一切都擺在桌面上
Everything's on the goddamn table!

333
00:13:07,430 --> 00:13:09,660
包括現有客戶名單分配
Including the existing client list allocations?

334
00:13:09,660 --> 00:13:10,640
你沒聽到我剛剛說的嗎
Did you hear what I just said?

335
00:13:10,640 --> 00:13:11,530
我說了"一切"
I said everything!

336
00:13:19,780 --> 00:13:20,960
你個狗娘養的
You son of a bitch.

337
00:13:21,630 --> 00:13:23,310
你知道我會去找三星了
You knew I'd come after samsung.

338
00:13:23,310 --> 00:13:24,770
我知道你到時會穿哪套西裝
I knew what suit you'd be wearing.

339
00:13:25,830 --> 00:13:28,150
我知道老虎伍茲星期天會穿紅色的
I know Tiger Woods wears red on Sundays.

340
00:13:28,150 --> 00:13:29,360
但那也不意味著我可以打敗他
It doesn't mean I can beat him.

341
00:13:29,550 --> 00:13:31,540
我不會讓你偷走我們的客戶的  哈維
I'm not going to let you poach our clients, Harvey.

342
00:13:31,880 --> 00:13:33,350
你偷走了我們的客戶
You poaching our clients

343
00:13:33,350 --> 00:13:36,260
就是這次該死的并購的起源
is what led us to this goddamn merger in the first place.

344
00:13:36,760 --> 00:13:37,590
那是場公平的競爭
That was fair game.

345
00:13:37,960 --> 00:13:38,840
而這個卻是背信棄義的
This is bad faith.

346
00:13:38,840 --> 00:13:41,170
背信棄義  我只是打算盯著三星
Bad faith? I'm going after samsung.

347
00:13:41,170 --> 00:13:42,310
我又沒謀殺了某個人
I'm not murdering anybody

348
00:13:42,310 --> 00:13:43,690
并就此事對我的搭檔撒謊
and lying about it to my partners.

349
00:13:43,690 --> 00:13:44,930
你敢把我和他們放在一起
Don't you dare put me in with them.

350
00:13:44,930 --> 00:13:46,410
你自己和他們攪合在了一起
You put yourself in with them.

351
00:13:46,630 --> 00:13:47,490
說到這個
Speaking of which,

352
00:13:47,490 --> 00:13:49,280
你到底還在床上和這些人做了什么
what the hell you still doing in bed with these people,

353
00:13:49,280 --> 00:13:50,010
斯科特
Scottie?

354
00:13:50,030 --> 00:13:52,710
你也知道  我不是總能明智地選擇
As you know, I don't always have the best judgment

355
00:13:52,710 --> 00:13:54,020
和什么人上床
of who I get in bed with.

356
00:13:54,020 --> 00:13:56,070
至于我為什么還和他們打交道
And as for why I'm still in business with them--

357
00:13:56,070 --> 00:13:56,940
讓我猜猜
Let me guess.

358
00:13:56,940 --> 00:13:59,000
只要你在解約談判上打敗了我
You beat me on the dissolution negotiation,

359
00:13:59,000 --> 00:14:00,110
你就能成為冠名合伙人了
you get your name on the door.

360
00:14:00,110 --> 00:14:01,300
是的  在你把他逐出去的那刻
Yep. Darby agreed to it

361
00:14:01,300 --> 00:14:02,720
達比就同意了我的要求
the second that you pushed him out.

362
00:14:03,190 --> 00:14:04,390
他這么做的唯一理由是因為他知道
He only did that because he knew

363
00:14:04,390 --> 00:14:06,040
當坊間開始流傳他家后院起火時
when word got out that his house was on fire,

364
00:14:06,040 --> 00:14:07,050
他必須得做點什么
he had to do something.

365
00:14:07,050 --> 00:14:09,160
他做了  他讓我來對付你
Well, he did. He put me against you.

366
00:14:09,250 --> 00:14:11,620
正如你剛剛提到  我們后院起火了
And as you just noted, our house is on fire,

367
00:14:11,620 --> 00:14:13,610
因此我會全力以赴解決這件事
and I'm gonna fight tooth and nail to put the damn thing out.

368
00:14:13,620 --> 00:14:15,740
你可以想怎么全力以赴就怎么全力以赴
You can fight tooth and nail all you like,

369
00:14:15,890 --> 00:14:18,250
但是你和我作對從來就沒成功過
but it's never done a thing for you against me before.

370
00:14:18,930 --> 00:14:21,590
那是因為我之前一直念著舊情
That's because I always had something else on my mind before,

371
00:14:21,930 --> 00:14:22,980
但是你已經讓我清楚的明白
But you've made it clear that

372
00:14:22,980 --> 00:14:23,850
我倆之間不可能了
that's never going to happen.

373
00:14:24,250 --> 00:14:25,750
所以  假如你覺得你這次能贏的話
So, if you think you're gonna win this time,

374
00:14:25,750 --> 00:14:27,080
你就大錯特錯了
you've got another thing coming.

375
00:14:27,710 --> 00:14:28,820
告訴我你想要什么  斯科特
Say what you want, Scottie.

376
00:14:28,820 --> 00:14:30,820
我要進去了  而你是阻止不了我的
I'm going in there, and you're not gonna stop me.

377
00:14:33,610 --> 00:14:34,960
恐怕我已經阻止你了
I'm afraid I already did.

378
00:14:35,360 --> 00:14:36,720
客戶名單剛剛鎖定了
Client list just got locked.

379
00:14:37,390 --> 00:14:38,710
所以你大可走進去試試
So you can go in there and give it a shot,

380
00:14:38,710 --> 00:14:39,760
但他們可不會和一個
but they're never gonna sign with a guy

381
00:14:39,760 --> 00:14:41,630
剛剛在他們的前門被耍了的人簽約的
who just got played on their front porch.

382
00:14:56,380 --> 00:14:57,540
我收到了你的短信
I got your message.

383
00:14:57,860 --> 00:14:58,860
謝謝你來見我
Thanks for meeting me.

384
00:14:59,070 --> 00:15:01,670
我不經常被邀請到外面來聽人道歉
It's not often I get invited out to hear an apology.

385
00:15:02,300 --> 00:15:03,800
我很抱歉我對你大吼大叫了
I'm so sorry I snapped at you.

386
00:15:05,540 --> 00:15:08,200
我反應過度了  然后我回頭想了想
I got defensive, and when I went away to think about it,

387
00:15:09,550 --> 00:15:10,690
我想明白了為什么
I came up with why.

388
00:15:10,700 --> 00:15:11,670
為什么
Why?

389
00:15:12,000 --> 00:15:13,880
我感覺像是個住在你家的客人
I feel like a guest in your apartment.

390
00:15:15,340 --> 00:15:17,600
并且我覺得這是因為我們每次都去你那里
And I think it's because we spend all of our time at your place

391
00:15:17,600 --> 00:15:19,850
卻沒有一次來我家
and none of the time at mine.

392
00:15:19,880 --> 00:15:20,690
是的  但我告訴過你
Yeah, but I told you,

393
00:15:20,690 --> 00:15:21,490
當我在你家的時候
when I'm at your place,

394
00:15:21,760 --> 00:15:24,030
我能想到的只有裹著床單的苔絲
all I can picture is Tess in a bedsheet.

395
00:15:24,030 --> 00:15:25,700
我知道  所以這就是我們在這里的原因
I know. And that's why we're here.

396
00:15:27,860 --> 00:15:29,500
來  我想給你看些東西
Come on, I want to show you something.

397
00:15:33,140 --> 00:15:34,580
路易  我們給了你一個任務
Louis, we gave you one job,

398
00:15:34,580 --> 00:15:35,360
你卻搞砸了
and you blew it.

399
00:15:35,360 --> 00:15:37,200
你到底是怎么搞砸那些談判的
How the hell did you screw up those negotiations?

400
00:15:37,200 --> 00:15:38,560
搞砸  拜托  你在說什么
Screw up? Come on. What are you talking about?

401
00:15:38,560 --> 00:15:39,840
我幫公司搞到了一架企業專機
I got us the corporate jet.

402
00:15:39,840 --> 00:15:41,210
我們保住了我們的第一股息支票
We keep our first dividend checks,

403
00:15:41,210 --> 00:15:42,670
而且他們為我們的新信箋印刷文句埋單了
and they pay for our new letterhead.

404
00:15:42,670 --> 00:15:43,270
所以你知道嗎
So you know what?

405
00:15:43,270 --> 00:15:45,060
你收回你剛剛的話  把它留給你自己吧
You just put that in your pipe, and you smoke it.

406
00:15:45,850 --> 00:15:47,770
我他媽一點都不關心該死的信箋印刷文句
I don't give a shit about the goddamn letterhead!

407
00:15:48,050 --> 00:15:49,110
你以為我不知道
You don't think I know that?

408
00:15:49,830 --> 00:15:51,800
沒人關心那該死的信箋印刷文句好嗎
Nobody cares about the goddamn letterhead, okay?

409
00:15:52,070 --> 00:15:53,440
奈杰爾用上了米卡度
Nigel went after Mikado.

410
00:15:53,440 --> 00:15:54,890
米卡度又他媽是什么
What the hell is Mikado?

411
00:15:54,970 --> 00:15:56,020
不是"什么"  是"誰"
Not "What," "Who."

412
00:15:56,020 --> 00:15:56,630
她是一只貓
She's a cat.

413
00:15:57,080 --> 00:15:58,220
他纏著你的貓
He went after your cat?

414
00:15:58,220 --> 00:15:59,640
他纏著他的貓
He went after his cat.

415
00:15:59,640 --> 00:16:01,120
他折磨他的貓
He tortured his cat?

416
00:16:03,260 --> 00:16:05,520
他剝奪了她讀我的信的權利
He deprived her of my letters.

417
00:16:08,580 --> 00:16:12,210
路易  你在談判的時候失去理智
Louis, you lost your shit during a negotiation

418
00:16:12,210 --> 00:16:14,690
就是因為某人沒給他的貓讀你寫的信
because someone didn't read your letters to their cat?

419
00:16:14,720 --> 00:16:18,620
哈維  拜托  我很抱歉我失去了理智
Harvey, please. I'm sorry I lost my head.

420
00:16:18,620 --> 00:16:20,800
我都不記得我簽了協議
I don't even remember signing the agreement.

421
00:16:20,810 --> 00:16:21,790
但你確實簽了
Well, you did!

422
00:16:23,110 --> 00:16:25,180
還有  路易  從我遇到你的那天起
And, Louis, you've been asking Jessica

423
00:16:25,180 --> 00:16:27,490
你就一直在求杰西卡重用你  而不是我
to give you the ball instead of me ever since the day I met you.

424
00:16:27,490 --> 00:16:28,640
而如今她重用你了
Well, she gave it to you,

425
00:16:28,710 --> 00:16:31,290
而你卻直接跑去為對方達陣得分了
and you just went and scored a touchdown for the other team.

426
00:16:43,860 --> 00:16:45,110
天吶
Oh, my God.

427
00:16:47,000 --> 00:16:48,810
你奶奶的公寓
Your grandmother's apartment.

428
00:16:49,240 --> 00:16:50,310
它還是屬于我的
I still own it.

429
00:16:51,540 --> 00:16:53,490
你一直以來都留著它
You kept it this entire time?

430
00:16:55,720 --> 00:16:56,950
我無法把它租出去
I couldn't rent it.

431
00:16:58,000 --> 00:16:58,930
我無法賣掉
I couldn't sell it.

432
00:16:58,930 --> 00:17:00,210
我
I...

433
00:17:01,300 --> 00:17:02,570
甚至無法來這里
couldn't even come here.

434
00:17:03,330 --> 00:17:04,790
那意味著最后一次你來這里
That means the last time you were here...

435
00:17:04,790 --> 00:17:05,970
我們一起來的
We were here.

436
00:17:07,450 --> 00:17:08,800
所以說你想搬進來
So you want to move in here?

437
00:17:08,800 --> 00:17:10,230
我想我們一起搬進來
I want us to move in here.

438
00:17:13,710 --> 00:17:14,370
邁克
Mike--

439
00:17:14,370 --> 00:17:14,970
瑞秋
Rachel.

440
00:17:15,480 --> 00:17:17,390
我只來過這里兩次
I've only ever been here twice,

441
00:17:18,290 --> 00:17:20,430
兩次都是和你一起來的
and both times were with you.

442
00:17:21,630 --> 00:17:24,380
第一次我們站在這里
The first time we stood here,

443
00:17:24,380 --> 00:17:25,730
我們描畫一起生活的場景
and we pictured living together.

444
00:17:27,000 --> 00:17:28,310
我永遠不會忘記
I'll never forget that.

445
00:17:29,690 --> 00:17:30,490
我也不會
Neither will I.

446
00:17:30,490 --> 00:17:31,690
而第二次
And the second time...

447
00:17:34,020 --> 00:17:36,160
是我人生中最艱難的幾天
was one of the hardest days of my life,

448
00:17:36,290 --> 00:17:40,290
但是我挺過去了  因為有你陪在我身邊
but I got through it because we were together.

449
00:17:45,420 --> 00:17:48,010
那是我聽過的最甜蜜的話了
That's one the sweetest things I've ever heard.

450
00:17:53,420 --> 00:17:55,200
你不需要現在就回答我  好嗎
You don't have to answer right now, okay?

451
00:17:57,010 --> 00:17:59,250
我只是想給你展示一下我們能擁有的東西
I just wanted to show you what we could have.

452
00:18:09,180 --> 00:18:10,240
該死的路易
Goddamn Louis.

453
00:18:10,560 --> 00:18:11,440
算了吧
Let it go.

454
00:18:12,110 --> 00:18:13,040
算了吧
Let it go?

455
00:18:13,650 --> 00:18:14,890
你不會說"算了吧"
You don't say "Let it go"

456
00:18:14,890 --> 00:18:16,780
除非你無法放過這件事
unless you already didn't let it go.

457
00:18:16,880 --> 00:18:19,370
你為了拿他出氣而要拿我出氣
You gonna take it out on me for taking it out on him?

458
00:18:19,740 --> 00:18:21,170
如今  我們可沒時間了
At the moment, we don't have the time.

459
00:18:21,180 --> 00:18:22,690
很好  因為我已經讓邁克
Good, because I've already got Mike

460
00:18:22,690 --> 00:18:24,420
想辦法修訂協議了
looking for ways to revise the agreement.

461
00:18:24,420 --> 00:18:26,130
問題不在于修訂它
The problem isn't revising it.

462
00:18:26,270 --> 00:18:28,180
問題是路易已經簽了
The problem is Louis already signed it.

463
00:18:28,180 --> 00:18:29,780
你的意思是我們得找個漏洞嗎
You're saying we need to find a loophole.

464
00:18:29,780 --> 00:18:30,530
是的
I am.

465
00:18:30,530 --> 00:18:32,510
如果我們沒法撬到他們的客戶
Well, if we can't steal from their clients

466
00:18:32,510 --> 00:18:34,380
新客戶的收入又不算的話
and the revenues from new ones don't count,

467
00:18:34,390 --> 00:18:35,730
那我們到底要怎么辦
what the hell are we supposed to do?

468
00:18:35,740 --> 00:18:37,140
只有一個方法
There's only one thing to do--

469
00:18:37,660 --> 00:18:39,290
把注意力集中在我們已經賺到的錢上
look at the money we're already owed.

470
00:18:39,540 --> 00:18:41,770
-什么意思  -比較建立在現金基礎上
- I don't follow you. - We're on a cash basis.

471
00:18:41,980 --> 00:18:44,450
未收到的收入不能計算在內
We can't count the revenues we haven't collected yet.

472
00:18:44,450 --> 00:18:47,160
如果我們能讓客戶快點支付律師費
But if we can entice someone to pay us sooner,

473
00:18:47,520 --> 00:18:49,400
我們就能按時湊夠金額了
We can get that revenue in under the window.

474
00:18:49,400 --> 00:18:50,990
耍手段  我喜歡
Bad faith-- I like it.

475
00:18:51,050 --> 00:18:52,970
問題是  目前誰還欠我們
The question is, who still owes us enough money

476
00:18:52,970 --> 00:18:53,950
足夠多的錢
to make a difference?

477
00:18:54,000 --> 00:18:55,280
福爾松食品公司
Folsom Foods.

478
00:18:55,710 --> 00:18:57,150
只要他們支付和解金
The second they pay their settlement,

479
00:18:57,150 --> 00:18:58,220
我們就能收到律師費
we get paid our fee.

480
00:18:58,270 --> 00:18:59,640
這是你自己想到的
You came to that all on your own.

481
00:18:59,640 --> 00:19:02,490
是啊  一個小時之前了  難道比你早
Yeah, about an hour ago. Don't tell me I beat you to it.

482
00:19:02,490 --> 00:19:04,310
也許  那是因為哈維沒有拖慢你的節奏
Maybe. But you didn't have Harvey slowing you down.

483
00:19:04,310 --> 00:19:06,030
-說的也對  -我人還在這呢
That's a fair point. - Okay, I'm right here.

484
00:19:06,050 --> 00:19:07,880
但你的點子不好用
Well, your idea is no good,

485
00:19:07,910 --> 00:19:09,430
因為如果你想等著丹尼爾·哈德曼
because it'll be a cold day in hell

486
00:19:09,430 --> 00:19:12,380
幫我們  那你可有得等了
before Daniel Hardman lifts a finger to help this firm,

487
00:19:12,600 --> 00:19:14,630
而且我寧可輸了這次談判
and I'd rather lose this negotiation

488
00:19:14,640 --> 00:19:16,440
也不愿意和那個混蛋談條件
than to cut a deal with that son of a bitch.

489
00:19:16,440 --> 00:19:18,560
你不用那樣做  哈德曼自己走了
You don't have to. Hardman was running point.

490
00:19:18,640 --> 00:19:19,980
福爾松不是他的客戶
Folsom's not his client.

491
00:19:19,980 --> 00:19:20,990
福爾松是羅伯特·贊恩的客戶
They're robert zane's.

492
00:19:21,200 --> 00:19:23,280
-他也同樣不喜歡我們  -話雖這么說
- He's no fan of us either. - Maybe not.

493
00:19:23,800 --> 00:19:25,400
但羅伯特·贊恩那邊我們可以搞定
But we can handle Robert Zane.

494
00:19:30,110 --> 00:19:31,380
你明白我剛才說的那個計劃了吧
You caught on to my plan there.

495
00:19:31,390 --> 00:19:33,040
你說的是那個全世界都能想到的計劃嗎
You mean the most obvious plan in the world?

496
00:19:33,050 --> 00:19:35,220
我說的是那個我想到你卻沒想到
I mean the plan that I thought of and that you didn't

497
00:19:35,220 --> 00:19:37,070
且最適合由我去執行的計劃
and that I'm the perfect person to implement.

498
00:19:37,070 --> 00:19:38,800
你真認為你能搞定羅伯特·贊恩
You really think you can handle Robert Zane?

499
00:19:39,360 --> 00:19:40,700
我跟他有些交情
I have a relationship with him.

500
00:19:40,700 --> 00:19:42,440
是啊  你在跟她的女兒睡覺
Yeah. You're sleeping with his daughter.

501
00:19:42,590 --> 00:19:44,090
他肯定特別喜歡你
I'm sure he's your biggest fan.

502
00:19:44,310 --> 00:19:46,920
不是的  我在他家吃過飯
Okay, it's not like that. I had dinner at the man's house.

503
00:19:46,920 --> 00:19:48,400
我還在白宮吃過飯呢
I had dinner at the White House.

504
00:19:48,480 --> 00:19:49,800
他們也不會讓我當司法部長啊
They're not gonna make me Attorney General.

505
00:19:49,800 --> 00:19:51,690
首先  你瞎扯
Okay, first of all, bullshit.

506
00:19:51,920 --> 00:19:53,560
其次  你還有更好的辦法么
Second of all, do you have a better idea?

507
00:19:53,560 --> 00:19:54,490
我沒有
No, I don't.

508
00:19:54,600 --> 00:19:56,690
但你真的準備好利用你和瑞秋的關系
But are you ready to use your relationship with Rachel

509
00:19:56,690 --> 00:19:57,930
去拉攏她爸爸了么
to get her father to turn?

510
00:19:57,940 --> 00:19:59,560
那不重要  因為我沒打算那么做
Doesn't matter, because I'm not gonna do that.

511
00:19:59,880 --> 00:20:01,290
我只是想讓他能認真的
I'm just gonna use it to get him to hear me out

512
00:20:01,290 --> 00:20:02,070
聽我解釋一下
in the first place.

513
00:20:03,110 --> 00:20:04,350
那祝你好運
Good luck with that.

514
00:20:05,140 --> 00:20:07,860
你是怎么知道白宮那件事我在瞎扯的
Hey, how'd you know that White House thing was bullshit?

515
00:20:16,940 --> 00:20:19,190
邁克  我還在想什么時候能讓你來這里呢
Mike. I was wondering when I was gonna get you out here.

516
00:20:19,190 --> 00:20:21,140
我對高爾夫不是很感興趣
Ah, golf isn't really my thing.

517
00:20:21,460 --> 00:20:22,870
那你對什么感興趣
What is your thing?

518
00:20:23,150 --> 00:20:24,410
運動
Sports.

519
00:20:24,430 --> 00:20:25,590
你的意思是你就是那種
You're telling me you're one of those guys

520
00:20:25,590 --> 00:20:27,110
不認為高爾夫是一種運動的人
that doesn't think golf is a sport?

521
00:20:27,110 --> 00:20:27,770
不是那個意思
Of course not.

522
00:20:27,770 --> 00:20:29,980
光看您的樣子就知道您是個運動員
I can tell you're an athlete just by looking at you, sir.

523
00:20:31,620 --> 00:20:33,920
態度這么好  一定是為了公事而來
With an attitude like that, you must be here on business.

524
00:20:33,920 --> 00:20:35,630
福爾松食品公司
Folsom Foods.

525
00:20:35,630 --> 00:20:37,390
你要當面提醒我一下那個失敗的案子么
You're gonna stick that loss in my face?

526
00:20:37,400 --> 00:20:39,880
不  我是來減輕您的痛苦的
No, I'm here to make that loss sting a little less.

527
00:20:39,880 --> 00:20:42,750
您提前一個季度支付和解金的話
You move up your payment by one fiscal quarter,

528
00:20:42,940 --> 00:20:44,840
我們愿意降低10%的和解費
we'll take a 10% haircut on our fee.

529
00:20:44,840 --> 00:20:46,420
10%有點少啊
10% is a little light.

530
00:20:46,440 --> 00:20:49,350
好  直截了當  我能給到20%
All right.I'll cut right to it. I can go as high as 20%.

531
00:20:49,350 --> 00:20:50,900
你是說20%嗎
Are you saying 20%?

532
00:20:50,920 --> 00:20:51,880
是的
Yes.

533
00:20:52,480 --> 00:20:53,790
那我不能同意
Then I'm saying no.

534
00:20:55,530 --> 00:20:57,930
這對你是有好處的啊
Sir, this... this is a win for you.

535
00:20:58,160 --> 00:21:00,110
不  這跟我沒什么關系
No, this isn't shit for me.

536
00:21:00,420 --> 00:21:02,680
是對哈維·斯佩克特和杰西卡·皮爾遜
This is about Harvey Specter and Jessica Pearson

537
00:21:02,680 --> 00:21:04,910
以及他們的分家談判有好處
and their divorce negotiations.

538
00:21:05,050 --> 00:21:06,640
你不能為了跟家里人較勁
And you don't go to the one you didn't marry

539
00:21:06,640 --> 00:21:08,170
而去投靠外人
to stick it to the one you did.

540
00:21:08,170 --> 00:21:10,080
我們也能直接去找您的客戶談
We could go straight to your client.

541
00:21:10,240 --> 00:21:12,070
等他們接受你的條件時
By the time they accepted the offer,

542
00:21:12,070 --> 00:21:13,480
已經太晚了
it'd be too late.

543
00:21:13,620 --> 00:21:15,650
你說20%的時候我就知道了
You just gave that away when you went straight to 20%.

544
00:21:15,700 --> 00:21:17,900
我出于尊重才會出到20%
I went straight to 20% out of respect.

545
00:21:17,910 --> 00:21:19,950
所以你這樣報答我  就像個...
Now you're repaying me by being a--

546
00:21:20,810 --> 00:21:21,890
像哪樣
What?

547
00:21:23,030 --> 00:21:24,560
你沒膽子說出來
You don't have the balls to say it.

548
00:21:24,560 --> 00:21:25,390
我來說
I will.

549
00:21:25,390 --> 00:21:27,310
混球  我像個混球
A dick. I'm being a dick.

550
00:21:27,850 --> 00:21:30,010
問題是  那你能怎樣呢
The question is, what are you gonna do about it?

551
00:21:32,500 --> 00:21:34,220
我不會怎么樣
I'm not gonna do anything about it.

552
00:21:35,590 --> 00:21:37,110
我只是想知道如果你女兒發現
I just wonder what your daughter's gonna think

553
00:21:37,110 --> 00:21:39,150
你犧牲自己客戶的利益
when she finds out you screwed over your own client

554
00:21:39,150 --> 00:21:41,030
目的只是為難她愛的人
just to stick it to the man she loves.

555
00:21:41,300 --> 00:21:43,170
她愛哈維·斯佩克特嗎
She loves Harvey Specter?

556
00:21:43,750 --> 00:21:47,030
不  但你為難哈維  就是為難我
No. But when you go after Harvey, you go after me.

557
00:22:00,990 --> 00:22:03,000
滿洲里的美洲鶴
The whooping crane of Manchuria.

558
00:22:03,090 --> 00:22:04,420
這是我的放松動物
It's my calming animal.

559
00:22:04,420 --> 00:22:05,770
你很會選
You've chosen well.

560
00:22:08,200 --> 00:22:09,540
找我什么事  卡特里娜
What can I do for you, Katrina?

561
00:22:09,550 --> 00:22:10,960
后來你就沒再找我了
I never heard back from you.

562
00:22:10,970 --> 00:22:11,840
找你干什么
About what?

563
00:22:11,840 --> 00:22:13,060
所有這些事
About anything...

564
00:22:13,080 --> 00:22:16,130
尤其是我們準備的關于談判的事
Especially what we're going to do about negotiations.

565
00:22:16,130 --> 00:22:17,770
沒有什么談判了
There's no more negotiation.

566
00:22:18,270 --> 00:22:20,110
我就這一個任務  還搞砸了
I had one assignment, and I blew it.

567
00:22:20,110 --> 00:22:23,460
路易  主角沒出場  歌劇怎能散場呢
Louis, the opera isn't over until the fat lady sings.

568
00:22:23,460 --> 00:22:25,150
這又不是歌劇
No, this is not the opera.

569
00:22:25,500 --> 00:22:26,640
是橄欖球
It's football.

570
00:22:27,840 --> 00:22:29,060
哈維已經說了
Harvey said it.

571
00:22:29,600 --> 00:22:30,500
他們把球給了我
They gave me the ball.

572
00:22:30,500 --> 00:22:32,050
我卻給對手了一個達陣得分
I scored a touchdown for the other team,

573
00:22:32,050 --> 00:22:32,700
已經第八局了
It's the eighth inning,

574
00:22:32,700 --> 00:22:34,590
而且已經沒時間了
and there's no more time left on the clock.

575
00:22:35,570 --> 00:22:36,940
我從沒想過會從你嘴里說出這些話
I never thought I'd hear you say that.

576
00:22:36,940 --> 00:22:38,870
這是事實  我們無能為力了
It's the fact. There's nothing we can do.

577
00:22:38,870 --> 00:22:39,830
我已經簽了協議
I signed the agreement,

578
00:22:39,830 --> 00:22:41,250
奈杰爾也絕對不會給我們修改的機會
and Nigel's never gonna reopen it.

579
00:22:41,250 --> 00:22:44,240
那幸好我找到了一個漏洞
Well, then I guess it's a good thing I found a loophole.

580
00:22:45,830 --> 00:22:46,750
什么意思
What are you talking about?

581
00:22:46,750 --> 00:22:48,520
我們沒法撬到他們的客戶了
We can't steal their clients,

582
00:22:48,520 --> 00:22:50,180
但我們還是可以提高自己的收入
but we can still increase our revenue.

583
00:22:50,190 --> 00:22:51,890
但是新客戶是不算的
No. New clients don't count.

584
00:22:51,890 --> 00:22:53,270
我不是指新客戶
I'm not talking about new clients.

585
00:22:53,270 --> 00:22:56,660
我是指已有客戶的新收入
I'm talking about new revenue from clients we already have.

586
00:22:56,700 --> 00:22:59,050
那這絕對屬于背后耍手段
Well, that's operating in complete bad faith.

587
00:23:01,730 --> 00:23:03,350
你在說哪個客戶
Now, what clients are you talking about?

588
00:23:03,350 --> 00:23:04,980
首先  我給你準備了一個小禮物
First, I got you something.

589
00:23:05,730 --> 00:23:06,790
卡特里娜  聽我說
Okay, Katrina, you know what?

590
00:23:06,790 --> 00:23:08,930
我現在真的沒時間多愁善感
I really don't have time for sentimental--

591
00:23:10,610 --> 00:23:12,930
你被"利特"點亮了

592
00:23:12,930 --> 00:23:14,610
十分鐘前新鮮出爐的標語
The trademark came through ten minutes ago.

593
00:23:14,610 --> 00:23:17,720
我不知道該說什么了
I... don't know what to say.

594
00:23:18,310 --> 00:23:21,260
就說你原諒我在奈吉爾面前沒控制住你
Say you forgive me for letting you lose control of Nigel.

595
00:23:23,350 --> 00:23:24,560
我原諒你了
I do.

596
00:23:27,200 --> 00:23:29,380
那我們趕緊去找點新收入吧
Now, let's go get some goddamn new revenue.

597
00:23:38,780 --> 00:23:39,980
是你
You.

598
00:23:40,810 --> 00:23:42,050
你怎么進來的
How'd you get in here?

599
00:23:42,050 --> 00:23:43,340
因為我知道如何搞定事情
'cause I know how to get things done.

600
00:23:43,340 --> 00:23:44,840
上次你可就沒搞定
You didn't the last time we met.

601
00:23:44,840 --> 00:23:46,620
上次因為你早有準備
Last time you saw me coming a mile away.

602
00:23:46,630 --> 00:23:48,380
這次我是攻其不備
This time, I'm blindsiding you.

603
00:23:50,860 --> 00:23:52,800
-我不知道我們在對戰  -我們沒有
- I didn't know we were at war. - We're not.

604
00:23:53,080 --> 00:23:55,100
這只是例行演習
It's just a training exercise.

605
00:23:56,450 --> 00:23:58,460
這是我個人的銀行對賬單
These are my personal bank statements.

606
00:23:58,910 --> 00:24:00,050
你偷了我的錢
You stole my money.

607
00:24:00,050 --> 00:24:01,520
不是偷
No, not stole...

608
00:24:01,830 --> 00:24:02,830
轉移而已
Relocated.

609
00:24:02,830 --> 00:24:04,030
我可以讓人把你抓起來
I could have you arrested.

610
00:24:04,030 --> 00:24:05,090
你是可以
You could.

611
00:24:05,170 --> 00:24:07,210
但接下來的東西你都將失去
But then you'd be missing out on all this...

612
00:24:10,100 --> 00:24:11,850
開曼群島的稅收壁壘
Tax shelter in the Caymans,

613
00:24:12,290 --> 00:24:14,920
轉化為附股權益的個人資產
carried interest classification for your personal holdings,

614
00:24:14,920 --> 00:24:17,340
無條件為你將來最多六個孩子設立不可撤銷信托
blind irrevocable trust for up to six of your unborn children.

615
00:24:17,340 --> 00:24:18,210
這意味著
And this means...

616
00:24:18,210 --> 00:24:20,620
你這輩子都不用再付一分錢稅費了
You'll never pay a nickel in taxes your entire life,

617
00:24:20,990 --> 00:24:22,740
更不用說將來你的財產
not to mention your money will be too secure

618
00:24:22,740 --> 00:24:24,550
安全到別人再也做不了手腳
for someone to do what I just did.

619
00:24:26,790 --> 00:24:27,810
你是怎么做到的
How'd you do all this?

620
00:24:27,810 --> 00:24:28,980
你說需要文書工作了會找我們
Well, you said you'd call us for the paperwork.

621
00:24:28,980 --> 00:24:30,160
我就是這么做文書工作的
This is how I do paperwork.

622
00:24:30,160 --> 00:24:31,340
對了  還有最后一點
Oh, and one last thing,

623
00:24:31,340 --> 00:24:33,910
你前妻拿走的那輛法拉利
that ferrari that your ex-wife took?

624
00:24:33,970 --> 00:24:34,990
怎么了
Yeah?

625
00:24:35,780 --> 00:24:36,930
我替你要回來了
I got it back.

626
00:24:40,440 --> 00:24:41,540
你被錄用了
You're hired.

627
00:24:44,620 --> 00:24:47,100
難道這不需要通過董事會的允許嗎
Don't you need to get board approval?

628
00:24:47,140 --> 00:24:48,850
做我的私人律師也要董事會允許嗎
To be my personal attorney?

629
00:24:48,850 --> 00:24:50,280
不  我是指拓寬揚諾普洛斯有限公司
No, for Gianopolous Limited Holdings

630
00:24:50,280 --> 00:24:52,120
與我方的業務關系
to expand their relationship with us.

631
00:24:53,800 --> 00:24:54,700
你瘋了吧
Are you crazy?

632
00:24:54,700 --> 00:24:55,340
這怎么是瘋了呢
How is that crazy?

633
00:24:55,340 --> 00:24:56,600
我不是剛證明了我的能力了嗎
I just showed you what I'm capable of.

634
00:24:56,600 --> 00:24:58,940
你證明給我看你能打敗一個西哥特部族
You showed me you could beat a tribe of visigoths.

635
00:24:56,600 --> 00:24:58,940
 西哥特人  日耳曼族的一族  于公元四世紀入侵羅馬帝國并在法國和西班牙建立王國

636
00:24:58,940 --> 00:25:01,450
就想讓我將整個羅馬帝國托付給你嗎
You want me to give you control of the Roman Empire?

637
00:25:01,460 --> 00:25:03,190
我能應付得了羅馬帝國
I can handle the Roman Empire.

638
00:25:03,920 --> 00:25:05,140
就算你能
Even if you could,

639
00:25:05,180 --> 00:25:07,540
對于揚諾普洛斯先生來說
from Mr. Gianopolous's perspective,

640
00:25:07,540 --> 00:25:08,910
你就是個無名小卒
you're a nobody.

641
00:25:12,170 --> 00:25:15,460
拜托了  你能想辦法說服他嗎
Please, can you at least find a way to convince him?

642
00:25:15,970 --> 00:25:16,970
抱歉
I'm sorry.

643
00:25:17,650 --> 00:25:18,780
如果我在他面前提你的名字
If I bring your name up to him,

644
00:25:18,780 --> 00:25:20,790
他會笑著趕我出門的
he will laugh me out of the room.

645
00:25:30,740 --> 00:25:32,020
福爾松食品公司的支票
That's a check from Folsom Foods.

646
00:25:32,020 --> 00:25:34,030
這是他們欠我們的所有余款
It's the remainder of what they owe us.

647
00:25:34,030 --> 00:25:36,910
我了個去  全都在這兒了
Holy shit. That's all of it.

648
00:25:37,330 --> 00:25:39,570
不利用她女兒也能讓贊恩買賬
It's hard to believe that you could get Zane to do this

649
00:25:39,570 --> 00:25:41,240
確實令人難以置信
without using his daughter against him.

650
00:25:41,240 --> 00:25:42,840
或許我就是個一流的交涉專家
Maybe I'm an excellent negotiator.

651
00:25:42,840 --> 00:25:44,460
如果你真的是一流的交涉專家
If you're an excellent negotiator,

652
00:25:44,460 --> 00:25:46,700
就不會有這20%的折扣了
this wouldn't include a 20% haircut.

653
00:25:46,700 --> 00:25:48,540
要是我出馬就只有10%
It would be 10%, like I would have gotten.

654
00:25:48,540 --> 00:25:50,560
就憑你  他根本不會和你說一句話
You? He wouldn't have even talked to you.

655
00:25:50,560 --> 00:25:52,510
像你現在沒和我說話一樣嗎
Like you're not talking to me right now?

656
00:25:53,380 --> 00:25:54,750
你是怎么說服贊恩的
What'd you say to Zane?

657
00:25:55,650 --> 00:25:58,370
我們或許如愿以償得到我們要的了  但是
Let's just say we may have gotten what we wanted, but...

658
00:25:58,540 --> 00:26:01,560
我女友的父親估計得生我一段時間的氣了
my girlfriend's dad's gonna be pissed at me for a little while.

659
00:26:01,560 --> 00:26:03,960
那你的確比我想象中會交涉
Then you're a better negotiator than I thought.

660
00:26:23,320 --> 00:26:24,900
我就不該給你房間鑰匙
I never should have given you my key.

661
00:26:24,900 --> 00:26:25,770
我也不該忘了
And I never should have forgotten

662
00:26:25,770 --> 00:26:27,880
你會不遺余力得擊敗我
that you'll stop at nothing to beat me.

663
00:26:29,060 --> 00:26:30,550
沒錯  你是該記著
No, you shouldn't have.

664
00:26:30,550 --> 00:26:31,580
哈維
Harvey...

665
00:26:31,580 --> 00:26:33,470
我認識的你或許會斗爭至死
The man that I knew may have fought to the death,

666
00:26:33,480 --> 00:26:35,500
但他從來都是正直守信的
but he always operated in good faith.

667
00:26:35,510 --> 00:26:38,650
我說過了  在你老板的所作所為之下
I told you, I am not bound by good faith on this deal

668
00:26:38,650 --> 00:26:39,980
這個案子里我不講信用
after what your boss did.

669
00:26:39,980 --> 00:26:41,710
這不只關乎愛德華的公司
It's not just Edward's firm.

670
00:26:41,710 --> 00:26:42,840
那還和什么有關系呢
What does that have to do with it?

671
00:26:42,840 --> 00:26:44,160
還和什么有關系
What does that have to do with it?

672
00:26:44,340 --> 00:26:46,570
你為了讓自己能多分一杯羹
You shrunk the whole pie for the sole purpose

673
00:26:46,570 --> 00:26:48,060
犧牲了大局
of getting a bigger piece for yourself,

674
00:26:48,060 --> 00:26:49,860
害了愛德華的同時也拖我下了水
and it screwed me, along with Edward.

675
00:26:49,860 --> 00:26:51,480
你想怎么樣  斯科特
What do you want, Scottie?

676
00:26:52,060 --> 00:26:54,130
我希望你把福爾松食品公司的支付費用
I want you to exclude the Folsom Foods payments

677
00:26:54,130 --> 00:26:55,900
從清償審核中剔除
from the settlement calculations.

678
00:26:56,130 --> 00:26:57,750
我為什么要這么做呢
And why would I do that?

679
00:26:59,440 --> 00:27:00,800
因為我需要你這么做
Because I need you to.

680
00:27:00,930 --> 00:27:02,630
恐怕這理由不夠充分
I'm afraid that's not enough.

681
00:27:06,060 --> 00:27:07,760
你之前找到我
You, uh-- you came to me.

682
00:27:08,100 --> 00:27:09,460
在你把我送回倫敦之后
You needed help with Ava Hessington

683
00:27:09,460 --> 00:27:11,300
你希望我在艾娃·海辛頓案子上幫你
after you sent me back to London.

684
00:27:11,660 --> 00:27:13,280
你說  你對我來說很重要
You said that I mean something to you,

685
00:27:13,280 --> 00:27:15,810
你說  一直都是
that I'll--I'll always mean something to you.

686
00:27:16,830 --> 00:27:18,730
-這些都是騙人的嗎  -當然不是
- Was that bullshit or not? - It wasn't bullshit,

687
00:27:18,730 --> 00:27:20,300
如果你私底下遇上麻煩的話
and if you're in trouble personally--

688
00:27:20,300 --> 00:27:23,160
我是遇上麻煩了  你自己說過的
I am in trouble personally. You said so yourself.

689
00:27:23,160 --> 00:27:25,880
我們的后院著了火  而我的任務就是撲滅它
Our house is on fire, and it's my job to put it out.

690
00:27:26,340 --> 00:27:27,550
如果你執意擊敗我
If you crush me...

691
00:27:27,850 --> 00:27:29,090
我就一無所有了
I'll have nothing.

692
00:27:29,830 --> 00:27:31,850
這不是私底下  這是工作上的
That's not personal. That's business.

693
00:27:31,860 --> 00:27:33,720
行  那我們就談工作
Okay, let's talk business.

694
00:27:33,720 --> 00:27:36,430
你靠著別人欠你的情成就了現在的事業
You made a career out of putting IOUs in the bank.

695
00:27:36,730 --> 00:27:38,310
現在做一遍同樣的事情
Do the same thing right now.

696
00:27:38,630 --> 00:27:40,460
讓我欠你的情
Put an IOU in with me.

697
00:27:41,800 --> 00:27:44,610
那之后我又怎么防止你再來整我呢
And what's to stop you from still trying to screw me after that?

698
00:27:46,130 --> 00:27:47,600
我保證  絕對不會
My word that I won't.

699
00:27:55,950 --> 00:27:57,430
他提出讓你和他同居
He asked you to move in together?

700
00:27:57,430 --> 00:27:59,930
-我知道這是...  -有點快
- I know. It's... - Quick?

701
00:28:01,320 --> 00:28:04,860
我是想說這的確是向前邁了一大步
I was going to say that it's a...a big step.

702
00:28:04,860 --> 00:28:05,800
其實并沒有很快了
Because it's not really that quick.

703
00:28:05,800 --> 00:28:07,190
我們認識彼此挺久了
We've known each other for a while.

704
00:28:07,200 --> 00:28:09,400
是  但你們才開始約會啊
Yes, but you only just started dating.

705
00:28:10,420 --> 00:28:11,820
言下之意你是不同意咯
So I guess that means you're against it.

706
00:28:11,820 --> 00:28:13,660
瑞秋  我并不是反對
Rachel, I'm not against it.

707
00:28:14,140 --> 00:28:15,560
你告訴我你愛他
You told me that you love him,

708
00:28:15,570 --> 00:28:17,300
我為你高興極了
and I couldn't be happier for you.

709
00:28:17,300 --> 00:28:19,930
但你現在還有好多事情要應付
But you got a lot going on right now.

710
00:28:19,930 --> 00:28:22,190
你都不知道你要去哪兒上法學院
You don't even know where you're gonna go to law school.

711
00:28:22,190 --> 00:28:23,700
我只是想說
I'm just saying

712
00:28:23,870 --> 00:28:26,600
或許你不想這么草率
maybe you don't want to rush into this so quickly.

713
00:28:26,600 --> 00:28:28,030
草率什么
Rush into what?

714
00:28:34,910 --> 00:28:37,510
邁克要我和他同居
Well, Mike asked me to move in with him.

715
00:28:37,700 --> 00:28:39,020
和他同居
Move in with him?

716
00:28:39,440 --> 00:28:41,730
該死的  他到時候該會怎么對我啊
Shit, what's he gonna do to me then?

717
00:28:42,050 --> 00:28:44,360
-你在說什么呢  -你沒聽說嗎
- What are you talking about? - You didn't hear?

718
00:28:44,370 --> 00:28:45,970
他來我高爾夫課上找我
He came to me on the golf course.

719
00:28:45,970 --> 00:28:47,830
請求你的同意嗎
To ask for permission?

720
00:28:48,450 --> 00:28:50,850
不  他什么都沒求我
No, he didn't ask for shit.

721
00:28:50,850 --> 00:28:53,180
是我乖乖交給他的  這孩子有點膽識
I got to hand it to him. The boy's got some balls.

722
00:28:53,290 --> 00:28:55,800
-什么  -他收拾了我一頓
- What? - he kicked my ass.

723
00:28:55,800 --> 00:28:57,380
甚至都沒給我留一點...
Didn't even have the courtesy to give me a--

724
00:28:57,380 --> 00:28:58,530
-羅伯特  -得了吧
- Robert! - Oh, come on.

725
00:28:58,530 --> 00:29:00,210
她遲早要當律師  還有更糟的話呢
She's gonna be a lawyer. Gonna hear a lot worse.

726
00:29:00,210 --> 00:29:03,260
爸  你在說什么  什么事
Dad, what are you talking about--what happened?

727
00:29:03,420 --> 00:29:06,030
他要福爾松提早清償余款
He wanted an advance on the Folsom settlement.

728
00:29:06,320 --> 00:29:08,230
他通過脅迫我來達到目的
And he put the screws to me to get it.

729
00:29:08,230 --> 00:29:10,600
他威脅你什么了
He put the screws to you how?

730
00:29:16,210 --> 00:29:18,510
瑞秋  真是意外
Rachel. This is a surprise.

731
00:29:18,510 --> 00:29:20,610
-你不是說...  -裹著床單的苔絲
- What happened to-- - Tess in a bedsheet?

732
00:29:20,740 --> 00:29:23,730
現在已經被你耍手段操縱我爸的景象代替了
It was replaced by the image of you manipulating my dad.

733
00:29:25,090 --> 00:29:27,210
我沒有操縱你父親
Okay, I did not manipulate your dad.

734
00:29:27,210 --> 00:29:28,890
那你倒是說該怎么形容
How exactly would you describe it?

735
00:29:28,890 --> 00:29:31,180
我不是去操縱他的  好嗎
I didn't go there to manipulate him, all right?

736
00:29:31,180 --> 00:29:32,520
他要做一個將會影響
He--he was about to make a decision

737
00:29:32,520 --> 00:29:34,880
他  我們  以及他的客戶的決定
that was going to affect him, us, and his client,

738
00:29:34,880 --> 00:29:35,990
我只是把它擺在他面前罷了
and I just pointed that out to him.

739
00:29:35,990 --> 00:29:37,060
當你發現它不起作用的時候
And then when that didn't work,

740
00:29:37,060 --> 00:29:38,140
你說我不會同意
you pointed out that I wouldn't approve.

741
00:29:38,140 --> 00:29:39,070
他當時是在欺負我
He was bullying me.

742
00:29:39,070 --> 00:29:41,020
所以你就利用我倒打一耙
So you used me to bully him back.

743
00:29:42,470 --> 00:29:45,080
我得知這事的時候正在和我媽
I was talking to my mom about moving in with you

744
00:29:45,080 --> 00:29:46,260
討論和你同居的事情
when I found out about this.

745
00:29:46,260 --> 00:29:47,440
好吧  瑞秋
Okay, Rachel...

746
00:29:48,460 --> 00:29:50,210
我很抱歉
I'm sorry, all right?

747
00:29:50,210 --> 00:29:52,040
我們現在就給他打電話  我給他道歉
Let me call him right now. I'll apologize to him--

748
00:29:52,040 --> 00:29:53,210
他
Him?

749
00:29:53,240 --> 00:29:55,070
-他太喜歡你這樣了  -真的嗎
- He loved it! - He did?

750
00:29:55,070 --> 00:29:56,330
他覺得你有膽識
Yeah, he thought you had balls.

751
00:29:56,330 --> 00:29:59,220
-那還有什么問題  -你聽我說話了嗎
- So then what's the problem? - Are you not listening to me?

752
00:29:59,220 --> 00:30:01,070
正在考慮是否要和你同居的是我
I was thinking about moving in with you,

753
00:30:01,070 --> 00:30:03,270
之后是我發現你找我爸
and then I find out that you go to my dad--

754
00:30:03,270 --> 00:30:07,110
等等 你是說這改變了一切嗎
Wait, wait, wait. Are-- are you saying this changes everything?

755
00:30:07,110 --> 00:30:09,500
-這很復雜  -有什么復雜的
- It's complicated. - What's complicated about it?

756
00:30:09,500 --> 00:30:11,270
行了當我沒說  我不想和你現在吵這個
Forget--I don't even want to get into this with you right now!

757
00:30:11,270 --> 00:30:12,410
瑞秋  如果你不想和我住
Rachel, if you don't want to live with me,

758
00:30:12,410 --> 00:30:14,080
你為什么不直截了當告訴我呢
why don't you just tell me you don't want to live with me?

759
00:30:14,080 --> 00:30:15,660
我沒這么說
I didn't say that.

760
00:30:17,550 --> 00:30:18,640
那你愿意嗎
Well, do you?

761
00:30:24,780 --> 00:30:27,210
你說過給我一段時間考慮
You said I could have some time, so...

762
00:30:30,020 --> 00:30:31,490
我還需要些時間
I just need some time.

763
00:30:49,450 --> 00:30:51,550
在總收益這項里
You excluded the Folsom Foods payment

764
00:30:51,550 --> 00:30:53,120
你沒算福爾松食品公司
from the revenue totals on this.

765
00:30:53,120 --> 00:30:55,390
那只是個草稿  我沒給任何人看過
It's a draft document. I haven't showed it to anyone.

766
00:30:55,390 --> 00:30:57,010
只想讓你先看看
I just wanted to run it by you.

767
00:30:57,010 --> 00:30:58,540
出于什么原因會讓你
Well, what reason could you possibly have

768
00:30:58,550 --> 00:31:00,150
想要這么做呢
for wanting to do it at all?

769
00:31:00,730 --> 00:31:02,410
因為斯科特來拜托我
Because Scottie came to me and asked,

770
00:31:02,420 --> 00:31:03,640
我覺得是個好交易
and I think it's good business.

771
00:31:03,640 --> 00:31:04,870
你眼里的好交易
Well, your idea of good business

772
00:31:04,880 --> 00:31:06,420
跟我眼里的可不太一樣
is different from mine,

773
00:31:06,420 --> 00:31:09,050
我們已經少拿了福爾松公司的錢
because we already took less money from Folsom Foods,

774
00:31:09,050 --> 00:31:11,260
現在你又想讓我們少拿達比的錢
and now you want us to take less money from Darby.

775
00:31:11,260 --> 00:31:13,650
杰西卡  要是把他惹毛了
Jessica, if we screw him over,

776
00:31:13,650 --> 00:31:15,380
他會報復的
he's gonna come back at us.

777
00:31:15,410 --> 00:31:16,840
也許明天不會
It might not be tomorrow.

778
00:31:16,840 --> 00:31:18,560
六個月之內不會
It might not be six months from now,

779
00:31:18,560 --> 00:31:19,990
但他總會找到機會的
but he's gonna find a way.

780
00:31:19,990 --> 00:31:22,300
-你是想說她會找機會  -就是這個意思
- You mean she'll find a way. - That's exactly what I mean.

781
00:31:22,300 --> 00:31:23,870
也許她會
And maybe she will.

782
00:31:24,110 --> 00:31:26,180
但我從前可沒見你當過逃兵
But I've never known you to run from a fight before.

783
00:31:26,180 --> 00:31:28,510
從前我的名字也沒掛在大門上
My name was never on the door before.

784
00:31:29,040 --> 00:31:30,370
你自已也說過
You said it yourself.

785
00:31:30,860 --> 00:31:33,670
身在其位  就要換個角度看問題
I have to think differently now that I'm in this position.

786
00:31:33,670 --> 00:31:34,950
我的確說過
I did say that.

787
00:31:34,950 --> 00:31:36,760
這可不會是唯一的戰斗
And it's not just gonna be one fight.

788
00:31:36,770 --> 00:31:40,240
這好比哈特菲爾德和麥科伊的恩怨重演
It's gonna be the Hatfields and the McCoys all over again.

789
00:31:40,350 --> 00:31:43,300
你確定這與你和她的往事無關嗎
Are you sure this isn't really about your history with her?

790
00:31:43,990 --> 00:31:46,450
-如果有關呢  -她可能是在耍我們
- What if it is? - She could just be playing us.

791
00:31:46,610 --> 00:31:49,360
也許吧  但  我相信她
She could, but... I trust her.

792
00:31:51,470 --> 00:31:53,280
杰西卡  往事該翻篇了
Jessica, it's time to turn the page.

793
00:31:56,000 --> 00:31:57,880
我可不想翻篇
Well, I don't want to turn the page.

794
00:31:58,140 --> 00:31:59,710
我想跟他們徹底劃清界限
I want to close the book.

795
00:32:01,350 --> 00:32:04,410
告訴她我們會排除福爾松的薪酬  同意交易
Tell her we'll exclude the payment and honor our deal.

796
00:32:10,610 --> 00:32:13,400
路易  我了解事情沒完全按計劃進行
Louis, I know it didn't go exactly as planned,

797
00:32:13,400 --> 00:32:15,910
但你得向前看  振作起來
but you need to pick yourself up and dust yourself off.

798
00:32:15,920 --> 00:32:17,830
完全按照計劃
Exactly as planned?

799
00:32:18,700 --> 00:32:20,270
我徹底失敗了
I utterly failed.

800
00:32:20,380 --> 00:32:21,580
我都不配用這個破杯子
I don't even deserve this stupid mug.

801
00:32:21,580 --> 00:32:23,180
"點亮"  應該寫"放屁"
"Litt up"? It should say "Shit up."

802
00:32:23,180 --> 00:32:25,480
你沒失敗  你讓他印象深刻
You didn't fail. You impressed him.

803
00:32:25,480 --> 00:32:28,690
而且花了45塊給我的貓買了巴西脫毛蠟
Yeah, that and $45 will get my cat a Brazilian bikini wax.

804
00:32:28,820 --> 00:32:30,140
你又養了一只貓
You got a new cat?

805
00:32:30,360 --> 00:32:31,470
替人代養的
Fostering.

806
00:32:31,470 --> 00:32:33,450
路易  夠了
Louis...enough.

807
00:32:33,450 --> 00:32:34,930
你得去找哈維
You need to go to Harvey.

808
00:32:36,940 --> 00:32:38,890
讓我告訴他  我比他嘴里的我
You mean tell him that I'm even more of an embarrassment

809
00:32:38,890 --> 00:32:40,000
還要不堪嗎
than he says I am?

810
00:32:40,000 --> 00:32:41,470
你沒有不堪
You're not an embarrassment.

811
00:32:41,470 --> 00:32:43,910
也許你需要哈維來幫你最后一擊
You may need Harvey to put the ball in the end zone,

812
00:32:43,910 --> 00:32:45,740
主意是你想的  過程是你策劃的
but you had the idea, you set it up,

813
00:32:45,740 --> 00:32:47,910
是你把他帶到得分區的
and you drove the ball down to the one-yard line.

814
00:32:47,910 --> 00:32:50,000
主意不是我想的
No, I didn't have the idea.

815
00:32:50,010 --> 00:32:51,470
是你想出來的
You had the idea!

816
00:32:51,470 --> 00:32:53,370
但是你執行的
And you executed it.

817
00:32:53,590 --> 00:32:54,950
你相信了我
But you're giving me credit.

818
00:32:54,950 --> 00:32:57,460
如果哈維幫你  他也會相信你的
If Harvey executes this, he'll give you credit.

819
00:32:57,470 --> 00:32:58,890
他才不會  他就沒信任過我
No, he won't. He never does.

820
00:32:58,890 --> 00:33:01,240
路易  他會的
Louis, he might.

821
00:33:01,650 --> 00:33:03,300
你想讓他見識到你的另一面
You want him to see a different side of you,

822
00:33:03,300 --> 00:33:05,130
也給他一個機會展示他的另一面
give him a chance to show a different side of him.

823
00:33:05,130 --> 00:33:07,010
已經不重要了
You know what? It doesn't matter anyway.

824
00:33:07,010 --> 00:33:08,410
哈維已經不需要我的幫助了
Harvey doesn't need my help anymore.

825
00:33:08,410 --> 00:33:10,550
-已經晚了  -才沒有
- It's too late. - No, it isn't.

826
00:33:11,580 --> 00:33:12,950
你沒聽說嗎
Haven't you heard?

827
00:33:13,210 --> 00:33:14,230
聽說什么
Heard what?

828
00:33:31,620 --> 00:33:33,040
哈維  我有些壞消息
Harvey, I have some bad news.

829
00:33:33,050 --> 00:33:35,480
-什么消息  -你還是坐下聽吧
- What is it? - I think you should sit down.

830
00:33:35,480 --> 00:33:37,610
唐娜  有人死了我才需要坐下
Donna, unless someone died, I don't need to sit down.

831
00:33:37,610 --> 00:33:40,130
-說吧  -海辛頓石油解雇了我們
- Just tell me. - Hessington Oil just fired us.

832
00:33:48,110 --> 00:33:50,350
-斯科特騙了我  -不一定是這樣
- Scottie betrayed me. - You don't know that.

833
00:33:50,350 --> 00:33:52,490
一加一等于二  唐娜
One plus one equals two, Donna.

834
00:33:52,490 --> 00:33:54,200
我會算數
And I know how to goddamn add.

835
00:33:54,200 --> 00:33:55,760
我沒計入福爾松的錢
I didn't count the Folsom money,

836
00:33:55,760 --> 00:33:58,030
突然之間石油公司的收益也沒了
and suddenly our Oil revenues are gone

837
00:33:58,030 --> 00:33:59,940
而她的利益一下子飛漲
and her piece of the pie just skyrocketed.

838
00:33:59,940 --> 00:34:02,270
哈維  別倉促下定論
Harvey, please, don't do anything rash.

839
00:34:02,270 --> 00:34:03,260
你什么意思
What the hell are you saying?

840
00:34:03,260 --> 00:34:05,890
-給她打個電話  -我要說什么
- I'm saying call her. - How would that go?

841
00:34:05,890 --> 00:34:08,150
斯科特  謝謝你耍的我團團轉
"Hey, Scottie, thanks for dicking me over.

842
00:34:08,150 --> 00:34:09,140
能求你別鬧了嗎
Could you please take it back?"

843
00:34:09,140 --> 00:34:11,010
你根本不了解實情
You don't know how it would go.

844
00:34:11,040 --> 00:34:12,990
只要你放下身段聽聽她的說辭
And you could find out if you would drop your pride

845
00:34:12,990 --> 00:34:15,230
就能了解情況了
and just give her the benefit of the doubt.

846
00:34:15,380 --> 00:34:17,120
你倒是聽信某人的甜言蜜語了
You gave someone the benefit of the doubt,

847
00:34:17,120 --> 00:34:18,750
看看你的下場
and look how that turned out.

848
00:34:20,940 --> 00:34:22,380
你以為給我買個手包
You think just because you bought me a handbag,

849
00:34:22,380 --> 00:34:23,850
就能這么跟我說話了嗎
you can say that to me?

850
00:34:25,650 --> 00:34:27,360
對不起  我不該那樣說
Okay, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said that.

851
00:34:27,360 --> 00:34:28,870
但我被人耍了
But I just got played,

852
00:34:28,870 --> 00:34:31,710
我不打算打給斯科特跟她哭訴
and I'm not about to call Scottie and cry about it.

853
00:34:31,710 --> 00:34:33,490
-那你要做什么  -我要想個法子
- So what are you gonna do? - I'm gonna figure out

854
00:34:33,490 --> 00:34:35,820
以牙還牙
how to do to her what she just did to me.

855
00:34:45,030 --> 00:34:46,270
-哈維  -現在別煩我  路易
- Harvey. - Not now, Louis.

856
00:34:46,270 --> 00:34:47,690
就得現在  我有答案了
Yes, now, Harvey. I've got the answer.

857
00:34:47,690 --> 00:34:48,440
什么的答案
The answer to what?

858
00:34:48,450 --> 00:34:51,440
如何煽動海辛頓石油跟愛德華·達比對掐
To shoving the Hessington Oil firing up Edward Darby's ass.

859
00:34:51,730 --> 00:34:52,620
哈維
Harvey.

860
00:34:52,930 --> 00:34:53,930
哈維
Harvey!

861
00:34:56,120 --> 00:34:57,390
托尼·揚諾普洛斯
Tony Gianopolous.

862
00:34:58,320 --> 00:35:00,750
他能給出損失在海辛頓石油的價錢的三倍
He can triple the revenue we lost with Hessington Oil.

863
00:35:00,750 --> 00:35:02,920
而且他們也不能算是新客戶
And they're technically not a new client.

864
00:35:02,920 --> 00:35:04,780
斯科特無法插手
So there's nothing Scottie can do.

865
00:35:04,970 --> 00:35:06,480
為什么你會認為他會這么干
Well, what makes you think he's gonna go for it?

866
00:35:06,480 --> 00:35:09,250
因為我去過了  他們已經準備答應了
Because I went there, and they are primed to say yes.

867
00:35:09,250 --> 00:35:10,650
但他們不會
They just won't...

868
00:35:11,870 --> 00:35:13,430
他們不會答應我
They just won't say yes to me.

869
00:35:15,180 --> 00:35:17,570
給他看這個  他就會答應你了
Give him this. They'll say yes to you.

870
00:35:23,590 --> 00:35:25,280
路易  這太棒了
Louis, this is brilliant.

871
00:35:26,010 --> 00:35:28,190
要是你沒種來找我的話
And if you hadn't had the balls to come to me,

872
00:35:28,700 --> 00:35:29,780
我們就一無所獲了
we'd have nothing right now.

873
00:35:29,780 --> 00:35:30,930
哈維
Harvey, no.

874
00:35:31,330 --> 00:35:32,520
我本該早點兒找你的
I should have come to you sooner,

875
00:35:32,520 --> 00:35:34,440
-但我沒有就因為...  -路易
- but I didn't because I just-- - Louis.

876
00:35:35,160 --> 00:35:36,630
這話我以前說過
I've told you this before,

877
00:35:36,630 --> 00:35:39,060
但那通常是有求于你的場面話
but it's always been when I needed something from you.

878
00:35:39,300 --> 00:35:41,580
現在我對你無欲無求
And I don't need anything from you right now,

879
00:35:41,910 --> 00:35:43,480
因為你已經幫完我了
because you just gave it to me.

880
00:35:43,480 --> 00:35:45,650
也許你能聽進去我說的話
So maybe you can hear it when I say it--

881
00:35:46,940 --> 00:35:48,280
我尊重你
I respect you.

882
00:35:50,240 --> 00:35:51,910
你是一個出色的律師
You're an excellent attorney,

883
00:35:52,450 --> 00:35:54,350
律所里寶貴的一員
a valuable member of this firm.

884
00:35:57,510 --> 00:35:58,660
一個朋友
And a friend?

885
00:35:59,590 --> 00:36:00,760
別為難我
Don't push it.

886
00:36:02,020 --> 00:36:02,970
抱歉
Sorry.

887
00:36:04,420 --> 00:36:06,820
說真的  哈維  我得說
Seriously, Harvey, I just have to say, um...

888
00:36:09,470 --> 00:36:11,480
你說的這些  對我意義重大
It means so much when you say all that.

889
00:36:11,480 --> 00:36:12,920
要給你張紙巾什么的嗎
Do you need a tissue or something?

890
00:36:12,920 --> 00:36:13,760
能用你的手帕嗎
Can I use your pocket square?

891
00:36:13,760 --> 00:36:15,400
絕對不行
Under no circumstances.

892
00:36:15,690 --> 00:36:18,170
我會沒事的  你和杰西卡
I'll be fine. And you and Jessica

893
00:36:18,180 --> 00:36:19,770
應該馬上把東西拿給揚諾普洛斯
need to take that over to Gianopolous right now.

894
00:36:19,770 --> 00:36:21,780
別扯了  咱倆一起去
Screw that. I'm going over there with you.

895
00:36:29,910 --> 00:36:30,960
他不在
He's not there.

896
00:36:32,040 --> 00:36:32,800
什么  他去哪兒了
What? Where is he?

897
00:36:32,800 --> 00:36:34,500
他去找托尼·揚諾普洛斯了
He went to see Tony Gianopolous.

898
00:36:34,500 --> 00:36:36,910
-自己去的  -不是  跟路易一起
- By himself? - No, with Louis.

899
00:36:37,260 --> 00:36:39,350
跟路易  他生我氣了嗎
With Louis? What, is he mad at me?

900
00:36:39,710 --> 00:36:41,760
生你氣的只有瑞秋
Rachel's the only one who's mad at you.

901
00:36:43,100 --> 00:36:44,090
她告訴你了
She told you.

902
00:36:44,100 --> 00:36:45,030
都不需要她張嘴
She didn't have to.

903
00:36:45,030 --> 00:36:45,770
你對著她爸瞎扯的時候
What were you thinking,

904
00:36:45,770 --> 00:36:47,120
你腦袋里在想什么
pulling all that shit with her dad?

905
00:36:47,120 --> 00:36:48,430
我也沒料到會發展成這樣
I didn't think it would come to that.

906
00:36:48,430 --> 00:36:50,240
他都不介意  她又為什么要介意呢
He didn't mind. Why should she?

907
00:36:51,290 --> 00:36:54,140
但凡對女人有一點了解的人
Anyone who understands women in any way

908
00:36:54,140 --> 00:36:56,020
都知道那根本就是個壞主意
would know that was a bad idea from the start.

909
00:36:56,020 --> 00:36:57,180
哈維就喜歡
Harvey liked it.

910
00:36:57,180 --> 00:36:58,470
這正好證明了我的觀點
Proving my point.

911
00:37:01,760 --> 00:37:03,500
我問她搬進來跟我一起住
I asked her to move in with me.

912
00:37:03,600 --> 00:37:04,350
我知道
I know.

913
00:37:04,350 --> 00:37:05,690
她告訴你的
She told you?

914
00:37:05,820 --> 00:37:07,110
當然是她告訴我的了
Of course she did.

915
00:37:07,110 --> 00:37:07,980
我又不能感知事物
I can't intuit everything.

916
00:37:07,980 --> 00:37:09,600
那我成什么了  達賴喇嘛嗎
What am I, the Dalai Lama?

917
00:37:09,600 --> 00:37:11,470
唐娜  你真該看看我問她時她的表情
Donna, you should have seen her face when I asked her.

918
00:37:11,470 --> 00:37:13,450
她高興極了
She was so happy.

919
00:37:13,450 --> 00:37:15,300
我猜也是  太浪漫了
I'm sure she was. It was very romantic.

920
00:37:15,300 --> 00:37:17,770
她這么高興為什么又不想來呢
How could she be so happy and then just not want to do it?

921
00:37:17,770 --> 00:37:19,500
誰說她不想來的
Who says she doesn't want to do it?

922
00:37:20,560 --> 00:37:22,060
我讓她好好考慮考慮
I told her to take her time,

923
00:37:22,210 --> 00:37:23,540
但我覺得她不需要時間考慮
but I-I didn't think she'd need it.

924
00:37:23,540 --> 00:37:25,040
為什么不需要
Why wouldn't she need it?

925
00:37:26,200 --> 00:37:27,790
不能因為你做些浪漫的事情
Just because you made some romantic gesture

926
00:37:27,790 --> 00:37:29,550
她就不需要考慮一切因果
doesn't mean that all reason goes out the window.

927
00:37:29,550 --> 00:37:31,480
我從昨晚起就心里沒底了
I've had a pit in my stomach since last night.

928
00:37:31,480 --> 00:37:32,780
我...
I...

929
00:37:33,570 --> 00:37:35,100
我得做點什么
I need to do something.

930
00:37:35,530 --> 00:37:37,110
你該去照照鏡子
You need to look in the mirror.

931
00:37:38,420 --> 00:37:39,460
什么
What?

932
00:37:40,440 --> 00:37:41,990
我才剛談了一場戀愛
I just jumped into a relationship with a man

933
00:37:41,990 --> 00:37:43,160
發現對方
who, it turns out,

934
00:37:43,160 --> 00:37:45,270
一切都是假的
was pretending to be something he wasn't.

935
00:37:45,890 --> 00:37:46,700
瑞秋已經知道
Rachel already knows

936
00:37:46,700 --> 00:37:48,830
你的學歷是假的了
that you're pretending to be something you're not.

937
00:37:49,830 --> 00:37:51,380
你現在需要做的就是  給她時間
All you need to do is just give her time

938
00:37:51,390 --> 00:37:53,040
讓她自己想清楚
to figure it all out.

939
00:37:54,790 --> 00:37:56,040
如果她不同意呢
What if she says no?

940
00:37:56,850 --> 00:37:58,190
那她就是不同意
Then she says no.

941
00:37:59,390 --> 00:38:01,740
逼迫她也不能避免這一切
But pushing her isn't going to stop that from happening.

942
00:38:07,100 --> 00:38:08,910
如果你是來控訴海辛頓石油的事情
If you're here to complain about Hessington Oil,

943
00:38:08,910 --> 00:38:10,320
我也束手無策
I had nothing to do with it.

944
00:38:10,320 --> 00:38:11,720
我只是大股東
I'm just the majority shareholder.

945
00:38:11,720 --> 00:38:13,590
我不管日常事務
I don't get involved in day-to-day stuff.

946
00:38:13,590 --> 00:38:14,860
我們不是來控訴的
We're not here to complain.

947
00:38:15,280 --> 00:38:16,400
我們帶了禮物來的
We're here to bring a gift.

948
00:38:16,400 --> 00:38:17,930
問題是  你能把什么東西給一個
The question is, what do you get a man

949
00:38:17,930 --> 00:38:19,940
把一張五萬美元的債券燒掉的人
who can burn a $50,000 bond?

950
00:38:19,940 --> 00:38:21,590
這可是錢買不到的東西
Something money can't buy.

951
00:38:25,600 --> 00:38:26,320
這還沒公開
This isn't public.

952
00:38:26,320 --> 00:38:28,600
48小時內會公開的  現在已經合法了
It will be in 48 hours. And it's legal now.

953
00:38:29,000 --> 00:38:29,800
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?

954
00:38:29,800 --> 00:38:31,490
因為我就是這么設計的
Because I structured it that way.

955
00:38:31,670 --> 00:38:33,690
我能為你做更多同樣的事情  但他沒告訴你
I can do more of the same for you, but he didn't tell you,

956
00:38:33,690 --> 00:38:35,350
因為我還不夠有名
Because I wasn't enough of a name.

957
00:38:36,580 --> 00:38:38,840
-確實  -但我夠了
- You're not. - But I am.

958
00:38:39,480 --> 00:38:41,360
確實  你行事直率
Well, you are, as a man who shoots from the hip,

959
00:38:41,360 --> 00:38:42,420
我很喜歡  但是
which I like, but--

960
00:38:42,420 --> 00:38:44,230
你需要樹立穩定的影響
You also need a stabilizing influence.

961
00:38:44,230 --> 00:38:45,250
不需要橄欖球運動員
Not a football player.

962
00:38:45,250 --> 00:38:46,580
而是個芭蕾舞迷
But a fan of the ballet.

963
00:38:46,590 --> 00:38:47,660
肌肉健碩
Muscle.

964
00:38:47,770 --> 00:38:49,250
靈活自如
And finesse.

965
00:38:49,960 --> 00:38:51,230
你們以為我不知道
And you guys think that I'm not aware

966
00:38:51,230 --> 00:38:53,220
這一切都跟你們的合并談判有關嗎
that this is all about your merger negotiations.

967
00:38:53,220 --> 00:38:54,990
我還指望你能意識到呢
Oh, I was counting on you being aware of it.

968
00:38:54,990 --> 00:38:55,730
因為那時候你也會發現
Because then you'll also be aware

969
00:38:55,740 --> 00:38:57,800
我們可以非常靈活地處理賬單
that we can be very flexible in our billings.

970
00:38:57,800 --> 00:38:59,210
只要我先付給你們一大筆錢
as long as I pay enough up front

971
00:38:59,210 --> 00:39:00,640
以助你們扭轉局面
to tip the scales in your favor.

972
00:39:00,640 --> 00:39:02,300
我們會設計一份計劃
We'll structure a schedule that results

973
00:39:02,300 --> 00:39:04,120
助你獲取大筆財務收益
in you getting a substantial financial benefit.

974
00:39:04,120 --> 00:39:05,870
這是他的專長
Which is his specialty.

975
00:39:06,410 --> 00:39:07,720
說吧  告訴他
Go ahead. Tell him.

976
00:39:08,250 --> 00:39:09,420
他很厲害
He's a badass.

977
00:39:11,190 --> 00:39:13,560
你覺得我們在芝加哥與邁克爾·喬丹共進晚餐
What do you say we celebrate our new association

978
00:39:13,570 --> 00:39:16,820
慶祝我們的新聯盟如何
over dinner in Chicago with Michael Jordan?

979
00:39:16,820 --> 00:39:18,270
我們可以坐我的私人飛機過去
We can take my private jet.

980
00:39:18,270 --> 00:39:20,180
這樣我們就能買單
Hey! Which will allow us to pay for it

981
00:39:20,180 --> 00:39:21,760
再找你報銷了
and for you to write it off.

982
00:39:39,600 --> 00:39:41,170
我知道你可能很忙
I know you're probably busy...

983
00:39:41,310 --> 00:39:42,550
其實沒有
I'm actually not.

984
00:39:50,110 --> 00:39:51,810
瑞秋  我...
Rachel, I...

985
00:39:52,390 --> 00:39:54,000
我知道跟我在一起很復雜
I know that dating me is complicated--

986
00:39:54,000 --> 00:39:55,430
-邁克  -我只是
- Mike-- - I just--

987
00:39:58,270 --> 00:40:01,090
我只想告訴你  你有充分的時間考慮
I just want you to know you can take as much time as you need.

988
00:40:03,920 --> 00:40:05,120
我愛你
I love you.

989
00:40:10,540 --> 00:40:11,780
我也愛你
I love you too.

990
00:40:17,230 --> 00:40:18,750
我被斯坦福錄取了
I got into Stanford.

991
00:40:30,610 --> 00:40:32,080
你到底是怎么回事
What the hell is wrong with you?

992
00:40:33,610 --> 00:40:35,500
看來你已經受到我的回擊了
I see you got my little gut punch.

993
00:40:35,500 --> 00:40:37,450
我畢恭畢敬地來找你  你就是這么對我的嗎
I came to you hat in hand, and this is what you do--

994
00:40:37,450 --> 00:40:38,510
暗中改了數字嗎
Stack the numbers?

995
00:40:38,510 --> 00:40:39,360
畢恭畢敬
Hat in hand?

996
00:40:39,360 --> 00:40:41,290
其實是披著羊皮的狼吧
More like a wolf in sheep's clothing.

997
00:40:41,290 --> 00:40:42,690
你在說什么
What are you talking about?

998
00:40:42,690 --> 00:40:43,610
海辛頓石油
Hessington Oil.

999
00:40:43,610 --> 00:40:45,440
跟我沒關系
I had nothing to do with that.

1000
00:40:45,440 --> 00:40:47,130
我一說要放你一馬
Something dropped from the sky,

1001
00:40:47,130 --> 00:40:48,490
就突然刮起東風
tilted everything in your favor

1002
00:40:48,500 --> 00:40:50,670
讓你開始轉劣勢為優勢嗎  我看不是吧
right after I cut you a break? I don't think so.

1003
00:40:50,670 --> 00:40:53,600
哈維  既然我跟你承諾了  我就會遵守
Harvey, I gave you my word, and I honored it.

1004
00:40:53,600 --> 00:40:55,120
胡說  你那么說
Bullshit. You're just saying that

1005
00:40:55,120 --> 00:40:56,270
至少因為我占據了上風
because I've got the upper hand.

1006
00:40:56,270 --> 00:40:57,470
這跟什么上風沒關系
This is not about the upper hand.

1007
00:40:57,470 --> 00:40:58,560
你總是在扯什么上風
You're always about the upper hand!

1008
00:40:58,560 --> 00:40:59,970
哈維  住口
Harvey, stop.

1009
00:41:01,270 --> 00:41:03,570
我來找你  求你幫忙
I came to you and asked for mercy.

1010
00:41:04,210 --> 00:41:06,170
你知道那對我來說有多難嗎
Do you know how hard that was for me?

1011
00:41:06,530 --> 00:41:08,130
然后我一轉身就利用這一切來欺騙你
And then for me to turn around and use that to dupe you--

1012
00:41:08,130 --> 00:41:09,490
你怎么會以為我會那么做
How could you think I would do that?

1013
00:41:09,490 --> 00:41:10,730
那你會怎么想
Well, what would you have thought?

1014
00:41:10,730 --> 00:41:12,870
我不知道  但你可以給我打電話啊
I don't know, but you could have called me.

1015
00:41:12,920 --> 00:41:13,920
說什么
And say what?

1016
00:41:13,920 --> 00:41:16,990
讓我把解雇排除掉
And asked me to exclude the firing from the calculations.

1017
00:41:17,000 --> 00:41:17,840
我不會
I'm not gonna do--

1018
00:41:17,840 --> 00:41:19,110
什么  你不會做什么
What? You're not gonna do what?

1019
00:41:19,110 --> 00:41:20,850
不會給我機會  讓我利用你的疑慮
Not gonna give me the benefit of the doubt

1020
00:41:20,850 --> 00:41:23,020
和你的脆弱  暴露你自己嗎
and be vulnerable-- expose yourself?

1021
00:41:23,600 --> 00:41:25,620
我以前信任你的時候就是那樣做的
I already did that when I trusted you.

1022
00:41:26,760 --> 00:41:29,490
那只是憐憫  這源于你的實力地位
That was mercy, which is from a position of strength.

1023
00:41:29,530 --> 00:41:32,140
而脆弱則是源于弱勢地位
Being vulnerable is from a position of weakness.

1024
00:41:33,300 --> 00:41:34,890
我不會那么做的
Well, I'm not gonna do that.

1025
00:41:38,560 --> 00:41:40,290
那我也不會那樣做的
Well, then I guess I'm not going to either.

1026
00:41:41,100 --> 00:41:41,840
意味著什么
Meaning what?

1027
00:41:41,840 --> 00:41:44,590
意味著我不會再解散這次合并了
Meaning that I am not going to dissolve this merger.

1028
00:41:44,990 --> 00:41:46,140
你已經簽署了協議
You already signed the agreement.

1029
00:41:46,140 --> 00:41:47,430
那就起訴我啊
Then sue me.

1030
00:41:48,250 --> 00:41:50,010
反正你也會對我開炮的
You're gonna totally shaft me anyway.

1031
00:41:50,750 --> 00:41:52,030
能對我有什么不利呢
What's my downside?

1032
00:41:52,360 --> 00:41:53,860
同時  你們有一位冠名合伙人
In the meantime, you'll have a name partner

1033
00:41:53,860 --> 00:41:56,510
并不能在美國執業  他的名聲壞透了
who can't practice in America, whose reputation is shit,

1034
00:41:56,510 --> 00:41:58,290
誰會阻止你們在未來五年的訴訟中
and who's gonna tie up all your profits in litigation

1035
00:41:58,290 --> 00:41:59,690
獲取利潤呢
for the next five years.

1036
00:41:59,810 --> 00:42:01,280
你愿意這么做
You're willing to do all that

1037
00:42:01,280 --> 00:42:03,250
還指望我相信你  我們被解雇
and expect me to believe you weren't behind

1038
00:42:03,250 --> 00:42:04,640
不是你在幕后操作的
us getting fired in the first place.

1039
00:42:04,640 --> 00:42:06,440
她說的是實話  哈維
She's telling the truth, Harvey.

1040
00:42:06,440 --> 00:42:08,310
-什么  -斯科特沒有害我們被解雇
- What? - Scottie didn't get us fired.

1041
00:42:08,310 --> 00:42:10,600
-艾娃·海辛頓解雇的  -說明不了什么
- Ava Hessington did. - That doesn't mean anything.

1042
00:42:10,600 --> 00:42:12,310
完全有可能是斯科特一手操控的
Scottie could have arranged it.

1043
00:42:12,430 --> 00:42:13,730
她沒有
Well, she didn't,

1044
00:42:13,740 --> 00:42:15,230
因為艾娃不僅解雇了我們
Because Ava didn't just fire us.

1045
00:42:15,230 --> 00:42:17,530
還將以玩忽職守
She's suing all of us...

1046
00:42:17,610 --> 00:42:19,370
起訴我們所有人
for malpractice.

