1
00:00:00,990 --> 00:00:02,260
《诉讼双雄》前情提要

2
00:00:02,380 --> 00:00:03,550
我十一岁那年
When I was 11,

3
00:00:03,560 --> 00:00:06,280
我父母遇到了一起严重事故
my parents were involved in a really horrible accident.

4
00:00:06,280 --> 00:00:07,430
我的奶奶收留了我
My grandmother took me in.

5
00:00:07,560 --> 00:00:09,770
是你奶奶  她去世了
It's your grandma. She passed away.

6
00:00:09,910 --> 00:00:12,190
一种结果是杰西卡继续留任
Either Jessica will retain her position,

7
00:00:12,190 --> 00:00:14,970
另一种就是我重新掌管皮尔逊·哈德曼律所
or I will resume control of Pearson Hardman.

8
00:00:14,970 --> 00:00:17,660
我有权每年任命一位新的资深合伙人
I'm entitled to name one new senior partner a year.

9
00:00:17,660 --> 00:00:21,310
若你站错了队伍  可没有后悔药
if you are on the wrong side, there'll be no coming back.

10
00:00:21,430 --> 00:00:24,200
新执行合伙人是丹尼尔·哈德曼
The managing partner is Daniel Hardman.

11
00:00:24,200 --> 00:00:26,240
杰西卡输了  你输了
Jessica lost! You lost!

12
00:00:26,240 --> 00:00:28,310
你又想到什么新法子来折磨我了吗
You looking for another way to make my life miserable?

13
00:00:28,310 --> 00:00:30,370
佐伊  我还是不确定我是否该雇你
Zoe, I'm still not convinced I should hire you.

14
00:00:30,370 --> 00:00:32,350
毕竟  哈维可没想睡泰德·菲利普斯
Well, Harvey never tried to sleep with Ted Phillips.

15
00:00:32,350 --> 00:00:33,430
希拉·赛斯女士
Ms. Sheila Zass.

16
00:00:33,570 --> 00:00:35,800
我看路易迷上女版的自己了
I think Louis is attracted to female Louis.

17
00:00:35,970 --> 00:00:37,830
-我叫苔丝  -那你们一定交情颇深了
- I'm Tess. - You guys must go way back.

18
00:00:37,830 --> 00:00:40,110
第一罐啤酒  第一次毕业舞会  第一次做爱
First beer, prom, sex.

19
00:00:40,960 --> 00:00:42,080
你祖母才刚去世
Your grandmother just died.

20
00:00:42,080 --> 00:00:43,090
就是在这种时候
When something like that happens,

21
00:00:43,090 --> 00:00:44,860
人往往没法做出明智的决定
people don't make smart choices.

22
00:00:44,860 --> 00:00:47,100
-你结婚了  -不过你还是打给我了
- You're married. - And you called me anyway.

23
00:00:47,100 --> 00:00:48,350
也许当初就是哈德曼捏造了
What if Hardman planted

24
00:00:48,350 --> 00:00:49,500
那份科斯特尔汽车的备忘
the CM memo in the first place?

25
00:00:49,510 --> 00:00:52,500
有人赞成丹尼尔·哈德曼离职吗
All those in favor of Daniel Hardman's dismissal?

26
00:00:54,280 --> 00:00:56,130
我不在乎是否明智
I don't care about being smart.

27
00:01:15,690 --> 00:01:17,940
提醒一句  披萨吃完了
FYI, we're out of pizza.

28
00:01:18,120 --> 00:01:19,760
你居然现在告诉我
You're telling me this now?

29
00:01:20,250 --> 00:01:21,910
我怎么知道你在嗑药
I didn't know you were gonna get high.

30
00:01:21,910 --> 00:01:23,810
你是说  你不知道我俩会嗑药
You mean you didn't know we were gonna get high.

31
00:01:24,070 --> 00:01:26,560
你是明天不打算去上班了吗
Oh, does this mean you're not going back to work tomorrow?

32
00:01:26,560 --> 00:01:28,840
不是  我是在庆祝明天能回去上班
No, it means I'm celebrating going back to work tomorrow.

33
00:01:28,840 --> 00:01:29,770
随你怎么说
Fine.

34
00:01:29,960 --> 00:01:31,940
别以为我不知道你在干什么
But don't think I don't know what you're really doing.

35
00:01:31,940 --> 00:01:33,830
怎么  我还需要让你嗑药  
What, getting you high,

36
00:01:33,830 --> 00:01:35,170
才能脱掉你的裤子  
so I can get into your pants

37
00:01:35,170 --> 00:01:36,390
或者扯下这块布吗
or under your sheet or whatever?

38
00:01:36,390 --> 00:01:37,720
我是说  你害怕了
I meant you're afraid.

39
00:01:38,670 --> 00:01:40,640
害怕  怎么可能
Afraid? Nope.

40
00:01:40,640 --> 00:01:42,400
我才不害怕呢  迫不及待想回去
I'm not afraid, I can't wait to get back.

41
00:01:42,400 --> 00:01:44,230
迫不及待想去和瑞秋谈谈吗
You can't wait to get back to talk to Rachel?

42
00:01:46,920 --> 00:01:48,540
我才不怕和瑞秋聊呢
I am not afraid to talk to Rachel.

43
00:01:48,540 --> 00:01:49,840
我还不怕大灰狼呢
And I'm not afraid of the big, bad wolf.

44
00:01:49,840 --> 00:01:51,540
我告诉过你  她就是个朋友
Look, I told you, she's a friend.

45
00:01:51,540 --> 00:01:53,700
过来看看我而已  就这么简单
She was just coming to check up on me, that's all.

46
00:01:53,840 --> 00:01:55,180
我也告诉过你  我相信过你
And I told you I believed you.

47
00:01:55,320 --> 00:01:56,350
不用谢啊
You're welcome.

48
00:01:57,770 --> 00:02:00,220
为什么不能假装相信我呢
So why can't you just keep pretending you believe me now?

49
00:02:00,420 --> 00:02:02,780
因为你明天要回去上班
Because you have to go back to work tomorrow.

50
00:02:04,600 --> 00:02:06,680
你丈夫明天也要回来了
And your husband gets back in town tomorrow.

51
00:02:09,510 --> 00:02:10,570
-还要披萨吗  -那就再订点吧
- You want more pizza? - Let's order more pizza.

52
00:02:10,570 --> 00:02:11,750
-好  -就这样
- Yeah. - Great.

53
00:02:30,280 --> 00:02:31,720
有人给你升职啦
Somebody give you a promotion?

54
00:02:31,720 --> 00:02:33,080
某人是该给我升职
Somebody should.

55
00:02:33,670 --> 00:02:36,910
洛佩兹并购推迟  菲利普合并完结
Lopez buyout delayed, Phillips merger closed.

56
00:02:36,920 --> 00:02:39,890
佐伊·劳福德打电话来了  很奇怪啊
Oh, and Zoe Lawford called, which is odd,

57
00:02:39,900 --> 00:02:41,500
我可不记得有哪个案子
because I don't remember us having a trial

58
00:02:41,500 --> 00:02:43,180
需要咨询服务的
we needed consulting services on.

59
00:02:43,180 --> 00:02:44,580
所以你才坐在我桌前
So that's why you're sitting at my desk.

60
00:02:44,580 --> 00:02:46,930
在捉弄你时  我希望能高你一等
I wanted to be in a position of power when I toyed with you.

61
00:02:50,200 --> 00:02:51,480
有件事可讲清楚了
Let's get one thing clear.

62
00:02:51,620 --> 00:02:52,870
我不是查理·布朗
I'm not Charlie Brown,

63
00:02:51,620 --> 00:02:54,810
动画片史努比中情节  露西总是让查理信任自己
又在查理踢球前把球抽走

64
00:02:53,000 --> 00:02:54,810
你也不是露西  这件事也不是橄榄球
You're not Lucy, and that's not a football.

65
00:02:55,470 --> 00:02:56,650
有两件事可讲清楚了
Let's get two things clear.

66
00:02:57,030 --> 00:02:59,220
我不记得给佐伊打过电话
I don't remember ever placing a call to Zoe,

67
00:02:59,430 --> 00:03:01,730
但她的留言说  她是回电
but her message said she was calling back.

68
00:03:01,930 --> 00:03:04,020
我打给她了  出于公事
I called her. For business.

69
00:03:04,020 --> 00:03:06,650
什么样的公事  合并吗
What kind of business? A merger?

70
00:03:06,810 --> 00:03:08,120
够了  你多大了  十二岁吗
Okay, what are you, 12 years old?

71
00:03:08,120 --> 00:03:09,370
玩老少恋的可不是我
I'm not the one robbing the cradle here.

72
00:03:09,370 --> 00:03:10,440
我可没玩老少恋
I'm not robbing anything.

73
00:03:10,440 --> 00:03:12,360
-佐伊和我年纪一样大  -是承认了吗
- Zoe and I are the same age. - So you admit it.

74
00:03:12,360 --> 00:03:13,660
是你打电话约她出来
You called to ask her on a date.

75
00:03:13,800 --> 00:03:15,410
-还背着我  -这不是背着你
- Behind my back. - It wasn't behind your back.

76
00:03:15,410 --> 00:03:16,340
你那时已经回家了
You'd gone home already.

77
00:03:16,340 --> 00:03:17,580
因为你特地等到我回家
Because you waited for me to go home.

78
00:03:17,580 --> 00:03:19,150
正如我所说  背着你
Like I said, it was behind your back.

79
00:03:22,120 --> 00:03:24,740
哈维  我只是好奇
Harvey, just out of curiosity,

80
00:03:24,750 --> 00:03:26,440
你怎么过了这么久才联系她
what took you so long to call her?

81
00:03:26,750 --> 00:03:28,280
我对付哈德曼还忙不过来呢
I had my hands full with Hardman.

82
00:03:28,280 --> 00:03:29,650
现在你该为她焦头烂额了
Well, now you're hands full of her.

83
00:03:29,650 --> 00:03:31,820
现在一切都结束了  我想庆祝庆祝
Look, now it's over, I want to celebrate.

84
00:03:31,950 --> 00:03:33,360
而她是庆祝的不二人选
And she's the person I want to do it with.

85
00:03:34,370 --> 00:03:35,400
这话你会对她说吗
Are you gonna tell her that?

86
00:03:36,190 --> 00:03:38,550
你应该听说洛佩兹并购推迟的消息了吧
I assume you heard that the Lopez buyout was delayed?

87
00:03:38,550 --> 00:03:39,260
我需要…
So I'm gonna need some--

88
00:03:39,260 --> 00:03:40,910
路易  我才不管你要什么
Louis, I don't give a shit what you need.

89
00:03:41,190 --> 00:03:42,080
哈维  知道吗
All right, Harvey, you know what?

90
00:03:42,080 --> 00:03:43,420
都一周了
Look, it's been a week.

91
00:03:43,940 --> 00:03:45,760
你赢了  这件事就过去吧
You won, you know, get over it.

92
00:03:45,760 --> 00:03:46,470
出去
Get out.

93
00:03:47,070 --> 00:03:48,310
告诉你一句
You know, for your information,

94
00:03:48,310 --> 00:03:50,380
我可不是唯一投给哈德曼的高级合伙人
I wasn't the only senior partner who voted for Hardman.

95
00:03:50,380 --> 00:03:52,620
我怎么没见你给别人这样的白眼
and I don't see you giving anyone else shit the way you give me.

96
00:03:52,720 --> 00:03:54,180
还有  在紧要关头
And by the way, when the chips were down,

97
00:03:54,180 --> 00:03:55,710
我支持了你  赶走了他
I backed you, I ousted him.

98
00:03:56,210 --> 00:03:57,280
你是说你这样投票的时候吗
You mean when you did this?

99
00:04:00,440 --> 00:04:01,730
路易  你想怎么说都行
Tell yourself whatever you want, Louis,

100
00:04:01,730 --> 00:04:02,880
对着镜子说去
but tell it to yourself.

101
00:04:18,810 --> 00:04:20,490
你是给我伤口上撒盐吗
You here to rip the band-aid off?

102
00:04:20,620 --> 00:04:22,980
奶奶总是说  做错了事就该这样
It's what grammy always said to do when you have a boo-boo.

103
00:04:24,440 --> 00:04:25,340
真的吗
Really?

104
00:04:25,510 --> 00:04:27,180
你要拿她当借口  来摆脱这件事吗
You're gonna use her to get out of this?

105
00:04:29,420 --> 00:04:31,440
瑞秋  我知道你生我的气
Look, Rachel, I understand that you're mad at me.

106
00:04:31,450 --> 00:04:32,360
不  我没有
No, I'm not.

107
00:04:33,880 --> 00:04:34,920
那句话怎么说来着
What's that expression?

108
00:04:34,920 --> 00:04:36,410
愚弄我一次  羞愧的是你
"Fool me once, shame on you.

109
00:04:36,540 --> 00:04:37,710
愚弄我两次
Fool me twice--"

110
00:04:37,710 --> 00:04:38,930
没有人想愚弄谁
Nobody's fooling anybody.

111
00:04:39,270 --> 00:04:40,770
-我很抱歉  -抱歉什么
- I'm sorry. - Sorry for what?

112
00:04:41,750 --> 00:04:43,570
为我看到的事  还是你做的事
For what I saw or what you did?

113
00:04:43,570 --> 00:04:44,370
瑞秋  别这样
Rachel, come on.

114
00:04:44,370 --> 00:04:45,390
-我只想…  -我想问问你
- I'm just trying to-- - Let me just ask you this.

115
00:04:45,390 --> 00:04:47,680
她知道  你搞上她六小时前
Does she know that six hours before you screwed her,

116
00:04:47,680 --> 00:04:48,810
你想搞我吗
you tried to screw me?

117
00:04:50,870 --> 00:04:52,540
别假装拿她当做重点  好吗
Okay, let's not pretend that this is about her, okay?

118
00:04:52,540 --> 00:04:54,130
那她是知道还是不知道
So she knows, or she doesn't?

119
00:04:54,540 --> 00:04:55,690
我是说  你拿她
I mean, is it fair to her

120
00:04:55,690 --> 00:04:57,030
当那晚的备胎  对她公平吗
that she was your second choice that night?

121
00:04:57,030 --> 00:04:59,280
-因为如果我是她  迈克  -她结婚了
- Because if I were her, Mike-- - She's married.

122
00:05:00,820 --> 00:05:01,590
我觉得她并不在乎
I don't think she's really worried

123
00:05:01,590 --> 00:05:03,580
做我的备胎
about being my second choice.

124
00:05:07,260 --> 00:05:08,190
欢迎回来
Welcome back.

125
00:05:08,820 --> 00:05:10,210
准备好迎接精彩的第一天了吗
Who's ready for a great first day?

126
00:05:10,360 --> 00:05:11,820
哈维  拜托能回避一分钟吗
Harvey, can you give us a minute, please?

127
00:05:11,980 --> 00:05:14,500
不能  我们出现危机了  该走了
I can't. We actually have a crisis. We gotta go.

128
00:05:26,460 --> 00:05:28,580
你曾告诉我你能摆平一切  哈维
You once told me you could fix anything, Harvey.

129
00:05:29,030 --> 00:05:30,390
这是我儿子  利亚姆
This is my son, Liam.

130
00:05:31,660 --> 00:05:33,120
你妈妈说你有麻烦了
Your mother says you have a problem.

131
00:05:35,600 --> 00:05:38,980
我昨晚从格林威治开车回家
Um, I was driving home from Greenwich last night.

132
00:05:39,390 --> 00:05:40,320
一个朋友的聚会
A friend's party.

133
00:05:42,330 --> 00:05:43,330
我撞了人
I hit someone.

134
00:05:45,240 --> 00:05:46,400
我  我没看到他
I-I didn't see him.

135
00:05:46,400 --> 00:05:47,790
-他不知从哪儿钻出来  -你喝酒了吗
- He came out of nowhere. - Were you drunk?

136
00:05:48,490 --> 00:05:49,430
别回答那个问题
Don't answer that.

137
00:05:49,930 --> 00:05:52,160
如果庭审的话  我不能让他上庭
If this comes to trial, I can't put him on the stand.

138
00:05:52,160 --> 00:05:53,140
但我没喝酒
But I wasn't drinking.

139
00:05:53,140 --> 00:05:54,070
如果我们问聚会上的其他人
And if we asked everybody else at the party,

140
00:05:54,070 --> 00:05:55,730
他们会也这么说吗
would they tell the same story?

141
00:05:56,520 --> 00:05:58,200
如果走到那一步  我们得知道
If it comes out, we need to know.

142
00:05:59,120 --> 00:06:00,640
你可以去问在场的人
Talk to anyone who was there.

143
00:06:00,640 --> 00:06:02,860
如果我现在就去你车里  会不会找到酒瓶子
What if I checked your car for beer bottles right now?

144
00:06:03,040 --> 00:06:04,940
你去找啊  随便你找
Go ahead. Check anything you want.

145
00:06:05,460 --> 00:06:06,610
我没撒谎
I'm telling the truth.

146
00:06:06,990 --> 00:06:09,300
好了  这是个意外  我们能处理
Okay, it was an accident. We can deal with this.

147
00:06:09,870 --> 00:06:12,900
告诉我  你撞到的那个人怎么样了
Tell me, what happened to the guy you hit?

148
00:06:14,710 --> 00:06:15,550
我不知道
I don't know.

149
00:06:16,580 --> 00:06:18,980
-这就是叫你们来的原因  -什么意思
- That's why we called you. - What do you mean?

150
00:06:19,800 --> 00:06:20,920
他逃逸了
He drove away.

151
00:06:21,200 --> 00:06:24,200
人人影视
YYeTs.com

152
00:06:21,200 --> 00:06:24,200
原创翻译  双语字幕

153
00:06:21,200 --> 00:06:24,200
■

154
00:06:21,200 --> 00:06:24,200
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

155
00:06:24,200 --> 00:06:27,200
翻译：某豚 一不二 爱卿遛小鸟 月月 CiciXT allenlovestar 叽咕

156
00:06:27,200 --> 00:06:30,200
校对：油炸电风扇 月月     总监：月月

157
00:06:30,200 --> 00:06:33,200
后期：仓鼠sama     时间轴：迟迟 凭陵新月

158
00:06:47,600 --> 00:06:49,770
第二季 第十一集

159
00:06:47,600 --> 00:06:49,770
诉 讼 双 雄

160
00:06:47,600 --> 00:06:49,770
蓝光-1080P-SHORTBREHD版调轴风格微修：字幕雷哥

161
00:06:55,580 --> 00:06:56,670
我知道你要说什么
I know exactly what you're gonna say.

162
00:06:56,670 --> 00:06:58,230
我们要了解被撞的人的现状
We have to find out what happened to the guy he hit.

163
00:06:58,230 --> 00:06:59,410
我打电话给各个医院问…
So I'm gonna call all the hospitals...

164
00:06:59,410 --> 00:07:01,290
我觉得你不能再跟这个案子了
I think you need to sit this one out.

165
00:07:01,980 --> 00:07:03,490
我知道我操之过急了
Look, I know I jumped the gun,

166
00:07:03,490 --> 00:07:04,810
但问错一个问题我就出局了吗
but one wrong question and I'm out?

167
00:07:04,810 --> 00:07:06,990
你不是操之过急  是没控制自己的怒气
You weren't jumping the gun, it set you off.

168
00:07:07,000 --> 00:07:07,830
哈维  我没事
Harvey, I'm fine.

169
00:07:07,830 --> 00:07:09,880
我不是在责怪你  我理解
Look, I'm not blaming you, I'm understanding you.

170
00:07:09,880 --> 00:07:11,460
你父母就是因为醉驾交通事故去世的
Your parents were killed by a drunk driver.

171
00:07:11,610 --> 00:07:13,610
-利亚姆说了他没喝酒  -这不重要
- And Liam said he wasn't drunk. - Doesn't matter.

172
00:07:13,610 --> 00:07:15,800
如果是并购案  你的情绪会令你振作
Your emotions get the better of you on a merger.

173
00:07:15,970 --> 00:07:17,430
吉莉安是律所的长期客户
Gillian's a longtime client.

174
00:07:17,430 --> 00:07:18,930
这是她的独子  我不能冒险
It's her only son, I can't have that.

175
00:07:18,940 --> 00:07:20,170
我没问题的
I can do this.

176
00:07:20,370 --> 00:07:21,950
你祖母刚刚去世
Your grandmother just died.

177
00:07:23,680 --> 00:07:25,060
我说了我能行
I said I'm onboard.

178
00:07:25,850 --> 00:07:26,820
我就能行
I'm onboard.

179
00:07:33,050 --> 00:07:34,380
你觉得如何
So what do you think?

180
00:07:34,980 --> 00:07:37,000
车损帮了我们  损害很小
The damage helps us. It's minimal.

181
00:07:37,120 --> 00:07:40,310
更重要的是  如果车损在车前中央
More importantly, if the impact was central,

182
00:07:40,310 --> 00:07:42,010
被撞的人会在你视线范围内
guy would have been directly in your field of vision,

183
00:07:42,010 --> 00:07:44,700
这说明你说的是事实  他是突然冲过来的
so this backs the story up. He came out of nowhere.

184
00:07:45,100 --> 00:07:47,510
有人打了求救电话
Albert Chung was rushed to the E.R. last night,

185
00:07:47,510 --> 00:07:48,930
艾伯特·钟被送进急诊
after a 911 call.

186
00:07:50,190 --> 00:07:51,790
-你报警了  -对
- You called 911? - Yeah.

187
00:07:51,940 --> 00:07:53,140
你应该告诉我们的
You should have told us that.

188
00:07:53,260 --> 00:07:56,000
他现在脑震荡  挫伤  四根肋骨骨折
He has a concussion, contusions, four cracked ribs,

189
00:07:56,010 --> 00:07:57,050
不过情况很稳定
but he's stable.

190
00:07:57,050 --> 00:07:58,750
谢天谢地  所以没事了
Thank God, so it's okay.

191
00:07:58,960 --> 00:08:01,110
吉莉安  利亚姆需要去自首
Gillian, Liam needs to turn himself in.

192
00:08:01,110 --> 00:08:02,710
那是个意外
It was an accident.

193
00:08:02,860 --> 00:08:04,670
正是如此  他只是个吓坏了的二十岁的孩子
Exactly, so if he comes forward,

194
00:08:04,670 --> 00:08:06,150
如果他能站出来
he's a 20-year-old kid who freaked out,

195
00:08:06,150 --> 00:08:07,380
去自首才是他该做的
but now he's doing the right thing.

196
00:08:07,380 --> 00:08:08,190
哈维说得对
Harvey's right.

197
00:08:08,190 --> 00:08:09,790
如果他们找上门  我肯定他们会的
If they come to us, which I know they will,

198
00:08:09,790 --> 00:08:11,830
我们就被动了  毫无胜算
we'll be on the defensive, we'll never recover.

199
00:08:12,020 --> 00:08:13,700
-该死  -你怎么能确定
- Shit. - You can't know that.

200
00:08:13,990 --> 00:08:15,160
他们也许永远都找不到我们
They might never find him.

201
00:08:15,320 --> 00:08:17,050
你愿意赌上你儿子的前途吗
You really want to risk your son's life on that?

202
00:08:17,050 --> 00:08:20,390
抱歉  这难道不应该由利亚姆自己决定吗
I'm sorry, but isn't this Liam's decision?

203
00:08:27,670 --> 00:08:30,160
-我会怎么样  -我不知道
- What's gonna happen to me? - I don't know.

204
00:08:30,270 --> 00:08:31,990
不过如果你在担心电影里监狱情节的话
But if you're worried about prison movies,

205
00:08:31,990 --> 00:08:33,680
你就放心吧
that's not what's gonna happen.

206
00:08:34,030 --> 00:08:34,930
你怎么知道
How do you know that?

207
00:08:35,110 --> 00:08:36,380
因为我了解哈维
Because I know Harvey.

208
00:08:37,470 --> 00:08:38,240
我不知道
I don't know.

209
00:08:39,010 --> 00:08:40,070
我不知道
I don't know.

210
00:08:41,300 --> 00:08:43,390
信不信由你
Hey, believe it or not,

211
00:08:43,780 --> 00:08:45,210
我也经历过这些
I've been where you are right now.

212
00:08:45,990 --> 00:08:46,800
什么
What?

213
00:08:47,190 --> 00:08:49,280
那年我16岁
Yeah. I was 16.

214
00:08:49,920 --> 00:08:52,370
藏了半盎司的毒品  被抓到了
Got busted for possession, 1/2 ounce.

215
00:08:53,800 --> 00:08:55,040
我当时害怕极了
I was so scared.

216
00:08:55,040 --> 00:08:55,990
你抽大麻
You smoke?

217
00:08:56,880 --> 00:08:57,860
抽过
I did.

218
00:09:00,920 --> 00:09:01,910
现在也抽
I do.

219
00:09:03,140 --> 00:09:04,820
但你没有伤害别人
But you didn't hurt anybody.

220
00:09:05,410 --> 00:09:07,310
我知道你感觉无路可走了
I know it feels like there's no way out.

221
00:09:07,310 --> 00:09:08,330
但告诉你
But I'm telling you,

222
00:09:08,470 --> 00:09:10,090
你今天一定能够回家吃晚饭
you're going to be home in time for dinner.

223
00:09:16,920 --> 00:09:19,360
我必须说  很高兴你能给我打电话
I must say, I'm so glad you called.

224
00:09:19,850 --> 00:09:21,680
-很高兴你能赏脸  -很高兴你能高兴
- I'm so glad you answered. - I'm glad you're glad.

225
00:09:22,080 --> 00:09:23,720
你准备什么时候告诉我你升职了
When were you gonna tell me about your promotion?

226
00:09:23,870 --> 00:09:24,890
你知道我升职了
You know about my promotion?

227
00:09:24,890 --> 00:09:26,570
资深合伙人的消息
Senior partnerships rocket to my ears

228
00:09:26,570 --> 00:09:28,050
我一向都能火速知道
with the speed of a late-night bullet.

229
00:09:28,050 --> 00:09:29,810
-是吗  -我在推特上看到了
- Really? - I read it on twitter.

230
00:09:30,060 --> 00:09:31,440
看到你的第一眼
From the moment I laid eyes on you,

231
00:09:31,450 --> 00:09:32,880
我就知道你有胆识
I could tell you were a baller.

232
00:09:32,880 --> 00:09:35,190
我有胆识  所以我才打给你
Oh, I ball, which is why I called you.

233
00:09:36,280 --> 00:09:37,720
我新职务的特权之一就是
One of the perks of my new title--

234
00:09:37,720 --> 00:09:38,610
说出来
Say it.

235
00:09:39,120 --> 00:09:40,190
资深合伙人
Senior partner.

236
00:09:41,070 --> 00:09:42,100
接着说
Go on.

237
00:09:42,260 --> 00:09:43,920
我可以雇一个自己的助理律师
I get to hire an associate of my own.

238
00:09:44,750 --> 00:09:46,520
蝙蝠侠的神奇小子
A boy wonder to my batman.

239
00:09:46,660 --> 00:09:48,270
与你同在  黑暗骑士
Well, I am with you, dark knight.

240
00:09:48,410 --> 00:09:50,050
把最好的介绍给我
I want you to send me the best of the best.

241
00:09:50,050 --> 00:09:50,990
我已经让最好的五个毕业生
I've already lined up interviews

242
00:09:50,990 --> 00:09:52,800
排好了队  等你面试
with my top five recent graduates.

243
00:09:52,800 --> 00:09:55,150
-是吗  -打个比方罢了
- Have you? - Figure of speech.

244
00:09:55,350 --> 00:09:56,910
但我必须得说  希望你给我打电话
But, I have to say, I was hoping you didn't call

245
00:09:56,910 --> 00:09:58,880
并不是只为公事
exclusively for business.

246
00:09:59,040 --> 00:10:00,410
我正期待你这么想
I was hoping you were hoping that.

247
00:10:00,410 --> 00:10:01,910
跟你说实话吧  路易
I'm gonna be honest with you, Louis.

248
00:10:02,120 --> 00:10:03,950
资深合伙人就是一种性吸引力
Senior partner has a certain sex appeal.

249
00:10:03,950 --> 00:10:05,330
初级合伙人没有
Junior partner doesn't.

250
00:10:05,910 --> 00:10:07,910
我也是这么看自己的
I thought that to myself about myself.

251
00:10:10,250 --> 00:10:13,650
明晚九点  405房间
Room 405. 9:00 PM, tomorrow.

252
00:10:13,840 --> 00:10:16,320
带上椰子油  滑雪面罩和胶带
Bring coconut oil, a ski mask, and duct tape.

253
00:10:23,230 --> 00:10:24,610
恐惧从未感觉如此美好
Fear never felt so good.

254
00:10:29,950 --> 00:10:31,090
我叫卡特里娜·班尼特
Katrina Bennett.

255
00:10:31,640 --> 00:10:34,050
-哈维·斯佩克特  -很高兴见到你
- Harvey Specter. - Nice to meet you.

256
00:10:34,660 --> 00:10:37,100
你的胜诉率简直是业界传奇
Your record is something of a legend around here.

257
00:10:37,100 --> 00:10:38,030
太好了
Excellent.

258
00:10:38,040 --> 00:10:40,660
希望我们在庭上能够相互学习
I hope we can extend each other some professional courtesy.

259
00:10:40,660 --> 00:10:42,270
我没想过要让着你
I'm not extending you anything.

260
00:10:42,570 --> 00:10:43,460
当然了
Of course.

261
00:10:43,460 --> 00:10:45,520
还有什么能比打败一个传奇更光彩呢
What better thing to do than to take down a legend?

262
00:10:45,520 --> 00:10:47,250
很高兴我们有同样的想法
Well, I'm glad we understand each other.

263
00:10:47,400 --> 00:10:49,820
的确是  但有一个问题
We do, but here's the problem.

264
00:10:49,920 --> 00:10:51,010
这件案子没那么大
This isn't the case for it.

265
00:10:51,670 --> 00:10:53,440
是轻罪  不过是当时离开了事故现场
It's a misdemeanor, leaving the scene,

266
00:10:53,580 --> 00:10:54,980
现在他已经自首了
and now he's turned himself in.

267
00:10:55,080 --> 00:10:57,150
那是因为你知道我会发现他报过警
Because you knew we'd trace the 911 call.

268
00:10:57,150 --> 00:10:59,210
不是  他很过意不去
That's not why. He feels terrible.

269
00:10:59,430 --> 00:11:00,660
他不过是害怕
He feels afraid.

270
00:11:00,770 --> 00:11:01,970
不能混为一谈
Not the same thing.

271
00:11:01,970 --> 00:11:03,930
卡特里娜  我明白你想打赢我
Katrina, I understand you want to take me out,

272
00:11:03,930 --> 00:11:05,150
但这是个意外
but this is an accident.

273
00:11:05,250 --> 00:11:07,240
利亚姆犯了错  他在悔改
Liam made a mistake, and he's rectifying it.

274
00:11:07,420 --> 00:11:09,290
我们可以接受最重的社区服务惩罚
We'll accept maximum community service

275
00:11:09,290 --> 00:11:10,990
和你提议的罚款
and whatever fine you deem appropriate.

276
00:11:11,140 --> 00:11:12,980
葬礼花费呢
And what about funeral costs?

277
00:11:13,370 --> 00:11:14,420
等一下  你说什么
Wait. What?

278
00:11:14,940 --> 00:11:15,900
他死了
He died?

279
00:11:16,110 --> 00:11:17,880
这个案子就是肇事逃逸的重罪了
Which makes it felony hit-and-run.

280
00:11:17,880 --> 00:11:18,910
他之前情况很稳定啊
He was stable.

281
00:11:18,920 --> 00:11:20,870
脑震荡引起了脑出血
His concussion led to a brain bleed.

282
00:11:20,870 --> 00:11:22,800
就算他死了也不能改变
That man's death doesn't change the fact

283
00:11:22,800 --> 00:11:23,880
这只是个意外的事实
that it was an accident.

284
00:11:23,880 --> 00:11:25,770
肇事逃逸是重罪  按现在的情况
Felony hit-and-run, under these circumstances,

285
00:11:25,770 --> 00:11:27,320
大概要判12到15年
is 12 to 15 years.

286
00:11:28,280 --> 00:11:30,950
想要礼节吗  这就是我的礼节
You wanted courtesy? Here it is.

287
00:11:31,470 --> 00:11:32,440
我可以接受十年
I'll go ten.

288
00:11:32,770 --> 00:11:34,740
你的提议太疯狂了  当时天色已晚
That's crazy. It was dark.

289
00:11:34,750 --> 00:11:35,680
他也没喝酒
He wasn't drinking.

290
00:11:36,610 --> 00:11:38,920
换成你  难道不会提出同样的提议吗
Tell me it's not what you would have offered.

291
00:11:49,590 --> 00:11:50,900
玛丽亚·门罗
Maria Monroe.

292
00:11:51,010 --> 00:11:52,960
哈佛法学院  班长
Secretary of your class at Harvard Law.

293
00:11:53,120 --> 00:11:55,060
为首席法官罗伯茨做过书记员
Clerked for Chief Justice Roberts.

294
00:11:55,060 --> 00:11:56,910
金光闪闪的推荐信
Glowing letters of recommendation.

295
00:11:57,070 --> 00:11:58,490
你觉得这就能打动我
You think this impresses me?

296
00:12:00,860 --> 00:12:02,010
那就错了
Negative.

297
00:12:02,130 --> 00:12:03,790
给你五分钟时间来说服我
Which means you have exactly five minutes

298
00:12:03,800 --> 00:12:05,110
你就是我要的人
to convince me that you're the one.

299
00:12:05,120 --> 00:12:07,340
不用五分钟  我是无人能及的
I don't need five minutes. I am the one.

300
00:12:07,450 --> 00:12:09,110
该着急的是你  路易
It's you who's on the clock, Louis.

301
00:12:09,110 --> 00:12:11,630
我收到了纽约最顶尖三家律所的持续邀约
I have standing offers from the top three firms in the city.

302
00:12:11,750 --> 00:12:13,690
皮尔逊·哈德曼律所就是顶尖的
Pearson Hardman is a top-three firm.

303
00:12:13,690 --> 00:12:15,080
我本来也这么以为
Well, I used to think so.

304
00:12:15,080 --> 00:12:16,930
但如果你要花这么久来面试我
But if it's taking you this long to meet with me,

305
00:12:16,930 --> 00:12:18,020
也许你们水平在下滑
maybe you're slipping.

306
00:12:18,020 --> 00:12:19,900
不  我没有  我们才没有
Oh, no, I'm not-- we're not slipping.

307
00:12:19,910 --> 00:12:22,360
如果你想让我考虑在这儿工作的话
You need to submit a formal offer by noon tomorrow

308
00:12:22,360 --> 00:12:24,770
明天中午之前给我一份正式工作邀请
if you want me to even consider working here.

309
00:12:25,180 --> 00:12:27,020
玛丽亚  等一下
Wh-- Maria, hold on a second.

310
00:12:27,020 --> 00:12:28,610
在这儿等着
Just wait right there, wait right there.

311
00:12:30,640 --> 00:12:32,720
你们四个  走吧  招到人了
You four, beat it. Position has been filled.

312
00:12:34,710 --> 00:12:37,630
他们出多少薪资  我加一半  签约金两万五
I'll beat any salary by 50%. 25,000 signing bonus.

313
00:12:37,900 --> 00:12:39,490
-写下来  -等等
- Put it in writing. - W-w-wait--

314
00:12:39,490 --> 00:12:41,590
要我带你参观一下律所吗
Don't you want me to give you a tour of the firm?

315
00:12:41,740 --> 00:12:42,870
看看你将来的工作环境
Show you where you'll be working?

316
00:12:42,880 --> 00:12:44,600
我不介意工作环境
Well, I don't care where I'd be working

317
00:12:44,600 --> 00:12:45,680
我就是台工作机器
because I'm a machine.

318
00:12:46,270 --> 00:12:47,740
我一定要聘请你
I have to have you.

319
00:12:48,180 --> 00:12:49,150
大家都这么说
That's what they all say.

320
00:12:50,400 --> 00:12:52,590
警方报告  十字路口的照片
Police report, photos of the intersection,

321
00:12:53,000 --> 00:12:54,000
法医报告
coroner's report.

322
00:12:54,000 --> 00:12:55,430
又不是六年级数学
This isn't sixth-grade math.

323
00:12:55,430 --> 00:12:56,900
我不用知道过程  只要知道结果
Don't show me your work, just give me the answer.

324
00:12:56,900 --> 00:12:58,820
天呐  真希望我六年级是你教的
God, I wish I had you in the sixth grade.

325
00:12:58,820 --> 00:13:01,480
可惜不是  当年詹森老师超性感
Except, no-- Miss Jenson, very hot.

326
00:13:01,640 --> 00:13:02,830
你需要自己待一会儿吗
You need a minute alone?

327
00:13:03,220 --> 00:13:07,380
利亚姆没看到艾伯特·钟是有原因的
There was a reason that Liam did not see Albert Chung.

328
00:13:07,380 --> 00:13:10,550
他穿着连帽运动衫  牛仔裤  运动鞋
He was wearing a hooded sweatshirt, jeans, and sneakers.

329
00:13:10,550 --> 00:13:11,480
一身黑色
All black.

330
00:13:11,690 --> 00:13:14,020
他是故意不想引人注意
Guy couldn't have been harder to see if he was trying.

331
00:13:14,020 --> 00:13:15,070
也许他真是故意的
Maybe he was trying.

332
00:13:15,080 --> 00:13:17,310
艾伯特·钟从艺校辍学了
Albert chung was an art school dropout.

333
00:13:17,430 --> 00:13:19,140
看看墙上的涂鸦
Look at that graffiti on the wall.

334
00:13:19,270 --> 00:13:21,010
A.C.就代表艾伯特·钟
"A.C." Albert Chung.

335
00:13:21,010 --> 00:13:22,150
他不想引人注意
He was trying to be invisible

336
00:13:22,150 --> 00:13:23,700
因为他在墙上涂鸦
because he was tagging that building.

337
00:13:23,700 --> 00:13:25,090
他在逃跑时被撞了
And he was running away when he got hit.

338
00:13:25,090 --> 00:13:26,730
也就是说  造成这场意外的不是利亚姆
Which means Liam didn't cause the accident,

339
00:13:26,730 --> 00:13:28,040
而是艾伯特·钟
Albert Chung did.

340
00:13:28,320 --> 00:13:30,400
你应该去假扮警察
I think you missed your calling as a fake cop.

341
00:13:30,400 --> 00:13:32,600
又说这茬是吧
Going back to that well again? Okay.

342
00:13:33,080 --> 00:13:34,830
你准备怎么做  跟卡特里娜谈判
So what are you gonna do? Stick it to Katrina?

343
00:13:34,830 --> 00:13:36,190
不  你去和卡特里娜谈判
No, you're gonna stick it to Katrina.

344
00:13:36,290 --> 00:13:37,250
你听到她说的了
You heard her.

345
00:13:37,440 --> 00:13:39,570
她的目的不是单单起诉利亚姆
Her agenda isn't just prosecuting Liam,

346
00:13:39,570 --> 00:13:40,690
而是打败我
it's beating me.

347
00:13:40,860 --> 00:13:42,450
我要把个人情感抽离这案子
See, I'm taking the personal out of it.

348
00:13:42,640 --> 00:13:44,880
你的问题是把个人情感带进案子里
Your problem is, you put the personal into it.

349
00:13:44,880 --> 00:13:45,970
我还以为
Okay, I thought my problem

350
00:13:45,970 --> 00:13:47,720
我的问题是爱卖弄
was showing you my work unnecessarily.

351
00:13:47,730 --> 00:13:49,140
谁说只有一个问题了
Who said there's only one problem?

352
00:13:49,970 --> 00:13:50,810
这招狠
Well-played.

353
00:13:55,370 --> 00:13:56,420
重大肇事逃逸罪
Felony hit-and-run hinges

354
00:13:56,420 --> 00:13:58,990
前提在于是否有共同过失
on a lack of contributory negligence.

355
00:13:58,990 --> 00:14:00,830
艾伯特·钟当时正逃离犯罪现场
Albert Chung was fleeing a crime scene.

356
00:14:00,830 --> 00:14:02,030
他将自己置于险境
He put himself in harm's way.

357
00:14:02,030 --> 00:14:03,890
你的委托人就完全没有责任了
So your client can't be held responsible?

358
00:14:03,890 --> 00:14:05,900
我们只会认驾车逃逸这一指控
We'll plead to misdemeanor leaving the scene,

359
00:14:05,900 --> 00:14:06,820
仅此而已
but that's all.

360
00:14:07,450 --> 00:14:09,730
我就帮你这个忙  接受这份协议
I'm going to do you a favor and take this deal.

361
00:14:09,830 --> 00:14:12,350
你不是帮我  是帮你自己
You're not doing me a favor, you're doing yourself a favor.

362
00:14:12,480 --> 00:14:13,400
我们赢了
We've got you.

363
00:14:13,400 --> 00:14:15,210
不管怎样  大家都知道
Got me or not, it's no secret

364
00:14:15,210 --> 00:14:17,060
地方检察官跟哈维有过不和
the D.A. And Harvey had a run-in.

365
00:14:17,060 --> 00:14:18,740
他要知道这是哈维的案子
He finds out this is Harvey's case,

366
00:14:18,740 --> 00:14:19,590
就会让你们庭审
it goes to trial.

367
00:14:19,590 --> 00:14:21,650
审讯时什么都可能发生
And anything can happen at trial,

368
00:14:21,650 --> 00:14:22,830
恕我直言
so let me be clear,

369
00:14:23,570 --> 00:14:24,870
是我帮你一个忙
I am doing you a favor.

370
00:14:25,910 --> 00:14:26,960
你要什么
What do you want?

371
00:14:27,510 --> 00:14:29,520
跟哈维一样跳槽
To make the same career jump Harvey did.

372
00:14:29,520 --> 00:14:30,860
做商业律师
To corporate litigation?

373
00:14:31,140 --> 00:14:32,330
去皮尔逊·哈德曼律所
To Pearson Hardman.

374
00:14:32,850 --> 00:14:33,820
等等  我以为你
Wait, I thought you--

375
00:14:33,820 --> 00:14:35,260
我要把哈维打得落花流水
That I wanted to kick Harvey's ass?

376
00:14:35,270 --> 00:14:36,800
我这么说是因为献慇勤
I said that because you don't impress

377
00:14:36,800 --> 00:14:38,930
无法给哈维这样的律师留下印象
a lawyer like Harvey with flowers.

378
00:14:39,750 --> 00:14:41,710
这份认罪协议很公平
Look, this is a fair plea.

379
00:14:42,270 --> 00:14:43,410
应该能通过
And it's one that should go through.

380
00:14:43,410 --> 00:14:44,600
我会保证它能通过
I'll make sure that it does.

381
00:14:45,250 --> 00:14:47,140
你要能帮我在哈维面前说说好话
And if you were to put a word in with Harvey,

382
00:14:47,720 --> 00:14:49,000
我将感激不尽
I would appreciate it.

383
00:14:52,600 --> 00:14:53,420
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me.

384
00:14:53,430 --> 00:14:54,410
-她真这么说  -是的
- She actually said that? - Yeah.

385
00:14:54,410 --> 00:14:57,370
我都搞不清是解决了案子还是接受了贿赂
I don't know if I settled a case or agreed to a bribe.

386
00:14:57,370 --> 00:14:59,080
-认罪协议她签了吗  -签了
- Did she sign the plea offer? - Yeah.

387
00:14:59,080 --> 00:15:01,850
那就满分通过  她又不能撤销协议
Then, "A," Because she can't rescind that thing

388
00:15:01,850 --> 00:15:03,780
除非出现新证据
unless new evidence comes to light,

389
00:15:03,780 --> 00:15:05,380
而我也就不必面试她了
and I don't have to interview her for shit.

390
00:15:05,390 --> 00:15:07,070
-很好  -很好
- Good. - Yeah, good.

391
00:15:07,070 --> 00:15:09,330
我不想再请一个助理了
I don't want to hire another associate ever again.

392
00:15:09,720 --> 00:15:11,500
我选的那个已经够让我头痛了
The one I picked causes me enough headaches.

393
00:15:11,500 --> 00:15:13,070
是吗  比如说帮你赢官司
Oh, right, like winning cases?

394
00:15:13,520 --> 00:15:15,890
涂鸦  穿了一身黑的男人  想起什么了吗
Graffiti, man in black-- is that ringing any bells?

395
00:15:16,010 --> 00:15:17,130
想起来了
It does indeed,

396
00:15:17,500 --> 00:15:19,410
也就带出了下一个任务
which leads us to our next assignment,

397
00:15:19,410 --> 00:15:20,730
若你愿意干的话
should you choose to accept it.

398
00:15:20,730 --> 00:15:22,680
拜托告诉我你要自杀
Please tell me you're about to self-destruct.

399
00:15:22,680 --> 00:15:24,310
我们要和钟家和解
We need to settle with the Chung family.

400
00:15:26,700 --> 00:15:28,280
哈维  他们的儿子刚刚过世
Harvey, their son just died.

401
00:15:28,400 --> 00:15:31,150
我知道  我也知道悲伤是有阶段的
I know, and I also know that grief comes in stages,

402
00:15:31,150 --> 00:15:33,300
和解的最佳时间就是在愤怒阶段之前
and the best time to settle is before it gets to anger.

403
00:15:33,300 --> 00:15:34,690
你的意思是  占便宜的最佳时间
You mean the best time to take advantage of them

404
00:15:34,700 --> 00:15:36,450
是在他们愤怒之前吧
is before it gets to anger.

405
00:15:36,560 --> 00:15:37,910
-这就…  -不关我们的事了
- That's not-- - Our concern?

406
00:15:38,770 --> 00:15:40,040
我知道我们帮利亚姆逃离了牢狱之灾
I know we got Liam out of prison,

407
00:15:40,040 --> 00:15:42,670
但他毕竟撞了人  那人毕竟死了
but he still hit a guy, and that guy is still dead.

408
00:15:42,820 --> 00:15:44,230
但我们是利亚姆的代表律师
And we still represent Liam.

409
00:15:44,580 --> 00:15:45,370
哈维
Harvey...

410
00:15:46,210 --> 00:15:48,300
我知道情况不一样  但是
I know it's not the same situation, but...

411
00:15:49,690 --> 00:15:51,830
我记得律师来我家的那天
I remember the day the lawyer came to our place.

412
00:15:53,240 --> 00:15:54,680
尼克·里纳尔迪  我
Nick Rinaldi. I...

413
00:15:55,410 --> 00:15:57,150
我记得他肮脏的鞋  我
I remember his dirty shoes. I...

414
00:15:57,900 --> 00:15:59,540
我记得他走进客厅
I remember how they scraped the floor

415
00:15:59,540 --> 00:16:00,710
告诉我奶奶
when he walked into the living room

416
00:16:00,710 --> 00:16:01,720
我父母的命值多少钱时
to tell my grandmother

417
00:16:01,720 --> 00:16:03,890
那双鞋发出的声音
how much my parents' lives were worth.

418
00:16:06,100 --> 00:16:07,510
我也经历过他们的悲剧
I've been where these people are.

419
00:16:08,990 --> 00:16:10,270
让我去告诉他们吧
Let me be the one to tell them.

420
00:16:12,130 --> 00:16:13,470
你确定没问题吗
You sure you can handle it?

421
00:16:13,600 --> 00:16:14,420
我很肯定不会
I'm sure as hell not going

422
00:16:14,420 --> 00:16:15,400
把他们留给你这样的人
to leave them to the likes of you.

423
00:16:15,400 --> 00:16:17,570
好吧  交给你吧
Okay, you can handle it.

424
00:16:19,370 --> 00:16:21,790
最高出价十万
You're authorized to go as high as $100,000.

425
00:16:36,900 --> 00:16:38,780
离婚案在43号架子上
Divorce is on 43.

426
00:16:40,940 --> 00:16:42,900
我知道你生我气
Look, I know that you're mad at me,

427
00:16:43,390 --> 00:16:45,120
我无意这样对你的
and I never meant to put you in this situation,

428
00:16:45,130 --> 00:16:46,940
如果你不告诉其他人
but I would really appreciate it

429
00:16:46,940 --> 00:16:49,100
我感激不尽
if you kept what I told you to yourself.

430
00:16:50,510 --> 00:16:51,610
让我来理理
Let me get this straight.

431
00:16:52,210 --> 00:16:53,220
你先找上我
You hit on me,

432
00:16:53,220 --> 00:16:55,210
然后又投入某个已婚女人的怀抱
then you run into the arms of some married woman.

433
00:16:55,360 --> 00:16:57,340
再故作潇洒地走进我办公室
You come waltzing into my office

434
00:16:57,340 --> 00:16:58,630
想要粉饰一切
trying to cutesy your way out of it.

435
00:16:58,630 --> 00:17:00,010
现在你还有脸认为
And now you have the nerve

436
00:17:00,010 --> 00:17:02,160
我会到处宣扬吗
to think I'm gonna go and tell other people?

437
00:17:07,060 --> 00:17:08,850
我当然不知道你会不会宣扬
I have no idea what you're gonna tell other people,

438
00:17:08,860 --> 00:17:10,010
但你明显就是
but you sure seem to have the ability

439
00:17:10,010 --> 00:17:11,590
带着有色眼镜看我
to judge everything that I do.

440
00:17:11,590 --> 00:17:13,740
你觉得你干过的蠢事还少吗
Do you think that you have the lock on bad decisions?

441
00:17:13,740 --> 00:17:15,290
我确实不像你  从没犯过错
All I know is I'm not little Miss Perfect.

442
00:17:15,300 --> 00:17:17,280
我以前也当过小三
I've had an affair before too.

443
00:17:18,820 --> 00:17:20,160
你真该看看你现在的表情
You see the look on your face?

444
00:17:20,680 --> 00:17:22,260
谁才是带着有色眼镜  迈克
Who's judging who now, Mike?

445
00:17:22,410 --> 00:17:25,010
而且不是什么50多岁的老男人
And, no, it was not some 50-year-old man

446
00:17:25,010 --> 00:17:27,220
因我年轻无知  试图占我便宜
trying to take advantage of poor, young me.

447
00:17:27,320 --> 00:17:30,380
我们年龄相似  还是我主动的
We were the same age, and I went after him.

448
00:17:32,530 --> 00:17:35,600
我可不是你所认为的乖乖女
I am not the goody-goody you think I am.

449
00:17:37,160 --> 00:17:40,390
你根本就不知道自己错过了什么
You have no idea what you passed on.

450
00:17:43,330 --> 00:17:44,740
而且我跟你说  迈克
And I'll tell you something, Mike.

451
00:17:44,740 --> 00:17:47,900
这种事情  肯定不会有好结果
What you're doing, it only ends one way.

452
00:17:56,940 --> 00:17:59,250
钟女士  我想告诉你
Ms. Chung, I just want you to know

453
00:17:59,250 --> 00:18:02,620
无论错在谁  利亚姆·柯顺因此事
that Liam Colson is devastated by this accident,

454
00:18:02,620 --> 00:18:04,240
心里备受煎熬
regardless of who caused it.

455
00:18:04,380 --> 00:18:05,380
谢谢
Thank you.

456
00:18:06,130 --> 00:18:07,810
我知道任何金额
I know that there's no amount of money

457
00:18:07,810 --> 00:18:09,190
都弥补不了
that can ever make up for it...

458
00:18:10,500 --> 00:18:13,380
而且眼下你们最不想提及的
And that this is probably the last thing

459
00:18:13,380 --> 00:18:14,930
也是赔偿一事
you want to be talking about.

460
00:18:15,010 --> 00:18:17,980
我弟弟并不是模范市民  罗斯先生
My brother wasn't exactly a model citizen, Mr. Ross.

461
00:18:18,150 --> 00:18:20,360
我们明白他不配
We know he's not entitled to much.

462
00:18:20,810 --> 00:18:23,480
我父母只想偿还艾伯特欠的债
All my parents want is to pay off Albert's debts

463
00:18:23,480 --> 00:18:25,090
再支付葬礼费用
and cover the funeral costs.

464
00:18:25,710 --> 00:18:26,940
总共需要多少
And how much would that be?

465
00:18:27,500 --> 00:18:29,490
两万
$20,000.

466
00:18:34,150 --> 00:18:36,670
我们愿意支付十万
Well, I'd like to offer you $100,000.

467
00:18:38,710 --> 00:18:40,280
事实上  我坚持如此
In fact, I insist on it.

468
00:18:43,420 --> 00:18:45,930
他们给  赔五倍

469
00:18:56,570 --> 00:19:01,090
你帮我告诉他  我们很感谢他

470
00:19:03,340 --> 00:19:04,480
在哪里签字
Where do we sign?

471
00:19:06,410 --> 00:19:07,660
这里和这里
Right here and here.

472
00:19:11,330 --> 00:19:12,820
要不要喝点茶
Will you stay for some tea?

473
00:19:14,170 --> 00:19:15,330
乐意至极
I'd be honored.

474
00:19:27,530 --> 00:19:29,850
晚上9点  一秒不差
9 P.M. To the second.

475
00:19:29,850 --> 00:19:31,620
准时最让人性奋了
Punctuality is the best aphrodisiac.

476
00:19:33,750 --> 00:19:34,950
真让人捉摸不透
Who are you?

477
00:19:37,010 --> 00:19:38,190
人家是蝙蝠侠么
I'm batman.

478
00:19:40,690 --> 00:19:42,090
全副武装吗
Did you bring the accoutrement?

479
00:19:42,090 --> 00:19:43,110
当然〔法语〕
Oui.

480
00:19:43,330 --> 00:19:45,900
我都迫不及待了
I'm on pins and needles.

481
00:19:47,390 --> 00:19:50,090
不过开始前  我要知道
Before we begin, I need to know...

482
00:19:50,450 --> 00:19:51,590
你挑中了谁
who's your front-runner?

483
00:19:52,070 --> 00:19:53,370
玛丽亚·门罗  其他人差远了
Maria Monroe. Wasn't even close.

484
00:19:53,370 --> 00:19:56,340
我知道  并非是五个最佳人选
I know. There were no five best.

485
00:19:56,340 --> 00:19:57,480
你是在考验我吗
You were testing me?

486
00:19:58,060 --> 00:20:00,010
上好的菜品  我可不会用
I wasn't about to serve up my best candidate

487
00:20:00,010 --> 00:20:00,950
次等餐具
on a silver platter.

488
00:20:00,950 --> 00:20:01,970
就喜欢你的品位
God, I love that.

489
00:20:03,060 --> 00:20:04,890
不过玛丽亚确实出类拔萃
After all, Maria is very desirable.

490
00:20:04,910 --> 00:20:06,660
不过  我需要你…
But the thing is, I'm gonna need you...

491
00:20:08,000 --> 00:20:09,500
帮我说服她
to help me close her.

492
00:20:09,500 --> 00:20:12,550
路易  走进点
Louis, come closer.

493
00:20:14,850 --> 00:20:16,020
停下
Stop.

494
00:20:17,390 --> 00:20:19,970
我肯定替你把玛丽亚搞定
I'm gonna close the shit out of Maria for you.

495
00:20:20,910 --> 00:20:23,300
你得先让我满意才行
And you're gonna close the shit out of me.

496
00:20:24,440 --> 00:20:25,770
没问题
All aboard.

497
00:20:29,070 --> 00:20:30,920
等下  若我没选她
Wait a minute, if I didn't pick her,

498
00:20:30,920 --> 00:20:32,910
我们是不是没戏了
we wouldn't be doing this?

499
00:20:32,910 --> 00:20:34,620
我可没这么说
Oh, I'm saying no such thing.

500
00:20:34,620 --> 00:20:36,770
但我们下面要做的事
But the nature of what we're about to do

501
00:20:36,770 --> 00:20:38,750
可就不在一个级别上了
would be radically different.

502
00:20:39,020 --> 00:20:42,150
我通过考验  就由我来主导
I dominated, so I get to dominate.

503
00:20:42,150 --> 00:20:44,350
-是被调教  -听你的
- You get to be dominated. - Yes, I do.

504
00:20:44,360 --> 00:20:46,030
要不要一个暂停口令
Do you need a safe word?

505
00:20:46,990 --> 00:20:49,180
没种的才要那个
Safe words are for pussies.

506
00:20:49,180 --> 00:20:50,370
从下面开始
Start with my slippers.

507
00:20:50,370 --> 00:20:51,800
你太了解我了
Oh, thank you.

508
00:21:04,150 --> 00:21:06,640
-你好啊  -花在哪呢
- Hello. - Where are your flowers?

509
00:21:06,640 --> 00:21:07,870
什么花
My flowers?

510
00:21:07,870 --> 00:21:10,300
约会要带花来的丫
You go on a date, you're supposed to bring flowers.

511
00:21:10,300 --> 00:21:12,980
-是吗  -是的  哈维
- Am I? - Yes, Harvey.

512
00:21:12,980 --> 00:21:14,750
大家都知道的
Everyone knows that.

513
00:21:14,750 --> 00:21:16,660
你有过几次约会啊
How many dates have you been on?

514
00:21:17,610 --> 00:21:19,540
-六次  -六次哦
- Six. - Six?

515
00:21:19,540 --> 00:21:22,380
挺认真的嘛  哪个男人这么幸运啊
Mm, sounds serious. Who's the lucky guy?

516
00:21:22,380 --> 00:21:23,830
杰森
Jason.

517
00:21:24,010 --> 00:21:25,830
不是男人  是男孩
He's not a guy, he's a boy.

518
00:21:25,830 --> 00:21:27,890
他都会带花
And he brings flowers.

519
00:21:28,940 --> 00:21:31,490
也许下次我们可以四人约会
Well, maybe next time we can have a double date.

520
00:21:31,490 --> 00:21:33,630
你就这么确信会有下次啊
You that sure it's gonna go well tonight?

521
00:21:33,630 --> 00:21:34,970
奥利维亚  你为何不上楼
Olivia, why don't you go upstairs

522
00:21:34,980 --> 00:21:36,830
继续看电视去
and finish watching your show?

523
00:21:36,830 --> 00:21:38,810
你是不是忘记跟我说什么了
Is there maybe something you forgot to tell me?

524
00:21:38,810 --> 00:21:40,430
你是指你女儿吗
You mean about your daughter?

525
00:21:40,430 --> 00:21:42,780
可说起来我们都还没上过床
See, that's funny because we never slept together.

526
00:21:42,780 --> 00:21:44,250
我可不觉得这事有趣
I don't find it funny in the least,

527
00:21:44,250 --> 00:21:46,570
我是指我们还没上过床
and by "it," I mean that we never slept together.

528
00:21:46,570 --> 00:21:49,850
说真的  哈维  我很抱歉
Seriously, Harvey, I'm really sorry about this.

529
00:21:50,340 --> 00:21:52,780
奥利维亚是我侄女  我哥哥丢给我的
Olivia's my niece. My brother just dropped her off.

530
00:21:52,780 --> 00:21:54,010
他没其他亲人了
He didn't have anybody else.

531
00:21:54,010 --> 00:21:55,650
那我们就排排坐
Then I guess we'll have to sit down,

532
00:21:55,650 --> 00:21:57,750
点份匹萨  看看兔八哥
watch Bugs Bunny, and order a pizza.

533
00:21:58,410 --> 00:22:00,030
兔八哥吗
Bugs Bunny?

534
00:22:00,660 --> 00:22:02,690
早就过时啦
Yeah, no one watches that anymore.

535
00:22:02,690 --> 00:22:05,360
她看《现代启示录》还太小了嘛
I thought Apocalypse Now would be a little much for her.

536
00:22:05,360 --> 00:22:06,730
我能进来吗
Can I come in?

537
00:22:09,590 --> 00:22:12,760
你怎么不等等我
Hey. Thanks for starting without me.

538
00:22:12,830 --> 00:22:15,130
-等不急了  -今天这么不顺啊
- Couldn't wait. - That bad a day?

539
00:22:15,130 --> 00:22:17,590
没  其实挺好的
Nope, that good of one.

540
00:22:18,440 --> 00:22:20,480
看样子你跟瑞秋谈得挺好
So your little chat with Rachel went well.

541
00:22:20,480 --> 00:22:22,040
我说的不是这方面
Not what I meant.

542
00:22:22,710 --> 00:22:24,560
有个死于车祸的男人
I negotiated a settlement with the sister

543
00:22:24,560 --> 00:22:27,050
我今天跟他姐姐谈好了协议
of the man who was killed in a car accident today.

544
00:22:27,720 --> 00:22:28,660
哦  我的天
Oh, my god.

545
00:22:28,660 --> 00:22:30,140
不  不是你想的那样
No, no. It's not what you think.

546
00:22:30,140 --> 00:22:31,510
我…
I, um,

547
00:22:31,530 --> 00:22:33,760
我给了他们尊严
I gave this family dignity.

548
00:22:33,990 --> 00:22:35,950
尽管很难
And as hard as it was...

549
00:22:38,040 --> 00:22:40,210
今天是我工作后最棒的一天
it was the best day of work I've ever had.

550
00:22:41,840 --> 00:22:43,030
那太好了
That's awesome.

551
00:22:47,940 --> 00:22:48,900
喂
Hey.

552
00:22:48,900 --> 00:22:50,920
利亚姆的认罪协议到了
Liam's plea deal came through.

553
00:22:50,920 --> 00:22:52,510
正在送往吉莉安家的路上
It's on its way to Gillian's.

554
00:22:52,510 --> 00:22:54,600
我需要你过去  帮他们签好
I need you to go over there and walk 'em through it,

555
00:22:54,600 --> 00:22:56,100
把此案弄完
so we can wrap this up.

556
00:22:56,100 --> 00:22:57,660
我这就去
Uh, I'm on my way.

557
00:22:58,070 --> 00:22:59,280
-惨了  -怎么了
- Shit. - What?

558
00:22:59,530 --> 00:23:01,140
我要去见客户
I have to go see a client.

559
00:23:01,140 --> 00:23:03,660
迈克  你嗑药了啊
Mike, you're high.

560
00:23:03,660 --> 00:23:05,080
被看出来怎么办
What if they can tell?

561
00:23:06,300 --> 00:23:08,370
苔丝  我之前有几年天天都嗑
Tess, I was high every day of my life for years,

562
00:23:08,370 --> 00:23:10,060
可没人知道
and nobody knew, okay?

563
00:23:10,060 --> 00:23:11,610
我能搞定
I can handle it.

564
00:23:13,190 --> 00:23:14,950
-她睡着了吗  -还没
- She asleep? - Not exactly.

565
00:23:14,950 --> 00:23:17,720
她希望你上去  给她个晚安吻
She wants you to go up there and kiss her good night.

566
00:23:18,870 --> 00:23:20,200
你不用去的
You don't have to do this.

567
00:23:20,200 --> 00:23:22,740
-没事  我去  -哈维
- No, I can do that. - Harvey.

568
00:23:22,760 --> 00:23:25,180
我想让你一会儿下来
Afterwards, I want you to come down here,

569
00:23:25,180 --> 00:23:26,860
也和我吻安
and kiss me good night.

570
00:23:34,620 --> 00:23:35,810
所以…
So...

571
00:23:36,840 --> 00:23:38,710
我签了这个就没事了
I sign this, and we're done?

572
00:23:41,480 --> 00:23:43,680
对
Yeah.

573
00:23:43,680 --> 00:23:45,660
助理检察官已经同意了
Uh, the A.D.A. agreed to it,

574
00:23:45,660 --> 00:23:48,990
你签完字  然后…
so you sign it, and then, um...

575
00:23:48,990 --> 00:23:50,800
然后法官也会签字
and then the judge'll sign it.

576
00:23:51,160 --> 00:23:53,200
然后就完事了
And then-- then we're done.

577
00:24:01,960 --> 00:24:03,900
社区服务和交罚款
Community service and a fine.

578
00:24:04,860 --> 00:24:06,620
听起来你还挺失望的
You sound disappointed.

579
00:24:07,280 --> 00:24:09,960
不不  我很感激
No, no, I appreciate it.

580
00:24:09,960 --> 00:24:11,040
只是…
It's just...

581
00:24:12,170 --> 00:24:13,720
我本来以为会更糟糕呢
It could have been so much worse.

582
00:24:13,720 --> 00:24:15,310
我还以为这辈子完蛋了呢
I thought my life over.

583
00:24:16,390 --> 00:24:17,930
我真是个混蛋
I'm such an asshole.

584
00:24:18,030 --> 00:24:21,210
利亚姆  你可以觉得解脱的
Hey, Liam, it's okay to feel relief.

585
00:24:21,210 --> 00:24:23,040
钟的家人不怪你的
The Chung family doesn't blame you.

586
00:24:23,650 --> 00:24:24,990
没人怪你
Nobody blames you.

587
00:24:26,450 --> 00:24:28,340
你还记得那天你说
Do you remember what you said the other day

588
00:24:28,340 --> 00:24:29,740
你以前嗑药吗
about getting high?

589
00:24:31,670 --> 00:24:35,030
为什么问这个
Why are you asking me that?

590
00:24:35,930 --> 00:24:37,230
我那天嗑药了
I was high.

591
00:24:39,640 --> 00:24:40,830
什么
What?

592
00:24:46,580 --> 00:24:48,900
你怎么不早告诉我们
How could you not tell us that?

593
00:24:49,100 --> 00:24:50,330
哈维不让我说
'Cause Harvey said not to.

594
00:24:50,340 --> 00:24:51,440
但你说你没醉
But you said you weren't drunk.

595
00:24:51,440 --> 00:24:52,640
你说我们可以随便去问
You said, "Ask everyone."

596
00:24:52,640 --> 00:24:53,730
你可以问
You could have.

597
00:24:53,730 --> 00:24:55,030
我自己嗑的
I was alone.

598
00:24:55,340 --> 00:24:57,540
我总嗑药  但从来没人知道
I get high all the time, and no one ever knows.

599
00:24:57,790 --> 00:24:59,910
-天哪  -怎么了
- Oh, my God. - What's the matter?

600
00:25:01,510 --> 00:25:03,250
你说这事已经定了
You said this was a done deal.

601
00:25:03,770 --> 00:25:05,050
是吧
It is, right?

602
00:25:06,080 --> 00:25:07,230
是
Yeah.

603
00:25:09,990 --> 00:25:11,480
是  已经定了
Yeah, it's a done deal.

604
00:25:25,820 --> 00:25:27,820
-出大事了  -没事  迈克
- We got a huge problem. - Don't worry, Mike.

605
00:25:27,820 --> 00:25:30,480
超级男孩还会有巡演的
I'm sure 'NSync will tour again someday.

606
00:25:31,910 --> 00:25:34,210
这和解协议不能交  那不是意外
We can't submit this deal because it wasn't an accident.

607
00:25:34,210 --> 00:25:35,270
是不当驾驶
It was a DUI.

608
00:25:35,270 --> 00:25:36,630
-什么  -他嗑药了
- What? - He was stoned.

609
00:25:36,630 --> 00:25:39,820
-性质变了  -没什么要变的
- This changes everything. - It changes nothing.

610
00:25:39,820 --> 00:25:41,860
可我并未向卡特里娜陈述事实
I misrepresented the facts to Katrina.

611
00:25:41,860 --> 00:25:42,720
你没有
No, you didn't,

612
00:25:42,720 --> 00:25:44,370
因为当时我们没问  你也不知道
because you didn't know because we didn't ask.

613
00:25:44,370 --> 00:25:46,550
我也没问  但他刚告诉我了
And I didn't ask now, but he told me now.

614
00:25:46,550 --> 00:25:48,780
而我们要遵守保密特权  谈都谈完了
And that's privileged, and the deal is done.

615
00:25:48,780 --> 00:25:50,670
等等  你打算什么都不做吗
Wait a minute, so you're not gonna do anything?

616
00:25:50,710 --> 00:25:52,810
我得让唐娜把这个送去地检办公室
I'm gonna have Donna messenger this to the D.A.'s office.

617
00:25:52,810 --> 00:25:55,150
哈维  那家人觉得是自己儿子的错
Harvey, this family thinks their son is to blame.

618
00:25:55,150 --> 00:25:56,910
本来他就是在逃离犯罪现场
Because he was fleeing the scene of a crime,

619
00:25:56,910 --> 00:25:58,920
-所以才会被撞  -好吧  就算是
- which put him in harm's way. - Okay, maybe.

620
00:25:58,920 --> 00:26:00,540
但如果我不告诉他们事实
But if I don't tell them this part,

621
00:26:00,540 --> 00:26:02,290
那我和尼克·里纳尔迪有什么区别
then I'm no different than Nick Rinaldi.

622
00:26:02,290 --> 00:26:03,940
-你已经和他不一样了  -什么意思
- You're already different. - What do you mean?

623
00:26:03,940 --> 00:26:06,120
我意思是他们都同意拿两万了
I mean, they were ready to take the $20,000,

624
00:26:06,130 --> 00:26:07,620
你给了人家十万
but you gave 'em $100,000.

625
00:26:07,620 --> 00:26:08,930
你觉得能一直瞒着我吗
Did you think I wasn't going to find out about that?

626
00:26:08,930 --> 00:26:09,870
哈维  拜托  别这样
Harvey, please, come on.

627
00:26:09,870 --> 00:26:11,840
我都警告你会有这种事了
You asked me to be on this case

628
00:26:11,840 --> 00:26:13,790
你还非要参与这案子
after I warned you about something like this.

629
00:26:13,790 --> 00:26:15,460
你说我没事
You said, "I'm onboard."

630
00:26:15,460 --> 00:26:16,970
要是吉莉安发现了你干的好事
Do you have any idea what would happen

631
00:26:16,970 --> 00:26:18,220
你想过后果没有
if Gillian found out what you did?

632
00:26:18,220 --> 00:26:19,850
要是她发现她儿子嗑药了呢
What if she found out about her son?

633
00:26:19,850 --> 00:26:21,390
大概也就多给点调解费吧
She'd probably give them a bigger settlement.

634
00:26:21,390 --> 00:26:24,100
不过反正你也已经多给了  我也没管你
But, hey, you already did that, and I let it go.

635
00:26:24,620 --> 00:26:26,520
-这事就这样了  -随你怎么说
- You need to let this go. - Say whatever you want.

636
00:26:26,520 --> 00:26:27,940
我都跟尼克·里纳尔迪没什么区别
That's no different than Nick Rinaldi.

637
00:26:27,940 --> 00:26:30,300
不过钱多点儿  鞋干净点儿罢了
That's just more money and cleaner shoes.

638
00:26:38,070 --> 00:26:39,180
天呐  让你等了
Oh, my God. You were waiting.

639
00:26:39,180 --> 00:26:41,400
我听说你在  就赶紧出来了
I heard you were here, so I rushed right out.

640
00:26:41,400 --> 00:26:42,700
我正式接受你的聘用
I formally accept your offer

641
00:26:42,700 --> 00:26:44,750
加入皮尔森·哈德曼律所
of employment at Pearson Hardman.

642
00:26:44,750 --> 00:26:46,810
这周真是棒极了
Oh, this is the best week ever.

643
00:26:46,810 --> 00:26:48,330
我不会令你失望的
I won't let you down.

644
00:26:48,850 --> 00:26:49,770
抱歉
I'm sorry.

645
00:26:49,770 --> 00:26:51,190
我不知道他具体指什么
I have no idea what this is regarding,

646
00:26:51,190 --> 00:26:53,840
不过他肯定会让你失望的  一向如此
but, yes, he will. He always does.

647
00:26:53,840 --> 00:26:56,040
-就当耳边风  -看到了吧
- Water off a snail's back. - See what I mean?

648
00:26:56,040 --> 00:26:58,600
唐娜·鲍尔森  这是玛丽亚·门罗
Donna Paulsen, Maria Monroe,

649
00:26:58,600 --> 00:26:59,340
我的新私人助理
my personal first-year.

650
00:26:59,350 --> 00:27:01,110
她是个工作狂
She's a machine.

651
00:27:01,110 --> 00:27:02,020
而且我跟你说
And let me just tell you something,

652
00:27:02,020 --> 00:27:03,830
迈克·罗斯跟她没得比
she's gonna run circles around Mike Ross.

653
00:27:03,830 --> 00:27:05,860
你在这儿等会  我去拿蛋糕来
You wait right here, and I'll get us some bundt cake.

654
00:27:05,860 --> 00:27:07,790
抱歉  迈克什么
I'm sorry, Mike who?

655
00:27:07,790 --> 00:27:10,140
-迈克·罗斯  -他也刚来吗
- Mike Ross. - Is he a first-year?

656
00:27:10,140 --> 00:27:11,030
为什么这么问
Why do you ask?

657
00:27:11,030 --> 00:27:13,130
我还以为你们只招哈佛的呢
I thought you only hired from Harvard.

658
00:27:13,130 --> 00:27:15,250
-没错  -我是班长
- We do. - I was secretary of my class.

659
00:27:15,250 --> 00:27:16,510
我知道所有人的名字
I knew every name.

660
00:27:16,510 --> 00:27:19,220
我们这届哈佛没有叫迈克·罗斯的
There was no Mike Ross my year at Harvard.

661
00:27:19,800 --> 00:27:21,150
不过你们不是一年的啊
But you weren't the same year.

662
00:27:21,150 --> 00:27:23,220
不  我做了一年书记员
No, I clerked for a year.

663
00:27:23,220 --> 00:27:24,600
他在这里比我早一年
He's a year ahead of me here,

664
00:27:24,600 --> 00:27:26,230
不过在学校应该和我一届
but he would have been in my class.

665
00:27:26,230 --> 00:27:28,240
迈克做了三年书记员
Oh, well, Mike clerked for three years,

666
00:27:28,240 --> 00:27:30,250
所以他不跟你一届
which means he wasn't in your class.

667
00:27:31,070 --> 00:27:33,690
我很期待与他见面
Well, I look forward to meeting him.

668
00:27:40,500 --> 00:27:42,640
昨晚
Uh...last night.

669
00:27:43,160 --> 00:27:44,720
我…
I was, uh...

670
00:27:45,200 --> 00:27:46,650
我开车回家
I was driving home,

671
00:27:47,270 --> 00:27:48,810
喝了不少酒
I'd had a lot to drink.

672
00:27:49,050 --> 00:27:50,360
然后撞人了
I hit someone.

673
00:27:51,740 --> 00:27:53,660
我觉得我肯定把人撞死了
And I'm pretty sure that they're dead.

674
00:27:54,820 --> 00:27:57,350
所以我需要你的帮助
So, uh, I need your help.

675
00:28:00,080 --> 00:28:02,170
抱歉  我不接这种案子
Sorry, I don't take cases like that.

676
00:28:02,170 --> 00:28:04,010
你不接这种案子吗
You don't take cases like that?

677
00:28:04,290 --> 00:28:06,500
那你1992年接的案子呢
What about your case from 1992?

678
00:28:06,500 --> 00:28:07,690
肇事者直接撞上别人的车
Driver plows into a car,

679
00:28:07,690 --> 00:28:09,830
之前喝了得有一桶威士忌加可乐
after drinking about a thousand jack and cokes,

680
00:28:09,830 --> 00:28:11,500
一对幸福的夫妻就这么死了
killing a happily married couple?

681
00:28:11,510 --> 00:28:13,040
叫詹姆斯·罗斯和妮娜·罗斯
James and Nina Ross?

682
00:28:13,330 --> 00:28:14,910
抱歉我不记得了
I'm afraid I have no recollection of that.

683
00:28:14,910 --> 00:28:17,130
是吗  那我给你提个醒
Oh, yeah? Let me ring a bell for you, then.

684
00:28:17,130 --> 00:28:19,190
车祸两天后  你走进他们家客厅
Two days later, you walk into their living room,

685
00:28:19,190 --> 00:28:21,850
发现只有个小男孩和他奶奶坐在那里
you find their little boy and his grandmother just sitting there,

686
00:28:21,850 --> 00:28:24,220
然后你就占尽了便宜
and then you stick it to them.

687
00:28:24,900 --> 00:28:27,490
他们都还没从悲伤中回过神
They hadn't even had time to hold a wake yet.

688
00:28:28,000 --> 00:28:29,650
你还不承认吗
Are you still gonna deny it?

689
00:28:29,650 --> 00:28:30,980
我没有不承认
I didn't deny it.

690
00:28:31,120 --> 00:28:32,380
我只是想不起来了
Just have no recollection of it

691
00:28:32,380 --> 00:28:34,340
因为这种事太多了
because I did it so many times.

692
00:28:34,350 --> 00:28:37,310
抱歉  你这是想感动我吗
I'm sorry, is that supposed to move me, huh?

693
00:28:37,310 --> 00:28:38,340
我难道该认为
Am I supposed to think

694
00:28:38,340 --> 00:28:39,930
你已经改过自新了吗
that you're somehow above all that now?

695
00:28:39,930 --> 00:28:42,120
我没想怎么样
It's not supposed to do anything.

696
00:28:42,130 --> 00:28:42,990
不过我提醒你下
But let me point out,

697
00:28:42,990 --> 00:28:44,430
两分钟前你进来
you walked in here two minutes ago,

698
00:28:44,430 --> 00:28:46,750
告诉我你撞人了  我没接你的案子
told me you'd hit somebody, and I turned you away.

699
00:28:51,910 --> 00:28:54,460
-你叫什么  -好像你在乎一样
- What's your name? - Like you give a shit.

700
00:28:55,220 --> 00:28:56,510
好吧
Okay.

701
00:28:56,880 --> 00:28:58,810
那你为什么来找我
What are you looking for from me?

702
00:28:58,810 --> 00:29:00,850
我想知道你怎么还能继续生活
I wanna know how you live with yourself.

703
00:29:01,250 --> 00:29:02,800
我想知道那之后你每天醒来
I wanna know how you wake up every morning

704
00:29:02,810 --> 00:29:04,040
怎么能忍住不开枪自杀
and not put a bullet in your brain,

705
00:29:04,040 --> 00:29:06,320
尽管明知自己干了些什么破事
knowing what a piece of shit you are!

706
00:29:06,800 --> 00:29:08,620
这话可能不好听
You might not want to hear this,

707
00:29:09,200 --> 00:29:10,610
我不记得你是谁
But just because I don't remember who you are

708
00:29:10,610 --> 00:29:12,830
并不代表对于我造成的伤害  我毫无悔意
doesn't mean I don't regret what I did to you.

709
00:29:13,240 --> 00:29:14,920
非常不幸的是  白纸黑字写清了
Now the sad fact is that once a deal is done,

710
00:29:14,920 --> 00:29:16,360
是无法改变的
it can't be undone.

711
00:29:16,360 --> 00:29:18,290
詹姆斯和尼娜·罗斯
James and Nina Ross.

712
00:29:20,540 --> 00:29:22,480
要是我再碰到你
If I ever see you again,

713
00:29:22,790 --> 00:29:25,170
你最好能记得这两个名字
you better remember who they are.

714
00:29:30,320 --> 00:29:31,840
谢谢
Thank you.

715
00:29:32,860 --> 00:29:35,270
你知道路易要雇佣私人助手吗
Did you know Louis is hiring his own associate?

716
00:29:35,270 --> 00:29:37,380
不是特别关心  他有这个权利
Not specifically, but he is entitled to it.

717
00:29:37,380 --> 00:29:38,720
我们得制止他
We got to stop him.

718
00:29:38,720 --> 00:29:40,430
哈维  我知道你在生路易的气
Harvey, I know you're mad at Louis.

719
00:29:40,430 --> 00:29:42,140
我也是  但事情过去了
So am I, but it's over.

720
00:29:42,140 --> 00:29:44,090
我们是赢家  他现在是为我们打工
We won, and the man has a job to do.

721
00:29:44,090 --> 00:29:45,600
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.

722
00:29:48,770 --> 00:29:51,440
他如果雇佣了现在这个人
We let him hire the person he just hired,

723
00:29:51,660 --> 00:29:53,190
迈克的身份就暴露了
Mike's gonna be exposed.

724
00:29:53,190 --> 00:29:54,180
你怎么知道
How do you know this?

725
00:29:54,180 --> 00:29:55,720
她是班长
She was secretary of his class.

726
00:29:55,720 --> 00:29:57,610
一个班得有600号人吧
And there's 600 kids in that class.

727
00:29:57,610 --> 00:30:00,330
-有谁能记住所有的人  -她号称她可以
- Nobody knows everybody. - She says she does.

728
00:30:01,110 --> 00:30:03,210
-你怎么就那么肯定呢  -唐娜和她打过照面
- How can you be so sure? - Donna met her.

729
00:30:03,210 --> 00:30:04,480
她非常肯定
She's sure.

730
00:30:04,480 --> 00:30:06,420
见鬼的迈克·罗斯
Goddamn Mike Ross.

731
00:30:06,680 --> 00:30:08,660
他老给我们添乱
He's the gift that keeps on giving.

732
00:30:09,930 --> 00:30:12,710
他还要拖我们多长时间后腿  哈维
How many more headaches is this kid gonna cause me, Harvey?

733
00:30:19,030 --> 00:30:20,300
你要见我
You wanted to see me?

734
00:30:20,490 --> 00:30:23,160
你是不是要招一个叫玛丽亚·门罗的
Did you make an offer to a Maria Monroe

735
00:30:23,170 --> 00:30:24,500
来做初级助理
to be a first-year associate?

736
00:30:24,510 --> 00:30:26,040
是的  我和你说吧
Yes, and let me just tell you something,

737
00:30:26,040 --> 00:30:27,810
-你绝对会喜欢她的  -让她别来了
- you're gonna love her. - Rescind it.

738
00:30:27,810 --> 00:30:29,480
-什么  -公司最近变动很大
- What? - Firm's been through a lot.

739
00:30:29,480 --> 00:30:30,780
我们需要重组
We have to regroup.

740
00:30:30,780 --> 00:30:33,220
所以  我决定停招新人 
Therefore, I'm instituting a hiring freeze,

741
00:30:33,230 --> 00:30:34,900
要是你招人之前问我一声
which you would have known about

742
00:30:34,900 --> 00:30:36,520
也不用现在这么大费周章了
had you come and asked my permission first.

743
00:30:36,530 --> 00:30:37,450
你不能这么对我
Okay, you can't do this.

744
00:30:37,450 --> 00:30:38,820
我是高级合伙人  公司规章允许我招
I'm a senior partner, and that's the rule.

745
00:30:38,820 --> 00:30:40,510
严格来说  并未成规章
Strictly speaking, it's not a rule,

746
00:30:40,510 --> 00:30:41,730
只是传统罢了
it's a tradition.

747
00:30:41,730 --> 00:30:43,000
我懂了
I get it.

748
00:30:43,040 --> 00:30:45,400
严格来说  并不是什么停招
Strictly speaking, this isn't about a hiring freeze,

749
00:30:45,400 --> 00:30:46,660
就是给我穿小鞋
this is punishment.

750
00:30:46,670 --> 00:30:49,080
你能这么做  我也可以
You can be punitive, I can be punitive.

751
00:30:49,990 --> 00:30:51,350
聘书已经发出去了
The offer already went out, Jessica.

752
00:30:51,350 --> 00:30:53,260
你不是律师吗  自己想办法
You're a lawyer, make it go away.

753
00:30:53,270 --> 00:30:54,630
我怎么对别人说啊
What am I gonna tell the world?

754
00:30:54,630 --> 00:30:55,930
搞得我像白痴一样
I'm gonna look like a freaking fool.

755
00:30:55,930 --> 00:30:57,980
就和他们说  现在公司停招
Well, tell them there's a hiring freeze.

756
00:30:59,690 --> 00:31:01,050
随你怎么说
I don't care.

757
00:31:01,440 --> 00:31:02,960
摆平就行
Make it go away.

758
00:31:06,590 --> 00:31:08,020
你可以走了
You're dismissed.

759
00:31:14,430 --> 00:31:16,860
你的留言看着有点耐人寻味
The message you left was a little cryptic.

760
00:31:16,860 --> 00:31:18,010
你到底想要什么
What do you want?

761
00:31:18,690 --> 00:31:20,670
我想要帮你得到你想要的
I want to help you get what you want.

762
00:31:20,850 --> 00:31:22,090
我想要的是什么
And what is that?

763
00:31:22,720 --> 00:31:24,850
利亚姆·柯顺开车撞倒艾伯特·钟那晚
Liam Colson was driving under the influence

764
00:31:24,850 --> 00:31:26,400
他嗑了药
when he hit Albert Chung.

765
00:31:26,930 --> 00:31:28,420
你是怎么知道的
How exactly did you come to know that?

766
00:31:28,420 --> 00:31:29,890
这无法奉告
I can't tell you that.

767
00:31:31,790 --> 00:31:33,570
谢谢你  迈克
Thank you, Mike.

768
00:31:33,570 --> 00:31:34,840
全体起立
All rise.

769
00:31:34,840 --> 00:31:37,400
有请尊敬的尼古拉斯·巴勒莫法官阁下
For the honorable judge Nicholas Palermo.

770
00:31:38,650 --> 00:31:39,850
全体坐下
Be seated.

771
00:31:39,860 --> 00:31:43,170
纽约州状告利亚姆·柯顺一案现在开庭
"State of New York versus Liam Colson."

772
00:31:45,720 --> 00:31:47,020
报告法官大人
I am happy to report

773
00:31:47,020 --> 00:31:48,690
昨晚被告已经和检方
the state entered into a plea agreement

774
00:31:48,690 --> 00:31:49,810
达成了认罪协议
with the defendant last night.

775
00:31:49,810 --> 00:31:51,750
协议条款已经呈送给您
You have a copy of the terms, your honor.

776
00:31:54,690 --> 00:31:56,510
一切进行得井井有条
Everything appears to be in order.

777
00:31:56,510 --> 00:31:57,700
本院批准这个协议
The agreement is approved.

778
00:31:57,700 --> 00:31:59,740
被告从下周一开始社区服务
Community service starts Monday.

779
00:32:02,170 --> 00:32:03,740
这就完了吗  你就这么走了吗
That's it? You're just walking away?

780
00:32:03,740 --> 00:32:05,150
是的  快步离开
As fast as I can.

781
00:32:05,150 --> 00:32:08,550
你知道你的“无可奉告”意味着什么吗
Because you know what "I can't tell you how I know that" means?

782
00:32:08,550 --> 00:32:10,000
你违反了保密特权
It means you just violated privilege.

783
00:32:10,010 --> 00:32:11,100
等等  你对他
Wait, so you don't care

784
00:32:11,100 --> 00:32:12,660
嗑药开车无动于衷
that he was driving under the influence?

785
00:32:12,660 --> 00:32:14,220
我不能证明他嗑了药
I can't prove he was under the influence.

786
00:32:14,220 --> 00:32:15,320
不把那孩子放上被告席
You don't know what you could prove

787
00:32:15,330 --> 00:32:16,690
你根本就不知道能问出点什么
if you got that kid in a room.

788
00:32:16,700 --> 00:32:17,890
如果我把你告诉我的作为证据
If I were to use what you just told me,

789
00:32:17,890 --> 00:32:20,390
别人还不都把我当傻瓜看
all I would be doing is making myself look like an idiot.

790
00:32:20,390 --> 00:32:22,640
你这么做晚上竟然能安然入梦
Are you really gonna be able to sleep at night?

791
00:32:23,470 --> 00:32:24,700
你能吗
Are you?

792
00:32:25,170 --> 00:32:26,590
你大摇大摆走进去
You're the one who walked in there

793
00:32:26,590 --> 00:32:29,060
想要毁了一个20岁少年的生活
and tried to sell out a 20-year-old kid.

794
00:32:29,060 --> 00:32:31,220
那个少年撞死了人
He took someone's life, right?

795
00:32:31,220 --> 00:32:33,840
而死者也是有父母  有姐姐
That someone had a mother and a father and a sister.

796
00:32:33,840 --> 00:32:36,330
现在他们一家生活全乱套了
That family is never gonna be the same.

797
00:32:36,450 --> 00:32:38,970
你听好了  你认为我就从来没有
Listen to me, you think I haven't had a case

798
00:32:38,970 --> 00:32:41,080
想要通过非正规手段把人送进监狱吗
where I could have crossed a line to put someone away?

799
00:32:41,080 --> 00:32:42,850
你觉得你当然想过
I wouldn't be surprised if you did,

800
00:32:42,850 --> 00:32:44,550
你不还想着要贿赂我吗
after that bribe you offered me.

801
00:32:44,560 --> 00:32:46,970
我贿赂你什么了
I didn't offer you shit.

802
00:32:46,970 --> 00:32:48,690
我只是帮了你个忙
I did you a favor.

803
00:32:48,700 --> 00:32:50,260
同时我也请你帮个忙
And then I asked for a favor,

804
00:32:50,260 --> 00:32:51,640
做不做都随你
which you could do or not.

805
00:32:51,650 --> 00:32:52,870
当你审视镜子中的自己
Is that really what you tell yourself

806
00:32:52,870 --> 00:32:54,350
就这么安慰自己吗
when you look in the mirror?

807
00:32:54,550 --> 00:32:55,910
如果你不惜违反保密特权
If you're willing to break privilege,

808
00:32:55,910 --> 00:32:58,360
你才应该去审视下自己
you're the one who needs to look in the mirror.

809
00:33:13,540 --> 00:33:15,160
卡特里娜·班尼特来电
Katrina Bennett called.

810
00:33:15,240 --> 00:33:16,490
事情确定了
The deal's done.

811
00:33:17,560 --> 00:33:19,340
你去起草文件吧
Get the paperwork started.

812
00:33:21,520 --> 00:33:23,020
哈维  你这是干什么
Harvey, what did you do?

813
00:33:23,770 --> 00:33:25,540
这事儿我没得选
I did what I had to do.

814
00:33:28,380 --> 00:33:30,150
你第一个雇的是迈克
Your first hire was Mike.

815
00:33:30,150 --> 00:33:32,200
你真想让她成为你的第二个雇员吗
Are you sure you want this to be your second?

816
00:33:32,210 --> 00:33:33,690
你别说了
I don't want to hear it.

817
00:33:33,950 --> 00:33:35,640
她从周一开始上班
She starts on Monday.

818
00:33:56,040 --> 00:33:57,970
教皇新堡  1985年产
Chateauneuf-du-Pape, 1985.

819
00:33:57,970 --> 00:34:00,160
我想他们83年的酒都卖光了
I guess they were out of the '83.

820
00:34:02,240 --> 00:34:03,410
路易
Louis,

821
00:34:03,780 --> 00:34:05,550
你看着好像  我刚给你一拳
you look like I just kicked you in the stomach

822
00:34:05,550 --> 00:34:07,280
-可你都不享受  -对不起
- but in a bad way. - I'm sorry.

823
00:34:07,280 --> 00:34:10,370
我心思不在这儿
I, my mind's on something else.

824
00:34:10,370 --> 00:34:11,630
怎么了
What is it?

825
00:34:13,550 --> 00:34:14,980
答应我听了别发火
Promise you won't be mad?

826
00:34:16,070 --> 00:34:18,360
你不是想让我去做什么艾滋病检查吧
You're not about to tell me I have to get tested, are you?

827
00:34:18,360 --> 00:34:21,010
什么  不是这件事
What? No. Nothing like that.

828
00:34:21,010 --> 00:34:22,110
我
I...

829
00:34:22,110 --> 00:34:23,920
我不得不撤回聘书
I had to rescind the offer...

830
00:34:24,320 --> 00:34:25,580
不招玛丽亚了
To Maria.

831
00:34:27,180 --> 00:34:28,940
-你生气了  -没有
- You're mad? - No.

832
00:34:29,040 --> 00:34:32,070
-我很失望  -希拉
- I'm disappointed. - Sheila...

833
00:34:32,080 --> 00:34:34,080
你和我想像中的不一样
You're not the man I thought you were.

834
00:34:34,580 --> 00:34:36,260
我别无选择
I-I didn't have a choice.

835
00:34:36,440 --> 00:34:37,870
是杰西卡·皮尔逊做的决定
It was Jessica Pearson's decision.

836
00:34:37,870 --> 00:34:39,020
好吧  我对你是看走眼了
Okay, well, then I must have read you wrong

837
00:34:39,020 --> 00:34:42,150
本以为你是有能力  有权力的高级合伙人
'cause I thought you were a strong, powerful senior partner.

838
00:34:42,150 --> 00:34:43,080
我是啊
I am.

839
00:34:43,080 --> 00:34:44,920
现在看来完全不是
The evidence suggests otherwise.

840
00:34:45,800 --> 00:34:47,310
你还是走吧
I think you should go.

841
00:34:50,210 --> 00:34:51,650
希拉  别这样
Sheila, please.

842
00:34:51,990 --> 00:34:54,850
我们对这事儿不能一笑了之吗
I mean, can't this snaff just be something we laugh at?

843
00:34:54,850 --> 00:34:56,620
过一两个小时就别去想它了
Like, in an hour and a half, hour and 45 minutes?

844
00:34:56,630 --> 00:34:58,900
你床上功夫再好也没有用
Your sexual prowess isn't gonna get you out of this.

845
00:34:58,900 --> 00:35:00,320
-你生气了  -是的
- You are mad. - Yeah.

846
00:35:00,320 --> 00:35:02,430
我以自己的名誉向她替你说好话
I put my reputation on the line to close Maria.

847
00:35:02,430 --> 00:35:03,780
听着  这不是我的错
Look, it's not my fault.

848
00:35:03,780 --> 00:35:05,600
公司已经停止招聘了
The firm instituted a hiring freeze.

849
00:35:05,600 --> 00:35:06,910
若真是如此
If there's a hiring freeze going on,

850
00:35:06,910 --> 00:35:08,100
为何我却听说
then why do I know for a fact

851
00:35:08,110 --> 00:35:11,300
哈维·斯佩克特今天招了一个助理呢
that Harvey Specter hired a fifth-year associate today?

852
00:35:12,710 --> 00:35:14,570
你把卡特里娜·班尼特招进来了吗
You offered Katrina Bennett a job?

853
00:35:14,570 --> 00:35:15,470
我查了她的背景
I looked into her.

854
00:35:15,470 --> 00:35:17,450
她在应聘者中算是佼佼者
Turns out she's a stellar candidate.

855
00:35:17,710 --> 00:35:19,020
你这是贿赂她
You bribed her.

856
00:35:19,320 --> 00:35:21,450
贿赂是需要明确地用某物
A bribe requires a clear exchange

857
00:35:21,450 --> 00:35:23,170
与另外一物进行交换才算成立
of something for something else.

858
00:35:23,170 --> 00:35:24,760
-我可没做这事  -扯淡
- That didn't happen here. - Bullshit.

859
00:35:24,760 --> 00:35:27,150
她说了你若聘她  她就签协议
She said she'd put the deal through if you offered her a job.

860
00:35:27,150 --> 00:35:28,510
是她先签了协议
She said she'd put the deal through,

861
00:35:28,510 --> 00:35:29,870
我再去聘她的
then I offered her a job.

862
00:35:29,870 --> 00:35:32,080
还真是啊  因为你需要份保障书
Oh, right, because you needed an insurance policy.

863
00:35:32,080 --> 00:35:34,340
是因为我料到了你会怎么做
Because I could see exactly what you were gonna do.

864
00:35:34,340 --> 00:35:37,110
所以你才给她份工作  以得到你想要的
So you offered her a job to get her to do what you wanted.

865
00:35:37,110 --> 00:35:38,620
这就是一物换一物
That's something for something else.

866
00:35:38,620 --> 00:35:40,090
你贿赂了她
You bribed her.

867
00:35:40,190 --> 00:35:41,840
你一口咬定我贿赂
You bet your ass I did.

868
00:35:41,840 --> 00:35:43,620
但你蠢到连我这是为了你
But what you're too stupid to understand is

869
00:35:43,620 --> 00:35:45,610
都想不到
I did it to save you.

870
00:35:45,610 --> 00:35:47,640
你这楠木脑袋给我想清楚了
Get it through your goddamn head.

871
00:35:47,640 --> 00:35:49,330
你没按规矩来
You're not like other lawyers.

872
00:35:49,330 --> 00:35:51,070
侵犯了当事人特权
You break attorney-client privilege.

873
00:35:51,070 --> 00:35:53,100
利亚姆倒没什么事儿
Nothing different happens with Liam,

874
00:35:53,120 --> 00:35:54,900
但他们是肯定要来调查你了
but they're sure as sh-- gonna look into you.

875
00:35:54,900 --> 00:35:56,680
他们会发现什么就不必我明说了吧
And you and I both know what they're gonna find when they do.

876
00:35:56,680 --> 00:35:58,440
他们发现了又如何
What difference does it make what they find?

877
00:35:58,450 --> 00:36:00,110
是非黑白是有个度的
There's such a thing as right and wrong.

878
00:36:00,110 --> 00:36:00,820
这事是错在我们
And we're wrong!

879
00:36:00,830 --> 00:36:01,370
告诉你
You know what?

880
00:36:01,370 --> 00:36:03,550
每次碰到了灰色地带  要做决定
I have had it up to here with you blaming me

881
00:36:03,550 --> 00:36:05,820
你就跑来指责我  我受够了
for every hard choice that comes with this job.

882
00:36:05,830 --> 00:36:07,130
-哈维  别这样  -闭嘴
- Harvey, come on. - Shut up!

883
00:36:09,770 --> 00:36:12,650
我雇用你后  生活是变好了还是变差了
Is your life better or worse than before I hired you?

884
00:36:13,880 --> 00:36:14,690
都有
It's both.

885
00:36:14,700 --> 00:36:16,360
你还是记着那些好的吧
Well, maybe you should focus on the better,

886
00:36:16,360 --> 00:36:18,220
因为下次若我还要
because the next time I have the option

887
00:36:18,220 --> 00:36:20,060
越界去救你
to cross a line to save you,

888
00:36:20,060 --> 00:36:22,900
我只会让你收拾包袱滚蛋
I'll send you packing and not think twice.

889
00:36:23,520 --> 00:36:25,480
给我好好想想吧
Now get your shit together.

890
00:37:26,120 --> 00:37:27,090
搞定了吗
Is it done?

891
00:37:27,100 --> 00:37:28,200
搞定了
It's done.

892
00:37:28,750 --> 00:37:32,000
太感谢了  这是干什么
Thank you. What's wrong?

893
00:37:32,000 --> 00:37:34,740
干什么  有人死了
That's wrong? A man is dead.

894
00:37:34,750 --> 00:37:37,310
是你杀了他  而我无能为力
You killed him, and I have to live with it.

895
00:37:37,840 --> 00:37:39,380
你以为我不知道吗
And you think I don't know that?

896
00:37:40,030 --> 00:37:42,460
我还得装作没事继续我的生活
I get to go back to my life like nothing happened,

897
00:37:42,510 --> 00:37:44,180
但事情无可挽回了
but something did happen.

898
00:37:44,920 --> 00:37:46,610
-我很难受  -你活该
- It makes me sick. - It should.

899
00:37:46,610 --> 00:37:49,260
所以你过来是让我更难受吗
Is that why you came here, to make me feel worse?

900
00:37:49,260 --> 00:37:52,090
这份协议你根本不配有
You've been given a gift that you don't deserve.

901
00:37:52,090 --> 00:37:53,750
所以你最好反思一下自己
So you better clean yourself up

902
00:37:53,750 --> 00:37:56,330
该怎么补偿艾伯特·钟
and figure out a way to make up for Albert Chung.

903
00:38:04,140 --> 00:38:06,240
你带花来了  有长进噢
You brought flowers. You're learning.

904
00:38:06,240 --> 00:38:07,820
这是给奥利维亚的
They're for Olivia.

905
00:38:08,690 --> 00:38:09,940
那我怎么办
What about me?

906
00:38:11,470 --> 00:38:12,900
那个是给你的
That's for you.

907
00:38:12,950 --> 00:38:15,060
你给我买了辆…车吗
You bought me a...car?

908
00:38:15,060 --> 00:38:17,480
对啊  我想着可以一起去趟伯克夏兹
Yeah, I was thinking we'd drive up to the Berkshires.

909
00:38:17,600 --> 00:38:19,010
那边有个小木屋
There's a little cabin I know.

910
00:38:19,010 --> 00:38:20,620
自带桑拿浴
It's got its own sauna,

911
00:38:20,620 --> 00:38:21,990
私人厨师
private chef.

912
00:38:25,810 --> 00:38:28,030
我不能跟你去  哈维
I can't go away with you, Harvey.

913
00:38:29,340 --> 00:38:30,510
怎么了
Why not?

914
00:38:35,190 --> 00:38:36,600
我哥哥得了癌症
My brother's got cancer.

915
00:38:36,610 --> 00:38:38,920
不知道能熬多久
He's-- he's not gonna make it.

916
00:38:39,950 --> 00:38:41,290
我的天啊
Oh, my god.

917
00:38:43,070 --> 00:38:44,110
是她爸爸
Her dad.

918
00:38:44,110 --> 00:38:45,610
我们知道迟早会这样
I mean, we knew that it was coming.

919
00:38:45,610 --> 00:38:48,080
但没想到会来的这么快
We just didn't know it would be this fast.

920
00:38:51,550 --> 00:38:53,930
-她在这里吗  -没有
- Is she here? - No.

921
00:38:53,930 --> 00:38:55,770
不过我准备去我父母那
But I'm going to my parents',

922
00:38:55,830 --> 00:38:58,260
我会让她跟着我生活
and I'm gonna-- I'm gonna take her with me.

923
00:38:59,010 --> 00:39:00,650
我要抚养她长大
I'm gonna raise her.

924
00:39:02,630 --> 00:39:04,220
你怎么不告诉我呢
Why didn't you tell me?

925
00:39:04,220 --> 00:39:06,370
因为我以为  要是…
Because I thought, you know, when...

926
00:39:06,380 --> 00:39:07,640
你看到奥利维亚在这里
you saw Olivia was here,

927
00:39:07,640 --> 00:39:09,760
就会重新找时间约我
that we'd reschedule or something, you know?

928
00:39:09,760 --> 00:39:11,300
结果…
And then...

929
00:39:11,300 --> 00:39:15,090
看见你 跟她在一起  真是…
I saw you with her, and it...

930
00:39:15,100 --> 00:39:16,480
很…
it was...

931
00:39:16,890 --> 00:39:18,620
你想留份美好回忆
You wanted to have a night.

932
00:39:20,190 --> 00:39:23,060
那并不是我的本意
Okay, I didn't think it would lead to that.

933
00:39:25,450 --> 00:39:27,770
但最后发现那晚很美好
But I'm really happy that it did.

934
00:39:29,970 --> 00:39:31,400
你什么时候走
When are you going?

935
00:39:32,180 --> 00:39:33,450
很快
Soon.

936
00:39:38,820 --> 00:39:40,260
抱歉
I'm sorry.

937
00:39:42,580 --> 00:39:45,170
真的很遗憾
I'm so, so sorry.

938
00:39:48,830 --> 00:39:50,400
惊喜一下
Surprise.

939
00:39:52,300 --> 00:39:54,630
你都没跟我联系  案子怎么样
Hey, I never heard from you. How did the case go?

940
00:39:54,630 --> 00:39:56,220
我没心情说
I don't want to talk about it.

941
00:39:57,730 --> 00:39:58,910
输得挺惨吧
That bad, huh?

942
00:39:58,910 --> 00:40:00,450
是啊  很惨
Yeah, that bad.

943
00:40:00,960 --> 00:40:03,170
这样  那你干嘛不过来
Well, why don't you come over here,

944
00:40:03,170 --> 00:40:04,800
我会让你感觉好点儿的
And I'll make you feel better?

945
00:40:05,050 --> 00:40:07,170
我没等你来就开始了
I already started without you.

946
00:40:11,260 --> 00:40:13,350
我不能再这样了  苔丝
I can't do this anymore, tess.

947
00:40:14,040 --> 00:40:14,950
吸毒吗
Get high?

948
00:40:14,950 --> 00:40:18,690
-太恶心了  -你中什么邪了
- It's so disgusting. - What got into you?

949
00:40:18,690 --> 00:40:20,740
整件事就很恶心
This whole thing is disgusting.

950
00:40:25,490 --> 00:40:27,200
你这是在跟我分手吗
Are you breaking up with me?

951
00:40:32,600 --> 00:40:34,600
-你爱你的丈夫吗  -什么
- Do you love your husband? - What?

952
00:40:34,600 --> 00:40:36,390
答案很简单  苔丝  回答我
It's a simple question, Tess, Answer it.

953
00:40:36,390 --> 00:40:37,870
你爱你的丈夫吗
Do you love your husband?

954
00:40:39,920 --> 00:40:43,450
-我不知道  -你看  我连这个都不知道
- Uh, I don't know. - See, I don't even know that.

955
00:40:43,450 --> 00:40:44,960
因为我们从没谈论过
Because we never even talk about it.

956
00:40:44,960 --> 00:40:45,830
那我们现在可以来谈谈啊
Well, we can talk about it now.

957
00:40:45,840 --> 00:40:47,810
我现在没心情跟你说这个
I don't want to talk about it now!

958
00:40:48,270 --> 00:40:51,020
苔丝  是非黑白都有个度
Tess, there is such a thing as right and wrong.

959
00:40:51,020 --> 00:40:52,730
我们做的这些…
And what we're doing here...

960
00:40:54,050 --> 00:40:55,730
是错的  何况…
It's just wrong, and...

961
00:40:55,730 --> 00:40:56,980
你结婚了
You're married.

962
00:40:58,130 --> 00:40:59,980
我不想搅合在里面
And I don't want a part of it anymore.

963
00:41:03,910 --> 00:41:05,570
如果我没结婚呢
What if I wasn't?

964
00:41:08,880 --> 00:41:10,030
迈克
Mike.

965
00:41:11,990 --> 00:41:13,290
你走吧
You need to go.

966
00:41:14,500 --> 00:41:16,420
我自己要好好想想
And I need to get my shit together.

