1
00:00:27,380 --> 00:00:29,990
2011款特斯拉敞篷运动跑车
The 2011 Tesla Roadster Sport,

2
00:00:29,990 --> 00:00:32,480
只为我们最为尊贵的会员提供
offered only to our most exclusive members.

3
00:00:32,480 --> 00:00:33,910
你果真懂车
You know your vehicles.

4
00:00:33,980 --> 00:00:36,600
我保证在她沦落成庞蒂亚克前还回来
I promise to have her back before she turns into a Pontiac.

5
00:00:33,980 --> 00:00:36,600
庞蒂亚克:通用旗下品牌  09年被砍从此消失

6
00:00:36,610 --> 00:00:38,760
-嗨  哈维  -劳伦斯
- Hey, Harvey. - Laurence.

7
00:00:38,820 --> 00:00:41,810
除了特斯拉  你今晚挑辆别的车如何
How would you feel about taking something other than the Tesla tonight?

8
00:00:41,810 --> 00:00:44,320
-这有违我的原则  -什么原则
- It goes against my policy. - What policy?

9
00:00:44,420 --> 00:00:46,210
"我要这辆特斯拉"原则
My "I want the Tesla" policy.

10
00:00:46,210 --> 00:00:47,940
-好吧  -这样吧
- Yeah. - Tell you what.

11
00:00:48,050 --> 00:00:50,160
如果你比我更了解这辆车
You know more about the car than I do,

12
00:00:51,670 --> 00:00:52,880
就归你
it's yours.

13
00:00:56,630 --> 00:00:57,540
马力
Horsepower.

14
00:00:57,540 --> 00:00:59,360
不是吧  第一问就是这个吗
Really? That's where we're starting?

15
00:00:59,360 --> 00:01:01,680
觉得简单的话  就请回答
Well, if it's so simple, just answer it.

16
00:01:01,680 --> 00:01:03,180
288匹
288.

17
00:01:03,180 --> 00:01:06,500
-最高时速  -每小时125英里[约200公里]
- Top speed. - 125 miles an hour.

18
00:01:07,220 --> 00:01:09,370
-从0加速到60迈...  -3.7秒
- 0 to 60-- - 3.7 seconds.

19
00:01:09,370 --> 00:01:11,620
看来你确实了解你的车
Yeah. You know your cars.

20
00:01:11,850 --> 00:01:13,090
我是个狂热的车迷
I'm an enthusiast.

21
00:01:13,090 --> 00:01:15,120
而且我等特斯拉上市好几个月了
And I've been waiting for the Tesla for months.

22
00:01:15,120 --> 00:01:15,920
好吧
Okay.

23
00:01:20,180 --> 00:01:21,080
劳伦斯
Laurence.

24
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:25,440
自便吧
Knock yourself out.

25
00:01:26,390 --> 00:01:27,600
你为什么要让给他
So why'd you let him have it?

26
00:01:27,600 --> 00:01:29,090
因为让一个运作20亿对冲基金的人
Because it never hurts to have a man

27
00:01:29,090 --> 00:01:31,580
欠我个人情总是有益无害的
who runs a $2 billion hedge fund owe you one.

28
00:01:31,580 --> 00:01:33,220
但如果你都决定给他了
But if you're just gonna give it to him,

29
00:01:33,220 --> 00:01:34,720
何必还跟他比呢
why bother to compete first?

30
00:01:34,720 --> 00:01:35,920
因为若不是我赢了他
Because if I didn't beat him,

31
00:01:35,970 --> 00:01:37,610
他不会觉得欠我个人情
he wouldn't feel he owed me one.

32
00:01:37,610 --> 00:01:39,380
我突然想要俩复古的车了
I'm suddenly feeling old school.

33
00:01:39,380 --> 00:01:40,960
你何不给我个惊喜
Why don't you surprise me, huh?

34
00:01:48,430 --> 00:01:49,980
你是迈克·罗斯吗
Are you Mike Ross?

35
00:01:52,950 --> 00:01:56,080
哈维让我告诉你  八点整就是八点整
Harvey told me to tell you that 8:00 means 8:00.

36
00:01:56,080 --> 00:01:58,040
在贾维茨中心跟我会合

37
00:02:20,460 --> 00:02:21,790
很高兴你还是来了
Glad you showed up.

38
00:02:21,790 --> 00:02:22,880
不好意思  我刚刚...
Oh, hey. I'm sorry. I was just--

39
00:02:22,880 --> 00:02:24,360
-闭嘴  -好的
- Shut up. - OK.

40
00:02:25,040 --> 00:02:26,130
你看到这些车了吗
You see these cars?

41
00:02:26,130 --> 00:02:27,740
看到了  太拉风了
Yeah. They're awesome.

42
00:02:27,740 --> 00:02:28,780
烂透了
They suck.

43
00:02:28,840 --> 00:02:30,840
跟这辆根本没法比
They're nothing compared to this.

44
00:02:31,860 --> 00:02:34,430
这车的引擎是麦肯诺汽车公司制造的
The engine in this car is made by McKernon Motors,

45
00:02:34,430 --> 00:02:37,250
是F1的行业标准
the industry standard in Formula One.

46
00:02:37,320 --> 00:02:39,540
事实上  靠这引擎拿的冠军
In fact, they've won more championships

47
00:02:39,540 --> 00:02:41,200
比其它任何引擎都多
than any other engine on the planet.

48
00:02:41,200 --> 00:02:42,660
你是怎么知道这些的
How do you know all this?

49
00:02:42,710 --> 00:02:44,510
艾弗里·麦肯诺曾经是
Avery McKernon was the first client

50
00:02:44,510 --> 00:02:45,690
我带进律所的第一位客户
I ever brought into the firm.

51
00:02:45,690 --> 00:02:48,190
-曾经  -他三个月前去世了
- Was? - He died three months ago.

52
00:02:48,260 --> 00:02:49,340
天呐  我很抱歉...
Oh, God. I'm so sorry--

53
00:02:49,340 --> 00:02:49,980
这不是重点
Not the point.

54
00:02:49,980 --> 00:02:52,030
麦肯诺的引擎和他的公司
McKernon's engines and his company

55
00:02:52,140 --> 00:02:53,310
有一个共同之处
have something in common--

56
00:02:53,310 --> 00:02:55,170
他们总是赢家  就像我
They win, like me.

57
00:02:55,250 --> 00:02:57,650
正因如此  我晋升为资深合伙人了
And because I win, I've been promoted to senior partner,

58
00:02:57,650 --> 00:02:59,610
这意味着你将处理他们所有的文件
which means you'll be handling all their paperwork.

59
00:02:59,610 --> 00:03:00,490
所以你带我来
Oh, so you brought me here

60
00:03:00,520 --> 00:03:02,060
就是让我欣赏下产品
to give me an appreciation for the product.

61
00:03:02,060 --> 00:03:04,280
不  我是带你来见罗伯特·斯坦斯兰
No, I brought you here to meet Robert Stensland,

62
00:03:04,280 --> 00:03:05,270
新任CEO
the new CEO.

63
00:03:05,300 --> 00:03:07,100
他希望把你的名字和长相对上号
He'll want to put your name with a face.

64
00:03:07,150 --> 00:03:07,980
你怎么知道
How do you know?

65
00:03:08,070 --> 00:03:09,470
因为罗伯特是个吝啬鬼
Because Robert's a tightwad,

66
00:03:09,470 --> 00:03:11,100
不是雇你来吃白饭的
and we don't bill you out for nothing.

67
00:03:11,320 --> 00:03:13,540
等下  我们现在聊天也计费吗
Wait a minute. Is this conversation right now billable?

68
00:03:13,540 --> 00:03:14,630
当然得计费
You bet your ass it is.

69
00:03:14,630 --> 00:03:17,330
耶  击掌庆祝下  快点
Yes. Up top. Come on.

70
00:03:18,270 --> 00:03:20,050
怎么  赚那么多钱  不该庆祝下吗
What? We're making all this money. We can't celebrate it?

71
00:03:20,050 --> 00:03:21,670
庆祝也得有品位
Not in poor taste.

72
00:03:24,180 --> 00:03:27,290
多米尼克  迈克  这位是多米尼克·巴伦
Dominic. Mike, I'd like you to meet Dominic Barone,

73
00:03:27,290 --> 00:03:31,000
他负责这个引擎的设计和制造
the man responsible for the design and production of this engine.

74
00:03:31,000 --> 00:03:32,690
这是我的新助理  迈克·罗斯
This is my new associate, Mike Ross.

75
00:03:32,740 --> 00:03:33,640
他还是个孩子呢
He's just a kid.

76
00:03:33,640 --> 00:03:35,640
你想在他青春期前就糟蹋他吗
Are you trying to steal his soul before he hits puberty?

77
00:03:35,640 --> 00:03:37,030
好吧  显然...
Okay, obviously...

78
00:03:37,030 --> 00:03:38,670
你还在为我们的劳资谈判郁闷啊
You're still upset about our labor negotiations.

79
00:03:38,670 --> 00:03:40,280
我的员工遭到严重打击
My-- My workers took a big hit.

80
00:03:40,470 --> 00:03:41,940
麦肯诺还丢了性命呢
And McKernon took a bigger one.

81
00:03:42,070 --> 00:03:44,800
这些年来  他们撑起了这个强大的公司
Both of which poised the company to be strong for years.

82
00:03:44,800 --> 00:03:46,180
这点我从不怀疑
I was always straight with you about that.

83
00:03:46,180 --> 00:03:48,080
一个搞垮我们的人  还说得出这种话
Sophisticated words for a guy who screwed us.

84
00:03:48,080 --> 00:03:49,310
很抱歉你会那么想
Look, I'm sorry you feel that way,

85
00:03:49,310 --> 00:03:50,000
但你不得不承认
but you have to admit,

86
00:03:50,000 --> 00:03:52,410
我那事做得光明磊落
I did have the courtesy to do it from the front.

87
00:03:54,970 --> 00:03:56,930
哇  真的  他很感激
Wow. Yeah, he really appreciates

88
00:03:56,930 --> 00:03:58,640
你为公司所做的一切
what you've done for the company.

89
00:03:58,830 --> 00:03:59,980
罗伯特·斯坦斯兰
Robert Stensland,

90
00:03:59,980 --> 00:04:02,640
给你介绍下你新的助理律师  迈克·罗斯
I'd like you to meet your new associate, Mike Ross.

91
00:04:03,340 --> 00:04:05,020
我们付他的报酬可没付你的那么高
We're not paying him what we pay you.

92
00:04:05,020 --> 00:04:07,980
那是自然  但我保证他很有效率
Nor should you, but I assure you he's highly effective.

93
00:04:08,630 --> 00:04:09,990
是吗  口说无凭啊
Well, I'll believe it when I see it.

94
00:04:09,990 --> 00:04:12,240
我上周让他读了你们的公司租赁合同
I had him read your corporate lease last week.

95
00:04:12,400 --> 00:04:13,890
尽管问
Ask him anything.

96
00:04:14,190 --> 00:04:15,970
那可是300页的文件
That's a 300-page document.

97
00:04:18,620 --> 00:04:20,310
好  说一下合同条款的内容
Okay, what are the terms?

98
00:04:20,560 --> 00:04:23,130
听着  我完全摸不着头脑
Okay, I have no idea what you're talking about.

99
00:04:23,130 --> 00:04:26,620
承租人是母公司  格兰登企业集团
The named lessee was the parent company, Glendon Enterprises.

100
00:04:26,860 --> 00:04:28,330
企业位于西19区57号  
35,000 square feet

101
00:04:28,330 --> 00:04:30,330
3万5千平方英尺[991平方米]
at 19 west 57th.

102
00:04:30,340 --> 00:04:31,830
每英尺80美元
$80 a foot.

103
00:04:31,890 --> 00:04:35,090
六个月后到期  可以续租
Expires in six months with an option to extend.

104
00:04:35,090 --> 00:04:36,970
操作期限为30天
Exercisable in 30 days.

105
00:04:37,860 --> 00:04:39,740
-谁签的合同  -你签的
- Who signed the lease? - You did.

106
00:04:39,990 --> 00:04:41,840
-我的中名是什么  -字母L
- What's my middle name? - The letter "L."

107
00:04:41,840 --> 00:04:44,910
如果公司不存在了怎么办
What happens in the event the company no longer exists?

108
00:04:45,200 --> 00:04:46,410
合同里没有这条
That wasn't in the lease.

109
00:04:46,410 --> 00:04:47,220
你如何能确定
How can you be sure?

110
00:04:47,220 --> 00:04:49,350
因为我看到的合同不是300页
Because the lease I read wasn't 300 pages.

111
00:04:49,350 --> 00:04:50,970
而是364页
It was 364.

112
00:04:50,970 --> 00:04:53,010
每一页的内容我都了如指掌
And I can tell you what's on any one of those pages,

113
00:04:53,010 --> 00:04:54,350
而那点我却不知道
but I can't tell you that.

114
00:04:54,350 --> 00:04:55,730
所以我能确定合同中没提到
That's how I can be sure.

115
00:04:55,850 --> 00:04:56,930
很好
Excellent.

116
00:04:57,140 --> 00:04:59,230
你可以让他马上着手处理新合同了
You can get him started on the new deal right away.

117
00:04:59,240 --> 00:05:00,860
-新合同  -没错
- New deal?  - Yeah.

118
00:05:00,860 --> 00:05:03,980
我找到一个买家  愿意出两亿美金
I have found a buyer willing to spend $200 million

119
00:05:03,980 --> 00:05:05,920
买下旗舰工厂所在的地方
for the ground underneath the flagship factory.

120
00:05:06,000 --> 00:05:07,550
那你们准备转移到哪里生产
Where are you moving manufacturing?

121
00:05:07,610 --> 00:05:08,860
这可就是重点了
Well, that's the beauty of it.

122
00:05:08,940 --> 00:05:11,300
麦肯诺真正的价值在于其品牌
The real asset of McKernon Motors is the name.

123
00:05:11,300 --> 00:05:13,370
我们将把工厂移到海外  省下一大笔钱
We move overseas, we save ourselves a bundle.

124
00:05:13,370 --> 00:05:15,000
保留品牌的同时进行预先付款
Up front payout while retaining the name

125
00:05:15,000 --> 00:05:16,540
长期维持现金的流动
and maintaining cash flow over time.

126
00:05:16,540 --> 00:05:18,190
-这点子太有才了  -正是
- That's genius. - Exactly.

127
00:05:18,190 --> 00:05:19,420
好的  我们会处理好一切的
All right, we'll take care of everything.

128
00:05:19,420 --> 00:05:22,160
很好
Okay.

129
00:05:22,160 --> 00:05:23,620
谢了
Thanks.

130
00:05:23,620 --> 00:05:24,720
不是吧
Really?

131
00:05:25,330 --> 00:05:27,330
天呐  我知道他很抠门
Jesus. I knew he was cheap.

132
00:05:27,330 --> 00:05:28,780
但没想到他还是个白痴
I didn't realize he was an idiot.

133
00:05:28,870 --> 00:05:29,740
你这话什么意思
What are you talking about?

134
00:05:29,740 --> 00:05:31,570
这车的价值不在于品牌  而是质量
The asset's not the name. It's the quality.

135
00:05:31,570 --> 00:05:33,300
他把工厂移到海外  
He moves overseas,

136
00:05:33,300 --> 00:05:35,540
根本就是杀鸡取卵
it's gonna kill the goose that laid the goddamn golden engine.

137
00:05:35,800 --> 00:05:36,580
等下  
Wait a minute.

138
00:05:36,580 --> 00:05:39,120
我记得你从不会对客户投入感情的
I thought you didn't get emotionally attached to the client.

139
00:05:39,160 --> 00:05:40,550
我这是对自己投入感情
I'm emotionally attached to me.

140
00:05:40,550 --> 00:05:42,740
我以前打赌这家公司会壮大
Look, I made a bet that this company would grow

141
00:05:42,740 --> 00:05:44,510
我的价位也会水涨船高
and my billables would grow with it.

142
00:05:44,520 --> 00:05:45,890
我们现在拿着一手好牌
We're holding a pair of aces,

143
00:05:45,890 --> 00:05:47,560
而这蠢蛋居然打算弃牌
and this asshole's trying to fold.

144
00:05:47,560 --> 00:05:49,310
所以呢  你打算怎么办
So? What are you gonna do?

145
00:05:49,310 --> 00:05:50,430
我什么都不干
I'm not gonna do anything.

146
00:05:50,430 --> 00:05:51,760
而你要去通读公司章程
You're gonna go through those bylaws,

147
00:05:51,760 --> 00:05:53,840
给我找出摆脱罗伯特·斯坦斯兰的方法
and you're gonna find me a way to get rid of Robert Stensland.

148
00:05:53,850 --> 00:05:55,510
不不不  我得去探望我奶奶
No, no, no, no. I have to go see my grandmother.

149
00:05:55,510 --> 00:05:57,000
她要不行了吗
Is she dying?

150
00:05:57,670 --> 00:05:59,550
-没有  -那取消行程
- No. - Cancel on her.

151
00:06:06,050 --> 00:06:10,050
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
 更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

152
00:06:06,050 --> 00:06:10,050
■

153
00:06:10,050 --> 00:06:14,050
翻译：暮羽  桃乐  猴子  马蒂  米苏  Lyra

154
00:06:10,050 --> 00:06:14,050
■

155
00:06:14,050 --> 00:06:18,050
时间轴：小怡子  潘叔  校对：饿得慌  地瓜

156
00:06:14,050 --> 00:06:18,050
■

157
00:06:18,050 --> 00:06:22,050
后期：飞飞  总监：丢丢

158
00:06:18,050 --> 00:06:22,050
■

159
00:06:30,990 --> 00:06:33,160
诉 讼 双 雄

160
00:06:30,990 --> 00:06:33,160
第一季 第三集

161
00:07:06,820 --> 00:07:07,590
是我
Yeah.

162
00:07:07,720 --> 00:07:09,870
找到摆脱斯坦斯兰的方法了吗
Did you find anything that'll help me get rid of Stensland?

163
00:07:10,060 --> 00:07:12,350
我找到了
Uh, yeah, I think so.

164
00:07:12,350 --> 00:07:13,930
你找到了不告诉我
Well, if you're not here when I need it,

165
00:07:13,930 --> 00:07:15,370
又有什么用
what good does that do me?

166
00:07:15,370 --> 00:07:17,760
什么  不是才7点15...
What? It's 7:15...

167
00:07:39,260 --> 00:07:40,030
拿来了吗
Did you get it?

168
00:07:40,470 --> 00:07:41,890
昨天取的
Picked it up yesterday.

169
00:07:41,930 --> 00:07:43,380
你把它放枕头底下枕着睡觉了吗
Did you sleep with it under your pillow?

170
00:07:43,380 --> 00:07:44,880
我怎么睡觉跟你无关
How I sleep is none of your concern.

171
00:07:44,880 --> 00:07:46,390
洋基队击球员的上场顺序也跟我无关
Yeah, neither is the Yankees' batting order,

172
00:07:46,390 --> 00:07:48,100
但并不代表我不能惦记
but that doesn't stop me from thinking about it.

173
00:07:48,230 --> 00:07:50,910
哈维  答应我别太得瑟
Harvey. Promise me you won't be cocky.

174
00:07:51,470 --> 00:07:52,670
我明白成败在此一举
I understand what's at stake here.

175
00:07:52,670 --> 00:07:53,800
我一定会相当谦虚
I'll be perfectly humble.

176
00:07:53,800 --> 00:07:55,270
很好  你准备好了吗
Great. You ready?

177
00:07:55,290 --> 00:07:57,150
别说笑了  我势在必得
You kidding? I was born for this.

178
00:07:58,330 --> 00:08:00,560
7点45  不容易啊  你居然赶来了
7:45. Nice of you to show up.

179
00:08:00,560 --> 00:08:02,560
我早上五点才睡的
Uh, yeah, I was up till 5:00 in the morning.

180
00:08:02,580 --> 00:08:04,490
我开玩笑的  路易·利特要见你
I'm kidding. But Louis Litt wants to see you,

181
00:08:04,490 --> 00:08:05,560
这句可不是玩笑
and I don't kid about that.

182
00:08:05,560 --> 00:08:07,120
-他又想要干什么  -我不知道
- What does he want?  - I don't know.

183
00:08:07,120 --> 00:08:08,650
路易的棋盘上可没有我这个子儿
Louis doesn't let me in on his game plan,

184
00:08:08,650 --> 00:08:09,780
但这样正合我意
but I kind of prefer it that way.

185
00:08:09,780 --> 00:08:12,530
你能告诉他我要先去见哈维吗
Okay, um, can you tell him that I have to see Harvey first?

186
00:08:12,530 --> 00:08:13,440
随你
Your call.

187
00:08:13,440 --> 00:08:15,560
还有  要是你常穿西装睡觉的话
But, uh, if you're gonna be sleeping in your suits,

188
00:08:15,560 --> 00:08:17,650
你最好在办公室里放一件备用的
you may want to keep a fresh one in the office.

189
00:08:17,810 --> 00:08:18,780
看起来有那么糟糕吗
Is it that bad?

190
00:08:18,780 --> 00:08:19,870
何止糟糕
It's worse.

191
00:08:21,320 --> 00:08:22,150
快醒醒
Come on.

192
00:08:22,170 --> 00:08:23,810
我只想说  这对我来说十分荣幸
I'd just like to say this is an honor,

193
00:08:23,810 --> 00:08:25,060
我对此很看重
I take it seriously,

194
00:08:25,060 --> 00:08:27,180
我会力争让你们感到骄傲
and I intend to make you all proud.

195
00:08:27,230 --> 00:08:28,450
除了你  弗雷德
Except you, Fred.

196
00:08:28,450 --> 00:08:30,700
99年起我就没妄想着能让你骄傲
I gave up on making you proud in '99.

197
00:08:32,310 --> 00:08:35,080
好了  还有最后一项程序
Okay. There is one more order of business.

198
00:08:36,630 --> 00:08:38,160
他不在里面
He's not here.

199
00:08:42,930 --> 00:08:44,250
没门
No.

200
00:08:46,210 --> 00:08:47,410
他去哪儿了
Where is he?

201
00:08:47,410 --> 00:08:49,520
他正在参加资深合伙人的入伙会议
He's at his senior partner initiation.

202
00:08:50,040 --> 00:08:51,020
我问个问题
But let me ask you something.

203
00:08:51,020 --> 00:08:53,230
资深合伙人和其他普通合伙人
What's the difference between a senior partner

204
00:08:53,230 --> 00:08:55,310
到底有什么区别
and...other partners?

205
00:08:55,400 --> 00:08:57,160
你假扮哈佛毕业生的时候
Isn't that something you should have been studying

206
00:08:57,160 --> 00:08:58,780
不就应该弄明白这些了吗
when you were pretending to go to Harvard?

207
00:08:59,640 --> 00:09:02,940
是这样  资深合伙人通过入股加入律所
Okay. Senior partners, they buy into the firm.

208
00:09:02,940 --> 00:09:04,000
他们有利润分成
They share in the profits,

209
00:09:04,000 --> 00:09:05,670
但同时需要入股
but they also have to put up equity.

210
00:09:06,450 --> 00:09:08,070
那入股要花多少钱
So how much does it cost to buy in?

211
00:09:08,230 --> 00:09:11,550
五十万  现在就要吗
$1/2 million... Right now?

212
00:09:11,580 --> 00:09:14,260
哈维  你应该清楚入股是什么意思
Harvey, you knew what the buy-in was.

213
00:09:14,270 --> 00:09:15,930
你也知道今天是你入伙的日子
You knew today was initiation.

214
00:09:15,930 --> 00:09:17,540
你怎么能不把钱准备好
How could you not have the money?

215
00:09:17,540 --> 00:09:19,300
我不知道今天就要交钱
I didn't think it was due today.

216
00:09:21,940 --> 00:09:23,340
不是今天截止  对吧
It's not due today, is it?

217
00:09:23,340 --> 00:09:25,480
对  不是
No. It's not.

218
00:09:28,100 --> 00:09:31,130
这屋子里的每个人都中过这圈套
Every man in this room fell for exactly the same thing.

219
00:09:31,130 --> 00:09:32,290
包括你在内吗
Does that include you?

220
00:09:32,290 --> 00:09:34,010
当然不包括
No. No, it doesn't.

221
00:09:34,010 --> 00:09:35,380
散会吧  先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.

222
00:09:46,510 --> 00:09:49,120
花生  谷蛋白  草莓
Peanuts, gluten, strawberries.

223
00:09:49,120 --> 00:09:50,880
这是什么  购物单吗
What is this? A shopping list?

224
00:09:50,880 --> 00:09:52,570
不是  这是所有我过敏的东西
No, it's just a list of foods that I'm allergic to,

225
00:09:52,570 --> 00:09:54,410
当你挑选餐馆的时候
so when you select the venue,

226
00:09:54,580 --> 00:09:56,490
注意菜单上不要有这些食物
these foods are not to be on the menu.

227
00:09:56,490 --> 00:09:58,140
选餐馆干什么
A venue for what?

228
00:09:58,580 --> 00:09:59,620
没人告诉你吗
No one told you?

229
00:09:59,800 --> 00:10:01,500
-没人说过  -糟糕
- No one told me.  - Oh, drats.

230
00:10:01,500 --> 00:10:04,040
这可是皮尔逊·哈德曼律所的悠久传统
Well, a long-standing Pearson Hardman tradition

231
00:10:04,080 --> 00:10:05,420
名叫菜鸟晚宴
is the rookie dinner,

232
00:10:05,480 --> 00:10:07,640
也就是指你这个...
which means you, the...

233
00:10:07,640 --> 00:10:09,180
-菜鸟  -没错
- Rookie.  - That's right.

234
00:10:09,180 --> 00:10:12,230
你得请其他同事吃顿晚饭
Are to host a dinner for your fellow associates.

235
00:10:13,140 --> 00:10:14,660
没事  别垂头丧气
Well, come on. Don't look so blue.

236
00:10:14,660 --> 00:10:15,960
这事其实真的挺简单
Oh, it's okay. It's really easy.

237
00:10:15,960 --> 00:10:18,520
不过就是挑个别具一格的地方
All you have to do is just find a unique location

238
00:10:18,610 --> 00:10:20,280
然后协调一下其他五十个人的时间
and then coordinate with 50 other associates.

239
00:10:20,280 --> 00:10:22,250
小菜一碟  毫无压力
It's really simple. No pressure.

240
00:10:23,000 --> 00:10:24,410
你对鸡肉也过敏吗
And you're allergic to chicken?

241
00:10:24,410 --> 00:10:25,600
不  我只是不喜欢吃
No, I just don't like it.

242
00:10:27,320 --> 00:10:29,820
对了  到底是多大的事
Oh, by the way, what was so important

243
00:10:29,820 --> 00:10:31,930
你必须在见我之前先见哈维
that you had to see Harvey before you came to see me?

244
00:10:31,990 --> 00:10:33,140
路易  哈维其实...
Louis, Harvey doesn't really--

245
00:10:33,140 --> 00:10:35,430
我们能否  能不能就...  闭嘴  
Can we-- Can we-- Can we-- Can we just-- Shut up.

246
00:10:36,000 --> 00:10:36,990
好吧
Okay.

247
00:10:36,990 --> 00:10:38,770
我这样跟你说吧
Let me just get something straight, okay?

248
00:10:38,770 --> 00:10:40,210
当我问你问题时
When I ask you a question,

249
00:10:40,210 --> 00:10:41,770
我只要听一个答案
I just expect an answer.

250
00:10:46,860 --> 00:10:47,770
麦肯诺汽车公司
McKernon Motors.

251
00:10:47,770 --> 00:10:49,570
我在做对他们进行尽职调查
I was working on the due diligence.

252
00:10:50,380 --> 00:10:54,330
那为何要看公司章程呢
And why would that require you to look at the bylaws?

253
00:10:56,150 --> 00:10:59,310
州法律要求土地买卖要准备章程摘要
State law requires a summary be prepared in the event of a sale.

254
00:10:59,310 --> 00:11:01,200
私人公司并不包括在内
Privately held corporations are exempted.

255
00:11:01,260 --> 00:11:03,040
除非买卖金额高于一亿五千万
Not if the sale exceeds 150 million.

256
00:11:03,040 --> 00:11:04,350
你的依据是
According to who?

257
00:11:09,190 --> 00:11:10,590
州政府官网
The state's website.

258
00:11:11,640 --> 00:11:13,330
我做事讲求缜密
I like to be thorough.

259
00:11:15,730 --> 00:11:17,150
做得不错  伙计
Well, put it there, buddy.

260
00:11:18,360 --> 00:11:19,960
你没搞错吧
Are you fricking serious?

261
00:11:24,090 --> 00:11:26,200
我听说由于麦肯诺汽车公司的土地买卖
I understand Stensland is throwing a large amount

262
00:11:26,200 --> 00:11:29,250
斯坦斯兰给了我们不少活干啊
of legal work our way with the McKernon Motors factory sale.

263
00:11:29,370 --> 00:11:30,210
你怎么知道的
How'd you know that?

264
00:11:30,210 --> 00:11:31,460
我自有眼线
I hear things.

265
00:11:31,530 --> 00:11:32,520
是你在帮他处理吗
You taking care of him?

266
00:11:32,520 --> 00:11:33,530
当然
I am.

267
00:11:33,550 --> 00:11:36,180
对了  截止前替我交了
By the way, for when it is due.

268
00:11:36,360 --> 00:11:37,400
这是什么
What's this?

269
00:11:37,590 --> 00:11:40,580
50万美金的现金支票
It's a cashier's check for $500,000.

270
00:11:42,150 --> 00:11:43,660
你时刻准备着吗
You had this the whole time.

271
00:11:43,660 --> 00:11:45,680
从我盯上资深合伙人那位置起
I've had the money since I set my sights

272
00:11:45,680 --> 00:11:46,770
我就准备好了
on senior partner.

273
00:11:54,180 --> 00:11:56,000
不容易啊  你终于来了
Nice of you to finally make it.

274
00:11:56,060 --> 00:11:57,810
为什么每个人都这么说
Why does everybody keep saying that?

275
00:11:57,810 --> 00:11:58,910
因为要你做事的时候
Because you're supposed to be here

276
00:11:58,980 --> 00:12:00,350
你就该随叫随到
when you're supposed to be here.

277
00:12:00,430 --> 00:12:01,670
看来你并没有以身作则啊
Doesn't seem to apply to you.

278
00:12:01,670 --> 00:12:03,720
这只针对你  和我无关
I'm not the topic of this conversation.

279
00:12:03,780 --> 00:12:06,550
关于麦肯诺汽车公司  你都找到了些什么
Now what'd you find me on McKernon Motors?

280
00:12:06,690 --> 00:12:09,790
在CEO提出土地买卖方案24小时之后 
The board can't vote for at least 24 hours after the CEO

281
00:12:09,790 --> 00:12:12,090
董事会才能进行投票表决
presents a deal involving the sale of company land.

282
00:12:12,090 --> 00:12:14,330
斯坦斯兰已经把方案提交给董事会了
But Stensland already presented it to the board.

283
00:12:14,430 --> 00:12:16,950
我知道  但是斯坦斯兰还不是CEO
Right, but Stensland isn't CEO.

284
00:12:17,660 --> 00:12:20,040
公司章程是我写的  他就是CEO
I wrote those bylaws myself. He's CEO.

285
00:12:20,050 --> 00:12:23,870
238页第137条指出
Hmm. Page 238, clause 137

286
00:12:23,870 --> 00:12:26,140
如果现任CEO去世
states if the CEO dies,

287
00:12:26,140 --> 00:12:28,100
在董事会投票决定前
an interim CEO will be appointed

288
00:12:28,100 --> 00:12:29,820
任何人都只是临时CEO
until the board convenes an election vote,

289
00:12:29,820 --> 00:12:32,000
但投票最早也得等到下个财政季度进行
which can't be called till the next fiscal quarter,

290
00:12:32,000 --> 00:12:34,370
也就是下周四
in this case next Thursday.

291
00:12:34,520 --> 00:12:36,620
那在周四前他当不上CEO咯
So they can't vote him in until Thursday?

292
00:12:36,700 --> 00:12:37,680
没错  周四
Thursday.

293
00:12:38,430 --> 00:12:39,720
很好
Okay.

294
00:12:39,740 --> 00:12:41,660
准备好尽职调查
Well, prepare the due diligence

295
00:12:41,660 --> 00:12:42,810
我要交给斯坦斯兰
for me to take to Stensland,

296
00:12:42,810 --> 00:12:44,520
但不要准备签署任何文件
but I don't want anything ready to sign.

297
00:12:44,560 --> 00:12:45,610
-你要去哪  -出去
- Where are you going? - Out.

298
00:12:45,610 --> 00:12:48,090
周四之前我要找到一位CEO
I have until Thursday to find a new CEO.

299
00:12:48,090 --> 00:12:49,520
-是吗  -怎么
- Huh.  - What?

300
00:12:49,620 --> 00:12:52,690
没什么  只是我花了六个小时
Oh, nothing. Uh, you know, just six hours,

301
00:12:52,690 --> 00:12:55,580
看了1500页  然后...
1,500 pages, and I, uh,

302
00:12:55,580 --> 00:12:56,900
找到了你犯的一个错误
I found your mistake.

303
00:12:56,930 --> 00:12:59,570
你找到的这个错误
Yeah, you found the one mistake I made

304
00:12:59,570 --> 00:13:02,400
是我十多年前起草这份章程时犯的
while drafting those bylaws a dozen years ago

305
00:13:02,400 --> 00:13:04,220
我那会儿还比你小两岁
when I was two years younger than you.

306
00:13:04,220 --> 00:13:05,150
也正是这个错误
A mistake, by the way,

307
00:13:05,210 --> 00:13:07,180
能让我摆脱斯坦斯兰
that's gonna help me get rid of Stensland.

308
00:13:07,500 --> 00:13:09,100
错误就是错误
Mistake.

309
00:13:27,450 --> 00:13:28,940
打扰一下  斯佩克特先生
Excuse me, Mr. Specter?

310
00:13:28,940 --> 00:13:30,770
我想问问  您手上有没有杂活
I was wondering if you might need a hand sometime

311
00:13:30,770 --> 00:13:32,050
需要我帮忙的
with one of your matters.

312
00:13:32,050 --> 00:13:33,160
随便什么活
Uh, any one.

313
00:13:33,330 --> 00:13:33,940
亚伦是吧
Well, Allen--

314
00:13:33,940 --> 00:13:34,810
我叫艾伦
It's Aaron.

315
00:13:35,160 --> 00:13:37,260
我想我已经回答你了吧
I think that says it all, don't you?

316
00:13:39,510 --> 00:13:40,610
你在做什么
What are you doing?

317
00:13:41,470 --> 00:13:43,460
我在找餐馆
Uh, I'm looking for a restaurant.

318
00:13:43,460 --> 00:13:44,860
你是在哪儿办的菜鸟晚宴
Where did you go for your rookie dinner?

319
00:13:44,860 --> 00:13:46,300
我大学二年级就进公司了
I came into the league a sophomore.

320
00:13:46,300 --> 00:13:46,990
你最好别为这个
You better not be prioritizing that

321
00:13:46,990 --> 00:13:48,780
耽误了麦肯诺汽车公司的案子
over McKernon Motors.

322
00:13:48,800 --> 00:13:50,510
我还需要点事由来稳住斯坦斯兰
I still need something to stall Stensland.

323
00:13:50,510 --> 00:13:51,780
全在里面了
It's right here.

324
00:13:53,160 --> 00:13:54,700
你在烦什么呢
What are you so irritated about?

325
00:13:54,700 --> 00:13:57,250
我和一个顶级猎头想了一整天
I spent a day with a top headhunter I know

326
00:13:57,280 --> 00:14:00,230
也没找到个周四就能上任的CEO
who couldn't produce one legitimate CEO candidate by Thursday.

327
00:14:00,230 --> 00:14:02,000
多米尼克·巴伦怎么样
What about that Dominic Barone guy

328
00:14:02,070 --> 00:14:03,180
负责生产的那人
who runs production?

329
00:14:03,260 --> 00:14:05,080
你说过引擎就是他的杰作
You said he was responsible for the engines,

330
00:14:05,270 --> 00:14:06,870
而且他看起来很为员工着想
and he clearly cares about the workers.

331
00:14:06,870 --> 00:14:08,170
不  他不行
No, he's not the guy.

332
00:14:08,170 --> 00:14:09,730
你是怕你说服不了他
Oh, you're scared you can't convince him

333
00:14:09,730 --> 00:14:11,720
因为他讨厌你  我懂了
because he hates you. I get it.

334
00:14:11,720 --> 00:14:12,570
激将对我没用
Nice try.

335
00:14:12,580 --> 00:14:14,080
你定那家餐馆可不行
You know you can't host your dinner there.

336
00:14:14,080 --> 00:14:16,510
档次太高
That's a Wachtell, Lipton, Klein restaurant.

337
00:14:16,730 --> 00:14:18,710
好吧
Okay. Fine.

338
00:14:18,990 --> 00:14:20,580
那这家怎么样
What about this place?

339
00:14:20,580 --> 00:14:22,930
2004年的时候还不错
Yeah, that'd be great if it was 2004.

340
00:14:22,930 --> 00:14:24,020
老天
Oh, my God.

341
00:14:24,020 --> 00:14:26,500
吃个饭有那么要紧吗  
Why does any of this matter? God.

342
00:14:28,340 --> 00:14:30,710
你看到传真机旁的那家伙吗
You see that guy over there by the fax?

343
00:14:31,380 --> 00:14:32,940
睁大眼睛看
Take a good look.

344
00:14:35,490 --> 00:14:37,320
他永远都成不了这里的合伙人
He's never gonna make partner.

345
00:14:37,320 --> 00:14:38,820
好吧  让我猜一下
Okay. Let me guess.

346
00:14:38,820 --> 00:14:41,380
因为他菜鸟晚宴办得太糟吗
Because he threw a lousy rookie dinner?

347
00:14:41,450 --> 00:14:43,780
不  因为他根本不懂
No, because he doesn't get it.

348
00:14:43,780 --> 00:14:44,620
不懂什么
Get what?

349
00:14:44,620 --> 00:14:45,840
他不懂把手头的任务做好
He doesn't get that doing good work

350
00:14:45,840 --> 00:14:47,840
并非工作的全部
isn't the whole job.

351
00:14:48,340 --> 00:14:49,330
聪明人明白
Part of getting it

352
00:14:49,330 --> 00:14:51,520
其实这种晚宴至关重要
is that things like the dinner actually matter,

353
00:14:51,520 --> 00:14:53,390
即使你觉得这毫无意义
even when you don't think they do.

354
00:14:53,430 --> 00:14:54,820
听着  你今天早上对我很不爽
Look, you were giving me shit this morning

355
00:14:54,820 --> 00:14:55,940
认为我想来就来  想走就走
because I come and go when I want to.

356
00:14:55,940 --> 00:14:57,350
知道为什么我能这样吗
You know why I can do that?

357
00:14:57,700 --> 00:15:00,040
因为我刚来的时候  我抢着做事
Because when I got here, I dominated.

358
00:15:00,040 --> 00:15:02,340
他们感觉我一天工作100个小时
They thought I worked 100 hours a day.

359
00:15:02,340 --> 00:15:04,970
所以现在  无论我什么时候踏进公司
Now, no matter what time I get in,

360
00:15:04,970 --> 00:15:07,800
没有人会质疑我的能力
nobody questions my ability to get the job done.

361
00:15:07,810 --> 00:15:09,340
你好好想想吧
Get it through your head.

362
00:15:09,430 --> 00:15:11,110
第一印象决定一切
First impressions last.

363
00:15:11,240 --> 00:15:13,200
一开始就落在后面
You start behind the eight ball,

364
00:15:13,280 --> 00:15:14,690
以后永远别想翻身了
you'll never get in front.

365
00:15:26,210 --> 00:15:28,120
-你忙吗  -现在是7点
- Hey, you busy? - It's 7:00.

366
00:15:28,120 --> 00:15:30,070
我这么早坐在这里难道是看风景吗
I'm not here 'cause I like the view.

367
00:15:30,440 --> 00:15:31,510
别误解我的话
And don't misunderstand me.

368
00:15:31,510 --> 00:15:33,840
我所说的"风景"  其实是指你的脸
When I say "the view," I'm referring to your face.

369
00:15:33,840 --> 00:15:35,400
这话真幽默  要知道我很丑
That's funny, because I'm hideous.

370
00:15:35,400 --> 00:15:37,540
-什么事  -你是个美食家吧
- What's up? - You're a foodie, right?

371
00:15:37,540 --> 00:15:38,760
为什么这么说
Why do you say that?

372
00:15:38,770 --> 00:15:39,710
因为在我认识的人中
Because you're the only person

373
00:15:39,710 --> 00:15:41,650
只有你会点对虾和山羊奶酪披萨
I've ever seen order a shrimp, red pepper,

374
00:15:41,650 --> 00:15:42,830
外加红椒
and goat cheese pizza.

375
00:15:42,830 --> 00:15:44,050
没错  但是不放红椒的话
Well, right, but without the pepper,

376
00:15:44,050 --> 00:15:45,910
山羊奶酪配虾又怎能对味呢
what connects the goat cheese and the shrimp?

377
00:15:46,280 --> 00:15:47,150
我的确是美食家
I'm a foodie.

378
00:15:47,150 --> 00:15:49,700
所以我想让你帮我找一家餐厅
Okay, so I need your help finding a restaurant

379
00:15:49,700 --> 00:15:50,470
办菜鸟晚宴
for the rookie dinner.

380
00:15:50,470 --> 00:15:51,690
那就抱歉了
Well, that's unfortunate,

381
00:15:51,710 --> 00:15:52,480
我忙得要死  
but I'm swamped,

382
00:15:52,480 --> 00:15:54,130
哪有时间教你美食攻略
and I don't have time to teach you about cuisine.

383
00:15:54,130 --> 00:15:55,590
你难道忘了
Well, no, don't make me remind you

384
00:15:55,590 --> 00:15:56,500
你欠我个人情吗  
that you owe me one.

385
00:15:56,500 --> 00:15:57,210
什么时候的事
How's that?

386
00:15:57,260 --> 00:15:59,610
你告诉了路易  我得先帮哈维做事
You told Louis I was working on Harvey's case before his.

387
00:15:59,610 --> 00:16:00,860
因为你让我说的啊
Because you told me to.

388
00:16:00,860 --> 00:16:03,170
我现在让你帮我搞定晚宴
Well, now I'm telling you to help me with my dinner.

389
00:16:03,610 --> 00:16:05,650
祝你好运
Good luck with that.

390
00:16:05,720 --> 00:16:07,350
看来她是不会帮我了
Not gonna help me with my dinner.

391
00:16:08,350 --> 00:16:09,970
她走了  我在自言自语
Now I'm talking to myself.

392
00:16:13,070 --> 00:16:14,400
好的  奶奶
Yeah, grammy.

393
00:16:14,580 --> 00:16:16,150
不  我说了我会来的
No, I told you I was coming.

394
00:16:16,440 --> 00:16:19,440
我在...我在路上了  好吗
I'm-- I'm on my way, okay? Yeah.

395
00:16:22,280 --> 00:16:25,550
15分钟后到
15 minutes.

396
00:16:25,640 --> 00:16:27,220
好的  再见  你来干...
Okay. Bye. Hey, what are you--

397
00:16:29,220 --> 00:16:30,790
好吧  我做错什么了
Okay, what was that for?

398
00:16:30,790 --> 00:16:31,800
如果你在乎我的话
If you cared about me,

399
00:16:31,800 --> 00:16:33,140
你早就该告诉我特雷弗这么长时间
you would have told me what Trevor was up to

400
00:16:33,140 --> 00:16:34,030
都在干那勾当
a long time ago.

401
00:16:34,030 --> 00:16:35,590
我是想要保护你
I was trying to protect you.

402
00:16:35,660 --> 00:16:37,200
我男友在贩毒
How is hiding the fact

403
00:16:37,200 --> 00:16:39,480
我却被蒙在鼓里  这叫保护我吗
that my boyfriend is selling weed protecting me?

404
00:16:39,480 --> 00:16:40,810
你想知道真相吗
You want to know the truth?

405
00:16:41,160 --> 00:16:44,220
你男友也是我最好的朋友
Your boyfriend also happens to be my best friend, all right?

406
00:16:44,220 --> 00:16:45,570
我不想出卖他
I didn't feel like ratting him out.

407
00:16:45,570 --> 00:16:46,750
如果你真是他朋友
If you were really his friend,

408
00:16:46,750 --> 00:16:48,890
你不会眼睁睁地让他糟蹋自己的生活
you wouldn't just stand by and let him throw his life away.

409
00:16:48,890 --> 00:16:50,150
是我让他...
Let him? Let--

410
00:16:50,150 --> 00:16:51,950
我从来左右不了特雷弗的想法
I've never let Trevor do anything.

411
00:16:51,950 --> 00:16:52,590
你刚认识他吗
Have you met him?

412
00:16:52,590 --> 00:16:54,410
特雷弗会听你的话  
Trevor listens to you,

413
00:16:54,420 --> 00:16:55,700
他现在正需要你
and he needs you right now.

414
00:16:55,860 --> 00:16:57,980
他在糟蹋自己的生活
He is throwing his life away,

415
00:16:58,160 --> 00:16:59,760
而你却抛弃了他
and you ditched us.

416
00:17:01,230 --> 00:17:02,440
和我
Both.

417
00:17:04,030 --> 00:17:06,330
好像我们对你来说只是路人甲
Like we didn't mean anything to you.

418
00:17:11,570 --> 00:17:13,660
我...我要迟到了
I'm...I'm late.

419
00:17:34,640 --> 00:17:37,200
路易  你来这干嘛
Louis. What are you doing here?

420
00:17:37,200 --> 00:17:39,440
斯坦斯兰打电话让我来的
Hi. Uh, Stensland called.

421
00:17:39,530 --> 00:17:42,220
很显然  尽职调查的进展不够迅速
And apparently the diligence wasn't proceeding apace.

422
00:17:42,270 --> 00:17:43,290
他打电话让你来的吗
He called you?

423
00:17:43,290 --> 00:17:45,320
是啊  他打给我  我打给他  有什么区别
Yeah, he called me, I called him, what's the difference?

424
00:17:45,390 --> 00:17:46,620
文件起草的时间拖得太长
The paperwork was taking too long,

425
00:17:46,620 --> 00:17:47,370
我搞定了
and I got it done.

426
00:17:47,370 --> 00:17:49,800
我建议你离我客户越远越好
I suggest you stay the hell away from my client.

427
00:17:50,000 --> 00:17:51,710
哈维  很高兴你来了
Harvey. Glad you could make it.

428
00:17:51,710 --> 00:17:52,940
我们正好要签文件
We were about to sign the papers.

429
00:17:52,940 --> 00:17:54,180
我在办公室听说了
I got word back at the office.

430
00:17:54,180 --> 00:17:55,340
特地过来看看路易
I just came to see how Louis

431
00:17:55,340 --> 00:17:56,980
怎么解决公司章程的问题
was getting around the bylaws.

432
00:17:58,180 --> 00:18:00,050
我...不知道
I...don't know.

433
00:18:02,440 --> 00:18:03,770
我也糊涂了
I'm at somewhat of a loss.

434
00:18:03,770 --> 00:18:04,710
罗伯特  我很抱歉
Robert, I'm sorry.

435
00:18:04,710 --> 00:18:06,600
这就是尽职调查拖延的原因
This is what was holding up your due diligence.

436
00:18:06,600 --> 00:18:09,140
严格来说  在周四董事会投票正式任命你之前
Technically, you're still interim CEO until the board

437
00:18:09,140 --> 00:18:10,590
你还只是临时CEO
votes you in on Thursday.

438
00:18:10,590 --> 00:18:11,850
如果你违反章程的话
If protocol isn't followed,

439
00:18:11,850 --> 00:18:13,800
会给别人对你提起诉讼留下把柄
it leaves you with huge litigation exposure.

440
00:18:13,800 --> 00:18:14,540
没错
That's right.

441
00:18:14,660 --> 00:18:17,970
那我们还是再等一等吧
Well, I imagine we should hold off, then.

442
00:18:18,170 --> 00:18:20,140
别怪路易  这都是我的错
Please don't blame Louis. It's my fault.

443
00:18:20,140 --> 00:18:22,850
通常资深合伙人都会监督这类问题
We usually have senior partners oversee transactions like this

444
00:18:22,850 --> 00:18:24,960
要知道初级合伙人容易忽视细节
because junior partners, they tend to miss things.

445
00:18:25,140 --> 00:18:26,050
那周四见了
See you Thursday?

446
00:18:26,050 --> 00:18:27,060
稍等片刻
One second.

447
00:18:27,580 --> 00:18:28,760
你该没忘吧
Uh, just so you know,

448
00:18:28,760 --> 00:18:30,910
你不久前也只是个初级合伙人
you were a junior partner until recently.

449
00:18:31,070 --> 00:18:32,490
而我晋升是有原因的
There's a reason I'm not anymore.

450
00:18:32,490 --> 00:18:33,800
好的  慢走
Okay. Take it easy.

451
00:18:34,480 --> 00:18:37,190
如果你和别的男人去俄罗斯会怎样
So what if you took a trip to Russia with another man?

452
00:18:37,190 --> 00:18:39,510
我记得那是在认识吉米爷爷之前吧
I mean, that was before you met grandpa Jimmy, right?

453
00:18:39,510 --> 00:18:41,860
他才不管那是不是认识他之前的事
He didn't care it was before I met him.

454
00:18:42,000 --> 00:18:43,580
总唠叨个没完
Never shut up about it.

455
00:18:43,580 --> 00:18:45,340
那个男人叫什么名字
So what was this other guy's name?

456
00:18:45,360 --> 00:18:47,580
格雷戈里  别管闲事了
Gregory. Mind your own business.

457
00:18:48,320 --> 00:18:50,700
好了  迈克  我们玩得很高兴
So, Michael, this has been fun.

458
00:18:50,700 --> 00:18:52,980
现在你可以别再拐弯抹角了
Now why don't you stop beating around the bush

459
00:18:52,980 --> 00:18:54,700
告诉我发生什么事了
and tell me what's going on.

460
00:18:57,760 --> 00:18:58,970
特雷弗
Trevor.

461
00:18:59,830 --> 00:19:02,170
是因为特雷弗  总是因为他
It's Trevor. It's always Trevor.

462
00:19:02,220 --> 00:19:04,170
他最近陷入了非常糟糕的...
He's gotten himself into some really bad...

463
00:19:04,680 --> 00:19:07,220
境况  他需要我帮他渡过难关
Stuff, and I think he needs my help to get out of it,

464
00:19:07,220 --> 00:19:09,720
但是我最近压力很大
but I've been under so much pressure,

465
00:19:09,720 --> 00:19:11,310
你也经常告诉我要为朋友两肋插刀
and I know you've always told me to be there for people...

466
00:19:11,380 --> 00:19:13,410
不  不  听我说
No, no, listen to me.

467
00:19:13,520 --> 00:19:15,260
-去他的特雷弗  -什么
- Screw Trevor. - What?

468
00:19:15,260 --> 00:19:16,800
你已经向前看了
You're moving forward,

469
00:19:16,850 --> 00:19:19,770
而他会想尽办法  把你拖回原地
and he'll do whatever he can to keep you where you are.

470
00:19:19,770 --> 00:19:20,860
没错  但是...  
Yeah, but...

471
00:19:20,860 --> 00:19:21,510
没有"但是"
But no buts.

472
00:19:21,510 --> 00:19:23,340
那孩子只会托你后腿
That kid is an anchor.

473
00:19:23,340 --> 00:19:25,430
你得和他撇清关系
You need to cut him loose.

474
00:19:26,750 --> 00:19:29,260
你欠我50元了
You owe me 50 bucks.

475
00:19:40,640 --> 00:19:42,540
罗伯特·斯坦斯兰那边什么情况
What's going on with Robert Stensland?

476
00:19:43,670 --> 00:19:45,280
路易和你说了什么
What did Louis tell you?

477
00:19:45,300 --> 00:19:47,350
你现在面对的不是路易  而是我
You're not dealing with Louis. You're dealing with me.

478
00:19:47,510 --> 00:19:48,490
你隐瞒了什么
What are you hiding?

479
00:19:48,490 --> 00:19:49,770
没有啊  我只是看了遍公司章程
Nothing. I looked through the bylaws

480
00:19:49,770 --> 00:19:51,640
排除了潜在的法律争端
and precluded potential litigation.

481
00:19:52,180 --> 00:19:54,370
你看公司章程肯定有自己的目的
You looked at the bylaws for a tactical reason,

482
00:19:54,370 --> 00:19:56,130
我要知道是什么目的
and I want to know what it is.

483
00:20:01,030 --> 00:20:02,130
我想让他滚蛋
I want him out.

484
00:20:02,420 --> 00:20:04,720
这由不得你  你只是个律师
That is not your call. You are an attorney.

485
00:20:04,940 --> 00:20:07,600
而这是麦肯诺汽车公司的内部事务
This is the internal business of McKernon Motors.

486
00:20:07,870 --> 00:20:09,100
听着  我花了十年时间
Look, McKernon had a plan,

487
00:20:09,310 --> 00:20:10,920
来描绘麦肯诺的宏图
and I didn't spend a decade shaping it

488
00:20:11,120 --> 00:20:12,370
绝不会让这白痴给毁了
to let this fool throw it away.

489
00:20:12,570 --> 00:20:13,340
麦肯诺已经名存实亡了
McKernon is dead.

490
00:20:13,550 --> 00:20:14,840
那又怎样  并不代表计划不好啊
So what? Doesn't mean the plan's no good.

491
00:20:15,040 --> 00:20:16,670
如果你失败了  我们就会被炒
You fail, we'll get fired.

492
00:20:16,860 --> 00:20:17,720
他要是搬到海外
He moves overseas,

493
00:20:17,920 --> 00:20:19,770
五年后我们就没钱赚了
our billables'll be gone in five years, anyway.

494
00:20:19,960 --> 00:20:21,220
那也比现在就被炒要强啊
Better five years than nothing.

495
00:20:21,420 --> 00:20:22,730
知道吗  依照斯坦斯兰的现在态度
You know what? That's Stensland's attitude,

496
00:20:22,930 --> 00:20:24,060
他注定会失败
and it's a losing one.

497
00:20:25,430 --> 00:20:28,600
哈维  我觉得你没义务
Harvey, I don't think you have any business

498
00:20:28,820 --> 00:20:30,450
告诉他该如何管理公司
telling that man how to run his company,

499
00:20:31,060 --> 00:20:32,710
而且你也无权
but I know you don't have any business

500
00:20:32,920 --> 00:20:34,050
干涉我对公司的管理
telling me how to run mine.

501
00:20:34,260 --> 00:20:35,700
你是一位资深合伙人
You are a senior partner.

502
00:20:35,890 --> 00:20:37,820
而不再是一个枪手了
You are not a gunslinger anymore.

503
00:20:38,100 --> 00:20:40,670
别管斯坦斯兰的事了  达成协议
Back off Stensland and close the deal.

504
00:20:54,450 --> 00:20:57,400
我要你起草周四CEO候选人的演讲稿
I need you to prepare the draft CEO candidate speech for Thursday.

505
00:20:57,590 --> 00:20:58,530
我觉得这件事你应该撒手了
Well, I thought you were supposed to back off.

506
00:20:58,730 --> 00:20:59,860
我应该做的事情多了
Yeah, I'm supposed to do a lot of things.

507
00:21:00,060 --> 00:21:02,080
等我回来的路上再打电话告诉你计划
I'll call you with the plan on my way back.

508
00:21:02,270 --> 00:21:02,990
你要去哪
From where?

509
00:21:03,180 --> 00:21:05,920
去说服那个讨厌我的人按我的计划行事
From convincing the man who hates me to do what I say.

510
00:21:05,930 --> 00:21:06,490
这样啊
Oh, right.

511
00:21:06,700 --> 00:21:08,840
就是我一开始让你去找的那个人吧
You mean the guy I suggested you go to in the first place.

512
00:21:09,500 --> 00:21:10,080
你还记得
Do you remember that

513
00:21:10,080 --> 00:21:11,530
我跟你提过的潜规则吗
whole getting it thing I was talking to you about?

514
00:21:11,720 --> 00:21:12,530
什么  幸灾乐祸都不行吗
What, I can't even gloat?

515
00:21:12,720 --> 00:21:14,410
可以  不过你幸灾乐祸的水平太差了
Gloating's fine. You just have to not suck at it.

516
00:21:15,610 --> 00:21:18,380
好吧  谢了  非常感谢
Okay. Thank you. So much.

517
00:21:19,290 --> 00:21:20,080
下手好重
That hurt.

518
00:21:25,970 --> 00:21:27,060
罗斯  你来啦
Hey, Ross.

519
00:21:27,300 --> 00:21:29,400
你电脑上关于菜鸟聚餐的搜索页面还没关呢
You left your search for the rookie dinner on your computer.

520
00:21:29,590 --> 00:21:30,300
不如省点时间
Why don't you just save time

521
00:21:30,510 --> 00:21:31,800
带我们去星期五餐厅吧
and take us to Friday's?

522
00:21:32,080 --> 00:21:33,670
瞧瞧  某人生气了
Ooh, ooh, somebody's mad.

523
00:21:33,860 --> 00:21:35,730
德文  偷看我的电脑上的内容
Devon, looking at my computer is a violation of

524
00:21:35,930 --> 00:21:39,590
违反了七条破坏职场氛围的法则
exactly seven hostile workplace environment statutes.

525
00:21:39,780 --> 00:21:40,970
你想干什么  起诉我吗
What are you gonna do? Sue me?

526
00:21:41,750 --> 00:21:42,720
不  不会的
No. No, no, no.

527
00:21:42,940 --> 00:21:44,010
如果我要教训你
I'm just gonna use it as legal cover

528
00:21:44,210 --> 00:21:46,140
我可以把这当作法律保护
if I decide to kick your ass.

529
00:21:56,030 --> 00:21:56,800
多米尼克
Dominic.

530
00:21:57,950 --> 00:21:58,770
哈维  你怎么来了
Harvey, what are you doing here?

531
00:21:58,970 --> 00:22:00,520
我们的合同还有两年才到期呢
Our contract's good for two more years.

532
00:22:00,700 --> 00:22:02,300
我想跟你单独谈几句
I need a word. In private.

533
00:22:03,480 --> 00:22:04,300
失陪了  比尔
Excuse me, Bill.

534
00:22:04,970 --> 00:22:06,200
有话快说  这里的员工
Make it fast, 'cause this is a place

535
00:22:06,380 --> 00:22:07,870
都是为了维持生计在工作
where people actually work for a living.

536
00:22:08,050 --> 00:22:09,390
别忘了有人看着呢
Well, keep in mind people are watching.

537
00:22:09,570 --> 00:22:11,200
所以你的言辞最好中立一点
Just try to keep your expression neutral.

538
00:22:11,410 --> 00:22:13,610
我以前可没学过口是心非
You know, they don't teach deceptive tactics where I come from.

539
00:22:13,800 --> 00:22:14,880
到了生死关头  你就学会了
Then you're gonna learn under fire.

540
00:22:15,350 --> 00:22:16,590
斯坦斯兰要把这里关掉
Stensland's shutting you down.

541
00:22:16,780 --> 00:22:18,130
什么  为什么
What? Why?

542
00:22:18,690 --> 00:22:19,460
为了钱
For money.

543
00:22:19,700 --> 00:22:21,780
有人想买工厂这块地
He's got a buyer for the land under the factory.

544
00:22:22,170 --> 00:22:23,100
那你为什么来找我
Why are you coming to me?

545
00:22:24,340 --> 00:22:25,460
因为只有你来做CEO
Because the only way to stop him

546
00:22:25,650 --> 00:22:27,760
才能阻止他卖地
is for you to challenge him as CEO.

547
00:22:27,930 --> 00:22:29,020
什么  你疯了吗
What? Are you crazy?

548
00:22:29,200 --> 00:22:30,210
你是管理层的
You've got a management title.

549
00:22:30,390 --> 00:22:31,680
我可不想加入管理层
That I choose not to identify with.

550
00:22:31,870 --> 00:22:32,710
你是工厂的负责人
You run the factory.

551
00:22:32,880 --> 00:22:35,510
仅此而已  我对高层的政治事务不感兴趣
Which I never left, 'cause I have no taste for boardroom politics.

552
00:22:35,620 --> 00:22:36,710
你是这里的元老
You've been here since day one.

553
00:22:36,900 --> 00:22:38,360
对产品了如指掌
You know the product inside out.

554
00:22:38,550 --> 00:22:39,660
这群工人对你推崇备至
These workers, they respect you.

555
00:22:40,040 --> 00:22:41,450
好大的烟
Pew, that's a lot of smoke.

556
00:22:41,910 --> 00:22:43,410
我是你找的第几个备胎
How many people did you go to before me?

557
00:22:43,600 --> 00:22:44,720
-第七个  -我就知道
- Seven. - Right.

558
00:22:44,920 --> 00:22:46,340
我从没说过你是我的第一选择
I never said you were my prom queen.

559
00:22:47,030 --> 00:22:48,770
我想赢  好吗
Look, I want to win, okay?

560
00:22:48,950 --> 00:22:49,660
我去找那些人
I went to those other people

561
00:22:49,840 --> 00:22:51,750
是因为他们有更强的政治手段
because they were better suited to get past the board,

562
00:22:51,940 --> 00:22:53,500
却没有你适合这份工作
not better suited for the job.

563
00:22:53,690 --> 00:22:55,070
不管你是否愿意  这都是事实
Those are the facts whether you like it or not.

564
00:22:55,980 --> 00:22:56,910
我为什么要相信你
And why should I trust you?

565
00:22:57,120 --> 00:23:00,030
因为如果你一意孤行  就没有工作可选了
Because if you don't, there aren't any jobs left to negotiate over.

566
00:23:00,220 --> 00:23:01,900
你和工厂都会完蛋的
You and the factory, you're finished.

567
00:23:12,750 --> 00:23:14,670
发自哈维·斯佩克特
我们快回来了  在会议室等我

568
00:23:16,880 --> 00:23:17,540
你在忙什么
What are you working on?

569
00:23:18,110 --> 00:23:20,070
没什么  就是哈维交代的事情  有事吗
Um, nothing. Just some stuff for Harvey. Why?

570
00:23:20,400 --> 00:23:21,490
快搞定  路易·利特想见你
Wrap it up. Louis Litt wants to see you.

571
00:23:21,670 --> 00:23:22,780
这次他可不想等你
This time he doesn't want to wait.

572
00:23:25,130 --> 00:23:29,150
不是路易·利特找你
晚上八点在哥伦布大街等我  别迟到

573
00:23:36,080 --> 00:23:36,730
另外
Furthermore,

574
00:23:36,910 --> 00:23:38,870
我觉得随着适当的
I feel that with the proper

575
00:23:38,870 --> 00:23:42,180
战略性合作联盟的建立
strategic and synergistic alliances moving forward--

576
00:23:42,360 --> 00:23:44,410
你得让我相信你说的话
I have to actually believe what you're saying.

577
00:23:44,580 --> 00:23:46,170
这都是些毫无意义的陈词滥调
They're just platitudes that don't mean anything.

578
00:23:46,170 --> 00:23:47,060
有意义啊  
Yes, they do.

579
00:23:47,060 --> 00:23:49,730
合作联盟的建立可以削减成本
Synergistic alliances mean you form relationships

580
00:23:49,910 --> 00:23:51,520
并把产品推销出去
to get the cost down and your product out.

581
00:23:51,710 --> 00:23:52,610
没用的
It's never gonna work.

582
00:23:52,780 --> 00:23:54,640
必须有用  不然我就吃不了兜着走了  
Well, it better goddamn work. My ass is on the line.

583
00:23:54,640 --> 00:23:55,530
那我呢
What about my ass?

584
00:23:55,730 --> 00:23:57,160
要不是因为你的木瓜脑袋
If it wasn't attached to your thick head,

585
00:23:57,350 --> 00:23:59,190
也许就不会出现这种问题了
maybe we wouldn't be having this problem.

586
00:23:59,370 --> 00:24:00,740
抱歉我并不擅长
I'm sorry I'm not as well practiced

587
00:24:00,960 --> 00:24:02,450
像你一样妙语连珠
at corporate double speak as you'd like,

588
00:24:03,230 --> 00:24:06,010
但这两小时我已经使出九牛二虎之力了
but I've been busting my ass on this for two hours.

589
00:24:06,170 --> 00:24:07,420
如果你对我的进展不满意
So if you're not happy with my progress,

590
00:24:07,600 --> 00:24:08,700
为什么不干脆滚出去
then why don't you get the hell out?

591
00:24:12,110 --> 00:24:13,740
他没学会就不准离开
He doesn't leave without getting it.

592
00:24:19,380 --> 00:24:20,250
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.

593
00:24:24,260 --> 00:24:24,980
你不去捡起来吗
You're not gonna pick it up?

594
00:24:26,260 --> 00:24:28,030
为什么要捡  反正都学不会
Why should I? Never gonna get it.

595
00:24:28,220 --> 00:24:29,070
说得太对了
You're right.

596
00:24:31,690 --> 00:24:32,620
我能问你点事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?

597
00:24:36,180 --> 00:24:38,310
你的引擎设计理念是什么
What's your engine design philosophy?

598
00:24:40,860 --> 00:24:42,700
让动力和持久性达到完美的平衡
Perfectly balanced power and durability.

599
00:24:43,080 --> 00:24:46,150
为什么不像布伦森一样偏重于动力呢
Okay. Why don't you favor power like Bronson does?

600
00:24:46,560 --> 00:24:48,620
因为车手一个赛季只能用八个引擎
Because drivers are limited to eight engines a season,

601
00:24:48,910 --> 00:24:50,060
布伦森的不够耐用
and Bronson's don't last.

602
00:24:50,250 --> 00:24:51,340
所以你会拿你的引擎
Well, so you would stack your engines

603
00:24:51,520 --> 00:24:52,500
同布伦森的相比
up against Bronson's, then?

604
00:24:52,690 --> 00:24:54,630
我拿我的引擎和布伦森
Uh, I have stacked my engines up against Bronson

605
00:24:54,820 --> 00:24:56,050
以及世界所有的引擎比过
and everyone else's in the world,

606
00:24:56,220 --> 00:24:57,790
-我的引擎完胜  -为什么
- and mine win. - Why?

607
00:24:58,070 --> 00:24:58,680
因为我确保
Because I make sure

608
00:24:58,880 --> 00:25:01,280
它们从构思到成品
they're designed better than anyone else's in the world

609
00:25:01,470 --> 00:25:04,110
都是全世界设计得最好的
from the day that they're conceived to the day they're born.

610
00:25:04,280 --> 00:25:05,310
所以人们才会购买
And that's why people buy them.

611
00:25:05,500 --> 00:25:06,630
太对了
Goddamn right.

612
00:25:07,240 --> 00:25:08,660
那这就是你的演讲内容
And that's the speech you're gonna give.

613
00:25:21,880 --> 00:25:23,390
律师界的无间道
Good lawyer, bad lawyer, baby.

614
00:25:23,600 --> 00:25:24,340
屡试不爽
Worked like a charm.

615
00:25:26,020 --> 00:25:27,160
来吧  你都忍不住了
Come on. You know you want it.

616
00:25:28,260 --> 00:25:29,900
-这就对了  -跟你说过
- There it is. - Told you.

617
00:25:30,180 --> 00:25:31,210
有些人不喜欢你
Someone doesn't like you,

618
00:25:31,380 --> 00:25:32,260
你就利用这点对付他们
you use it against them.

619
00:25:32,470 --> 00:25:33,780
或者像这次一样  为他们好
Or, in this case, for them.

620
00:25:33,970 --> 00:25:35,750
我不是为多米尼克好
I didn't do this for Dominic.

621
00:25:35,930 --> 00:25:37,180
我是为了除掉斯坦斯兰
I did it to get rid of Stensland.

622
00:25:37,450 --> 00:25:40,270
天哪  你想过去做贺曼的编剧吗
Wow. Have you ever considered writing for Hallmark?

623
00:25:37,450 --> 00:25:40,270
霍尔马克  电影娱乐公司

624
00:25:40,470 --> 00:25:42,220
-想过很多次  -好吧
- Many times. - Yeah.

625
00:25:43,180 --> 00:25:44,030
恭喜
Congrats.

626
00:25:46,070 --> 00:25:46,660
看起来不错
Looking good.

627
00:26:01,990 --> 00:26:02,850
我说过别迟到
I said don't be late.

628
00:26:03,200 --> 00:26:04,570
迟到  我没迟到啊
Late? I'm not late.

629
00:26:04,890 --> 00:26:06,630
要想在这里请客吃饭
When you host your dinner here,

630
00:26:06,850 --> 00:26:09,250
别迟到的意思就是提前半个小时到
not being late means getting here a half hour early.

631
00:26:09,540 --> 00:26:11,640
原来如此  你怎么改变主意了
Aha. So what made you change your mind?

632
00:26:11,960 --> 00:26:14,870
这些食品是供你选择菜品的样品
The food items are samples to help you select your menu,

633
00:26:15,060 --> 00:26:18,110
所以  既然我一个人吃不起这种地方...
so since I could never really afford to eat here myself...

634
00:26:22,240 --> 00:26:23,600
好了  从那个开始
Okay, start there.

635
00:26:23,900 --> 00:26:24,830
-尝尝这个吗  -是的
- Try that? - Yes.

636
00:26:25,140 --> 00:26:27,200
-看起来有点怪  -蛋卷也很怪啊
- It looks kind of funny. - So does an egg roll.

637
00:26:27,450 --> 00:26:28,620
我可没法把它当成蛋卷
I don't accept that premise.

638
00:26:29,050 --> 00:26:30,160
你还想不想让我帮忙
You want my help or not?

639
00:26:37,680 --> 00:26:38,860
这是什么啊
Ugh. What is that?

640
00:26:39,070 --> 00:26:39,870
鱿鱼
Squid.

641
00:26:40,080 --> 00:26:41,200
我觉得它还在动呢
I-- I think it's still moving.

642
00:26:44,850 --> 00:26:46,250
这才是食物呢
That's what I'm talking about.

643
00:26:49,230 --> 00:26:49,920
真弄不明白
I don't get it.

644
00:26:50,120 --> 00:26:52,220
你怎么就不喜欢精致的食物呢
How do you have no appreciation for fine food?

645
00:26:53,780 --> 00:26:56,700
我们小时候家里不宽裕  我也说不清
Mm. We didn't have a lot of money growing up. I don't know.

646
00:26:56,790 --> 00:26:58,580
我想我就是喜欢我习惯了的东西吧
I guess I'm just comfortable with what I'm comfortable with.

647
00:26:59,390 --> 00:27:00,830
这跟我正相反
That is the exact opposite of me.

648
00:27:01,010 --> 00:27:03,860
我一直都喜欢新鲜的体验
I've-- I've always loved new experiences.

649
00:27:04,280 --> 00:27:05,110
你家境如何
And your parents?

650
00:27:05,570 --> 00:27:06,450
非常富裕
They're loaded.

651
00:27:06,690 --> 00:27:09,370
那干嘛还要我请你
Mm. So then what do you need a free meal for?

652
00:27:10,030 --> 00:27:11,400
我想靠我挣的钱生活
I want to live on what I make.

653
00:27:14,630 --> 00:27:15,780
-怎么了  -没什么
- What? - Nothing.

654
00:27:16,600 --> 00:27:18,270
刚刚突然想到了多米尼克
I was just thinking about Dominic for a second.

655
00:27:18,440 --> 00:27:21,330
然后我意识到这是几周以来
And then I realized this is the first time in weeks

656
00:27:21,500 --> 00:27:22,880
我第一次没在为工作操心
that I haven't been thinking about work.

657
00:27:23,140 --> 00:27:24,580
这就是新体验带来的好处
That's what new experiences do for you.

658
00:27:25,020 --> 00:27:28,410
做个美食家不单纯是喜欢精致的食品
Being a foodie doesn't mean only liking fancy food.

659
00:27:29,540 --> 00:27:30,730
而是有尝试的勇气
Means having the courage to try it.

660
00:27:31,100 --> 00:27:32,730
之后就可以选你喜欢的吃了
And then you get to serve what you like.

661
00:27:32,980 --> 00:27:35,890
除了草莓  花生  谷蛋白和鸡肉
Except strawberries, peanuts, gluten, and chicken.

662
00:27:36,120 --> 00:27:37,410
为什么不能选那些东西
Okay, why not those things?

663
00:27:37,600 --> 00:27:38,720
因为路易犯浑了
Because Louis is an asshole.

664
00:27:38,900 --> 00:27:40,900
如果你因为路易犯浑就不上这些食物
If you can't serve things just 'cause Louis is an asshole,

665
00:27:41,350 --> 00:27:42,830
你可没多少可选的了
you're not gonna have that many choices.

666
00:27:43,010 --> 00:27:43,890
那倒是
Good point.

667
00:27:46,020 --> 00:27:47,300
珍妮来电

668
00:27:47,300 --> 00:27:47,980
拒接

669
00:27:51,140 --> 00:27:52,540
你到底为什么改主意
So what really made you change your mind?

670
00:27:55,420 --> 00:27:56,110
同情你了
Pity.

671
00:27:58,400 --> 00:27:59,060
那我领情了
I'll take it.

672
00:28:10,740 --> 00:28:13,340
司机  送我去威廉斯堡
Driver, taketh me to Williamsburg.

673
00:28:16,260 --> 00:28:16,980
是珍妮
It's Jenny.

674
00:28:17,160 --> 00:28:18,870
特雷弗告诉我你跟他谈了
Trevor told me you talked to him,

675
00:28:18,870 --> 00:28:20,480
他打算洗手不干了
and he's gonna stop.

676
00:28:20,890 --> 00:28:21,480
谢谢你了  迈克
Thanks, Mike.

677
00:28:21,670 --> 00:28:22,460
等等
Hold on.

678
00:28:23,200 --> 00:28:24,520
不去威廉斯堡了
Change of destination.

679
00:28:27,970 --> 00:28:28,560
特雷弗
Trevor.

680
00:28:28,920 --> 00:28:29,840
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?

681
00:28:32,080 --> 00:28:32,960
我们能聊聊吗
Can we talk for a minute?

682
00:28:34,690 --> 00:28:35,530
行啊
Yeah.

683
00:28:40,650 --> 00:28:42,560
我知道你跟珍妮撒谎说我们谈过了
I know you lied to Jenny about us talking.

684
00:28:43,770 --> 00:28:45,860
你根本就不该告诉她我在贩毒
You never should have told her i was dealing in the first place.

685
00:28:46,030 --> 00:28:47,940
我根本就不该替你隐瞒
I never should have had to hide it in the first place.

686
00:28:49,990 --> 00:28:53,380
听着  特雷弗  你不用靠贩毒为生
Look, Trevor, you don't need to be dealing for a living, man.

687
00:28:54,470 --> 00:28:55,550
你可以有所作为的
You could make something of yourself.

688
00:28:55,750 --> 00:28:56,560
你过来就为了跟我说这个吗
Is that what you came here to tell me?

689
00:28:56,740 --> 00:28:58,570
你有真正的软件客户啊
You've got real software clients, man.

690
00:28:58,750 --> 00:28:59,440
留住他们
Stick to them.

691
00:28:59,630 --> 00:29:01,230
天啊  你还当真了
Jeez. You believe that crap?

692
00:29:02,230 --> 00:29:04,350
我没有什么软件客户
I don't have any software clients.

693
00:29:04,530 --> 00:29:05,950
老天  你跟珍妮一样天真
Jesus. You're as naive as Jenny.

694
00:29:06,940 --> 00:29:07,650
听我说
Look...

695
00:29:08,860 --> 00:29:10,730
你要是需要周转资金什么的
if you need some kind of transition money or something--

696
00:29:10,900 --> 00:29:12,170
什么  你哪来的钱
What? How?

697
00:29:12,880 --> 00:29:13,790
有关系吗
Does it matter?

698
00:29:14,230 --> 00:29:17,910
有关系  不用你来帮我
Look, what matters is that you don't help me out, okay?

699
00:29:18,110 --> 00:29:18,760
是我来帮你
I help you out.

700
00:29:18,950 --> 00:29:22,290
而且我也不想周转成别的什么
And I'm not interested in transitioning into anything.

701
00:29:22,470 --> 00:29:23,280
好吧
Okay.

702
00:29:24,920 --> 00:29:26,420
但至少你该跟珍妮说实话
But the least you could do is be honest with Jenny.

703
00:29:26,610 --> 00:29:27,550
这才是问题的关键吧
That's what this is all about.

704
00:29:27,830 --> 00:29:29,200
-没错  -你一直喜欢她
- Yeah. - You always liked her.

705
00:29:29,420 --> 00:29:31,290
我觉得她应该知道真相
I think she deserves to know the truth.

706
00:29:32,430 --> 00:29:33,840
你总觉得自己比我强
You always thought you were better than me.

707
00:29:35,240 --> 00:29:36,310
或许我就是比你强
Maybe that's because I am.

708
00:29:48,050 --> 00:29:49,110
别闹了
Come on now. All right?

709
00:30:00,650 --> 00:30:01,300
一刀两断吧
We're done.

710
00:30:03,040 --> 00:30:03,980
别撞门上
Don't let the door hit you--

711
00:30:27,600 --> 00:30:28,280
给多米尼克打电话了吗
Call Dominic?

712
00:30:28,690 --> 00:30:29,750
他在门外等着我们
He's waiting for us outside.

713
00:30:30,240 --> 00:30:31,320
他准备好演讲了吗
He's got the speech down?

714
00:30:31,740 --> 00:30:32,620
准备好了
Yeah, he's got it down.

715
00:30:32,860 --> 00:30:34,570
最好如此  我把宝押在他身上了
Better. I'm taking a big risk on him.

716
00:30:35,460 --> 00:30:36,890
你把宝押在他身上了
You're taking a risk on him?

717
00:30:38,040 --> 00:30:38,830
你看看他
Look at him.

718
00:30:39,180 --> 00:30:40,210
他都吓得魂不附体了
He's scared out of his mind.

719
00:30:40,210 --> 00:30:41,460
就因为是听了你的劝
He's leaving his comfort zone

720
00:30:41,460 --> 00:30:43,610
-他要做自己不擅长的事  -那又如何
- because you convinced him to. - So?

721
00:30:44,050 --> 00:30:46,610
不如说两句鼓励他的话
So maybe some words of encouragement.

722
00:30:47,030 --> 00:30:47,960
帮多米尼克最好的办法
The best way to help Dominic

723
00:30:48,150 --> 00:30:50,040
是不让他对自己有疑虑
is not to let him second guess himself.

724
00:30:50,440 --> 00:30:52,560
一个律师最宝贵的资本
The most important asset an attorney has

725
00:30:52,760 --> 00:30:54,930
是一直保持自信的能力
is his ability to always be self-assured.

726
00:30:56,090 --> 00:30:57,910
好了  程序是这样的
Okay. Here's what's gonna happen.

727
00:30:58,240 --> 00:31:01,330
一般会由我来为董事会的投票程序做准备
It's standard for me to prep the board on any voting procedure.

728
00:31:01,630 --> 00:31:02,610
我什么时候发言
When do I speak?

729
00:31:03,210 --> 00:31:05,330
我让你讲的时候  我们走吧
When I tell you to. Let's go.

730
00:31:09,260 --> 00:31:10,850
我向斯坦斯兰建议让你过来
I suggested to Stensland you be there

731
00:31:11,040 --> 00:31:12,840
向董事会保证生产不会受到
to convince the board the production won't be hurt

732
00:31:13,050 --> 00:31:14,150
向海外搬迁的影响
by an overseas move.

733
00:31:14,350 --> 00:31:16,560
他带你过来  有助于提升你的公信力
It helps your credibility that he brought you here,

734
00:31:16,750 --> 00:31:18,960
但你要跟他争CEO一职时  他就不好看了
and it'll hurt his when you challenge him for CEO.

735
00:31:24,060 --> 00:31:25,730
紧张也是人之常情
Look, it's natural to be nervous, okay?

736
00:31:25,930 --> 00:31:27,600
只要记住  你懂技术
Just remember, you know your stuff.

737
00:31:27,790 --> 00:31:28,960
董事会一直不喜欢斯坦斯兰
The board's never loved Stensland,

738
00:31:29,170 --> 00:31:30,230
而且我会给你撑腰
and I'm here to back you up.

739
00:31:30,460 --> 00:31:31,280
好吧
Okay.

740
00:31:40,190 --> 00:31:40,810
罗伯特
Robert.

741
00:31:42,750 --> 00:31:43,490
哈维
Harvey.

742
00:31:45,000 --> 00:31:46,720
要知道  我得承认我差点没料到你这一招
You know, I have to admit, i almost didn't see it coming.

743
00:31:47,420 --> 00:31:48,260
你说什么
Excuse me?

744
00:31:48,610 --> 00:31:50,210
尽职调查的延迟一事
It was the delay in the due diligence.

745
00:31:50,390 --> 00:31:51,370
就是觉得不对劲
It just didn't smell right.

746
00:31:51,950 --> 00:31:52,770
唯一可能的解释
So the only thing it could be

747
00:31:52,970 --> 00:31:55,400
就是你不想让我当CEO
was that you were going after my CEO appointment.

748
00:31:56,550 --> 00:31:58,480
而我还有权利重新安排董事会
So since I'm still within my rights to move a board meeting,

749
00:31:58,480 --> 00:31:59,700
我就调时间了
I did.

750
00:32:00,100 --> 00:32:01,590
我今天中午当选了
I was voted in today at noon.

751
00:32:02,420 --> 00:32:04,750
明天董事会将批准工厂的出售
And tomorrow the board will ratify the sale of the factory.

752
00:32:05,770 --> 00:32:07,300
现在我要解雇你们公司
And now I'm firing your firm.

753
00:32:09,890 --> 00:32:10,940
还要解雇你
And I'm firing you.

754
00:32:13,120 --> 00:32:14,170
尝尝羊角面包吧  先生们
Try the croissant, gentlemen.

755
00:32:14,850 --> 00:32:16,110
橙子酱好吃极了
Marmalade's fantastic.

756
00:32:27,150 --> 00:32:27,870
我们该怎么做
What are we gonna do?

757
00:32:28,510 --> 00:32:29,910
你要去再翻一遍章程
You're gonna go through those bylaws again,

758
00:32:30,120 --> 00:32:32,520
看看有没有别的办法阻止出售
and see if there isn't another way we can stop this sale.

759
00:32:32,710 --> 00:32:34,780
我是说拿多米尼克怎么办  他刚刚丢了工作
I'm talking about Dominic. He just lost his job.

760
00:32:34,970 --> 00:32:36,550
他是个成人了  是他自己做的决定
He's a grown man. He made a decision.

761
00:32:37,140 --> 00:32:38,730
还不是你说服他做的
Because you convinced him to.

762
00:32:38,920 --> 00:32:39,670
主意是你出的
Based on your idea,

763
00:32:39,870 --> 00:32:41,630
我记得你当时还极力推荐来着
which I recall you pushed on me at the time.

764
00:32:41,810 --> 00:32:43,320
因为当时我以为能奏效呢
Because I thought it would work at the time.

765
00:32:43,520 --> 00:32:44,830
结果没奏效  那你要我怎么办
Well, it didn't. What do you want me to do about it?

766
00:32:45,010 --> 00:32:45,930
帮他啊
Help him.

767
00:32:46,920 --> 00:32:48,500
他又不是要死了  就是丢了饭碗
He's not dying. He lost his job.

768
00:32:48,700 --> 00:32:49,640
他再找一个就得了
He has to look for another one.

769
00:32:49,920 --> 00:32:51,040
要是他一开始就选择
Which, if he hadn't chosen to fight for

770
00:32:51,040 --> 00:32:52,100
不为他的公司抗争
his company in the first place,

771
00:32:52,280 --> 00:32:53,320
也得另谋出路
would have happened anyway.

772
00:32:53,550 --> 00:32:54,690
用行动告诉我你开窍了
Now, show me that you get it,

773
00:32:54,890 --> 00:32:56,160
再去翻一遍章程
go back through those bylaws again,

774
00:32:56,370 --> 00:32:58,190
看看你有没有漏掉什么
and see if you missed anything. Okay?

775
00:33:01,980 --> 00:33:03,720
提升错的人做资深合伙人
So this is what happens when you promote the wrong guy

776
00:33:03,720 --> 00:33:04,320
就是这种下场
to senior partner.

777
00:33:04,320 --> 00:33:06,230
你要是没有背着我去找斯坦斯兰
If you hadn't gone to Stensland behind my back,

778
00:33:06,420 --> 00:33:07,660
-事情就不会这样  -这可难说
- this wouldn't have happened. - You don't know that.

779
00:33:07,870 --> 00:33:09,980
我在公司和你有着相同的资历
And I'm a member of this firm just as much of you.

780
00:33:10,180 --> 00:33:11,570
我觉得你只是个职员而已
Oh, I think we both agree that you're a member.

781
00:33:11,750 --> 00:33:13,230
跟你说  我都没...
For your information, I didn't even--

782
00:33:13,410 --> 00:33:15,640
路易  哈维  先处理问题
Louis. Harvey, eye on the ball.

783
00:33:16,390 --> 00:33:18,730
现在的问题是你试图背后捅客户一刀
The issue here is you tried to torpedo a client--

784
00:33:18,910 --> 00:33:21,320
客户是麦肯诺汽车公司  而不是斯坦斯兰
The client is McKernon Motors, not Stensland.

785
00:33:21,520 --> 00:33:22,410
我还没说完
You didn't let me finish.

786
00:33:22,890 --> 00:33:24,750
而且没经我同意
Without my consent.

787
00:33:25,500 --> 00:33:27,610
这比"谁是客户"的问题严重
That trumps the "who's the client" part.

788
00:33:27,990 --> 00:33:30,570
路易  去找斯坦斯兰  挽回败局
Louis, go to Stensland, repair the relationship.

789
00:33:30,770 --> 00:33:33,160
多说好话  就说这是场误会
Say what you have to. Call it a misunderstanding.

790
00:33:33,340 --> 00:33:36,120
保证哈维不会再插手了
Promise Harvey is no longer involved.

791
00:33:37,040 --> 00:33:37,710
没问题
Consider it done.

792
00:33:42,680 --> 00:33:43,650
等等
Wait a second.

793
00:33:44,080 --> 00:33:45,700
路易没有背着我找斯坦斯兰
Louis didn't go to Stensland behind my back.

794
00:33:45,890 --> 00:33:47,310
你是派他挽回损失的
You send him there to hedge your bets.

795
00:33:50,350 --> 00:33:52,940
要么是斯坦斯兰退出  我们的收入翻倍
Either Stensland's out and we double our billings,

796
00:33:53,160 --> 00:33:55,050
要么你给出合理的解释
or you have plausible deniability,

797
00:33:55,310 --> 00:33:56,630
他才能继续雇用我们事务所
and he stays with the firm.

798
00:33:57,610 --> 00:34:00,090
我有那么聪明吗
Am I smart enough to do that?

799
00:34:01,230 --> 00:34:02,610
要是我赢  我有面子
If I win, I look great.

800
00:34:03,330 --> 00:34:04,640
要是路易赢  他有面子
If Louis wins, he looks great.

801
00:34:05,230 --> 00:34:08,710
不管谁赢  你都有面子
Either way... You look great.

802
00:34:08,950 --> 00:34:11,310
你是说事务所有面子吧
You mean the firm looks great.

803
00:34:11,730 --> 00:34:13,300
哈维  我要灌输给你的思想是
Harvey, what I've been trying to get into your head

804
00:34:13,500 --> 00:34:14,600
你已经入伙了
is that you bought in.

805
00:34:15,350 --> 00:34:16,450
你就代表事务所
You are the firm.

806
00:34:20,350 --> 00:34:21,040
没错
That's it.

807
00:34:24,650 --> 00:34:25,730
迈克  跟我来
Mike, follow me.

808
00:34:25,960 --> 00:34:27,410
我要你去和多米尼克谈谈
I need you to go talk to Dominic.

809
00:34:27,840 --> 00:34:30,280
什么  为什么  斯坦斯兰已经当上CEO了
What? Why? Stensland's already CEO.

810
00:34:30,470 --> 00:34:32,160
如果我们买下那破公司  那就不成问题了
That won't matter if we just buy the damn company.

811
00:34:32,860 --> 00:34:33,670
什么
What?

812
00:34:37,010 --> 00:34:37,920
为什么你还在工作
Why are you still working?

813
00:34:41,550 --> 00:34:42,560
这是我的心血之一
It's one of my creations.

814
00:34:43,090 --> 00:34:44,360
我不会半途而废的
I'm not leaving it unfinished.

815
00:34:46,260 --> 00:34:47,020
你想要什么
What the hell do you want?

816
00:34:48,550 --> 00:34:50,170
如果你把那个扳手放下  我很乐意说
I'd be happy to tell you if you put that wrench down.

817
00:34:50,170 --> 00:34:51,090
你真会开玩笑
Yeah, you're quick with the jokes.

818
00:34:51,170 --> 00:34:52,530
我是个刚刚被开除的人
I'm the guy who just got fired.

819
00:34:54,880 --> 00:34:55,730
你说得对  抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.

820
00:34:58,000 --> 00:34:59,310
如果我们可以让你重拾工作
What would you say if I told you

821
00:34:59,500 --> 00:35:01,510
还能狠狠教训斯坦斯兰  你有何想法
we could get your job back and stick it to Stensland.

822
00:35:01,690 --> 00:35:03,360
我不想再跟哈维掺和了  明白吗
I'm done with Harvey and his plans, yeah?

823
00:35:03,900 --> 00:35:05,170
你当时在场  我们也被解雇了
You were there. We got fired too.

824
00:35:05,370 --> 00:35:06,680
那你和哈维还有工作吗
You and Harvey still have jobs?

825
00:35:07,280 --> 00:35:09,930
除了他自己  他谁也不在乎
He doesn't care about anybody but himself,

826
00:35:10,120 --> 00:35:11,490
包括你  迈克
including you, Mike.

827
00:35:11,970 --> 00:35:13,890
是的  你也许是对的
Yeah. You're probably right.

828
00:35:16,230 --> 00:35:18,520
但是他的确冒着风险想保住你的公司
But he did stick his neck out to keep your company here,

829
00:35:19,760 --> 00:35:21,970
他也确实有个想法需要你的帮助
and he does have an idea that requires your help,

830
00:35:22,170 --> 00:35:25,070
所以你要么留在这里继续骂他
so you can stay here and call him an asshole,

831
00:35:25,310 --> 00:35:26,930
要么和我来一起  助他一臂之力
or you can come with me and we can help him.

832
00:35:31,970 --> 00:35:33,160
把我该死的衬衣给我
Give me my goddamn shirt.

833
00:35:48,610 --> 00:35:50,040
你知道吗  它从0加速到60迈
You know, it goes from 0 to 60--

834
00:35:50,220 --> 00:35:51,480
只需眨眼之间
in the blink of an eye.

835
00:35:54,910 --> 00:35:57,160
你叫我来就是告诉我  我能开这辆车吗
Did you bring me down here to tell me I can drive this?

836
00:35:57,430 --> 00:35:58,250
还有好消息
Better.

837
00:35:58,470 --> 00:36:00,290
只需两亿五千美金  你就可以买下来
For $250 million, you can own it.

838
00:36:02,250 --> 00:36:03,880
麦肯诺汽车公司在打折吗
McKernon Motors is for sale?

839
00:36:04,060 --> 00:36:04,950
只要我们出手够快
If we act fast.

840
00:36:05,340 --> 00:36:06,720
我要查看一下财政报告
I'll need to see the financials.

841
00:36:07,020 --> 00:36:08,250
你整合一份意向书
You put together a letter of intent,

842
00:36:08,430 --> 00:36:09,700
他们就会给你财政报告了
they'll get you the financials.

843
00:36:09,910 --> 00:36:12,360
他们公司真正的价值是引擎质量
You know, their real asset is engine quality.

844
00:36:12,650 --> 00:36:13,830
我不想只买个牌子
I don't want to just buy the name.

845
00:36:14,770 --> 00:36:15,690
说曹操  曹操到
Speak of the devil.

846
00:36:16,130 --> 00:36:17,850
劳伦斯  我想为你介绍一下麦肯诺汽车公司
Laurence, I'd like you to meet the man responsible

847
00:36:18,040 --> 00:36:20,120
历代引擎的设计者
for every McKernon Motors engine ever built.

848
00:36:20,310 --> 00:36:22,190
多米尼克·巴伦  很荣幸
Dominic Barone. Very nice to meet you.

849
00:36:22,370 --> 00:36:22,920
我也是
Good to meet you.

850
00:36:22,950 --> 00:36:24,280
如果你有空  我想带你看样东西
I'd like to show you something if you have a minute.

851
00:36:24,470 --> 00:36:25,350
当然可以
Absolutely.

852
00:36:27,970 --> 00:36:29,750
在明天前董事会投票批准合同之前
So how do we get an offer to the board

853
00:36:29,960 --> 00:36:31,700
我们该怎样对他们报价
before they vote to ratify the deal tomorrow?

854
00:36:32,330 --> 00:36:33,650
你再去仔细看一遍章程
You're gonna go through those bylaws,

855
00:36:33,840 --> 00:36:34,800
想出点办法来
and you're gonna figure something out.

856
00:36:36,210 --> 00:36:37,490
我不用看一遍才能想到办法
I don't have to look through them to figure it out,

857
00:36:37,690 --> 00:36:38,540
因为我看过了
because I just did.

858
00:36:38,730 --> 00:36:39,650
怎么那么久
Well, what took you so long?

859
00:36:40,280 --> 00:36:41,160
你在模仿我吗
You trying to look like me?

860
00:36:47,740 --> 00:36:49,020
各位有24小时
Each of you have 24 hours

861
00:36:49,210 --> 00:36:50,570
来审阅你们面前的文件
to review the documents in front of you,

862
00:36:50,880 --> 00:36:52,290
所以此时此刻
so at this time...

863
00:36:52,450 --> 00:36:53,490
抱歉  打扰一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.

864
00:36:54,210 --> 00:36:55,480
他在这里干什么
What is he doing here?

865
00:36:55,690 --> 00:36:56,830
抱歉  我来处理
I'm sorry. I'm gonna take care of this.

866
00:36:57,010 --> 00:36:57,880
不  不  我来
No, no, I will.

867
00:36:58,090 --> 00:37:00,960
你们各位无权出席本次会议
You gentlemen have no right to attend this meeting.

868
00:37:01,160 --> 00:37:02,100
事实上  我们有权出席
Actually, we do.

869
00:37:02,310 --> 00:37:04,830
章程明规定  任何初始雇员
The bylaw states that any original employee

870
00:37:05,030 --> 00:37:07,370
都有权随时向董事会提出申请
has the right to petition the board any time they meet.

871
00:37:07,570 --> 00:37:10,320
多米尼克·巴伦已授权于我
Dominic Barone has assigned that right to me.

872
00:37:10,840 --> 00:37:11,890
他已经被解雇了
He was fired.

873
00:37:12,080 --> 00:37:13,450
他没有那样的权利
He no longer has that right.

874
00:37:13,630 --> 00:37:15,780
第17章5节C款规定
Per section 17-5, point "C,"

875
00:37:15,950 --> 00:37:17,390
多米尼克未在解雇前三天收到通知
Dominic wasn't given three days' notice,

876
00:37:17,580 --> 00:37:19,840
严格来说他还没被解雇
so technically he wasn't fired.

877
00:37:20,020 --> 00:37:22,260
所以我有权敦促董事会
Which is why I do have the right to urge the board

878
00:37:22,260 --> 00:37:25,810
接受对麦肯诺汽车公司的报价
to accept the offer for the purchase of McKernon Motors.

879
00:37:26,000 --> 00:37:28,020
我可以告诉各位  本次收购
Now, I can tell you that this offer

880
00:37:28,230 --> 00:37:30,270
将会保留工厂生产和工作机会
will keep manufacturing here and save jobs

881
00:37:30,480 --> 00:37:33,610
同时保留将公司推向世界的旗舰引擎
while retaining the flagship engine that put this company on the map,

882
00:37:33,610 --> 00:37:34,430
但我无需如此
but I don't have to,

883
00:37:34,430 --> 00:37:37,770
因为碰巧有个机会能让在座各位
because it happens to be for way more goddamn money

884
00:37:37,770 --> 00:37:39,100
获得更多的利润
than the one in front of you right now.

885
00:37:41,720 --> 00:37:42,560
鲍勃  你好吗
Hey, Bob. How are ya?

886
00:37:46,020 --> 00:37:47,440
那个适当通知的例外情况
It's funny how you held out on me

887
00:37:47,640 --> 00:37:49,130
你居然对我有所隐瞒
on that proper notice exception.

888
00:37:49,350 --> 00:37:50,240
我没隐瞒
I didn't hold out.

889
00:37:50,450 --> 00:37:51,700
我当场编的
I made that up on the spot.

890
00:37:51,900 --> 00:37:52,960
真的  当场吗
Really? On the spot?

891
00:37:53,160 --> 00:37:54,400
记住要学习
Remember that getting it stuff--

892
00:37:54,600 --> 00:37:55,670
我懂  我在学
I know, right? I'm getting it.

893
00:37:56,070 --> 00:37:58,180
我正准备说  但现在被你吐槽了
Well, I was gonna say that, but now you ruined it.

894
00:37:59,490 --> 00:38:00,760
那是你唯一学到的
That's one thing you definitely get.

895
00:38:02,340 --> 00:38:03,320
怎么吐槽
How to ruin it.

896
00:38:04,640 --> 00:38:05,590
怎么吐槽
How to ruin it?

897
00:38:05,790 --> 00:38:06,680
我听见了
I heard that.

898
00:38:20,000 --> 00:38:22,270
我得承认  你没那么糟糕
I have to admit, you don't suck.

899
00:38:23,490 --> 00:38:24,860
我希望也能对你做出同样的评价
I wish I could say the same for you.

900
00:38:28,040 --> 00:38:30,850
该付钱了  告诉你一声
Time to pay the Piper. Just so you know,

901
00:38:30,850 --> 00:38:33,550
我过了一把随便点好酒的瘾
I took the liberty of ordering some really expensive wines.

902
00:38:34,390 --> 00:38:35,300
希望你不介意
Hope that's okay.

903
00:38:43,130 --> 00:38:45,350
总计10658.48美元

904
00:38:47,530 --> 00:38:49,300
抱歉  先生  账单已由哈维·斯佩克特
Sorry, sir, but the check's been paid for in full

905
00:38:49,490 --> 00:38:50,430
全部付清
by a Harvey Specter.

906
00:38:55,990 --> 00:38:57,810
馄饨里貌似有点谷蛋白
There, uh, might have been some gluten in the ravioli.

907
00:39:05,180 --> 00:39:07,310
我听说麦肯诺汽车公司有新总裁了
I hear McKernon Motors is getting a new owner.

908
00:39:07,530 --> 00:39:08,980
我们不仅要负责销售
We're not only handling the sale,

909
00:39:09,170 --> 00:39:11,260
还要负责他们正在准备的扩展计划
but with the expansion plan they're putting in place,

910
00:39:11,450 --> 00:39:12,820
我们的佣金可以翻倍了
our billables should double.

911
00:39:13,010 --> 00:39:13,880
做得好
Nicely done.

912
00:39:14,920 --> 00:39:15,990
为公司效劳
I did it for the firm.

913
00:39:44,730 --> 00:39:45,410
你过来干什么
What are you doing here?

914
00:39:49,160 --> 00:39:49,800
你说得对
You were right.

915
00:39:50,700 --> 00:39:51,860
我不该对你有所保留
I should never have kept it from you

916
00:39:52,030 --> 00:39:53,630
特雷弗一直都在贩毒
that Trevor was dealing all that time.

917
00:39:56,150 --> 00:39:58,560
我说  那个...
Well, I mean, it's, uh...

918
00:40:00,780 --> 00:40:02,170
都过去了  对吗
It's all in the past, right?

919
00:40:04,230 --> 00:40:04,970
没有
No.

920
00:40:07,230 --> 00:40:08,290
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?

921
00:40:11,030 --> 00:40:11,880
他骗了你
He's lying to you.

922
00:40:16,260 --> 00:40:17,040
他还在贩毒
He's still dealing.

923
00:40:18,300 --> 00:40:19,070
我和他一刀两断了
And I'm done with him.

924
00:40:28,660 --> 00:40:29,660
混蛋
Son of a bitch.

925
00:40:33,320 --> 00:40:35,620
谢谢你告诉了我
Well, thank you, uh, for telling me.

926
00:40:35,820 --> 00:40:37,260
别  别这样
No, don't. Stop.

927
00:40:39,880 --> 00:40:40,570
我们扯平了
We're even.

928
00:40:41,950 --> 00:40:44,500
这也是我最后一次告发别人
And that is the last time I am ever ratting on anyone.

929
00:40:46,540 --> 00:40:47,770
如果你再上当
So if you fall for it again...

930
00:40:50,920 --> 00:40:51,570
只能怪你自己了
It's on you.

931
00:40:53,990 --> 00:40:55,600
你生我的气了吗
Are you angry with me?

932
00:40:58,270 --> 00:40:59,600
你说他会听我的
You told me he would listen to me.

933
00:40:59,890 --> 00:41:01,290
-我以为他会  -他不会
- I thought he would. - Well, he didn't.

934
00:41:02,460 --> 00:41:03,150
我...
I...

935
00:41:03,800 --> 00:41:04,720
对不起
I'm sorry.

936
00:41:06,170 --> 00:41:07,230
对不起
I'm s-- I'm sorry.

937
00:41:15,920 --> 00:41:16,890
不  我不能
No, I can't.

938
00:41:17,580 --> 00:41:18,340
不能这样
I can't.

939
00:41:19,190 --> 00:41:19,770
什么
What?

940
00:41:19,980 --> 00:41:21,560
不  我和他吵了一架
No, I-- I fought with him.

941
00:41:23,550 --> 00:41:24,480
天啊
Oh, God.

942
00:41:25,460 --> 00:41:26,500
这样太过了
This is too much.

943
00:41:34,140 --> 00:41:37,370
瑞秋来电

