1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:01,910
《訴訟雙雄》前情提要

2
00:00:01,380 --> 00:00:03,320
我證明艾娃·海辛頓無罪
I get Ava Hessington acquitted...

3
00:00:03,320 --> 00:00:05,120
達比支持我當經營合伙人
Darby backs me for managing partner.

4
00:00:05,130 --> 00:00:06,220
我不想接受了
I don't want it anymore.

5
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:07,730
你趕快從我眼前消失
Get out of my sight.

6
00:00:07,730 --> 00:00:08,620
你給馬里加打電話了
You called Mariga.

7
00:00:08,620 --> 00:00:09,730
提出賄賂他
To offer him a bribe.

8
00:00:09,730 --> 00:00:10,340
無所謂了
Doesn't matter.

9
00:00:10,350 --> 00:00:11,760
丹尼斯根本就沒找到馬里加上校
Dennis never had him in the first place.

10
00:00:11,760 --> 00:00:12,920
但現在找到了
But he does now.

11
00:00:12,930 --> 00:00:15,000
你是說他追蹤了我的電話
You're saying he traced my call?

12
00:00:15,000 --> 00:00:17,620
你為了米卡度的所有權起訴我
You're suing me for ownership of Mikado.

13
00:00:17,650 --> 00:00:20,190
他說他還不如把貓
He said he might as well have left his cat

14
00:00:20,190 --> 00:00:21,790
交給邁克爾·維克
with Michael Vick.

15
00:00:22,080 --> 00:00:23,870
我現在提出一個協議
I'm offering you a settlement.

16
00:00:23,870 --> 00:00:25,680
你重新掌管律師們
You get back the associates.

17
00:00:25,680 --> 00:00:27,250
但要把貓還給我
I get back my cat.

18
00:00:27,250 --> 00:00:28,890
克利福德·丹納當時十八歲
Clifford Danner. He was 18.

19
00:00:28,900 --> 00:00:30,450
十二年前  我控他入獄
I put him in jail 12 years ago.

20
00:00:30,450 --> 00:00:31,520
他是清白的
He's innocent.

21
00:00:31,520 --> 00:00:33,040
卡梅隆掩蓋了證據
Cameron buried the evidence.

22
00:00:33,050 --> 00:00:34,690
這是伊曼紐爾·馬里加二十年前
Emmanuel Mariga 20 years ago

23
00:00:34,690 --> 00:00:36,070
在開普敦大學的照片
at the University of Cape Town.

24
00:00:36,070 --> 00:00:37,060
他是英式橄欖球隊隊員
He was on the rugby team.

25
00:00:37,060 --> 00:00:38,180
你知道還有誰也打英式橄欖球嗎
You know who else played rugby?

26
00:00:38,180 --> 00:00:39,110
史蒂芬·亨特利
Stephen Huntley.

27
00:00:39,110 --> 00:00:41,130
史蒂芬才是下令殺人的幕后黑手
Stephen was the one who ordered those killings.

28
00:00:41,150 --> 00:00:42,810
我很抱歉  哈維
I'm so sorry, Harvey.

29
00:00:56,360 --> 00:00:57,830
告訴我他看起來更慘
Tell me he looks worse.

30
00:00:59,070 --> 00:01:00,050
必須的
He does.

31
00:01:02,500 --> 00:01:03,570
痛嗎
Are you hurt?

32
00:01:04,200 --> 00:01:05,660
不  沒事
No, I'm fine.

33
00:01:08,140 --> 00:01:09,920
希望你不是因為我才這么做的
I hope you didn't do that because of me.

34
00:01:10,640 --> 00:01:12,830
打架而已  唐娜  又不是決斗
It was a fight, Donna, not a duel.

35
00:01:15,290 --> 00:01:17,610
-我怎么會...  -聽我說
- How could I not have-- - Listen to me.

36
00:01:18,590 --> 00:01:20,500
史蒂芬背叛了我們所有人
Stephen betrayed us all.

37
00:01:21,960 --> 00:01:23,450
你不明白  哈維
You don't understand, Harvey.

38
00:01:23,510 --> 00:01:25,110
我當時和他在一起
I was with him.

39
00:01:26,750 --> 00:01:28,490
他能干出這種事
And he was capable of something like that,

40
00:01:28,490 --> 00:01:30,030
我卻毫不知情
and I didn't even see it.

41
00:01:30,470 --> 00:01:32,060
-我應該...  -唐娜
- You know, I'm supposed to-- - Donna!

42
00:01:34,810 --> 00:01:36,140
沒事的
It's okay.

43
00:01:37,370 --> 00:01:39,010
告訴我你會讓他付出代價的
Just tell me you're gonna make him pay.

44
00:01:40,370 --> 00:01:41,570
會的
He'll pay.

45
00:01:50,600 --> 00:01:52,160
什么都別說
Let's not talk about it.

46
00:01:53,410 --> 00:01:54,620
說什么
Talk about what?

47
00:01:56,570 --> 00:01:57,870
你要我做什么
What do you need me to do?

48
00:01:57,960 --> 00:01:59,770
我要你繼續追查手頭資料
I need you to keep going with everything you have

49
00:01:59,770 --> 00:02:01,380
推翻馬里加的證詞
to impeach Mariga's testimony.

50
00:02:01,380 --> 00:02:02,780
那史蒂芬那邊呢
What about the stuff on Stephen?

51
00:02:02,780 --> 00:02:04,660
-按兵不動  -為什么
- Not yet. - Why not?

52
00:02:04,730 --> 00:02:05,970
因為我們沒有證據
Because we don't have proof.

53
00:02:05,970 --> 00:02:06,810
庭審就在兩天后
The trial's in two days.

54
00:02:06,810 --> 00:02:08,110
我們應該請艾娃過來告訴她...
We should bring Ava in and tell her--

55
00:02:08,110 --> 00:02:09,130
-先不要  -為什么
- Not yet. - Why not?

56
00:02:09,130 --> 00:02:10,310
因為我們沒有證據
Because we don't have proof.

57
00:02:10,310 --> 00:02:11,490
哈維  我們總得有所行動吧
Harvey, we have to do something.

58
00:02:11,490 --> 00:02:12,930
要怎么說
And how would that conversation go?

59
00:02:12,930 --> 00:02:15,170
艾娃  看來我們律所的一位律師
"Hi, Ava, turns out one of the lawyers from our firm

60
00:02:15,170 --> 00:02:17,160
想把他犯下的罪行誣陷給你
is trying to frame you for a crime he committed."

61
00:02:17,160 --> 00:02:19,560
但現在我們可能束手無策
"But right now we're not sure we can do anything about it."

62
00:02:20,020 --> 00:02:20,910
你準備怎么做
What are you gonna do?

63
00:02:20,910 --> 00:02:22,510
我準備回家好好睡上一覺
I'm gonna go home, get a good night's sleep,

64
00:02:22,520 --> 00:02:24,050
明早再弄清楚
and then tomorrow I'm gonna find out

65
00:02:24,050 --> 00:02:25,010
整件事的來龍去脈
what the whole story is.

66
00:02:25,010 --> 00:02:26,220
哈維  史蒂芬可不會告訴你
Harvey, Stephen isn't gonna tell you

67
00:02:26,230 --> 00:02:27,150
整件事的來龍去脈
what the whole story is.

68
00:02:27,150 --> 00:02:29,910
他是不會  但有別人會
No, but there's someone else who can.

69
00:02:32,550 --> 00:02:33,800
在你來找我們之前
You knew this case was heading your way

70
00:02:33,800 --> 00:02:35,800
就知道這案子會找上你
before you ever came after us.

71
00:02:35,800 --> 00:02:37,340
所以你才要合并
That's why you wanted to merge.

72
00:02:37,350 --> 00:02:38,200
沒錯
Yes, it is.

73
00:02:38,200 --> 00:02:40,280
我跟你們一樣對此局面深表遺憾
And I regret the situation as much as you do.

74
00:02:40,280 --> 00:02:41,440
但木已成舟
But what's done is done.

75
00:02:41,440 --> 00:02:43,690
你得知史蒂芬的所作所為之后也這么說嗎
Is that what you told Stephen when you found out he did it?

76
00:02:43,690 --> 00:02:44,900
得知
Found out?

77
00:02:45,140 --> 00:02:46,510
誰知道是不是他下的令
How do we know he didn't order it?

78
00:02:46,520 --> 00:02:48,400
我向你們保證  不是我
Because I am giving you my word.

79
00:02:48,400 --> 00:02:50,740
我們憑什么相信一個派史蒂芬過來
Why should we trust a man who sent Stephen over here

80
00:02:50,740 --> 00:02:51,730
擦屁股的人
to cover his ass?

81
00:02:51,730 --> 00:02:55,160
我派史蒂芬過來是因為我關心艾娃
I sent Stephen over here because I care about Ava,

82
00:02:55,930 --> 00:02:58,700
也正是如此我當初才派他去處理環境影響調查
which is why I sent him to the E.I.R. in the first place.

83
00:02:58,700 --> 00:03:00,380
我不知道他會做出這種事
I had no idea he would do what he did,

84
00:03:00,390 --> 00:03:02,430
自那之后我也一直想撥亂反正
and I have been trying to fix it ever since.

85
00:03:02,430 --> 00:03:05,250
-那就現在處理好  -怎么處理
- Then fix it right now. - And how exactly can I do that?

86
00:03:05,250 --> 00:03:06,870
在法庭上直言
By stating in court

87
00:03:06,870 --> 00:03:09,140
是史蒂芬背著艾娃下令殺人
Stephen acted alone without Ava's knowledge.

88
00:03:09,140 --> 00:03:10,740
-不行  -為什么
- I can't. - Why not?

89
00:03:10,740 --> 00:03:12,770
因為他從沒親口跟我說過
Because he never told me.

90
00:03:12,950 --> 00:03:15,580
你從沒問過  因為你從來不想知道
And you never asked because you never wanted to know.

91
00:03:15,580 --> 00:03:17,190
你個雜碎
You piece of shit.

92
00:03:17,610 --> 00:03:19,260
你這么關心艾娃
You care about Ava so much.

93
00:03:19,260 --> 00:03:20,690
怎么能這么對她
How could you do this to her?

94
00:03:20,690 --> 00:03:23,200
我沒對她怎么樣
I wasn't doing anything to her.

95
00:03:23,400 --> 00:03:25,680
我本想為她做些事
I was trying to do something for her.

96
00:03:25,680 --> 00:03:28,180
提醒我千萬別請你幫忙
Remind me never to ask you for any favors.

97
00:03:29,150 --> 00:03:31,020
這不是請你幫忙
Well, I'm not asking for a favor.

98
00:03:31,020 --> 00:03:33,840
你現在得答應做些事
But you are going to agree to do something right now.

99
00:03:34,100 --> 00:03:35,470
什么事
And what is that?

100
00:03:44,870 --> 00:03:46,190
沒用的
It's not gonna work.

101
00:03:47,460 --> 00:03:49,470
為了引起你的注意  我把電話線切斷了
I cut you off to get your attention.

102
00:03:52,210 --> 00:03:54,320
我注意到你了
Well, you have it.

103
00:03:54,320 --> 00:03:56,870
很好  我就想問你一個問題
Good, 'cause I just have one question for you.

104
00:03:57,390 --> 00:03:59,040
你怎么對得住自己的良心
How can you live with yourself?

105
00:03:59,660 --> 00:04:00,390
-什么  -我跟你說
- What? - You know what?

106
00:04:00,390 --> 00:04:01,680
我沒什么要問的
I don't have any questions for you.

107
00:04:01,680 --> 00:04:04,490
我只是過來告訴你  你讓我惡心
I just came in here to let you know that you make me sick.

108
00:04:04,890 --> 00:04:06,970
顯然我傷害了你  唐娜
Obviously I hurt you, Donna,

109
00:04:06,970 --> 00:04:08,790
我也不想的
and I never meant to do that.

110
00:04:08,790 --> 00:04:10,240
你沒傷害我
Oh, you didn't hurt me.

111
00:04:10,450 --> 00:04:12,490
你只是把我變成了一個跟殺人兇手上床的人
You just made me somebody who slept with a murderer.

112
00:04:12,490 --> 00:04:13,440
殺人兇手
Murderer?

113
00:04:15,850 --> 00:04:17,160
我不知道你自以為了解什么
I don't know what you think you know,

114
00:04:17,160 --> 00:04:20,470
那些被殺的人都是恐怖分子
but those people that were killed were terrorists.

115
00:04:20,470 --> 00:04:21,600
他們只是些
They were people...

116
00:04:21,610 --> 00:04:23,400
阻礙你達成目的的人
who lived on top of something that you wanted.

117
00:04:23,400 --> 00:04:26,320
他們都是持槍的兇手  唐娜
People who had guns-- murderers, Donna.

118
00:04:26,320 --> 00:04:28,920
這些處事手段讓你這么震驚的話
Now, if you're so appalled by how business is done,

119
00:04:28,920 --> 00:04:30,050
我建議你把那些
may I suggest that you return

120
00:04:30,060 --> 00:04:33,380
將你襯托得美艷動人的名牌衣服都退回去
all of your designer clothes that you look so ravishing in,

121
00:04:33,380 --> 00:04:35,270
因為那是你用
because they're paid for

122
00:04:35,270 --> 00:04:37,330
這家律所賺的骯臟錢買的
by the dirty work this firm does.

123
00:04:37,330 --> 00:04:38,690
我們不會殺人
We don't kill people.

124
00:04:38,690 --> 00:04:41,160
你是說哈維代表的化學公司
You mean chemical companies that Harvey represents

125
00:04:41,160 --> 00:04:43,550
還是他辯護的汽車公司
or car companies that Harvey defends?

126
00:04:43,550 --> 00:04:47,060
抑或是他幫忙駁回索賠的保險公司
How about insurance providers whose claims he helps deny?

127
00:04:47,060 --> 00:04:50,250
-別把他扯進來  -他一直這么干
- Don't bring him into this. - He's always been in this.

128
00:04:50,250 --> 00:04:51,990
我告訴你  我受夠了
You know what? I've had enough of this.

129
00:04:51,990 --> 00:04:54,850
我切斷電話線不是為了引起你的注意
I didn't really cut off your shit to get your attention.

130
00:04:54,850 --> 00:04:57,460
而是因為你再也不需要了
I cut it off because you don't need it anymore.

131
00:04:59,230 --> 00:05:00,440
你被炒了
You're fired.

132
00:05:01,490 --> 00:05:03,260
達比不會允許的
Darby would never allow that.

133
00:05:03,790 --> 00:05:06,360
愛德華·達比一小時前簽了你的解雇通知書
Edward Darby signed your pink slip an hour ago.

134
00:05:14,010 --> 00:05:17,010
人人影視
YYeTs.com

135
00:05:14,010 --> 00:05:17,010
原創翻譯  雙語字幕

136
00:05:14,010 --> 00:05:17,010
■

137
00:05:14,010 --> 00:05:17,010
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com

138
00:05:17,010 --> 00:05:22,010
 翻譯：愛卿遛小鳥  swears  Reginamoon  病貓珞小娘  小飯

139
00:05:17,010 --> 00:05:22,010
■

140
00:05:22,010 --> 00:05:27,010
時間軸：憑陵新月  aaaBao  六水  校對：油炸電風扇  swears

141
00:05:22,010 --> 00:05:27,010
■

142
00:05:27,010 --> 00:05:32,010
 翻譯：大簾看這里  小小   后期 & 特效：倉鼠sama     總監：swears

143
00:05:27,010 --> 00:05:32,010
■

144
00:05:38,670 --> 00:05:40,840
第三季 第八集

145
00:05:38,670 --> 00:05:40,840
訴 訟 雙 雄

146
00:05:45,510 --> 00:05:47,900
在奈杰爾指導的兩個月零五天又十三小時中
2 months 5 days and 13 hours under Nigel's tutelage

147
00:05:47,900 --> 00:05:49,500
你就這么點長進嗎
this is what you have to show for it?

148
00:05:49,610 --> 00:05:51,170
那可是二十多份動議書
That's over 20 motions.

149
00:05:51,180 --> 00:05:52,850
二十份狗屎
20 dog shits.

150
00:05:53,230 --> 00:05:54,470
你這是從格里森姆的小說里抄的嗎
Did you get this out of a Grisham novel?

151
00:05:53,230 --> 00:05:54,470
美國知名暢銷小說家

152
00:05:54,480 --> 00:05:55,590
這也太假了
Because that's fiction.

153
00:05:56,200 --> 00:05:57,340
而你
And you...

154
00:05:57,370 --> 00:05:59,570
我媽媽都能寫好這份動議書
My mother can get this motion thrown out.

155
00:05:59,740 --> 00:06:01,560
還有你  反正你兩天后也得走人
And you--well, you're gone anyway in two days.

156
00:06:01,570 --> 00:06:03,110
聽好了  大伙兒
Listen up, people.

157
00:06:03,110 --> 00:06:06,090
我檢查了我不在時你們的工作
I've reviewed your work in my absence.

158
00:06:06,150 --> 00:06:07,330
你們猜怎么著
And guess what.

159
00:06:07,930 --> 00:06:09,190
真可悲啊
It's pathetic.

160
00:06:09,670 --> 00:06:12,530
你們這些賤人全該雙膝跪下
Every stinking one of you should get down on your knees

161
00:06:12,530 --> 00:06:14,090
感謝上蒼和我
and thank god and me

162
00:06:14,090 --> 00:06:16,950
還能讓你們留在這家律所
for letting you continue to exist in our kingdoms.

163
00:06:19,840 --> 00:06:21,720
路易  火氣怎么那么大  怎么了
Louis, what was that about? What's going on?

164
00:06:21,720 --> 00:06:23,890
我在讓那些混蛋搞清楚誰才是老大
It was about me letting these assholes know who's in charge.

165
00:06:23,890 --> 00:06:25,370
他們都知道你是老大
They know you're in charge.

166
00:06:25,370 --> 00:06:27,950
-是他們推選的你  -他們推選我個屁
- They put you in charge. - They didn't put me in shit.

167
00:06:27,950 --> 00:06:30,040
我的人格被強奸時  他們就坐在那品頭論足
They sat there in judgment while my character got ripped apart,

168
00:06:30,040 --> 00:06:32,050
連想幫忙的念頭都沒有
and not one of them lifted a single finger to help.

169
00:06:32,050 --> 00:06:34,810
他們判你勝訴  他們選擇了你  而非奈杰爾
They ruled in your favor. They chose you over Nigel.

170
00:06:34,810 --> 00:06:37,930
不  因為他們我才失去了米卡度
No, they made me give up Mikado for them.

171
00:06:39,630 --> 00:06:43,580
你在把失去米卡度的怒火撒在他們身上
Okay, you're displacing your anger over Mikado onto them.

172
00:06:43,580 --> 00:06:45,790
這又不是他們的錯
They didn't put you in this position.

173
00:06:46,840 --> 00:06:48,070
這不公平
It's not fair.

174
00:06:48,720 --> 00:06:49,430
你說的對
You're right.

175
00:06:49,440 --> 00:06:51,010
這不是他們的錯
They didn't put me in this position,

176
00:06:52,340 --> 00:06:53,430
我知道這是誰的錯
But I know who did.

177
00:06:53,430 --> 00:06:54,770
該死的達比
Goddamn Darby.

178
00:06:54,770 --> 00:06:56,900
放出了他的狗  然后讓我們來擦屁股
Unleashes his dog, leaves us to clean up the mess.

179
00:06:56,900 --> 00:06:58,510
我們仍然可以在法庭上訊問馬里加
We can still go after Mariga in court.

180
00:06:58,520 --> 00:06:59,770
他為了自保而達成協議
I mean, he's an admitted murderer

181
00:06:59,770 --> 00:07:01,140
對謀殺供認不諱
who cut a deal to save his life.

182
00:07:01,140 --> 00:07:02,140
等一下
Wait a second.

183
00:07:02,190 --> 00:07:04,360
只有說出實情  協議才有效
That deal is only good if he's telling the truth.

184
00:07:04,360 --> 00:07:06,440
等他出庭了我們就沒法問出實情了
We can't go after him with the truth on the stand.

185
00:07:06,440 --> 00:07:09,530
或許吧  但我們可以在庭外訊問他
Maybe, but we can go after him with the truth not on the stand.

186
00:07:09,880 --> 00:07:11,630
卡梅倫必須得愿意聽
Cameron would have to be willing to listen.

187
00:07:11,630 --> 00:07:12,860
我負責說服他
Then I better get him to listen.

188
00:07:12,860 --> 00:07:14,250
那我去找馬里加
And I better go after Mariga.

189
00:07:14,260 --> 00:07:16,450
-換身行頭  -什么  為什么
- And change your clothes. - What? Why?

190
00:07:16,450 --> 00:07:18,610
如果他們在二十碼的范圍內發現一名律師
If they see a lawyer within 20 yards of that lobby,

191
00:07:18,610 --> 00:07:20,110
他們就會把那里封鎖掉
they'll lock the place down.

192
00:07:53,240 --> 00:07:54,490
你不是客房服務啊
Oh, you're not room service.

193
00:07:54,500 --> 00:07:56,580
不  我不是  但...
No, I'm not, but...

194
00:07:56,600 --> 00:07:58,540
我很想跟馬里加上校談談
I do need to talk to Colonel Mariga.

195
00:07:58,540 --> 00:08:01,380
我還很想不給我那出軌的前妻贍養費呢
And I need to stop paying alimony to my cheating ex-wife,

196
00:08:01,380 --> 00:08:02,680
但那是不可能的
but that's not going to happen.

197
00:08:02,680 --> 00:08:04,880
如果你讓我進去  我也許能幫你實現
If you let me in, maybe I can make that happen.

198
00:08:05,040 --> 00:08:07,200
你又怎么能辦到呢
And how the hell are you gonna make that happen?

199
00:08:07,200 --> 00:08:08,260
我是名律師
I'm a lawyer.

200
00:08:10,010 --> 00:08:11,390
你看上去可不像個律師
You don't look like a lawyer to me.

201
00:08:11,390 --> 00:08:12,900
好吧  被你識破了
Okay. All right. You got me.

202
00:08:12,900 --> 00:08:15,230
我不是律師
Look, I'm not-- I'm not a lawyer.

203
00:08:15,240 --> 00:08:17,650
別告訴別人  實際上  我是個冒牌的
In fact, between you and me, I'm a complete fraud.

204
00:08:17,650 --> 00:08:20,330
但我其實是馬里加上校的堂弟
But what I am is Colonel Mariga's cousin.

205
00:08:23,980 --> 00:08:25,110
他媽媽那邊的親戚
On his mother's side.

206
00:08:25,110 --> 00:08:26,030
-夠了  -好吧  好吧
- All right. - Okay, all right!

207
00:08:26,030 --> 00:08:27,430
你不相信我
All right, you don't believe me?

208
00:08:27,430 --> 00:08:29,700
那好  幫我一個忙  行嗎
That's fine. Just do me a favor, okay?

209
00:08:30,060 --> 00:08:32,520
我這有張他與我叔叔史蒂芬的合照
Give him this photo of him and my uncle Stephen.

210
00:08:35,420 --> 00:08:37,530
遞給他  讓他做決定
Then let him decide if he wants to talk to me.

211
00:08:39,730 --> 00:08:40,710
路易  你是怎么進來的
Louis, how did you get in here?

212
00:08:40,710 --> 00:08:41,710
我跟他們說我是你叔叔
I told them I was your uncle.

213
00:08:41,710 --> 00:08:42,750
不過我很納悶他們為何會相信
Though how they could believe that we share

214
00:08:42,750 --> 00:08:44,520
咱倆有著相同的遺傳基因
the same DNA is beyond me.

215
00:08:44,990 --> 00:08:46,500
是因為庭審的事吧
This is about your trial, isn't it?

216
00:08:46,500 --> 00:08:47,780
你說的太他媽對了
You're goddamn right it is!

217
00:08:47,790 --> 00:08:48,990
你他媽為什么要背叛我
Why the hell would you do that to me?

218
00:08:48,990 --> 00:08:50,590
我別無選擇  我收到傳票了
I had no choice. I was subpoenaed.

219
00:08:50,590 --> 00:08:53,820
那只是模擬法庭  你可以拒絕的
It was a mock trial. You could have refused.

220
00:08:53,820 --> 00:08:54,960
你到底想怎么樣  路易
What do you want from me, Louis?

221
00:08:54,960 --> 00:08:55,800
我想朝你吼
I want to yell at you!

222
00:08:55,800 --> 00:08:58,060
你再也不能朝我吼了  你把我炒了
Well, you can't do that anymore-- you fired me.

223
00:08:58,060 --> 00:08:59,450
這就是一切的緣由嗎
Is that what this whole thing was all about?

224
00:08:59,460 --> 00:09:01,660
你說的太他媽對了  你想知道真相嗎
You're damn right it was. And you want to know the truth?

225
00:09:01,660 --> 00:09:03,350
當我聽說了那場愚蠢的庭審
When I found out about your stupid trial,

226
00:09:03,350 --> 00:09:05,400
我打給奈杰爾主動請纓
I called Nigel and volunteered.

227
00:09:05,400 --> 00:09:06,520
你怎么敢
How dare you?

228
00:09:07,040 --> 00:09:09,020
我炒了你是公事公辦
Me firing you was business.

229
00:09:09,060 --> 00:09:10,940
你提起我的愛貓之死
You bringing up the death of my cat,

230
00:09:10,980 --> 00:09:12,140
完全是公報私仇
that was personal.

231
00:09:12,140 --> 00:09:14,270
你命令我照看你的蠢貓
You made me take care of that stupid cat.

232
00:09:14,270 --> 00:09:16,520
我對貓過敏  可能會害死我的
I'm allergic. It could have killed me.

233
00:09:16,520 --> 00:09:18,110
而且那只貓死掉的時候
And when that cat did die,

234
00:09:18,110 --> 00:09:20,400
你不僅沒對我說"這不是你的錯"
not only did you never tell me that it wasn't my fault,

235
00:09:20,400 --> 00:09:23,310
還當著我摯友的面  把我給炒了
you then fired me in front of my very best friend.

236
00:09:23,560 --> 00:09:26,070
難道這還不算公報私仇嗎
If that's not personal, then I don't know what is.

237
00:09:26,490 --> 00:09:28,530
立刻滾出我的辦公室
Now get the hell out of my office.

238
00:09:29,050 --> 00:09:30,020
我會的
I will.

239
00:09:31,890 --> 00:09:34,570
但在那之前
But before I do,

240
00:09:34,570 --> 00:09:36,710
我知道一些小秘密
I have some personal news for you

241
00:09:36,710 --> 00:09:40,200
能夠解開你被開除的真實經過
about how your firing really went down.

242
00:09:42,690 --> 00:09:46,300
我喜歡這張照片  我們當時剛剛贏得了冠軍
Ah, I love this. We'd just won the championship.

243
00:09:46,310 --> 00:09:47,460
能給我一張嗎
Might I get a copy?

244
00:09:47,460 --> 00:09:49,150
我會裝裱一份給你的
Yeah, I'll get one framed for you.

245
00:09:49,150 --> 00:09:50,370
在你受刑前的十分鐘
You can look at it in the ten minutes

246
00:09:50,370 --> 00:09:52,060
你可以一直看著它
before they put you to death.

247
00:09:52,670 --> 00:09:54,390
照片證明不了什么
The photograph proves nothing.

248
00:09:55,170 --> 00:09:57,610
相信我  我們還有很多類似的證據
Trust me, there's a whole lot more where that came from.

249
00:09:58,010 --> 00:10:00,450
你和史蒂芬的關系我們全都知道了
We know all about the ties between you and Stephen.

250
00:10:01,100 --> 00:10:02,320
那就呈到臺面上
Then bring them up.

251
00:10:02,320 --> 00:10:04,610
但我答應他要指證艾娃
But I made a deal to testify against Ava,

252
00:10:04,610 --> 00:10:05,910
這件事絲毫不會改變
and that is what I'm going to do.

253
00:10:05,920 --> 00:10:07,150
不  你答應的是要供出
No, you made a deal to put away

254
00:10:07,150 --> 00:10:09,220
指使殺人的幕后黑手
the person responsible for ordering these killings,

255
00:10:09,230 --> 00:10:11,700
我建議你能指證真兇  以免為時已晚
and I suggest you do that while you still can.

256
00:10:11,920 --> 00:10:13,060
年輕人...
Young man...

257
00:10:13,370 --> 00:10:15,650
如果你想讓我改變證言
if your intention is to shake my testimony,

258
00:10:15,650 --> 00:10:16,810
那是不可能發生的事
that is not going to happen.

259
00:10:16,810 --> 00:10:18,250
根本不需要發生
It doesn't need to happen,

260
00:10:18,680 --> 00:10:21,230
一旦我們證明你對艾娃的事撒謊
'cause once we prove that you're lying about Ava,

261
00:10:21,370 --> 00:10:23,140
卡梅隆·丹尼斯就會取消協議
Cameron Dennis is going to cancel your deal,

262
00:10:23,140 --> 00:10:25,680
而你就會向我乞求幫助
and you're gonna come to me begging for help.

263
00:10:28,610 --> 00:10:30,330
你以為你是我面對過的
Do you think you're the scariest man

264
00:10:30,330 --> 00:10:31,820
最可怕的對手嗎
I've ever sat across from?

265
00:10:32,030 --> 00:10:33,700
我知道你不怕我
I know you're not scared of me.

266
00:10:34,430 --> 00:10:36,300
但你應該怕自己人
But you are scared of your own people,

267
00:10:37,140 --> 00:10:38,330
你確實該害怕
and you should be,

268
00:10:39,070 --> 00:10:40,110
因為你我都清楚
because you and I both know

269
00:10:40,110 --> 00:10:42,490
你一回去他們就會殺掉你
they're gonna kill you the minute you get back.

270
00:10:42,850 --> 00:10:45,630
我認識史蒂芬不代表我對艾娃的事撒謊
That I know Stephen doesn't mean I'm lying about Ava.

271
00:10:45,630 --> 00:10:46,670
但你撒謊了
But you are.

272
00:10:46,670 --> 00:10:48,710
你能看穿我的靈魂
Ah, and you can see into my soul.

273
00:10:48,710 --> 00:10:50,840
不是算命師也能看出你在撒謊
It doesn't take a fortune teller to know you're lying.

274
00:10:50,840 --> 00:10:53,290
誰都能輕易猜出  如果你們有證據
And it doesn't take one to know that if you had proof,

275
00:10:53,290 --> 00:10:55,470
你就不會來找我了
you wouldn't be here talking to me.

276
00:10:57,780 --> 00:11:00,200
所以你并非是出于原則而保護史蒂芬
So you're not protecting Stephen out of principle.

277
00:11:00,200 --> 00:11:02,220
我不是個有原則的人
I'm not a man of principle.

278
00:11:02,280 --> 00:11:04,960
-我是個懂得權宜的人  -我懂了
- I'm a man of expediency. - I get it.

279
00:11:05,080 --> 00:11:07,640
如果你改了證詞  你現有的協議就會泡湯  
If you change your tune now, you'll lose the deal you have.

280
00:11:07,640 --> 00:11:11,520
因此  我寧愿  你會怎么說
Therefore, I prefer to-- how do you say it--

281
00:11:11,700 --> 00:11:13,570
忠于利我之人
dance with the one who brought me.

282
00:11:19,950 --> 00:11:21,230
哈維  你來這做什么
Harvey, what are you doing here?

283
00:11:21,230 --> 00:11:23,180
明天才開庭  我現在跟你無話可說
Game time's tomorrow. We got nothing to say.

284
00:11:23,180 --> 00:11:24,350
我是來幫你的
I'm here to help you.

285
00:11:24,590 --> 00:11:25,940
我不需要你的幫助
I don't need your help.

286
00:11:26,040 --> 00:11:28,370
除非你需要我的幫助  否則你不會在這兒
And you wouldn't be here unless you need mine.

287
00:11:28,370 --> 00:11:29,230
你錯了
You're wrong.

288
00:11:29,240 --> 00:11:31,630
我可以幫你達成你總掛在口上的理想
I can help you do what you always said you're all about--

289
00:11:31,630 --> 00:11:33,060
把壞人關起來
putting bad guys away.

290
00:11:33,560 --> 00:11:35,100
你要對我懺悔嗎
You got a confession for me?

291
00:11:35,100 --> 00:11:37,030
你找錯了人
You're going after the wrong person.

292
00:11:37,130 --> 00:11:38,790
你是她的律師  自然會這么說
You're her lawyer. That's what you would say.

293
00:11:38,790 --> 00:11:40,560
我現在并非以律師的身份說話
I'm not here as her lawyer.

294
00:11:40,580 --> 00:11:42,110
這不是說給陪審團聽的演講
This isn't a speech for a jury.

295
00:11:42,110 --> 00:11:44,790
我在跟我的老朋友進行一對一的談話
I'm here man-to-man to talk to the guy I used to know.

296
00:11:46,040 --> 00:11:46,850
好吧
All right.

297
00:11:46,980 --> 00:11:47,740
說吧
Talk.

298
00:11:47,960 --> 00:11:49,190
我知道到底是誰做的
I know who really did this.

299
00:11:49,920 --> 00:11:51,550
那就告訴我吧
Then tell me who it is.

300
00:11:51,650 --> 00:11:52,310
我要你保證
I need a guarantee

301
00:11:52,310 --> 00:11:54,270
你不會用我告訴你的事來攻擊艾娃
you won't use what I tell you against Ava.

302
00:11:54,270 --> 00:11:55,960
假如你認為我會向你保證
If you think I'm gonna guarantee you

303
00:11:55,960 --> 00:11:57,950
除了明天的決戰之外的任何事
anything but a war tomorrow,

304
00:11:57,960 --> 00:11:59,350
你就犯了個可悲的錯誤
You are sadly mistaken.

305
00:11:59,350 --> 00:12:00,560
我無法告訴你誰做了這件事
I can't tell you who did it,

306
00:12:00,560 --> 00:12:01,680
但是另外一個人可以
but somebody else can.

307
00:12:01,680 --> 00:12:02,580
誰
Who?

308
00:12:02,870 --> 00:12:04,220
馬里加上校
Colonel Mariga.

309
00:12:05,740 --> 00:12:06,920
你在逗我玩嗎
Are you kidding me?

310
00:12:07,660 --> 00:12:09,200
我已經找到了兇手
I've got the murder weapon.

311
00:12:09,380 --> 00:12:11,590
而他說是艾娃·海辛頓下令讓他殺人的
He says Ava Hessington pulled his trigger,

312
00:12:11,600 --> 00:12:13,680
但你卻想要我讓他改供詞
and you want me to have him change his story?

313
00:12:13,680 --> 00:12:14,760
他指正艾娃的唯一原因是
He's only pointing at Ava

314
00:12:14,760 --> 00:12:16,130
你想聽他這么說
because that's what you want to hear.

315
00:12:16,140 --> 00:12:17,030
改下你和他的協議
Change his deal,

316
00:12:17,030 --> 00:12:18,260
他就會告訴你真相了
he'll tell you the truth.

317
00:12:18,260 --> 00:12:20,110
假如他現在改了自己的供詞
He changes his story now,

318
00:12:20,110 --> 00:12:20,790
那么他所說的
anything he says

319
00:12:20,790 --> 00:12:22,490
關于任何人的任何事都相當于放屁
about anybody means shit.

320
00:12:22,490 --> 00:12:23,610
在法庭上是放屁
It means shit in court,

321
00:12:23,610 --> 00:12:25,100
但是假如你是你自稱的那種人
but if you are who you say you are,

322
00:12:25,110 --> 00:12:26,830
那么那些對你而言就應該有意義
it should mean something to you.

323
00:12:27,550 --> 00:12:28,830
你知道嗎  哈維
You know what, Harvey?

324
00:12:29,260 --> 00:12:31,390
我相信你認為她是無辜的
I believe that you believe she's innocent,

325
00:12:31,390 --> 00:12:32,790
并且假如你能說服我
and if you can convince me of that,

326
00:12:32,790 --> 00:12:33,710
我就不會盯著她不放了
I won't go after her,

327
00:12:34,010 --> 00:12:35,250
但是在我聽到之前
but I'm not gonna guarantee

328
00:12:35,250 --> 00:12:37,190
我不能保證我不會利用你告訴我的事情
I won't use what you say before I hear it.

329
00:12:37,190 --> 00:12:38,380
你想要我就這樣相信你
You want me to just trust you?

330
00:12:38,380 --> 00:12:39,930
那正是你對我提出的要求
That's what you're asking me.

331
00:12:39,930 --> 00:12:40,520
但假如你認為
But if you think

332
00:12:40,520 --> 00:12:44,470
我會在庭審的前一天打我星級證人的嘴巴
that I'm gonna kneecap my star witness the day before the trial,

333
00:12:45,100 --> 00:12:46,310
那你就是瘋了
you are out of your mind.

334
00:12:50,690 --> 00:12:52,080
哈羅德  最近如何啊兄弟
Harold, what's up, man?

335
00:12:52,080 --> 00:12:53,010
見到你真開心
It's good to see you.

336
00:12:53,010 --> 00:12:54,770
我還以為你是我朋友呢
I thought you were my friend.

337
00:12:55,420 --> 00:12:56,390
我是啊  怎么回事
I am. What the hell?

338
00:12:56,390 --> 00:12:58,480
朋友才不會一邊說自己試圖幫你保住工作
Friends don't say they tried to save your job

339
00:12:58,480 --> 00:13:00,670
實際上卻把你坑慘了
when, really, they hung you out to dry.

340
00:13:01,360 --> 00:13:02,560
這么說來這是真的了
So it's true.

341
00:13:02,660 --> 00:13:04,000
哈羅德  我不是故意
Look, Harold, I didn't mean to--

342
00:13:04,000 --> 00:13:05,900
省省你的狗屁解釋吧
You know what? Save whatever bullshit explanation you have,

343
00:13:05,900 --> 00:13:07,060
因為我不想聽
because I don't want to hear it.

344
00:13:07,060 --> 00:13:08,160
我沒想著要給你什么狗屁解釋
I'm not trying to give you a bullshit explanation.

345
00:13:08,160 --> 00:13:09,750
因為你沒得解釋
Because there is none.

346
00:13:09,750 --> 00:13:11,620
你得在你我之間做一個選擇
You got to choose between you and me,

347
00:13:11,620 --> 00:13:13,080
然后你選了你自己
And you chose yourself.

348
00:13:13,080 --> 00:13:14,320
然后就此你還對我撒謊了
And then you lied to me about it.

349
00:13:14,320 --> 00:13:15,760
是的  哈羅德  我是這么做了
Yes, yes, Harold, I did.

350
00:13:15,760 --> 00:13:16,860
但是在我向你撒謊之后
And then after I lied to you,

351
00:13:16,860 --> 00:13:19,690
我幫你在一家有權有勢的律所找了份工作
I got you a job at a huge, powerful firm.

352
00:13:19,690 --> 00:13:20,670
是啊  你幫我找了份工作
Yeah, you got me that job

353
00:13:20,670 --> 00:13:22,230
所以我到時就會欠你個人情
so I'd owe you one when the time came.

354
00:13:22,230 --> 00:13:22,990
我幫你找了份工作
I got you that job

355
00:13:23,000 --> 00:13:25,120
是因為我覺得你理應擁有第二次機會
because I thought you deserved a second chance.

356
00:13:25,120 --> 00:13:26,220
然后你又打電話找我
And then you came calling

357
00:13:26,220 --> 00:13:27,690
在你需要提交一份訴訟
when you needed a lawsuit filed

358
00:13:27,690 --> 00:13:29,930
來擺脫你謀殺案庭審上的證人的時候
to get rid of your witnesses in your murder trial.

359
00:13:29,930 --> 00:13:31,170
我在那起訴訟上信任你
I trusted you with that lawsuit

360
00:13:31,170 --> 00:13:32,870
是因為我覺得你是一個誠摯的律師
because I thought you were a competent attorney.

361
00:13:32,880 --> 00:13:34,800
而且你當時很高興的接受了
And you were more than happy to take it.

362
00:13:35,270 --> 00:13:37,500
而你剛剛說到的那個庭審馬上就要開始了
And that murder trial you just mentioned is about to start.

363
00:13:37,500 --> 00:13:39,980
所以你可以選擇對我發脾氣或放眼向前
So you can choose to be pissed off with me or move on.

364
00:13:39,990 --> 00:13:42,180
但現在  我還有工作要做
But right now I have a job to do.

365
00:13:48,510 --> 00:13:50,540
-瑞秋  -路易  你干了什么
- Rachel. - Louis, what did you do?

366
00:13:50,580 --> 00:13:52,140
你什么意思  這是什么
What do you mean? What is this?

367
00:13:52,210 --> 00:13:53,930
費爾菲爾德電腦公司被起訴了
Fairfield Computers is being sued.

368
00:13:53,930 --> 00:13:54,580
這怎么成了我的錯
How's that my fault?

369
00:13:54,580 --> 00:13:55,480
因為他們是你的客戶
Because they're your client,

370
00:13:55,480 --> 00:13:57,660
然后記錄上寫的律師是哈羅德·甘德森
and the attorney of record is Harold Gunderson.

371
00:13:57,660 --> 00:13:59,400
他同時還提供了一份和解協議
He also sent a settlement offer.

372
00:14:00,730 --> 00:14:02,300
他想和我干一架
He wants to pick a fight with me.

373
00:14:02,860 --> 00:14:04,430
他會后悔自己出生在這個世上
He's gonna regret the day he was born.

374
00:14:04,440 --> 00:14:06,030
難道不是你找他干了一架嗎
Aren't you the one who picked a fight with him?

375
00:14:06,030 --> 00:14:07,720
瑞秋  你是哪一邊的
Rachel, whose side are you on?

376
00:14:08,320 --> 00:14:09,330
別回答這個問題
Don't answer that question.

377
00:14:13,190 --> 00:14:14,340
你不應該在這兒
You shouldn't be here.

378
00:14:14,880 --> 00:14:17,390
斯蒂芬說過我們和他沒什么不同
Stephen said that we're no different than he is.

379
00:14:18,550 --> 00:14:20,160
我要看著你證明他錯了
I need to see you show him that he's wrong.

380
00:14:20,160 --> 00:14:22,230
這不是他的庭審  這是艾娃的
This isn't his trial. It's Ava's.

381
00:14:22,520 --> 00:14:24,140
你不打算讓他出庭作證
You're not gonna put him on the stand?

382
00:14:24,140 --> 00:14:25,820
你說過你會讓他付出代價的
You said you were gonna make him pay.

383
00:14:25,830 --> 00:14:28,150
唐娜  我會的  但現在不是好時機
Donna, I will, but now is not the time.

384
00:14:28,160 --> 00:14:29,110
那什么時候才是
Then when?

385
00:14:29,110 --> 00:14:30,610
因為他可是殺了人啊
Because he killed people,

386
00:14:30,620 --> 00:14:32,380
假如我們讓他逃脫了
and if we let him get away with it...

387
00:14:33,780 --> 00:14:35,460
那么說不定我們和他是沒有什么不同了
then maybe we are no different than he is.

388
00:14:37,090 --> 00:14:38,910
假如以這些造反者的方式
Had these insurgents had their way,

389
00:14:39,280 --> 00:14:41,240
他們會炸掉油管的
they would have blown up the pipeline.

390
00:14:41,560 --> 00:14:44,290
相反  海辛頓女士則保住了大量的資產
Instead, Ms. Hessington retained a valuable asset,

391
00:14:44,530 --> 00:14:47,380
而我  也因為做好自己的工作而受補償
and I, in turn, was compensated for a job well done.

392
00:14:47,380 --> 00:14:50,990
這個補償是直接來自艾娃·海辛頓嗎
And this compensation came directly from Ava Hessington?

393
00:14:51,430 --> 00:14:52,370
是的
Yes.

394
00:14:52,420 --> 00:14:55,060
她明確地指示你要你去殺人
She specifically directed you to kill people?

395
00:14:56,690 --> 00:14:57,660
是的
Yes.

396
00:14:58,070 --> 00:14:59,860
還有一件事  馬里加上校
One more thing, Colonel Mariga--

397
00:14:59,860 --> 00:15:00,840
我和你有做交易
Do you and I have a deal

398
00:15:00,840 --> 00:15:04,400
讓你出庭作證以換取寬大處理嗎
for you to testify in exchange for a more lenient sentence?

399
00:15:05,130 --> 00:15:05,770
有的
Yes.

400
00:15:05,770 --> 00:15:07,260
那么陪審團為什么要相信
And why should the jury believe

401
00:15:07,260 --> 00:15:09,450
你不是為了救自己一命而在此胡編亂造呢
that you aren't making this up to save yourself?

402
00:15:09,450 --> 00:15:12,170
因為假如我對你說的東西被證明是謊言
Because if what I say to you proves to be a lie,

403
00:15:12,750 --> 00:15:14,270
你就會把我送回家
you'll send me back home,

404
00:15:14,340 --> 00:15:16,190
在那里我馬上就會被殺
where I will be dead within minutes.

405
00:15:17,550 --> 00:15:18,790
沒有別的問題了
No further questions.

406
00:15:23,080 --> 00:15:24,420
休庭十分鐘
Ten minutes recess.

407
00:15:24,670 --> 00:15:26,340
你為什么不立刻反擊
Why didn't you just jump right in there?

408
00:15:26,340 --> 00:15:27,820
我懂了  你讀了一本書
I get it-- you read a book

409
00:15:27,820 --> 00:15:29,920
上面說你不能讓陪審團安于現狀地坐著
that says you don't let the jury sit with things.

410
00:15:29,920 --> 00:15:30,900
唯一的問題是
The only problem is...

411
00:15:30,900 --> 00:15:32,060
我們不能紙上談兵
we're not inside of a book.

412
00:15:32,060 --> 00:15:33,410
并且我不想看上去被動
And I don't want to seem defensive.

413
00:15:33,420 --> 00:15:35,490
哈維  我們還有一堆料可以用來打擊他
Harvey, we still have a ton of shit to hit him with.

414
00:15:35,490 --> 00:15:36,290
你剛剛在里面嗎
Were you in there?

415
00:15:36,290 --> 00:15:37,670
他們對他說的話很買賬
They're buying what he saying.

416
00:15:37,670 --> 00:15:39,320
那我們就讓他們對其他的事情買賬
Then we make them buy something else.

417
00:15:39,320 --> 00:15:40,500
我們手中有一對A
We got a pair of aces.

418
00:15:40,510 --> 00:15:42,610
假如陪審團相信卡梅隆有三條三
If the jury believes that Cameron's got three of a kind,

419
00:15:42,610 --> 00:15:43,470
我們就贏不了了
we're not gonna win.

420
00:15:43,470 --> 00:15:44,830
我們不能盯著斯蒂芬
We can't go after Stephen.

421
00:15:44,830 --> 00:15:46,260
卡梅隆不會盯著艾娃
Cameron won't go after Ava

422
00:15:46,260 --> 00:15:47,770
假如我能說服他斯蒂芬是兇手
if I can convince him it was Stephen.

423
00:15:47,780 --> 00:15:49,310
-你去找了卡梅隆  -是的
- You went to Cameron? - Yes.

424
00:15:49,570 --> 00:15:50,780
而且你還打算相信他
And you're going to trust him?

425
00:15:50,780 --> 00:15:52,540
我不確定我們是否還有別的選擇
I'm not sure we have another choice.

426
00:15:56,360 --> 00:15:58,240
假如你們在想我認為你們在想的事
If you're thinking what I think you're thinking,

427
00:15:58,330 --> 00:15:59,010
別想了
don't.

428
00:15:59,010 --> 00:16:01,220
我在想我很樂意把你的臉撕下來
I'm thinking I'd like to rip your face off.

429
00:16:01,370 --> 00:16:02,960
你讓馬里加指證我的話
You get Mariga to point the finger at me,

430
00:16:02,970 --> 00:16:04,970
我會直接指證艾娃
I will point it straight at Ava.

431
00:16:04,970 --> 00:16:07,790
斯蒂芬  杰西卡可不會乖乖地被威脅
Stephen, Jessica doesn't respond well to threats.

432
00:16:07,800 --> 00:16:09,310
我不威脅人
Well, I don't make threats.

433
00:16:09,390 --> 00:16:10,670
我只是給予警告
I give warnings.

434
00:16:11,480 --> 00:16:12,730
你們被警告了
You've been warned.

435
00:16:19,590 --> 00:16:20,680
斯佩克特先生
Mr. Specter...

436
00:16:21,870 --> 00:16:24,380
我沒問題要問馬里加上校了  法官大人
I have no questions for Colonel Mariga, Your Honor,

437
00:16:24,380 --> 00:16:26,350
但我想傳喚一名反駁證人
but I'd like to call a rebuttal witness.

438
00:16:26,470 --> 00:16:28,130
哈維  拜托  你知道他會說什么的
Harvey, come on, you know what he's gonna say.

439
00:16:28,130 --> 00:16:29,360
我不在乎他要說什么
I don't care what he's gonna say.

440
00:16:29,360 --> 00:16:32,100
他對陪審團說  我對卡梅隆·丹尼斯說
He's talking to the jury. I'm talking to Cameron Dennis.

441
00:16:32,360 --> 00:16:35,120
辯方傳喚史蒂芬·亨特利作證
The defense calls Stephen Huntley to the stand.

442
00:16:36,090 --> 00:16:39,030
斯蒂芬和這件事有什么關系
What has Stephen Huntley got to do with this?

443
00:16:39,030 --> 00:16:40,410
哈維知道他做了什么
Harvey knows what he's doing.

444
00:16:40,410 --> 00:16:41,770
這就是你想供給我的
This is what you wanted to sell me--

445
00:16:41,770 --> 00:16:43,530
一個你自己律所的律師
a lawyer from your own goddamn firm?

446
00:16:43,530 --> 00:16:44,670
你想把壞人繩之以法
You want to put away the bad guy?

447
00:16:44,670 --> 00:16:46,690
我馬上就要把他打包好交給你了
I'm about to hand him to you on a silver platter.

448
00:16:47,380 --> 00:16:48,160
亨特利先生
Mr. Huntley,

449
00:16:48,560 --> 00:16:52,780
你去年是在愛德華·達比的律所工作嗎
did you work at the law firm headed by Edward Darby last year?

450
00:16:53,760 --> 00:16:54,490
是的
Yes.

451
00:16:54,490 --> 00:16:58,240
達比先生有沒有讓你去解決海辛頓石油
Did Mr. Darby ask you to solve any problems for Hessington Oil

452
00:16:58,240 --> 00:17:00,400
在環境影響報告中的管道問題
regarding their pipeline in the E.I.R.?

453
00:17:00,400 --> 00:17:03,050
根據第五修正案的權利  我拒絕回答
I decline to answer under my Fifth Amendment rights.

454
00:17:03,250 --> 00:17:05,310
反對自我控告的權利
The right against self-incrimination.

455
00:17:05,360 --> 00:17:06,900
你認識馬里加上校多久了
How long have you known Colonel Mariga?

456
00:17:06,900 --> 00:17:08,050
我拒絕回答
I decline to answer.

457
00:17:08,050 --> 00:17:09,640
你曾經和他在開普敦大學一起念書
Is it true that you went to school with him

458
00:17:09,640 --> 00:17:11,040
這是真的嗎
at the University of Cape Town?

459
00:17:11,040 --> 00:17:12,260
我拒絕回答
I decline to answer.

460
00:17:12,270 --> 00:17:13,700
讓我幫你回憶一下
Well, let me refresh your memory.

461
00:17:13,700 --> 00:17:15,430
你們曾是橄欖球隊的隊友
You were teammates on a championship rugby team.

462
00:17:15,430 --> 00:17:17,410
反對  律師在自己作證
Objection. Counsel is testifying.

463
00:17:17,410 --> 00:17:18,960
證人對我心懷敵意  法官大人
The witness is hostile, your honor.

464
00:17:18,960 --> 00:17:21,150
敵意  他們在同一家事務所工作
Hostile? They work at the same law firm.

465
00:17:21,150 --> 00:17:22,810
他昨天被解雇了
He was fired yesterday.

466
00:17:22,810 --> 00:17:24,600
先生們  過來一下
Gentlemen, approach.

467
00:17:27,290 --> 00:17:29,490
他在捏造事實混淆視聽
He's making things up to create reasonable doubt.

468
00:17:29,490 --> 00:17:32,180
我在提出事實  這樣你就能看到真相
I'm bringing things up, so you'll see the truth.

469
00:17:32,180 --> 00:17:34,830
涉及到艾娃的只有馬里加的證詞
The only thing tying Ava to this is Mariga's testimony.

470
00:17:34,830 --> 00:17:37,250
你找到馬里加是因為竊聽史蒂芬的電話
You only have Mariga because you tapped Stephen's phone.

471
00:17:37,250 --> 00:17:38,400
這是個荒唐的控訴
That's a ridiculous accusation.

472
00:17:38,410 --> 00:17:40,060
卡梅隆  拜托
Cameron, please.

473
00:17:40,350 --> 00:17:42,890
他為什么打給他  他是怎么打給他的
Why did he call him? How did he call him?

474
00:17:42,890 --> 00:17:43,880
夠了
Enough.

475
00:17:44,710 --> 00:17:46,580
你被束縛了  斯佩克特先生
You're on a short leash, Mr. Specter.

476
00:17:46,580 --> 00:17:48,580
那位先生有他的權利
The gentleman invoked his rights.

477
00:17:53,530 --> 00:17:56,130
亨特利先生  你有沒有
Mr. Huntley, did you meet with your old friend

478
00:17:56,130 --> 00:17:58,880
在艾娃·海辛頓毫不知情的情況下
Emmanuel Mariga and direct him

479
00:17:58,880 --> 00:18:01,800
和你的老朋友伊曼紐爾·馬里加見面
to kill the opponent of Hessington Oil's pipeline

480
00:18:01,800 --> 00:18:04,000
并讓他殺了反對海辛頓石油鋪設管道的人
without Ava Hessington's knowledge?

481
00:18:04,660 --> 00:18:06,180
我拒絕回答
I decline to answer.

482
00:18:08,070 --> 00:18:09,650
我沒有問題了
I have no further questions.

483
00:18:09,820 --> 00:18:11,700
丹尼斯先生  你有問題嗎
Mr. Dennis, do you have any questions?

484
00:18:13,460 --> 00:18:14,720
丹尼斯先生
Mr. Dennis.

485
00:18:21,550 --> 00:18:23,600
亨特利先生  直到你被解雇之前
Mr. Huntley, until you were let go,

486
00:18:23,600 --> 00:18:26,960
你和斯佩克特先生在同一家公司工作對嗎
you worked at the same firm as Mr. Specter, correct?

487
00:18:26,990 --> 00:18:27,870
是的
Yes.

488
00:18:28,930 --> 00:18:31,190
而他今天的工作是讓陪審團
And his job today is to give this jury

489
00:18:31,200 --> 00:18:34,480
認為他的客戶不是殺人犯
cause to doubt that his client is the murderer?

490
00:18:35,440 --> 00:18:37,160
-是的  -根據你的經驗
- Yes. - In your experience...

491
00:18:37,170 --> 00:18:39,480
針對另外的某個人是個
Is pointing the finger at someone else

492
00:18:40,190 --> 00:18:41,540
好策略嗎
a good strategy?

493
00:18:41,970 --> 00:18:43,750
那會是個很好的策略
It can be an excellent strategy.

494
00:18:44,720 --> 00:18:46,550
那么你認為斯佩克特先生
And why do you think that Mr. Specter

495
00:18:46,560 --> 00:18:48,270
為什么會針對你
is pointing the finger at you?

496
00:18:48,270 --> 00:18:50,360
也許是因為幾周前
Well, maybe it has something to do with the fact

497
00:18:50,360 --> 00:18:53,190
海辛頓女士找到我
that a few weeks ago Ms. Hessington approached me

498
00:18:53,190 --> 00:18:54,260
要我去賄賂
and asked me to bribe witnesses

499
00:18:54,260 --> 00:18:56,570
那些要指證她的目擊者
who were about to testify against her,

500
00:18:56,570 --> 00:18:57,790
而我拒絕了她
and I refused.

501
00:18:57,790 --> 00:18:59,580
如果你覺得我在宣誓后撒謊
And if you think I'm lying under oath,

502
00:18:59,580 --> 00:19:02,300
那請去問問斯佩克特先生
then, please, ask Mr. Specter.

503
00:19:02,470 --> 00:19:03,950
他知道那是事實
He knows that's the truth.

504
00:19:04,180 --> 00:19:06,900
而一個賄賂指證她的目擊者的女人
And a woman who bribes witnesses against her

505
00:19:06,900 --> 00:19:07,960
不會是無辜的
is not innocent.

506
00:19:08,150 --> 00:19:08,810
反對
Objection.

507
00:19:08,810 --> 00:19:10,720
撤回  最后一件事
Withdrawn. One last thing.

508
00:19:11,120 --> 00:19:14,220
被告有沒有讓你安排
Did the defendant ask you to arrange a meeting

509
00:19:14,220 --> 00:19:16,500
跟馬里加上校的會面
with Colonel Mariga where she she would pay him

510
00:19:16,510 --> 00:19:19,510
以便她用幾百萬美元讓他
millions of dollars in exchange for...

511
00:19:20,120 --> 00:19:21,920
殺害那些反對她鋪設管道的人
killing opponents of her pipeline?

512
00:19:22,020 --> 00:19:23,340
我拒絕回答
I decline to answer.

513
00:19:24,400 --> 00:19:25,870
我努力了
Can't blame a guy for trying.

514
00:19:27,300 --> 00:19:28,470
沒有問題了
No further questions.

515
00:19:37,300 --> 00:19:40,110
史蒂芬·亨特利跟他剛才
Is Stephen Huntley involved in all this

516
00:19:40,110 --> 00:19:43,160
跟陪審團說的那些破事真有關系嗎
some kind of stunt like he just told the jury it was?

517
00:19:49,640 --> 00:19:51,230
是他下令殺人的
He ordered the killings.

518
00:19:51,420 --> 00:19:54,420
-你們為什么沒告訴我  -我們沒有證據
- Why didn't you tell me? - We didn't have proof.

519
00:19:54,420 --> 00:19:57,070
你們為什么要讓他坐上證人席
Why would you put that man on the stand?

520
00:19:57,070 --> 00:19:58,910
那是計算過的風險
It was a calculated risk.

521
00:19:59,690 --> 00:20:03,140
你們用我的人生冒險卻沒有告訴我
You took a calculated risk with my life without telling me.

522
00:20:05,290 --> 00:20:06,310
對不起
I'm sorry.

523
00:20:16,190 --> 00:20:17,490
你騙了我
You screwed me.

524
00:20:18,620 --> 00:20:20,040
我說過如果你讓我信服我就
I said I wouldn't go after her

525
00:20:20,040 --> 00:20:21,820
放過她  你沒有讓我信服
if you convinced me. You didn't convince me.

526
00:20:21,820 --> 00:20:24,360
然后就申請休庭而不是歪曲他的話
Then take a recess instead of twisting everything he said.

527
00:20:24,360 --> 00:20:26,410
我不會讓陪審團坐在那兒聽他廢話
I'm not gonna let the jury sit with that shit.

528
00:20:26,410 --> 00:20:27,850
謝天謝地我也沒有那么做
And thank God I didn't.

529
00:20:28,100 --> 00:20:29,340
另外  我可能已經發現了
Otherwise, I would have found out

530
00:20:29,340 --> 00:20:31,580
她試圖賄賂目擊者
that she tried to bribe witnesses

531
00:20:31,580 --> 00:20:32,680
而你沒有告訴我
and you kept it from me.

532
00:20:32,680 --> 00:20:34,330
那跟謀殺沒有任何關系
It had nothing to do with the murders.

533
00:20:34,330 --> 00:20:36,130
真有意思  當我瞞著你那些
That's funny-- when I kept things from you

534
00:20:36,130 --> 00:20:37,380
跟其他謀殺案沒有任何關系的事時
that had nothing to do with other murders,

535
00:20:37,380 --> 00:20:38,190
你說我是罪人
you called me a criminal.

536
00:20:38,190 --> 00:20:39,320
但那次的結果是
Well, that ended up with you

537
00:20:39,320 --> 00:20:41,030
你把一個無辜的人送進了監獄
putting an innocent person in prison.

538
00:20:41,030 --> 00:20:42,550
現在你要重蹈覆轍
And now you're doing it again.

539
00:20:42,550 --> 00:20:43,760
別跟我胡扯
Oh, don't give me that shit.

540
00:20:43,760 --> 00:20:46,090
史蒂芬·亨特利參與了這件事
Stephen Huntley is up to his goddamn neck in this,

541
00:20:46,090 --> 00:20:47,220
你知道的
and you know it.

542
00:20:47,540 --> 00:20:50,370
他就那么背著他的客戶殺掉
So he just goes around killing his clients' enemies

543
00:20:50,370 --> 00:20:51,740
他們的敵人嗎
behind their backs?

544
00:20:51,740 --> 00:20:52,690
我不這么認為
I don't think so.

545
00:20:52,690 --> 00:20:55,040
你想要證明嗎  去問馬里加
You want corroboration? Ask Mariga.

546
00:20:55,040 --> 00:20:56,120
我剛剛問過
I just did.

547
00:20:56,430 --> 00:20:58,410
他在法庭上回答了我
And he answered me in open court.

548
00:20:58,410 --> 00:21:00,200
我不是在把一個無辜的女人送進監獄
And I'm not putting an innocent woman away.

549
00:21:00,200 --> 00:21:01,470
-我在履行我的職責  -卡梅隆
- I'm doing my job. - Cameron...

550
00:21:01,470 --> 00:21:03,360
律師殺人
Lawyers killing people?

551
00:21:04,130 --> 00:21:06,490
那就是掛著你名字的好公司  哈維
That's a hell of a firm you got your name on, Harvey.

552
00:21:07,300 --> 00:21:09,860
你離開檢察官辦公室去那里一定非常自豪
You must be proud to have left the D.A.'s office for that.

553
00:21:13,940 --> 00:21:15,710
一起打球吧  詹姆斯
Let's do racquetball, James.

554
00:21:16,540 --> 00:21:18,380
又來了  路易  你應該
Again? Louis, you were supposed to be waiting

555
00:21:18,380 --> 00:21:19,580
-在會議室等著  -我從不等人
- in the conference... - I don't wait for anyone.

556
00:21:19,580 --> 00:21:20,830
而且你不能告我
And you don't sue me.

557
00:21:21,050 --> 00:21:22,580
我可以
Yes, I do.

558
00:21:22,810 --> 00:21:25,150
因為我意識到我現在在一家大公司工作
Because I realized I now work at a huge firm,

559
00:21:25,150 --> 00:21:26,990
而且我有能力這么對你
and I have the power to do this to you.

560
00:21:26,990 --> 00:21:28,490
現在我們可以協商和解
Now, we can negotiate a settlement,

561
00:21:28,490 --> 00:21:30,760
當然  除非你覺得你沒法解決我
unless, of course, you don't think you can handle me.

562
00:21:30,760 --> 00:21:31,810
你真的想在你媽媽的注視下
Do you really want to embarrass yourself

563
00:21:31,810 --> 00:21:33,020
讓自己尷尬嗎
with your mother watching?

564
00:21:33,870 --> 00:21:35,680
他們不像你一樣禁止我們把母親的照片
It kills you that they don't ban us having pictures

565
00:21:35,680 --> 00:21:37,480
擺在這兒  這讓你很難受對嗎
of our mothers, like you did, doesn't it?

566
00:21:37,480 --> 00:21:39,660
人們會以一個人擺的照片來評價他
A man is judged by the photos he displays.

567
00:21:39,850 --> 00:21:41,380
你有一張自己的照片
You have a photo of yourself.

568
00:21:41,380 --> 00:21:42,960
現在你在證明我的觀點
And now you're making my point for me.

569
00:21:44,780 --> 00:21:47,150
你不能再威脅我了  路易
You don't intimidate me anymore, Louis.

570
00:21:47,160 --> 00:21:49,600
真的嗎  我了解你  哈羅德
Really? I know you, Harold.

571
00:21:50,380 --> 00:21:53,600
我知道你在參加讓你緊張的會面前會漱口
I know that you gargle before meetings that make you nervous.

572
00:21:54,390 --> 00:21:58,270
而且我  聞到了  薄荷味
And I...smell...mint.

573
00:21:58,740 --> 00:22:01,210
-我  -我們不同意第三段
-I... - We don't agree to paragraph three

574
00:22:01,210 --> 00:22:02,320
-和第四段  -我需要第四段
- or four. - I need to have four.

575
00:22:02,320 --> 00:22:03,590
還有第七段到第十段
Or seven through ten.

576
00:22:03,590 --> 00:22:06,150
我媽  我的客戶不會同意的
My mo--my client won't stand for that.

577
00:22:06,150 --> 00:22:08,950
你的客戶會同意我給他們的任何東西
Your client will stand for whatever the hell I give them!

578
00:22:10,390 --> 00:22:11,970
拜托  我能留著第九段嗎
Please, can I have nine?

579
00:22:18,660 --> 00:22:19,920
你知道嗎  我會給你第九段
You know what? I'll give you nine...

580
00:22:20,510 --> 00:22:21,690
因為它毫無意義
Because it's meaningless,

581
00:22:21,700 --> 00:22:22,850
然后我會讓它
and I want it to tell all the other paragraphs

582
00:22:22,860 --> 00:22:24,210
告訴剩下的幾段
out there what happens

583
00:22:24,210 --> 00:22:26,240
在你和我談判的時候發生了什么
when Harold Gunderson goes after Louis Litt.

584
00:22:26,980 --> 00:22:28,330
那沒有任何意義啊
That doesn't make any sense.

585
00:22:28,330 --> 00:22:29,460
你沒看過暴力電影嗎
Haven't you ever seen a mob movie?

586
00:22:29,460 --> 00:22:30,900
他們總會留個活口去告訴其他人
They always let one survive to tell the others.

587
00:22:30,900 --> 00:22:32,490
是的  可是段落不會說話
Well, yeah, but paragraphs can't talk--

588
00:22:32,490 --> 00:22:35,090
好吧  隨便吧  趕緊把這協議打出來
Okay, whatever. Fine. Just type this up as agreed,

589
00:22:35,250 --> 00:22:37,510
然后再也別讓我看見你那張蒼白的
and don't you ever let me see your pasty, Norwegian,

590
00:22:37,510 --> 00:22:39,210
自以為是的挪威臉
carrot top-wannabe face again.

591
00:22:42,060 --> 00:22:44,360
卡羅特·托普是被嚴重低估的喜劇演員
Carrot Top is a very underrated comedian

592
00:22:44,360 --> 00:22:45,900
向來人畜無害
who's never done anything to anyone.

593
00:22:48,610 --> 00:22:51,570
你知道哈維打算在庭上伏擊史蒂芬嗎
Did you know that Harvey was going to ambush Stephen on the stand?

594
00:22:51,580 --> 00:22:53,360
就算知道我也不會阻止他
I wouldn't have stopped him if I did.

595
00:22:53,400 --> 00:22:55,180
你就沒考慮過后果嗎
And to hell with the ramifications?

596
00:22:55,180 --> 00:22:57,550
會對誰產生后果  愛德華
The ramifications for who, Edward?

597
00:22:57,550 --> 00:22:59,770
我不是來跟你吵架的  杰西卡
I didn't come here to fight with you, Jessica.

598
00:22:59,770 --> 00:23:02,200
但現在的箭靶子不是史蒂芬
But Stephen didn't take the most direct hit.

599
00:23:02,200 --> 00:23:03,180
而是艾娃
Ava did.

600
00:23:03,180 --> 00:23:05,690
你總說你有多關心艾娃
You keep talking about how much you care about Ava.

601
00:23:05,760 --> 00:23:07,110
但我跟她只是萍水相逢
But I've only just met her.

602
00:23:07,110 --> 00:23:08,910
再說事都是你干的
And you're the one who did what you did.

603
00:23:13,950 --> 00:23:16,760
我把你當作我的手足
I treated you as if you were my own blood.

604
00:23:16,760 --> 00:23:17,610
艾娃
Ava...

605
00:23:18,310 --> 00:23:19,690
是你做的嗎
Did you do this to me?

606
00:23:19,690 --> 00:23:21,040
當然不是
Of course I didn't.

607
00:23:21,050 --> 00:23:23,130
是你一直在瞞著我嗎
Did you keep this from me?

608
00:23:24,900 --> 00:23:26,740
我要聽你親口說出來
I want to hear you say it.

609
00:23:28,650 --> 00:23:30,760
我知道的時候已經晚了
I didn't know until it was too late.

610
00:23:33,880 --> 00:23:36,080
輸油管道的事木已成舟
I didn't want to burden you with what had been done

611
00:23:36,080 --> 00:23:37,580
我不想給你增加負擔
to get your pipeline,

612
00:23:37,800 --> 00:23:40,210
而且覆水難收  我無計可施
and there was nothing I could do to undo it.

613
00:23:40,210 --> 00:23:41,290
增加負擔
Burden me?

614
00:23:41,660 --> 00:23:43,420
你怎么不保護我
What about protecting me?

615
00:23:43,420 --> 00:23:44,780
就是為了保護你
Well, that's exactly what I was doing

616
00:23:44,780 --> 00:23:46,580
我才讓哈維來打這場官司
when I assigned Harvey to the case.

617
00:23:46,580 --> 00:23:48,400
就在我要接受謀殺指控的時候
And after I was brought up on murder charges,

618
00:23:48,400 --> 00:23:50,010
你瞞著我
rather than tell me,

619
00:23:50,010 --> 00:23:52,360
把犯下罪行的那個人派了過來
you send the very man who committed the crime.

620
00:23:52,740 --> 00:23:54,920
你到底想甩掉誰的負擔
Who were you trying not to burden then?

621
00:24:06,770 --> 00:24:09,820
你問過我她知不知道我和她父親的事
You once asked me if she knew about her father and I.

622
00:24:11,210 --> 00:24:14,130
那個年代  做一個出柜的律師
In those days, to be a lawyer and to be out--

623
00:24:14,920 --> 00:24:16,010
是不可能的
not possible.

624
00:24:17,050 --> 00:24:18,720
她父親做的是石油生意
Her father was in the oil business.

625
00:24:18,720 --> 00:24:21,130
-他會一無所有的  -這跟案子有什么...
- He would have been finished. - What does that have to do--

626
00:24:21,130 --> 00:24:23,550
我們偶爾會出去私會
We used to go away on occasion.

627
00:24:24,400 --> 00:24:25,790
為了不被人懷疑
In order to do that,

628
00:24:26,130 --> 00:24:28,830
艾娃會裝作我的女朋友跟我們同行
Ava joined us and pretended to be my girlfriend.

629
00:24:30,040 --> 00:24:31,630
她愿意幫助我們
She did that for us.

630
00:24:36,090 --> 00:24:37,940
艾娃就是我的親人
Ava is family to me.

631
00:24:38,790 --> 00:24:40,720
我派史蒂芬去幫她
I sent Stephen out there to help her.

632
00:24:40,800 --> 00:24:42,260
但我不知道他會那么做
I didn't know what he'd do.

633
00:24:42,700 --> 00:24:45,070
我愿不惜一切來收回覆水
And I would give anything to undo it.

634
00:24:48,210 --> 00:24:49,810
你要我怎么做  愛德華
What do you want from me, Edward?

635
00:24:50,820 --> 00:24:52,610
我想讓你把怒氣消一消
I want you to put aside your anger

636
00:24:52,610 --> 00:24:54,480
想個方法幫幫她
and figure out a way to help.

637
00:25:01,760 --> 00:25:02,800
你來干什么
What are you doing here?

638
00:25:02,990 --> 00:25:04,580
我是來消氣的
I'm here to put aside my anger.

639
00:25:06,200 --> 00:25:07,890
我們可還在忙謀殺案呢
We're in the middle of a murder trial.

640
00:25:07,890 --> 00:25:09,710
不差這五分鐘
We can spare five minutes for this.

641
00:25:10,470 --> 00:25:11,470
等一下
Wait a second.

642
00:25:11,860 --> 00:25:14,590
那瓶酒是你干掉丹尼爾的時候我送的
I gave you that bottle when you took over from Daniel.

643
00:25:14,910 --> 00:25:18,880
-我知道  -我還說過只有緊急情況才能喝它
- I know. - I told you to only open it in case of an emergency.

644
00:25:18,930 --> 00:25:20,990
現在還不是緊急情況嗎
You think this isn't an emergency?

645
00:25:21,090 --> 00:25:23,570
我們就要輸掉一場謀殺案了
We're about to lose a huge murder case,

646
00:25:23,650 --> 00:25:25,800
而幕后主使
and it turns out the person behind it

647
00:25:25,800 --> 00:25:27,460
居然還是我們律所的律師
is one of our own lawyers.

648
00:25:28,000 --> 00:25:29,860
幫他瞞天過海的人
And we're in business

649
00:25:29,870 --> 00:25:31,940
還與我們有著生意往來
with the man who helped cover it up.

650
00:25:32,060 --> 00:25:33,980
但我最在意的是
But the thing that's been most on my mind

651
00:25:33,980 --> 00:25:36,090
你他媽的居然背叛我
is that you goddamn betrayed me.

652
00:25:40,110 --> 00:25:41,080
現在
Now...

653
00:25:42,410 --> 00:25:45,380
是你提醒了我這些事
the truth is, you warned me about all of this.

654
00:25:46,170 --> 00:25:49,860
你背叛我這事我也不愿再想了
And I am tired of feeling betrayed by you.

655
00:25:49,860 --> 00:25:51,270
我寧愿原諒你
I'd rather forgive you.

656
00:25:54,250 --> 00:25:55,240
你能原諒嗎
Can you?

657
00:25:55,780 --> 00:25:57,340
要不我怎么會來
Why do you think I'm here.

658
00:25:58,610 --> 00:26:00,350
我不該背叛你
I never should have come after you.

659
00:26:00,650 --> 00:26:01,730
對不起
I'm sorry.

660
00:26:04,460 --> 00:26:05,790
你又沒殺人
You didn't kill anybody.

661
00:26:06,200 --> 00:26:08,180
如果我真要原諒你的話
And if I'm really going to forgive you,

662
00:26:09,100 --> 00:26:11,230
那我也要告訴你  我很抱歉
then I need to tell you I'm sorry

663
00:26:11,410 --> 00:26:13,420
讓你產生了背叛我的想法
that I made you want to do it in the first place.

664
00:26:20,930 --> 00:26:22,150
為什么改主意了
What changed your mind?

665
00:26:23,470 --> 00:26:24,470
愛德華
Edward.

666
00:26:26,600 --> 00:26:29,170
他說艾娃是他的親人
He said Ava was family to him.

667
00:26:30,700 --> 00:26:31,980
你也是我的親人
You're family to me,

668
00:26:33,110 --> 00:26:34,860
而你有著他沒有的東西
and you did what he didn't.

669
00:26:35,160 --> 00:26:36,340
你身家清白
You came clean.

670
00:26:38,250 --> 00:26:39,980
你來就是為了跟我說這些嗎
Is that all you came here to tell me?

671
00:26:40,090 --> 00:26:42,450
你不是說  我們還要忙謀殺案嗎
Like you said, we're in the middle of a murder trial.

672
00:26:42,800 --> 00:26:44,220
你有主意了
And you have an idea.

673
00:26:45,280 --> 00:26:46,570
有著親人般感情的人
We're not the only people

674
00:26:46,570 --> 00:26:48,390
可不止我們一對
that are like family to each other.

675
00:26:48,790 --> 00:26:50,570
有時候你不得不
And sometimes you have to put your family

676
00:26:50,580 --> 00:26:52,630
把親人逼上絕境
in a position where they don't have a choice.

677
00:26:53,160 --> 00:26:54,300
要我做什么
What do you need me to do?

678
00:27:03,300 --> 00:27:06,220
計劃有變  我們要證明艾娃的清白
New plan--we're gonna convince that Ava's innocent.

679
00:27:06,320 --> 00:27:07,360
你喝酒了
Have you been drinking?

680
00:27:08,140 --> 00:27:09,470
喝了  怎么了
Yeah. Why?

681
00:27:09,530 --> 00:27:10,790
你剛說的不就是原計劃嗎
Because wasn't that the old plan?

682
00:27:10,790 --> 00:27:11,790
那是老目標
That was the old goal.

683
00:27:11,790 --> 00:27:13,580
這次  你要去對陣卡梅隆
This time, it's you who's going to Cameron.

684
00:27:14,180 --> 00:27:15,640
他連你說的都不聽
If he won't hear the truth from you,

685
00:27:15,640 --> 00:27:17,090
又怎么會聽我的
how's he gonna hear it from me?

686
00:27:18,920 --> 00:27:21,180
卡梅隆了解不到真相是因為
Cameron can't see the truth because all he sees

687
00:27:21,180 --> 00:27:22,570
他覺得這個案子必勝無疑
is that he has a winnable case.

688
00:27:22,570 --> 00:27:24,190
這對我剛說的有什么影響嗎
How does that affect what I just said?

689
00:27:24,200 --> 00:27:25,600
檢察官就像是錘子
Prosecutors are hammers,

690
00:27:25,600 --> 00:27:27,280
他們把被告當成釘子
and they see the accused as nails.

691
00:27:27,280 --> 00:27:28,770
我要怎么改變這一點
How am I gonna change that?

692
00:27:29,470 --> 00:27:30,430
你要去提醒他
You're gonna remind him

693
00:27:30,430 --> 00:27:31,870
這次他敲錯了釘子
about the time he hit the wrong nail.

694
00:27:35,200 --> 00:27:37,040
這兒的華夫餅怎么樣
Can you tell me how the waffles are here?

695
00:27:38,360 --> 00:27:40,150
邁克·羅斯  伙計
Mike Ross, my man.

696
00:27:40,990 --> 00:27:41,830
很高興見到你
It's good to see you, man.

697
00:27:41,840 --> 00:27:43,520
我也很高興  克利福德
It's good to see you too, Clifford.

698
00:27:43,890 --> 00:27:45,680
大半夜的你來這干什么
What the hell you doing out in the middle of the night?

699
00:27:45,680 --> 00:27:46,910
我剛說了
Oh, you know, I told you.

700
00:27:46,910 --> 00:27:48,560
突然想吃華夫餅
I got an urge for some waffles.

701
00:27:49,250 --> 00:27:50,900
這可不是個巧合  對吧
This isn't a coincidence, is it?

702
00:27:51,480 --> 00:27:52,500
我需要你的幫忙
I need a favor.

703
00:27:53,160 --> 00:27:54,390
沒問題  要做什么
No doubt. What you need?

704
00:27:54,400 --> 00:27:56,120
我要你去找卡梅隆·丹尼斯談談
I need you to talk to Cameron Dennis.

705
00:27:58,280 --> 00:27:59,220
不行
No.

706
00:27:59,640 --> 00:28:00,500
絕不
Hell, no.

707
00:28:00,500 --> 00:28:02,280
-克利福德  -你看看我
- Clifford... - Look at me, man.

708
00:28:02,390 --> 00:28:03,660
看看我工作的地方
Look where I am...

709
00:28:04,480 --> 00:28:05,510
收拾別人的殘羹剩飯
Cleaning up people's shit!

710
00:28:05,510 --> 00:28:06,370
我了解
I know.

711
00:28:06,370 --> 00:28:08,340
那你知道這都是拜他所賜嗎
You know this is all I can get because of him?

712
00:28:08,780 --> 00:28:10,900
我的人生都被那個混蛋毀了
My life passed me by because of that motherf....

713
00:28:12,860 --> 00:28:14,500
要是我見到他  絕對會殺了他
I get in a room with him, I'll kill him.

714
00:28:14,500 --> 00:28:16,320
我要你把這些話告訴他
And I need you to tell him all of that

715
00:28:16,320 --> 00:28:18,820
好讓他不在別人身上重蹈你的覆轍
so that he doesn't do the same thing to somebody else.

716
00:28:19,380 --> 00:28:20,390
你需要
You need?

717
00:28:21,540 --> 00:28:22,920
我知道這個"你"是誰
I know who "you" is.

718
00:28:23,730 --> 00:28:25,360
我可不欠哈維什么
And I don't owe Harvey shit.

719
00:28:25,760 --> 00:28:27,400
也許是他還了我的清白
Now, he may have got me out,

720
00:28:27,410 --> 00:28:28,980
但當初他也是卡梅隆的幫兇
but he and Cameron put me there in the first place.

721
00:28:28,990 --> 00:28:31,580
沒錯  你不欠哈維的
Yeah, you're right. You don't owe Harvey.

722
00:28:32,730 --> 00:28:34,060
但你欠我的
But you do owe me...

723
00:28:34,830 --> 00:28:36,750
你被冤枉的事跟我沒有關系
'cause I didn't have anything to do with putting you in there,

724
00:28:36,750 --> 00:28:39,400
但我不惜違法把你救了出來
but I broke the law to get you out.

725
00:28:46,600 --> 00:28:48,070
我今天心情不錯
I am feeling generous,

726
00:28:48,070 --> 00:28:50,250
當然  完全沒問題
so absolutely, 100%,

727
00:28:50,590 --> 00:28:52,540
毋庸置疑  去你媽的
without a doubt, go screw yourself.

728
00:28:53,260 --> 00:28:54,460
出什么事了嗎
Everything okay?

729
00:28:54,510 --> 00:28:55,330
沒事
Yeah, of course.

730
00:28:55,330 --> 00:28:56,770
我正在用第36計
I was just using tactic number 36

731
00:28:56,770 --> 00:28:58,570
取自《路易·利特兵法》  私家絕版  市面無售
In Louis Litt's handbook, due to be published never.

732
00:28:58,580 --> 00:29:00,100
因為我從不分享我的計謀
Because I don't share my tactics.

733
00:29:00,100 --> 00:29:01,810
順便一提  這是第七計
Tactic number seven, by the way.

734
00:29:02,970 --> 00:29:03,980
好吧
Okay.

735
00:29:04,280 --> 00:29:06,660
不管你對哈羅德用了什么計  看似不奏效
Well, whatever tactic you used on Harold didn't work.

736
00:29:06,660 --> 00:29:08,050
他不肯妥協
He's not caving.

737
00:29:08,500 --> 00:29:09,470
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about,

738
00:29:09,480 --> 00:29:11,070
他答應了我所有的條件啊
because he gave me everything I wanted.

739
00:29:11,080 --> 00:29:12,570
客戶剛剛來電話了
The client just called.

740
00:29:12,570 --> 00:29:14,700
哈羅德發來的合同里有一處漏洞
The contract Harold sent over has a loophole in it.

741
00:29:14,700 --> 00:29:16,590
他會因此被責令懲罰性賠償
It leaves him open to punitive damages.

742
00:29:17,860 --> 00:29:19,060
第九段
Paragraph nine.

743
00:29:20,020 --> 00:29:21,320
把合同拿回來
Get that contract back.

744
00:29:21,320 --> 00:29:22,810
我們得重新談判
We need to renegotiate.

745
00:29:24,200 --> 00:29:26,360
老天  你也被哈羅德騙過去了
Oh, my god, Harold pulled one over on you.

746
00:29:27,200 --> 00:29:28,560
不許宣揚出去
Don't you dare say that out loud.

747
00:29:28,560 --> 00:29:30,580
聯系上他  約好面談時間  我去找他
Call him up, set up the appointment for me to go over there.

748
00:29:30,580 --> 00:29:31,310
我試過了
I tried.

749
00:29:31,310 --> 00:29:33,970
可他堅持要過來  他已經在路上了
He insisted on coming here. He's on his way right now.

750
00:29:39,190 --> 00:29:40,480
你在這干什么
What the hell are you doing here?

751
00:29:41,200 --> 00:29:42,960
來告訴你你到底是誰
He's here to tell you who you are.

752
00:29:43,260 --> 00:29:44,070
我自己清楚
I know who I am.

753
00:29:44,070 --> 00:29:45,800
用不著他來告訴我
I don't need to hear it from him.

754
00:29:46,530 --> 00:29:48,060
你覺得你有得選嗎
You think I'm giving you a choice?

755
00:30:01,940 --> 00:30:05,450
我說了我們在會議室談
Okay. We were supposed to meet in the conference room.

756
00:30:05,450 --> 00:30:06,960
不用在會議室談
I don't need to wait in the conference room

757
00:30:06,960 --> 00:30:08,760
我也能揍你個七葷八素
to knock your dick in the dirt.

758
00:30:09,070 --> 00:30:10,080
你說什么
What'd you just say to me?

759
00:30:10,090 --> 00:30:11,540
這是《早餐俱樂部》的臺詞  蠢貨
It's from The Breakfast Club, asshole.

760
00:30:11,540 --> 00:30:13,580
現在誰還只看《音樂之聲》啊
Not all of us only watch The Sound of Music.

761
00:30:13,590 --> 00:30:15,980
你個小混蛋  收回你剛才的話
You little bastard. You just crossed a line.

762
00:30:15,980 --> 00:30:18,320
出演《音樂之聲》的女演員

763
00:30:15,980 --> 00:30:18,320
朱莉·安德魯斯是不可多得的國民偶像
Julie Andrews is a national treasure.

764
00:30:18,640 --> 00:30:20,770
那你的客戶跟著她會更好些吧
Maybe your client would be better off with her.

765
00:30:20,770 --> 00:30:21,810
有可能
Maybe they would be.

766
00:30:21,810 --> 00:30:23,610
但她不在這  老子在
But she isn't here. And I am.

767
00:30:23,610 --> 00:30:26,110
而且老子這有些好東西
And here are a few of my favorite things...

768
00:30:26,350 --> 00:30:27,990
誹謗反訴
Countersuit for slander,

769
00:30:27,990 --> 00:30:30,070
訴訟案動議
motion to decertify class,

770
00:30:30,070 --> 00:30:31,830
即決審判動議
motion for summary judgment,

771
00:30:31,830 --> 00:30:33,930
地點變更動議  制裁書
change of venue, sanctions,

772
00:30:33,930 --> 00:30:36,210
書面證詞  調查證據
depositions, discovery!

773
00:30:37,550 --> 00:30:39,850
很會收集材料嘛  路易
Great use of folders there, Louis.

774
00:30:39,850 --> 00:30:41,650
只可惜它們都不管用啊
Too bad none of them are gonna work.

775
00:30:41,650 --> 00:30:42,800
是啊  對案子它們是不管用
Well, they may not work on the case,

776
00:30:42,800 --> 00:30:44,350
但收拾你  這些足夠了
but they're definitely gonna work on you.

777
00:30:45,760 --> 00:30:46,990
你什么意思
What are you talking about?

778
00:30:47,000 --> 00:30:49,060
我是說  可能最終你會贏
Oh, I'm talking about you may win in the end,

779
00:30:49,070 --> 00:30:51,780
但這并不能證明
but it won't justify

780
00:30:51,780 --> 00:30:53,240
你每天清醒的時間都用于這些破爛上
you spending every waking minute of your life on this bullshit,

781
00:30:53,240 --> 00:30:56,110
公司交給你的任務卻壓根沒做
instead of doing everything else you've been assigned to do.

782
00:30:56,560 --> 00:30:57,340
你竟然這樣對我
You'd do that to me?

783
00:30:57,340 --> 00:30:58,710
我不會這樣對你
I won't be doing it to you.

784
00:30:58,710 --> 00:31:00,780
我是為了布萊頓·古爾德
I'll be doing it for Bratton Gould.

785
00:31:00,820 --> 00:31:02,150
到時候你會被眾人哄笑驅趕
And you'll be laughed out of there

786
00:31:02,150 --> 00:31:03,780
就像你在這如過街老鼠般被驅趕一樣
the same way you were laughed out of here.

787
00:31:03,780 --> 00:31:05,550
-路易  -談話到此為止
- Louis... - We got nothing left to say!

788
00:31:05,550 --> 00:31:07,630
周末前給我停止訴訟
Drop the suit by the end of the week,

789
00:31:07,630 --> 00:31:09,610
要不然我們就法庭上見
or one of my associates will see you in court.

790
00:31:09,610 --> 00:31:10,780
現在滾吧
Get out!

791
00:31:24,870 --> 00:31:26,260
讓他出去
I don't want him here.

792
00:31:26,260 --> 00:31:29,380
艾娃  不管他做過什么  他是來幫忙的
Ava, whatever he did, he's here to help,

793
00:31:30,010 --> 00:31:31,450
而且他相當重要
and he's an asset.

794
00:31:31,840 --> 00:31:34,990
那么大名鼎鼎的愛德華·達比想說些什么呢
Then what does the mighty Edward Darby have to say?

795
00:31:34,990 --> 00:31:37,170
你的無罪推定
You're innocent until proven guilty

796
00:31:37,170 --> 00:31:38,660
現在備受質疑
beyond a reasonable doubt.

797
00:31:38,660 --> 00:31:39,800
即使出庭作證
Take the stand.

798
00:31:39,800 --> 00:31:42,090
所有陪審員也都會懷疑你
Any juror that hears you will have that doubt.

799
00:31:42,090 --> 00:31:43,660
只要她一入場  卡梅隆的第一個問題就是
She opens that door, the first question Cameron asks is,

800
00:31:43,660 --> 00:31:47,140
她有沒有賄賂過目擊證人
did she try and bribe those witnesses?

801
00:31:47,490 --> 00:31:50,120
答案是肯定的  所以陪審員的懷疑很合理
The answer is yes. There goes reasonable doubt.

802
00:31:52,140 --> 00:31:53,450
你們給了他多少錢
How much did you pay him?

803
00:31:53,450 --> 00:31:55,400
-卡梅隆  -給誰
- Cameron. - Pay who?

804
00:31:55,400 --> 00:31:57,730
別裝傻  克利福德·丹納
Don't play dumb. Clifford Danner.

805
00:31:57,730 --> 00:31:59,180
克利福德·丹納又是誰
Who the hell is Clifford Danner?

806
00:31:59,180 --> 00:32:02,040
他是被卡梅隆投入監獄的無辜人
He was an innocent person that Cameron put behind bars.

807
00:32:02,040 --> 00:32:03,690
我以為你知道他是無辜的
And I thought he would make you see reason.

808
00:32:03,690 --> 00:32:04,830
跟這沒關系
That has nothing to do with this.

809
00:32:04,830 --> 00:32:06,680
他身陷囹圄可不是因為我  是因為你
And I didn't put him behind bars...you did.

810
00:32:06,690 --> 00:32:07,970
然后我將他放了出來
Then I got him out.

811
00:32:07,970 --> 00:32:09,860
那她你可救不了  因為她有罪
Well, you're not getting her out, because she did it,

812
00:32:09,860 --> 00:32:12,740
昨天你自己的同事親口承認  她有罪
and yesterday your own colleague said that she did it.

813
00:32:12,740 --> 00:32:15,060
他沒那么說  你很清楚
He did not say that, and you know it.

814
00:32:15,060 --> 00:32:16,540
你敢賭這一把嗎
You willing to take that risk?

815
00:32:16,540 --> 00:32:17,500
那你想怎樣
What are you suggesting?

816
00:32:17,500 --> 00:32:20,250
跟他共事這么久  我知道他打什么主意
I've worked with him long enough to know what he's suggesting.

817
00:32:20,250 --> 00:32:22,030
卡梅隆·丹尼斯從來不等待裁決
Cameron Dennis doesn't go to verdict.

818
00:32:22,030 --> 00:32:23,110
他直接提條件
He cuts deals.

819
00:32:23,110 --> 00:32:25,490
那我直接告訴你  等待你們的是什么
Then let me tell you...about what's behind door number one...

820
00:32:25,490 --> 00:32:26,670
八年
Eight years.

821
00:32:29,280 --> 00:32:32,290
-八年監禁代替終身牢獄  -你出去
- Eight years instead of forever. - Leave us alone.

822
00:32:32,570 --> 00:32:34,820
還有十分鐘開庭  仔細考慮考慮
Court's in ten minutes. You have until then.

823
00:32:36,950 --> 00:32:37,940
哈維
Harvey...

824
00:32:38,430 --> 00:32:39,840
我們栽他手里了  你知道的
He's got us, and you know it.

825
00:32:39,840 --> 00:32:41,130
不  才沒有
No, he doesn't.

826
00:32:41,130 --> 00:32:43,100
她一天牢都不用坐
She's not going to prison for one day.

827
00:32:43,100 --> 00:32:45,390
如果我們不答應的話
She's going for the rest of her life

828
00:32:45,390 --> 00:32:46,620
她就要坐一輩子牢了
if we don't take this deal.

829
00:32:46,620 --> 00:32:48,640
我不會輸給他的
I am not losing to him.

830
00:32:48,640 --> 00:32:51,400
你  跟你的夙仇
You...your blood feud

831
00:32:51,400 --> 00:32:53,550
我不知道你們之間有什么過節
or whatever it is you have with that man

832
00:32:53,550 --> 00:32:56,210
但我成了頭號受害者
is what put the target on my back in the first place.

833
00:32:56,220 --> 00:32:58,810
艾娃  面對現實吧
Ava, we need to face reality.

834
00:32:58,810 --> 00:33:00,960
她不會接受交易的
She is not taking that deal.

835
00:33:00,970 --> 00:33:04,170
她最好接受  金錢已經無法擺平了
She better, because she can't buy her way out of it.

836
00:33:04,170 --> 00:33:06,770
而且你也束手無策了
And you can't cover up your way out of it.

837
00:33:06,780 --> 00:33:07,680
我不在乎
I don't care.

838
00:33:07,680 --> 00:33:08,470
那你怎么想呢
Well, what's your idea?

839
00:33:08,470 --> 00:33:09,670
除非你肯出庭作證
Because unless you're gonna testify

840
00:33:09,670 --> 00:33:12,120
史蒂芬在艾娃不知情的情況下做了一切
that Stephen did this without Ava's knowledge,

841
00:33:12,130 --> 00:33:13,200
否則你毫無用處
you can't help.

842
00:33:13,200 --> 00:33:15,110
可你也說了  你沒有證據
And as you said, you have no proof.

843
00:33:15,110 --> 00:33:17,860
所以還是請你閉嘴離開  讓我們談正事
So why don't you get out of the room and let the grown-ups talk?

844
00:33:18,850 --> 00:33:21,770
如果我可以作證呢
What if I was to testify to that?

845
00:33:23,390 --> 00:33:24,790
你說什么
What are you talking about?

846
00:33:25,050 --> 00:33:27,520
我說  是時候說出
I'm talking about putting words to a conversation

847
00:33:27,520 --> 00:33:29,850
我早該說出的實情了
that should have happened but didn't.

848
00:33:29,850 --> 00:33:33,350
你是說你質問過史蒂芬  而他承認了
You'd say that you confronted Stephen, and he admitted it?

849
00:33:33,350 --> 00:33:36,580
我留下的爛攤子  理應由我收拾
I made this mess. It's up to me to clear it up.

850
00:33:36,580 --> 00:33:37,860
這不管用
This isn't gonna help.

851
00:33:37,860 --> 00:33:40,670
你是她的老朋友  最后一刻才趕來支援
You're her old friend coming to her aid at the last second.

852
00:33:40,670 --> 00:33:41,730
根本說不通
It's a lie.

853
00:33:41,730 --> 00:33:43,130
陪審員會一眼看穿的
The jury will see right through it.

854
00:33:43,130 --> 00:33:45,090
讓卡梅隆相信就行了
Then we need to make Cameron believe it.

855
00:33:45,200 --> 00:33:47,180
哈維  卡梅隆想贏而已
Harvey, Cameron wants a win.

856
00:33:47,240 --> 00:33:49,040
你要說服他  這對他大有裨益
You need to convince him this is a win.

857
00:33:49,040 --> 00:33:50,450
你能做到嗎
Can you do that?

858
00:33:51,560 --> 00:33:53,650
我們也只能孤注一擲了
I guess it's the best shot we have.

859
00:34:05,220 --> 00:34:06,550
我就知道你沉不住氣
I knew you'd care.

860
00:34:06,550 --> 00:34:08,600
這不是還有5分鐘嗎
And with five minutes to spare.

861
00:34:08,600 --> 00:34:10,530
我們不是來答應你條件的  卡梅隆
We're not here to take your offer, Cameron.

862
00:34:10,530 --> 00:34:11,720
我們要你答應我們的條件
We want you to take ours.

863
00:34:11,720 --> 00:34:13,820
本人拒絕討價還價  八年是底線了
Nah, I'm not negotiating. Eight years is final.

864
00:34:13,820 --> 00:34:15,830
我不是來為艾娃做交易的
This isn't about making a deal for Ava.

865
00:34:15,840 --> 00:34:17,850
是為我
It's about making a deal for me.

866
00:34:18,370 --> 00:34:20,510
如果他知道什么內幕的話
If he's got something to say about this,

867
00:34:20,510 --> 00:34:22,250
你應該讓他上證人席
you should put him on the stand.

868
00:34:22,780 --> 00:34:25,460
我相信過你一次了  這次換你
I already trusted you once. I need your word.

869
00:34:26,730 --> 00:34:28,440
說吧  我不會外傳
Go ahead. Off the record.

870
00:34:28,650 --> 00:34:32,080
是我指使史蒂芬·亨特利要不惜一切代價
I instructed Stephen Huntley to do whatever it took

871
00:34:32,080 --> 00:34:33,420
獲得艾娃的輸油管道
to get Ava her pipeline,

872
00:34:33,420 --> 00:34:36,060
我還告訴他不能讓艾娃知道
and I told him to do it behind her back.

873
00:34:36,060 --> 00:34:38,010
所以授權這些謀殺的人是你
So you authorized these murders.

874
00:34:38,010 --> 00:34:39,360
當然不是
Absolutely not.

875
00:34:39,360 --> 00:34:40,740
我一聽說有人被殺
When I heard people had been killed,

876
00:34:40,740 --> 00:34:42,480
就立馬找他對質
I confronted him immediately.

877
00:34:42,640 --> 00:34:43,840
那他說什么了
And what did he say?

878
00:34:43,840 --> 00:34:45,650
他不在乎利用謀殺來達成目的
He didn't care that he'd resorted to murder.

879
00:34:45,650 --> 00:34:47,520
他的工作就是完成任務
His job was to get things done.

880
00:34:48,500 --> 00:34:51,720
你等于是在承認你是知情不報的從犯
You just admitted to being an accessory after the fact.

881
00:34:51,720 --> 00:34:52,900
不  他沒有
No, he didn't.

882
00:34:53,020 --> 00:34:55,820
我懂了  不得公開
I get it. Off the record.

883
00:34:57,550 --> 00:34:58,640
你想怎么樣
What do you want?

884
00:34:58,710 --> 00:35:00,740
愛德華承認妨礙司法公正罪
Edward pleads to obstruction of justice--

885
00:35:00,740 --> 00:35:02,120
五年緩刑
Five years probation.

886
00:35:02,120 --> 00:35:04,310
你撤銷對艾娃的起訴
You drop the charges against Ava.

887
00:35:04,310 --> 00:35:05,310
他會在史蒂芬·亨特利的
And he testifies

888
00:35:05,310 --> 00:35:07,550
謀殺庭審上出庭作證
at Stephen Huntley's murder trial.

889
00:35:10,440 --> 00:35:13,510
我為什么要拿艾娃換她的奴才呢
And why would I swap out Ava for her minion?

890
00:35:13,820 --> 00:35:17,320
卡梅隆  你提出那項提議是有原因的
Cameron, you gave us that offer for a reason.

891
00:35:17,320 --> 00:35:19,720
你站在終點線上  可以品嘗勝利的果實
You're at the finish line-- you can taste the win,

892
00:35:19,720 --> 00:35:22,620
但那并不是完美的  你自己也知道
but it's not 100%, and you know it,

893
00:35:22,620 --> 00:35:24,710
因為你還是得依靠一個有撒謊動機
because you're still banking on an admitted murderer

894
00:35:24,710 --> 00:35:26,020
并且已認罪的兇手
with an incentive to lie.

895
00:35:26,020 --> 00:35:28,030
而我提供的則是一個
I'm giving you a respected lawyer

896
00:35:28,240 --> 00:35:30,500
會守口如瓶且受人尊敬的律師
with an incentive to keep his mouth shut.

897
00:35:31,870 --> 00:35:33,590
你知道誰更有可能
You know who has a better chance

898
00:35:33,590 --> 00:35:35,050
助你獲取勝利
at getting you a win.

899
00:35:41,920 --> 00:35:43,430
起草文件吧
Draw up the paperwork.

900
00:36:05,200 --> 00:36:07,060
我以為你再也不想見我了
I thought you never wanted to see me again.

901
00:36:07,950 --> 00:36:09,320
我考慮你之前說的
I thought about what you said.

902
00:36:09,990 --> 00:36:12,290
什么  關于你們公司所涉及的業務嗎
What, about the kind of business your firm does?

903
00:36:12,850 --> 00:36:13,800
對
Yes.

904
00:36:15,510 --> 00:36:18,460
我意識到也許你沒有我之前說的那么壞
And I realized that maybe you're not as bad as I said you were.

905
00:36:19,280 --> 00:36:20,200
沒有嗎
No?

906
00:36:21,000 --> 00:36:22,050
沒有
No.

907
00:36:24,310 --> 00:36:25,730
你比我說的要壞多了
You're much worse.

908
00:36:31,230 --> 00:36:33,340
哈維和卡梅隆達成協議要拿下你
Harvey and Cameron made a deal to take you down,

909
00:36:33,340 --> 00:36:37,640
協議的一部分就是  這一切必須由我來告訴你
and part of that deal was that I got to be the one to tell you about it.

910
00:36:42,950 --> 00:36:46,050
我說我不想傷害你都是真的
I meant it when I said I never meant to hurt you.

911
00:36:46,230 --> 00:36:49,560
而我說你讓我惡心也是真的
And I meant it when I said that you make me sick.

912
00:36:58,580 --> 00:36:59,640
都寫上去了
It's all there.

913
00:36:59,870 --> 00:37:02,480
你作證  然后獲得五年緩刑
You testify, you get five years probation.

914
00:37:02,480 --> 00:37:04,700
他承認妨礙司法公正
and he pleads obstruction of justice.

915
00:37:05,240 --> 00:37:06,890
-這是什么  -什么是什么
- What is this? - What is what?

916
00:37:06,890 --> 00:37:08,990
這上面說我在本國的律師執業許可
This says that I forfeit my license

917
00:37:08,990 --> 00:37:10,800
將因犯罪被沒收
to practice law in this country.

918
00:37:10,800 --> 00:37:12,650
那條啊  我剛剛加進去的
Oh, that--that's just something I added in.

919
00:37:12,650 --> 00:37:14,970
-這不能接受  -稍等一下
- This is unacceptable. - Wait a minute.

920
00:37:14,970 --> 00:37:17,500
如果是我們寫的文件  你怎么能把那條加進去
How could you add that in if we did the paperwork?

921
00:37:17,500 --> 00:37:19,540
如果他沒有獲得本國的律師執業許可
And if he can't practice law in the country,

922
00:37:19,540 --> 00:37:21,100
他就不能在我們公司就職
he can't be a member of our firm.

923
00:37:21,100 --> 00:37:23,220
這是我們必須達成一致的大前提
We must have agreed to it in advance.

924
00:37:25,580 --> 00:37:26,890
這一切都是你一手操辦的
You set this whole thing up.

925
00:37:26,890 --> 00:37:29,060
是杰西卡一手操辦的
Jessica set this whole thing up.

926
00:37:29,060 --> 00:37:30,230
但又有什么關系呢
But what's it matter?

927
00:37:30,230 --> 00:37:31,720
只要受點輕罰就能脫罪
You really gonna put this on Ava

928
00:37:31,730 --> 00:37:34,050
你還想讓艾娃受罪嗎
when you can get off with a slap on the wrist?

929
00:37:34,050 --> 00:37:36,130
我還求你將憤怒擱置一旁
I asked you to put aside your anger.

930
00:37:36,130 --> 00:37:38,950
我已經擱置一旁了  你說艾娃是你的親人
I did. You said Ava was family.

931
00:37:39,210 --> 00:37:41,970
家人的特點就在于  他們會輕而易舉地
The thing about family is they make it easy

932
00:37:42,050 --> 00:37:45,100
把你逼到一個絕境上
to put you in the position where you don't have a choice.

933
00:37:45,480 --> 00:37:47,120
現在  你要簽署這份協議
Now, you gonna sign the deal,

934
00:37:47,220 --> 00:37:50,740
還是要我按之前的計劃繼續訴訟
or do I just pick up the trial right where we left off?

935
00:37:55,380 --> 00:37:57,000
你這樣做才對  愛德華
You're doing the right thing, Edward.

936
00:37:57,010 --> 00:37:59,610
我們會考慮明天解約的條款
We'll worry about the terms of our dissolution tomorrow.

937
00:38:01,500 --> 00:38:02,700
另外  愛德華
And, Edward...

938
00:38:03,300 --> 00:38:04,830
看來我們得"離婚"了
we may be getting a divorce,

939
00:38:04,830 --> 00:38:07,960
但我還是打算保留房子的所有權
but I fully intend on keeping ownership of the house.

940
00:38:14,400 --> 00:38:16,180
誰能想到我們會就此結案呢
Who'd have thought we'd end up here?

941
00:38:16,630 --> 00:38:17,700
我
I did.

942
00:38:18,260 --> 00:38:19,130
不  你沒有
No, you didn't.

943
00:38:19,130 --> 00:38:21,030
你冒險用了克利福德·丹納
You took a chance with Clifford Danner,

944
00:38:21,030 --> 00:38:22,390
你自己也知道
and you know it.

945
00:38:22,500 --> 00:38:23,920
那不是冒險
It wasn't a chance.

946
00:38:24,150 --> 00:38:25,360
而是像男子漢一樣行事
I played the man.

947
00:38:25,540 --> 00:38:28,460
卡梅隆  你不只是常勝將軍
And, Cameron, you're not only about winning.

948
00:38:28,990 --> 00:38:31,410
還能將罪犯繩之于法
You're about putting guilty people away.

949
00:38:34,550 --> 00:38:36,110
很高興與你合作
Nice working with you.

950
00:38:36,890 --> 00:38:38,020
一錘子買賣
One-time deal.

951
00:38:40,200 --> 00:38:42,910
我猜你的意思是不想再找冠名合伙人了
I guess this means you're not looking for another name partner?

952
00:38:42,950 --> 00:38:44,190
再見  卡梅隆
Good-bye, Cameron.

953
00:38:52,280 --> 00:38:53,480
諾瑪說你有東西要給我
Norma said you had something for me?

954
00:38:53,480 --> 00:38:54,610
沒錯
I do.

955
00:38:58,050 --> 00:38:59,480
他撤訴了  我贏了
He dropped it. I win.

956
00:39:01,140 --> 00:39:02,250
是嗎
Do you?

957
00:39:04,900 --> 00:39:06,330
什么  你在說什么
What? What are you talking about?

958
00:39:07,960 --> 00:39:10,050
你為什么這么恨哈羅德
Why do you hate Harold so much?

959
00:39:10,320 --> 00:39:11,550
-我不恨他  -不  你恨他
- I don't hate him. - Yeah, you do...

960
00:39:11,550 --> 00:39:14,370
因為我覺得你對他比對任何人都刻薄
Because I've never seen you be as mean to anyone as you are to him.

961
00:39:14,370 --> 00:39:14,990
瑞秋  我
Rachel, I--

962
00:39:14,990 --> 00:39:16,950
別再叫我"瑞秋"了  他也是個人
Don't "Rachel" me. He's a human being.

963
00:39:16,950 --> 00:39:19,060
你到底怎么回事
What's the matter with you?

964
00:39:25,240 --> 00:39:27,820
我小時候上體操課時
When I was a kid in gym class...

965
00:39:30,610 --> 00:39:32,320
我們得爬繩索
we had to climb the rope.

966
00:39:33,880 --> 00:39:36,590
我每天都非常努力
Every day I tried really hard,

967
00:39:36,600 --> 00:39:37,800
但每一天
And every day...

968
00:39:38,630 --> 00:39:40,160
大家都會嘲笑我
everyone would laugh at me.

969
00:39:46,360 --> 00:39:49,080
我這輩子真正擅長的
The one thing in my life that I've always been great at

970
00:39:49,080 --> 00:39:51,030
就是訓練助理律師
is training the associates...

971
00:39:52,210 --> 00:39:53,720
除了哈羅德
except for Harold.

972
00:39:54,950 --> 00:39:56,170
他是我的敗筆
He's my failure.

973
00:39:56,780 --> 00:39:59,110
我每次看到他  都感覺...
And every time I look at him, it...

974
00:40:03,050 --> 00:40:04,970
回到了體操課一樣
puts me right back in gym class.

975
00:40:10,760 --> 00:40:11,870
路易
Louis...

976
00:40:13,350 --> 00:40:15,180
哈羅德正在爬那根繩索
Harold's climbing that rope.

977
00:40:15,420 --> 00:40:16,940
他快成功了
He's succeeding.

978
00:40:17,160 --> 00:40:19,030
而且你獲取這場勝利的方式
And the way you got this victory

979
00:40:19,110 --> 00:40:21,170
就是剝奪了他的工作
was by going after his career.

980
00:40:21,480 --> 00:40:24,430
相當于把他猛地往下拉了一把
And you're just yanking him right back down.

981
00:40:37,730 --> 00:40:38,930
我們從沒收到這個
We never got this.

982
00:40:40,020 --> 00:40:42,590
接受他原來的提案  然后送回去
Send back his original offer marked "Accepted."

983
00:40:51,610 --> 00:40:53,390
我以后不想再提到這個了
I never want this spoken of again.

984
00:40:54,830 --> 00:40:56,640
你不想再提到什么了
You never want what spoken of again?

985
00:40:59,780 --> 00:41:02,340
哈維  艾娃應該說什么
Harvey, what did Ava have to say?

986
00:41:02,340 --> 00:41:04,310
她已經去機場了
She'd already left for the airport.

987
00:41:04,600 --> 00:41:07,770
要是有人救了我的命  我會停下腳步說聲謝謝的
Someone saves my life, I might stop to say thank you.

988
00:41:08,050 --> 00:41:08,940
我們律所讓她經歷了這么多
You really blame her

989
00:41:08,940 --> 00:41:10,780
你真的要為此責備她嗎
after what this firm put her through?

990
00:41:11,040 --> 00:41:12,100
既然你這么說
When you put it that way...

991
00:41:12,100 --> 00:41:14,130
沒關系  反正已經取得了大勝利
It doesn't matter. It was a huge win.

992
00:41:14,170 --> 00:41:15,360
去慶祝吧
Go celebrate.

993
00:41:16,030 --> 00:41:17,760
你的意思難道不是一起去慶祝
Don't you mean "Let's go celebrate"?

994
00:41:18,580 --> 00:41:20,190
你真的想跟我一起慶祝
Am I really the person you wanna celebrate

995
00:41:20,200 --> 00:41:22,280
這場重大謀殺審判的勝訴嗎
this big murder trial victory with?

996
00:41:22,280 --> 00:41:24,110
我不知道  看你說誰了
I don't know. It depends who you put out.

997
00:41:24,220 --> 00:41:25,520
你何不去找瑞秋
Why don't you just ask Rachel?

998
00:41:25,520 --> 00:41:26,840
一點也不好笑
That's not funny.

999
00:41:42,220 --> 00:41:43,410
哈維
Harvey.

1000
00:41:45,110 --> 00:41:46,390
唐娜
Donna.

1001
00:41:47,550 --> 00:41:48,850
還好嗎
How does it go?

1002
00:41:49,710 --> 00:41:51,900
挺好的
As well as it could.

1003
00:41:55,210 --> 00:41:56,200
哈維
Harvey.

1004
00:42:00,190 --> 00:42:01,300
謝謝
Thank you.

1005
00:42:01,890 --> 00:42:03,480
今晚何不你坐車
Why don't you keep the car?

1006
00:42:04,030 --> 00:42:05,900
我今晚想散散步
I feel like walking tonight.

