1
00:06:10,950 --> 00:06:15,950
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:06:10,950 --> 00:06:15,950
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:06:11,450 --> 00:06:15,950
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

4
00:06:11,450 --> 00:06:15,950
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

5
00:06:11,450 --> 00:06:15,950
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

6
00:06:11,450 --> 00:06:15,950
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

7
00:06:11,450 --> 00:06:15,950
原创翻译  双语字幕

8
00:06:11,950 --> 00:06:15,950
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供学习  禁止用于任何商业盈利行为

9
00:06:16,350 --> 00:06:46,350
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

10
00:06:15,850 --> 00:06:46,350
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

11
00:06:16,350 --> 00:06:21,350
翻 译     草草  Kahiko  木浅  嫕嫕嫕   Alex

12
00:06:21,350 --> 00:06:26,350
翻 译     小食人魔   Giggles  辰星晓Reginamoon

13
00:06:26,350 --> 00:06:31,350
校 对     木浅  某羽

14
00:06:31,350 --> 00:06:36,350
时间轴   风吹来的那片云

15
00:06:36,350 --> 00:06:41,350
后 期     斯人

16
00:06:41,350 --> 00:06:46,350
总 监     木浅

17
00:00:05,920 --> 00:00:07,260
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
Previously on Suits.

18
00:00:07,260 --> 00:00:09,270
塔拉·梅瑟  你愿意嫁给我吗
Tara Messer, will you marry me?

19
00:00:09,270 --> 00:00:11,290
愿意  路易  我愿意
Yes, Louis, I'll marry you.

20
00:00:12,110 --> 00:00:14,030
哈维  我不在乎你挣多少钱
I don't care how much money you make

21
00:00:14,030 --> 00:00:15,820
或者睡过多少女人
or how many you women you sleep with.

22
00:00:15,820 --> 00:00:17,470
你的生活存在问题
You have issues in your life

23
00:00:17,470 --> 00:00:20,180
会导致你难以获得真正的爱情
that are going to keep you from having real relationships.

24
00:00:20,190 --> 00:00:22,460
我们的软件和另一个公司的产品
Benjamin and I have an overlap on our software

25
00:00:22,460 --> 00:00:23,520
存在重合部分
with another company.

26
00:00:23,520 --> 00:00:27,260
他使劲了浑身解数拿到了这个
Louis pulled out every trick in the book to get us this.

27
00:00:28,420 --> 00:00:30,470
-那就把钱收下吧  -我想要的不是钱
- Take the money. - I don't want the money.

28
00:00:30,760 --> 00:00:32,430
-唐娜  -我想要更多
- Donna-- - I want something more.

29
00:00:32,430 --> 00:00:33,580
你说"更多"是什么意思
What do you mean more?

30
00:00:33,590 --> 00:00:35,490
我做了个交易  我们解决矿工的案子
I made a deal that we would handle the miners' case

31
00:00:35,490 --> 00:00:37,460
以换取进入律师协会的机会
in exchange for the chance to be admitted to the Bar.

32
00:00:37,460 --> 00:00:39,100
你在逗我吗  你被解雇了
Are you goddamn kidding me? You're fired.

33
00:00:39,100 --> 00:00:41,270
-别这样  -他撒谎  而且不止一次
- Don't do it. - He lied--not once, not twice--

34
00:00:41,270 --> 00:00:42,860
我不在乎  因为我们需要他
I don't care because we need him.

35
00:00:43,950 --> 00:00:45,270
周一早晨  你最好拿出实际行动
Monday morning, you better start putting your money

36
00:00:45,270 --> 00:00:48,030
再为我们接个能赚五万美元的案子
where your mouth is and find us another $50,000 case.

37
00:00:48,070 --> 00:00:49,960
塔拉给我留了个十五秒的留言
Tara left a 15-second voicemail.

38
00:00:49,960 --> 00:00:52,110
内容不是要跟我说她再也不想见到我了
She's either gonna tell me that she never wants to see me again

39
00:00:52,120 --> 00:00:53,510
就是要和好
or she wants to make up.

40
00:00:57,990 --> 00:00:58,810
那是什么
What's that?

41
00:00:58,810 --> 00:01:01,270
预付你一年工资  欢迎回来
Your first year's salary in advance. Welcome back.

42
00:01:01,270 --> 00:01:02,410
哈维  我已经不知道
Harvey, I'm running out of ways

43
00:01:02,410 --> 00:01:04,250
该怎么告诉你我不想做企业律师了
to tell you I don't want to be a corporate lawyer.

44
00:01:04,250 --> 00:01:07,020
我提出了个交易  为你  也为我
I'm offering you a deal. One for you, one for me.

45
00:01:07,030 --> 00:01:08,470
赞助诊所一年  不够
I don't wanna just fund the clinic for a year.

46
00:01:08,470 --> 00:01:09,390
我要两年的赞助
I want to fund it for two,

47
00:01:09,390 --> 00:01:11,560
我想给诊所什么案子  就给什么案子
and any case I want to bring the clinic onto, I can.

48
00:01:11,560 --> 00:01:12,110
成交
Done.

49
00:01:12,110 --> 00:01:14,320
-还有一件事  -你别想要我的办公室
- And there's one more thing. - You are not getting my office.

50
00:01:14,320 --> 00:01:16,080
我不仅要  还要告诉你为什么该给我
Oh, yes, I am, and I will tell you why.

51
00:01:16,080 --> 00:01:17,950
-为什么  -因为她走了  哈维
- Why? - 'Cause she's gone, Harvey.

52
00:01:17,950 --> 00:01:19,820
是时候由你掌权了
It's time for you to take the reins.

53
00:01:56,760 --> 00:01:59,620
哈维  你来做什么
Harvey. What are you doing here?

54
00:01:59,700 --> 00:02:01,600
没事  我就是开着这车兜兜风
Nothing, I was just driving this baby around

55
00:02:01,600 --> 00:02:03,420
然后想起你家这边车位多
and remembered how much street parking you had.

56
00:02:03,420 --> 00:02:04,950
你是想打动我吗
Is that supposed to impress me?

57
00:02:05,610 --> 00:02:08,570
希望能  我是很受打动的
Well, I hope so. Sure as hell impresses me.

58
00:02:09,100 --> 00:02:10,730
见到你很高兴
Well, it's nice to see you,

59
00:02:10,730 --> 00:02:13,010
但如果你想预约  应该先打电话
but if you wanted an appointment, you should have called.

60
00:02:13,010 --> 00:02:14,250
我不是来预约的
I'm not here for an appointment.

61
00:02:14,250 --> 00:02:15,490
我来约你出去
I'm here to ask you out.

62
00:02:17,590 --> 00:02:18,630
你是认真的
You're serious.

63
00:02:18,630 --> 00:02:20,250
我最近想了很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking lately, and...

64
00:02:20,250 --> 00:02:21,920
-哈维  -求你  让我说完
- Harvey... - Please, let me finish.

65
00:02:21,920 --> 00:02:23,920
我们上次分别之后  情况变了很多
Things have changed since the last time I saw you.

66
00:02:23,920 --> 00:02:25,320
我已经不是之前的我了
I'm not the same man that I was.

67
00:02:25,320 --> 00:02:26,860
我跟家人和解
I made peace with my family;

68
00:02:27,110 --> 00:02:28,700
我以前的同事也回来了
I got my old associate back,

69
00:02:28,700 --> 00:02:30,960
从今早起  我是公司的老板了
and as of this morning, I'm the head of my firm,

70
00:02:30,960 --> 00:02:33,140
当我去想该跟谁分享这一切时
and when I thought of sharing that with someone,

71
00:02:35,200 --> 00:02:36,170
我想到了你
I thought of you.

72
00:02:36,170 --> 00:02:38,540
这些不重要
Well, it doesn't matter,

73
00:02:38,540 --> 00:02:40,760
因为医生跟病人约会
because it's completely unethical for a doctor

74
00:02:40,770 --> 00:02:42,760
完全有违道德
to engage in a relationship with her patient.

75
00:02:42,760 --> 00:02:43,760
隔了足够的时间就无所谓
Not if enough time has passed,

76
00:02:43,760 --> 00:02:45,420
而按心理学协会的规定
and according to the APA,

77
00:02:45,500 --> 00:02:47,900
三周前  间隔的时间就足够了
as of three weeks ago, enough time has passed.

78
00:02:48,290 --> 00:02:49,790
-调查的很细致  -当然
- You did your homework. - Sure did.

79
00:02:49,790 --> 00:02:50,950
所以唯一的问题是
So the only question is:

80
00:02:50,950 --> 00:02:53,480
周四八点  还是周六九点
Thursday at 8:00 or Saturday at 9:00?

81
00:02:55,700 --> 00:02:57,670
就一顿饭  如果你显然认为存在的
One dinner, and if this chemistry you

82
00:02:57,670 --> 00:03:00,760
火花并不存在  那我们友好分别
so clearly think exists doesn't, then we part as friends,

83
00:03:00,760 --> 00:03:01,940
不伤感情
no hard feelings.

84
00:03:01,940 --> 00:03:03,390
如果不成
If it doesn't work out,

85
00:03:03,530 --> 00:03:04,980
没伤害  不犯规
no harm, no foul.

86
00:03:07,100 --> 00:03:08,110
周四
Thursday.

87
00:03:11,480 --> 00:03:13,670
如果车太酷炫了
And if the car's too much,

88
00:03:13,670 --> 00:03:15,690
我还是可以让雷开车的
I can always have Ray drive.

89
00:03:15,780 --> 00:03:17,130
我喜欢这车
I like the car.

90
00:03:18,740 --> 00:03:20,750
你说什么  我没听到
What did you say? I couldn't hear you.

91
00:03:20,750 --> 00:03:22,370
我喜欢你的车
I like the car.

92
00:03:37,390 --> 00:03:39,430
很好  你早到了
Good. You're here early.

93
00:03:39,790 --> 00:03:42,550
我需要你为桑德拉办一起消费者诈骗的听证会
I need you to take poing on a consumer fraud hearing for Sandra.

94
00:03:42,550 --> 00:03:44,270
纳森  我们得谈谈
Nathan, I need to talk to you.

95
00:03:45,300 --> 00:03:46,310
好吧
Okay.

96
00:03:46,900 --> 00:03:48,810
我知道那天晚上我们吵得有点凶
I know things got heated between us the other night,

97
00:03:48,810 --> 00:03:51,410
但就我看来  那都过去了
but as far as I'm concerned, it's water under the bridge,

98
00:03:51,410 --> 00:03:52,880
如果你在想我是不是还生你的气
so if you're wondering if I'm still upset at you--

99
00:03:52,880 --> 00:03:53,810
我没有
I'm not.

100
00:03:54,450 --> 00:03:57,580
这是为了确保你听完我要说的
And this is to make sure you're still not upset with me

101
00:03:57,580 --> 00:03:59,310
能继续保持不生我的气
after you hear what I'm about to say.

102
00:04:05,660 --> 00:04:08,320
我为什么拿着一张五十万美元的支票
Why am I holding a check for $500,000?

103
00:04:08,320 --> 00:04:10,840
因为我决定回皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特律所
Because I've decided to go back to Pearson Specter Litt,

104
00:04:11,060 --> 00:04:13,530
我向你保证过不会抛下你
and I gave you my word that I wouldn't leave you high and dry.

105
00:04:13,530 --> 00:04:16,320
是这样吗  你改了主意
So let me get this straight: you changed your mind,

106
00:04:16,360 --> 00:04:18,580
现在哈维·斯佩克特要买你回去
and now Harvey Specter is buying you back?

107
00:04:18,580 --> 00:04:20,690
如果哈维能说了算  你一分都别想捞到
If it were up to Harvey, you wouldn't be getting a penny.

108
00:04:20,690 --> 00:04:22,540
这是我坚持的
I insisted on this.

109
00:04:23,050 --> 00:04:25,510
我还坚持从今后  我每隔一个案子
Just like I insisted on every other case I take

110
00:04:25,510 --> 00:04:27,120
就办一个无偿案
from now on being pro bono.

111
00:04:27,120 --> 00:04:29,260
听上去你这么做是为了让自己良心好受
It sounds like you insisted on that to make yourself feel better.

112
00:04:29,260 --> 00:04:30,380
不  纳森  我那么做
No, Nathan, I did that

113
00:04:30,380 --> 00:04:32,920
是因为我喜欢做这样的工作
because I care about doing this kind of work,

114
00:04:34,350 --> 00:04:37,730
如果你接受  我甚至愿意
and if you're okay with it, I'd even like the idea

115
00:04:37,730 --> 00:04:39,550
偶尔跟你们合作一些案子
of us partnering on a case every now and then.

116
00:04:39,550 --> 00:04:41,490
但如果我说我不接受这些呢
But what if I say I'm not okay with any of this?

117
00:04:41,520 --> 00:04:43,700
我知道是你在别人都不愿再给我机会
I know that you were the one that gave me another chance

118
00:04:43,700 --> 00:04:45,730
做律师时  给了我机会
to be a lawyer when no one else would,

119
00:04:45,740 --> 00:04:47,200
但别惩罚诊所
but don't punish the clinic.

120
00:04:47,200 --> 00:04:49,970
这是笔大钱  用这钱  你可以另找人
It's a lot of money. With that, you could replace me

121
00:04:49,970 --> 00:04:52,950
并在很长一段时间里帮助很多人
and help a lot of people for a long time.

122
00:05:00,590 --> 00:05:03,320
-那是给我的吗  -不  其实是给我的
- Is that for me? - No, actually, it's for me.

123
00:05:03,320 --> 00:05:04,710
你今晚比以往晚
You're later than usually this morning.

124
00:05:04,710 --> 00:05:05,670
我等了你好一会儿
I've been waiting for you.

125
00:05:05,670 --> 00:05:07,040
唐娜  那晚的事
Donna, about the other night.

126
00:05:07,040 --> 00:05:09,650
我知道你说想要更多  但先听我...
I know you said you wanted more, but before you say anything--

127
00:05:09,650 --> 00:05:12,190
-我想做合伙人  -合伙人
- I want to be a partner. - Partner?

128
00:05:12,190 --> 00:05:13,470
是的  我知道我想要什么了
Yes. I figured out what I want,

129
00:05:13,470 --> 00:05:15,120
我想做律所的合伙人
and I want to be a partner at this firm.

130
00:05:15,120 --> 00:05:16,680
唐娜  我无意侮辱你
Donna, I don't mean to insult you,

131
00:05:16,680 --> 00:05:18,340
但你都不是律师
but you're not even a lawyer.

132
00:05:18,340 --> 00:05:20,970
很好  因为我成为合伙人跟法律无关
Good, because my being a partner isn't about the law.

133
00:05:21,080 --> 00:05:22,410
而是维持律所的运作
It's about keeping this firm running,

134
00:05:22,410 --> 00:05:24,390
而这本就是我一直在做的
which I've been doing for as long as I can remember.

135
00:05:24,390 --> 00:05:27,010
我知道  但那不代表我能让你...
I know that, but it doesn't mean that I can get you--

136
00:05:27,020 --> 00:05:30,000
我为这里奉献了十多年  哈维
I've given over ten years of my life to this place, Harvey,

137
00:05:30,000 --> 00:05:32,000
仅以你秘书的身份我都维持住了律所
and I've done it all from your desk.

138
00:05:33,210 --> 00:05:35,320
我只求一个决策的位置
All I'm asking is for a seat at the table.

139
00:05:37,040 --> 00:05:38,680
这我得跟路易商量
I'll have to ask Louis about it.

140
00:05:38,680 --> 00:05:39,900
那么你是同意了吗
Does that mean that you're on board?

141
00:05:39,900 --> 00:05:42,060
我不知道  今天迈克第一天回来
I don't know. It's Mike's first day back,

142
00:05:42,060 --> 00:05:44,160
这事不小  不仅如此
it's a big ask, and on top of all of that,

143
00:05:44,160 --> 00:05:45,810
我还决定告诉路易
I've decided to tell Louis

144
00:05:45,930 --> 00:05:48,050
我要作为经营合伙人完全做主
that I'm taking full control as managing partner.

145
00:05:48,060 --> 00:05:50,260
恭喜  哈维  但究竟是哪个
Well, congratulations, Harvey, but which is it?

146
00:05:50,340 --> 00:05:52,300
路易  迈克
Louis? Mike?

147
00:05:52,300 --> 00:05:53,980
"不小的事"  因为我不希望
"Big ask." Because I'd hate to think

148
00:05:53,980 --> 00:05:55,730
我鼓起勇气来这么做
I mustered the courage to do this,

149
00:05:55,730 --> 00:05:58,250
可你一上了电梯  就抛在脑后了
and then once you get on that elevator, it's out of your mind.

150
00:05:58,290 --> 00:06:00,890
我保证  我不会忘记的
I give you my word. I will not forget about it.

151
00:06:01,780 --> 00:06:02,680
好
Okay.

152
00:06:11,390 --> 00:06:14,830
看到钱  就愿意留下吃饭*
*See the money, wanna stay for your meal

153
00:06:14,830 --> 00:06:18,250
给你太太再拿块馅饼*
*Get another piece of pie for your wife

154
00:06:18,250 --> 00:06:21,590
所有人都想知道那感觉*
*Everybody wanna know how it feel

155
00:06:21,590 --> 00:06:24,750
所有人都想见见那景象*
*Everybody wanna see what it's like

156
00:06:24,750 --> 00:06:28,150
豆子馅饼我也愿吃  我不在乎*
*I'll even eat a bean pie, I don't mind

157
00:06:28,150 --> 00:06:32,170
我和妹子忙着赚钱*
*Me and Missy is so busy, busy making money

158
00:06:32,170 --> 00:06:33,250
好了*
*All right

159
00:06:33,310 --> 00:06:38,040
退开点  我要跳舞*
*All step back, I'm 'bout to dance

160
00:06:36,880 --> 00:06:39,060
诉 讼 双 雄

161
00:06:36,880 --> 00:06:39,060
第七季   第一集

162
00:06:39,210 --> 00:06:41,090
美钞爵士摇摇摇*
*The greenback boogie

163
00:06:48,990 --> 00:06:50,280
你是睡在这里了吗
Did you sleep in here?

164
00:06:50,280 --> 00:06:52,370
只是来感受一下我的新办公室
Just getting a feel for my new office.

165
00:06:52,710 --> 00:06:54,520
你觉得这墙上能挂得下自行车架吗
You think a bike rack would fit on this wall?

166
00:06:54,520 --> 00:06:56,910
你敢装自行车架  你的第一个无偿案
You put a bike rack in here, your first pro bono,

167
00:06:56,910 --> 00:06:59,760
就只能在我把车塞进你屁股后  自己去打了
you'll be representing yourself after I shove it up your ass.

168
00:06:59,760 --> 00:07:01,380
听上去很不舒服
Wow. That sounds uncomfortable.

169
00:07:02,290 --> 00:07:03,860
说到无偿案
Now, speaking of pro bonos,

170
00:07:03,860 --> 00:07:06,630
你什么时候能把你家老头子的唱片拿出去
when are you gonna get your old man records out of here

171
00:07:06,630 --> 00:07:08,410
好让我安顿下来开始工作
so I can settle in and get to work?

172
00:07:08,460 --> 00:07:10,950
等我们搞定了尼尔·斯蒂尔曼我就搬
I'll get out of here once we take of Neil Stillman.

173
00:07:10,950 --> 00:07:12,620
尼尔·斯蒂尔曼  迪特尔工业那个
Neil Stillman? Detour Industries?

174
00:07:12,620 --> 00:07:15,650
不  尼尔·斯蒂尔曼  绝地议会那个
No, Neil Stillman, Jedi counsel.

175
00:07:15,670 --> 00:07:20,100
好吧  我问是因为尼尔·斯蒂尔曼是公司客户
Okay, I was asking because Neil Stillman is a corporate client,

176
00:07:20,230 --> 00:07:23,530
不是先给我一个我要的  再一个你要的吗
so what happened to one for me, then one for you?

177
00:07:23,530 --> 00:07:26,100
要我提醒你  在企业法律所
Do I need to remind you that at a corporate law firm,

178
00:07:26,100 --> 00:07:28,210
我们优先接手利润丰厚的案子吗
we do the cases that pay the bills first?

179
00:07:28,210 --> 00:07:30,360
更何况  我还没告诉你最妙的部分
Besides, I haven't even told you the best part yet.

180
00:07:30,370 --> 00:07:31,440
再过两星期你就要离开人世了吗
You only got two weeks to live?

181
00:07:31,440 --> 00:07:33,200
不是  等这个案子结束
No. After we're done with this case,

182
00:07:33,200 --> 00:07:35,080
我把尼尔·斯蒂尔曼给你
I'm giving you Neil Stillman.

183
00:07:35,080 --> 00:07:37,170
哈维  我很感谢你的好意  但说实话
Harvey, I appreciate that, but seriously,

184
00:07:37,170 --> 00:07:38,970
既然案子结束你就要把他给我
if you're just gonna give him to me when we're done,

185
00:07:38,970 --> 00:07:40,280
为何不干脆现在就给我
why don't you give him to me now?

186
00:07:40,280 --> 00:07:42,050
无论发生什么情况  我都能处理好
Whatever it is, I can handle it myself.

187
00:07:42,210 --> 00:07:43,900
-我知道  -那你到底是为什么
- I know that. - Then what's going on?

188
00:07:43,900 --> 00:07:46,260
我们完全没有必要一起办这个案子
It doesn't make sense for us to be working together on this.

189
00:07:46,360 --> 00:07:47,880
行  你想听真话
All right, you want the truth?

190
00:07:48,060 --> 00:07:50,110
杰西卡成为管理合伙人后
When Jessica made managing partner,

191
00:07:50,610 --> 00:07:54,110
我和她就不怎么一起办案子了
she and I never really got to do cases together anymore.

192
00:07:54,110 --> 00:07:55,660
你们之前一起办过案子
You used to work on cases together?

193
00:07:55,660 --> 00:07:56,920
是  当年她和我就是现在的我和你
Yeah. She was me and I was you.

194
00:07:56,920 --> 00:07:58,400
黄金组合
We kicked ass.

195
00:07:58,680 --> 00:08:01,190
是吗  那这黄金组合里你主要负责什么
Right. And what exactly did you contribute to the equation?

196
00:08:01,190 --> 00:08:05,040
引用电影台词吐槽  但这不是重点
Oh, movie quotes, mostly, but that's not the point.

197
00:08:05,040 --> 00:08:07,350
重点是我们在一起工作真的很开心
The point is we had a great time doing it.

198
00:08:07,350 --> 00:08:08,890
-哈维  -迈克  我说真的
- Harvey... - Mike, I'm serious.

199
00:08:08,890 --> 00:08:11,700
杰西卡一晋升  我们的关系就变了
Once Jessica stepped up, our relationship changed.

200
00:08:12,110 --> 00:08:13,940
而如果你早知道会如此
And if you'd known that was gonna happen,

201
00:08:14,960 --> 00:08:16,510
肯定希望当时能再一起办最后一个案子
you would have wanted one last case together.

202
00:08:16,520 --> 00:08:19,440
没错  所以怎么样
Exactly. So what do you say?

203
00:08:19,840 --> 00:08:21,880
一起出去找点乐子  顺便大杀四方
We go out and have some fun and kick some ass?

204
00:08:21,880 --> 00:08:24,400
还是留在这里量你的单车架
Or do you want to stay here measuring for your bike rack?

205
00:08:24,550 --> 00:08:26,140
但我不量就没人量了
It's not gonna measure itself.

206
00:08:26,920 --> 00:08:29,620
好好好  我选办案子
All right, fine. Kick ass.

207
00:08:30,050 --> 00:08:33,050
不过这个案子里  我要当绝地律师
But we do this, I want on that Jedi counsel.

208
00:08:33,050 --> 00:08:35,110
长袍  光之剑  都得有
Robes, light saber, whole deal.

209
00:08:40,110 --> 00:08:41,520
你来了  太好了
Good, you're here.

210
00:08:41,650 --> 00:08:42,770
格雷琴  你来干什么
Gretchen, what are you doing here?

211
00:08:42,770 --> 00:08:44,700
-给你送东西  -什么东西
- I'm here to give you these. - What are those?

212
00:08:44,700 --> 00:08:46,820
北半球前九泥浆温泉度假村
Brochures from the top nine mud resorts

213
00:08:46,820 --> 00:08:48,200
宣传册
in the northern hemisphere,

214
00:08:48,200 --> 00:08:50,380
虽然我是不能理解泡泥浴的意义
though I don't know why a person would do that in the first place.

215
00:08:50,390 --> 00:08:53,120
基本等同于泡在自己的粪便里
It's like sitting in a bathtub of your own poop.

216
00:08:53,810 --> 00:08:54,870
你到底想说什么
What the hell are you talking about?

217
00:08:54,880 --> 00:08:57,110
路易  你需要休息
Louis, you need to take yourself some time off.

218
00:08:57,110 --> 00:08:59,220
你还记得你上次休假是什么时候吗
When's the last time you even had a vacation?

219
00:08:59,230 --> 00:09:00,590
9年前的7月
Nine years ago July.

220
00:09:00,760 --> 00:09:03,580
倒霉旅行社给我卖了份地中海俱乐部的孟加拉套餐
Goddamn travel agent sold me a package to Club Med Bangladesh,

221
00:09:03,580 --> 00:09:04,950
所以  绝不
so, hard pass.

222
00:09:04,950 --> 00:09:08,160
什么样的人会去转孟加拉色情俱乐部
What kind of person goes to a sex club in Bangladesh?

223
00:09:08,170 --> 00:09:09,370
不是那样
It's not like that.

224
00:09:09,370 --> 00:09:11,110
我当时刚看完《贫民窟的百万富翁》
I had just seen "Slumdog Millionaire,"

225
00:09:11,110 --> 00:09:12,640
我是想去找寻芙蕾达·平托
and I was trying to find Freida Pinto.

226
00:09:12,640 --> 00:09:14,660
没记错的话她住在伦敦吧
I believe she considers London her place of habitat.

227
00:09:14,660 --> 00:09:16,140
不  我不是说真-芙蕾达·平托
No, I'm not talking about the real Freida Pinto.

228
00:09:16,140 --> 00:09:17,110
我是说属于我的芙蕾达·平托
I'm talking about my Freida Pinto.

229
00:09:17,110 --> 00:09:19,350
叫芙蕾达·平托的人多了去了好吗
There's many different Freida Pintos out there, okay?

230
00:09:19,350 --> 00:09:21,780
所以  我不是白痴  别来烦我
So just--I'm not an idiot. Leave me alone.

231
00:09:22,150 --> 00:09:25,510
路易  我是担心你再这样无所事事郁闷下去
Louis, I'm just worried that if you sit around and stew,

232
00:09:25,510 --> 00:09:27,420
会因为这次分手做出出格的事
this breakup's gonna get the best of you.

233
00:09:27,420 --> 00:09:28,900
格雷琴  我真心感谢你的好意
Gretchen, I really appreciate that,

234
00:09:28,900 --> 00:09:29,950
但我不会无所事事的
but I'm not just gonna sit around.

235
00:09:29,950 --> 00:09:32,260
我将会把伤心焚化为滋润助理们的沃土
I'm gonna be pouring my heartbreak into those new associates.

236
00:09:32,260 --> 00:09:34,600
这样真的好吗
Are you sure that's the best idea?

237
00:09:35,390 --> 00:09:36,220
听着
Look...

238
00:09:37,680 --> 00:09:39,190
我不只是失去了塔拉
I didn't just lose Tara.

239
00:09:40,530 --> 00:09:42,280
我还失去了成为爸爸的机会
I lost a chance at being a father.

240
00:09:42,850 --> 00:09:46,150
而我一直将助理们视如己出
And those associates have always been my children to me.

241
00:09:46,620 --> 00:09:47,750
他们是我的孩子
My children.

242
00:09:48,360 --> 00:09:49,300
而且事实是
And the truth is,

243
00:09:49,300 --> 00:09:51,310
他们进公司后我都没怎么管他们
I've been neglecting them ever since they got here,

244
00:09:51,620 --> 00:09:54,060
但这种情况就到今早为止了
but that ends this morning.

245
00:09:55,620 --> 00:09:57,210
路易  我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you, Louis.

246
00:09:58,930 --> 00:10:00,100
谢谢你  格雷琴
Thank you, Gretchen.

247
00:10:06,260 --> 00:10:07,610
你跑哪儿去了
Where the hell have you been?

248
00:10:07,900 --> 00:10:09,370
尼尔  你一小时前给我打的电话
Neil, you called an hour ago.

249
00:10:09,370 --> 00:10:11,470
也就意味着你应该在半小时内赶到
Well, that means you should have been here in 30 minutes.

250
00:10:11,470 --> 00:10:13,720
可能你不知道  我不是超时免费的披萨快递
Well, I got news for you: I'm not Dominos.

251
00:10:13,720 --> 00:10:15,340
真不幸  因为如果你继续掉链子
That's too bad, because slinging pizzas

252
00:10:15,340 --> 00:10:16,610
做披萨饼搞不好
might be the only job you can get

253
00:10:16,610 --> 00:10:18,080
就是你唯一能做的工作了
if you don't stop shitting the bed.

254
00:10:18,080 --> 00:10:19,850
掉链子  怎么讲
Shitting the bed? How's that?

255
00:10:19,850 --> 00:10:21,930
这两个周我一直在给你打电话
I've been trying to get you on the phone for two weeks.

256
00:10:21,930 --> 00:10:23,160
杰西卡走了  突然之间
Jessica leaves, and all of a sudden,

257
00:10:23,160 --> 00:10:24,460
我就没人管了吗
I start falling through the cracks?

258
00:10:24,460 --> 00:10:26,530
不会没人管  现在我来了
You're not falling through anything. I'm here now,

259
00:10:26,530 --> 00:10:28,330
而且我还带来了最好的初级合伙人
and I brought the best junior partner in the firm.

260
00:10:28,330 --> 00:10:30,710
他就是最好的初级勤杂工也无所谓
I don't give a shit if he's the best junior towel boy.

261
00:10:30,710 --> 00:10:33,580
我有工作交给你  而且十分紧急
I got something for you to do, and I want it done yesterday.

262
00:10:33,580 --> 00:10:36,130
我猜你是想卖掉伏特加酒厂的业务
Let me guess, you want to sell your vodka business.

263
00:10:37,360 --> 00:10:38,560
你怎么知道的
How the hell could you know that?

264
00:10:38,560 --> 00:10:39,690
因为如果你不打算把它卖掉
Because you don't clean up the balance sheet

265
00:10:39,690 --> 00:10:42,710
就不会想要在公司重组半年之后
of your third largest division six months after you restructure

266
00:10:42,710 --> 00:10:44,190
动第三大部门的资产负债表
if you're not looking to put it on the market.

267
00:10:44,190 --> 00:10:46,390
好  我承认你带的人不错
Okay, you brought the right guy.

268
00:10:46,710 --> 00:10:48,730
我想知道的是  你动作怎么这么慢
My question is, what took so long?

269
00:10:48,730 --> 00:10:50,560
我想知道的是  那么着急干什么
And my question is what's the rush?

270
00:10:50,590 --> 00:10:52,520
"因为如果不是为势所迫
'Cause you also don't ram a transaction through

271
00:10:52,520 --> 00:10:53,290
你根本就不必急于脱手
if you don't have to.

272
00:10:53,290 --> 00:10:55,220
我有并购另一个公司的机会
I have an opportunity to buy another company,

273
00:10:55,220 --> 00:10:57,360
-我不想让机会流失掉  -什么公司
- and I don't wanna let it slip away. - What company?

274
00:10:57,370 --> 00:10:59,130
-我可以帮你做尽职调查  -俄罗斯的
- I'll start vetting them for you. - They're Russian,

275
00:10:59,130 --> 00:11:00,230
他们家的业务叫
and they make a little product

276
00:11:00,230 --> 00:11:02,100
不关你事
called none of your goddamn business.

277
00:11:02,510 --> 00:11:04,060
尼尔  为什么这么藏着掖着
Neil, what's with the secrecy?

278
00:11:04,060 --> 00:11:04,780
我们是你的律师
We're your lawyers.

279
00:11:04,790 --> 00:11:06,110
我们需要知道你的打算
We need to know what you're looking to do.

280
00:11:06,110 --> 00:11:08,420
藏着掖着是以防着两周后
The secrecy is in case you're not my lawyers

281
00:11:08,420 --> 00:11:09,710
你们不再是我的律师
two weeks from now.

282
00:11:09,710 --> 00:11:11,380
我不想你们知道我要并购哪家
I don't want you knowing who I'm going after.

283
00:11:11,380 --> 00:11:12,380
你在威胁我们吗
Is that a threat?

284
00:11:12,380 --> 00:11:13,450
这只是确保
It's just my way of making sure

285
00:11:13,450 --> 00:11:15,230
你们不会再甩手不管我的手段
I don't keep falling through the cracks.

286
00:11:15,580 --> 00:11:17,120
现在我们来谈谈条款吧
Now let's talk terms.

287
00:11:26,040 --> 00:11:29,090
早上好  格雷琴  你见到路易了吗
Good morning, Gretchen. Have you seen Louis?

288
00:11:29,590 --> 00:11:32,050
昨晚的事之后  我有点担心他
I'm worried about how he's doing after last night.

289
00:11:32,050 --> 00:11:35,450
我估计他是在拿他的小鸟雏们弥补空虚
My guess is he's in the bullpen with his hatchlings.

290
00:11:35,450 --> 00:11:36,400
他的小鸟雏们
His hatchlings?

291
00:11:36,400 --> 00:11:38,210
我和你一样担心此事
I was concerned about him as you were,

292
00:11:38,210 --> 00:11:40,360
所以之前我打算逼他休假
so I tried to get him to take a vacation.

293
00:11:40,480 --> 00:11:43,750
结果他说他更想好好培养助理
He said he'd rather focus on raising those associates.

294
00:11:43,830 --> 00:11:45,850
好好培养还是好好出气
Focus on them or take it out on them?

295
00:11:45,850 --> 00:11:48,250
就我对他的了解  一半一半
Knowing him, probably 50/50,

296
00:11:48,250 --> 00:11:50,010
但是他拒绝了去世界
but the man turned down a trip

297
00:11:50,010 --> 00:11:52,000
最好的泥浆温泉度假村的机会
to the finest mud resorts in the world,

298
00:11:52,000 --> 00:11:55,670
所以我姑且相信他好的可能更大
so I decided to give him the benefit of the doubt.

299
00:11:56,810 --> 00:11:58,030
那我也相信他吧
Then I will too.

300
00:12:03,600 --> 00:12:05,470
早安  孩子们
Good morning, boys and girls.

301
00:12:06,050 --> 00:12:08,790
谁准备好干掉沃森工业了
Who's ready to tear Watson Industries a new asshole?

302
00:12:10,080 --> 00:12:12,880
这才是好样的  现在在你们的桌子上
That's what I like to see. Now, on your desks,

303
00:12:12,880 --> 00:12:15,430
每个人都发了一份我写的简报初稿
I've made each of you a copy of my initial brief.

304
00:12:15,680 --> 00:12:17,980
要掌握到如数家珍的地步
Cling to it as if you wrote it yourself,

305
00:12:17,980 --> 00:12:19,060
如果有人需要去卫生间
and if any of you need to go to the bathroom,

306
00:12:19,060 --> 00:12:22,280
我建议现在赶紧去  因为接下来两周
I suggest you do it now, because for the next two weeks,

307
00:12:22,280 --> 00:12:24,100
我们都要在这间屋子里过
we are not leaving this room.

308
00:12:24,100 --> 00:12:27,410
谁也不许大便  小便都不行
No one will be shitting. No one will be pissing.

309
00:12:27,510 --> 00:12:29,710
-谁也...  -问吧  问他
- No-- - Go ahead, ask him.

310
00:12:29,920 --> 00:12:30,950
问我什么
Ask me what?

311
00:12:34,000 --> 00:12:36,870
我听说了你的事迹 但是
I heard about your reputation, but...

312
00:12:36,870 --> 00:12:37,880
但是什么
But what?

313
00:12:38,170 --> 00:12:40,070
不用担心我的事迹  孩子
Don't you worry about my reputation, son.

314
00:12:40,070 --> 00:12:41,780
我已经不再是过去的路易了
I am not the same Louis I used to be.

315
00:12:41,780 --> 00:12:43,620
我也许还是很严格  但我也通情达理
I still may be tough, but I have a soft spot,

316
00:12:43,620 --> 00:12:44,790
你有什么需要
so what do you need?

317
00:12:45,650 --> 00:12:46,750
两天假
Two days off.

318
00:12:48,950 --> 00:12:49,970
没问题
No problem.

319
00:12:50,240 --> 00:12:51,640
周六周日你可以休息
Feel free to take Saturday and Sunday off.

320
00:12:51,640 --> 00:12:54,290
他是说周末之外还需要请假
He meant in addition to the weekend.

321
00:12:54,290 --> 00:12:56,130
之外  布莱恩  是这样吗
In addition? Brian, is this true?

322
00:12:56,360 --> 00:12:58,000
-是的  -那么
- Yes. - Then...

323
00:12:58,940 --> 00:13:01,350
周日和周一允许你休假
Monday and Sunday you shall have.

324
00:13:03,290 --> 00:13:05,360
好吧好吧  周一周二
Okay, fine. Monday and Tuesday it is.

325
00:13:06,000 --> 00:13:08,610
-谢谢  利特先生  -不不不  叫路易
- Thank you, Mr. Litt. - No, no, just call me Louis.

326
00:13:08,610 --> 00:13:09,740
介意我问问请假原因吗
Mind if I ask what the occasion is?

327
00:13:09,740 --> 00:13:12,720
-我要当父亲了  -什么
- I'm gonna be a father. - What?

328
00:13:13,540 --> 00:13:15,140
我们要有儿子了
We're gonna have a baby boy.

329
00:13:15,580 --> 00:13:18,440
一个大家都知道你是不可能有的东西
Something everybody here knows is never gonna happen to you.

330
00:13:23,600 --> 00:13:25,180
要当父亲了
Gonna be a father

331
00:13:25,180 --> 00:13:27,510
当一辈子哦
for the rest of his life.

332
00:13:34,280 --> 00:13:37,060
-你说什么  -我说剖腹产
- What'd you just say to me? - I said it's a C-section,

333
00:13:37,230 --> 00:13:39,050
因为孩子有点移位
'cause the baby's actually sideways,

334
00:13:39,050 --> 00:13:40,120
所以我们要...
which means we have to go in there...

335
00:13:40,120 --> 00:13:41,620
你这个目中无人的混蛋
You self-centered piece of shit.

336
00:13:41,620 --> 00:13:44,430
你以为我是真的想知道吗
Do you think I care about the graphic details?

337
00:13:44,430 --> 00:13:46,080
-我只是以为...  -以为什么
- I just thought-- - Thought what?

338
00:13:46,080 --> 00:13:48,170
以为你根本不在乎自己的工作吗
That you don't give a shit about your job?

339
00:13:48,220 --> 00:13:51,630
我告诉你  你人在这里  就得工作
Let me tell you something: when you work here, you work here.

340
00:13:51,630 --> 00:13:54,890
不允许想家想亲人想孩子
You don't think about home and families and babies.

341
00:13:54,890 --> 00:13:56,990
所以下次你要把你的私人生活
So the next time you want to put your personal life

342
00:13:56,990 --> 00:13:58,700
置于公司需求之上时
ahead of the needs of this firm,

343
00:13:58,700 --> 00:14:01,330
最好提前一年跟我请假
you better goddamn come to me a year in advance.

344
00:14:01,330 --> 00:14:02,150
这不公平
That's not fair.

345
00:14:02,150 --> 00:14:03,550
他不可能提前一年知道要生孩子...
He couldn't have known he was gonna have a baby a year--

346
00:14:03,550 --> 00:14:04,880
我告诉你  斯蒂芬妮
Let me tell you something, Stephanie:

347
00:14:04,880 --> 00:14:06,090
也许是你不清楚生孩子的事
maybe you don't know how babies are made,

348
00:14:06,090 --> 00:14:08,810
因为想要孩子的人  就知道自己在尝试
because when people are trying, they know they're trying,

349
00:14:08,810 --> 00:14:11,350
就因为没人愿意和你尝试
and just because no one ever wants to try with you

350
00:14:11,350 --> 00:14:12,420
不代表你就有权
doesn't give you the right

351
00:14:12,420 --> 00:14:14,730
教我怎么管理助理
to tell me how to run my associates.

352
00:14:14,730 --> 00:14:16,090
听懂了吗
You got that?

353
00:14:17,300 --> 00:14:18,170
懂了
Got it.

354
00:14:28,780 --> 00:14:30,290
你在想我在想的吗
You thinking what I'm thinking?

355
00:14:30,290 --> 00:14:31,540
不一定  你在想什么
Depends. What are you thinking?

356
00:14:31,540 --> 00:14:33,530
我在想我们有加伏特加酒厂要卖了
I'm thinking we've got a vodka company to sell.

357
00:14:33,530 --> 00:14:35,310
你还说过你想找点乐子
You already said you wanted to have some fun.

358
00:14:35,310 --> 00:14:36,990
没错  二者相加
That's right, and you put those two together,

359
00:14:36,990 --> 00:14:38,350
结论是什么
what have we got?

360
00:14:38,850 --> 00:14:39,900
派对
Party.

361
00:14:39,900 --> 00:14:42,250
看  我们达成一致了
See? We're already on the same page.

362
00:14:42,300 --> 00:14:43,810
不如你去找个好地方
Why don't you get a kick-ass location,

363
00:14:43,820 --> 00:14:45,790
-我负责找模特  -模特
- and I'll get the models. - Models?

364
00:14:45,790 --> 00:14:48,080
我喜欢模特  为什么不能让我找模特
I like models. Why can't I get the models?

365
00:14:48,080 --> 00:14:49,530
有道理
You make a good point.

366
00:14:49,650 --> 00:14:51,750
这活需要两个人  我们一起找吧
It's a two-man job. We'll both get the models.

367
00:14:51,750 --> 00:14:53,100
哈维  说真的  这个派对
Harvey, seriously, why do we even have to

368
00:14:53,110 --> 00:14:54,680
为什么需要模特
have models at this party?

369
00:14:54,690 --> 00:14:58,380
两个原因  其一  大家想看模特
Well, two reasons. First, people expect it,

370
00:14:58,380 --> 00:15:00,370
总要满足大家的需求
and you've got to give the people what they want.

371
00:15:00,370 --> 00:15:01,670
没错  其二
Right, and second,

372
00:15:01,680 --> 00:15:04,110
到场的凡是整晚调戏模特的人
any dipshit who shows up and hits on the models all night

373
00:15:04,110 --> 00:15:06,150
都不是诚意买家
isn't a serious bidder for the company.

374
00:15:06,150 --> 00:15:08,900
看来你确实有资格入住我办公室了
Huh, you really are ready for my office.

375
00:15:08,900 --> 00:15:09,440
说到你办公室
Hey, speaking of which,

376
00:15:09,440 --> 00:15:10,930
你到底什么时候让出来
when exactly is that gonna happen.

377
00:15:10,930 --> 00:15:12,220
现在没空说这个
I can't talk about that right now.

378
00:15:12,230 --> 00:15:13,450
我忙着去调戏模特呢
I got to go hit on some models.

379
00:15:13,450 --> 00:15:16,070
哈维  撇开玩笑话
Hey, Harvey,jokes aside,

380
00:15:16,070 --> 00:15:17,210
之前你说
what you said before about

381
00:15:17,210 --> 00:15:19,430
希望我们像以前一样一起办案
us working together like the old days,

382
00:15:19,570 --> 00:15:20,730
我很感激
I appreciate it.

383
00:15:21,760 --> 00:15:23,180
对我意义重大
It means a lot to me.

384
00:15:23,500 --> 00:15:24,620
我也是
Me too.

385
00:15:25,770 --> 00:15:26,980
-没种  -没种
- Pussy. - Pussy.

386
00:15:34,960 --> 00:15:37,170
唐娜  有时间吗  我需要你帮忙
Donna, do you have a minute? I need your help.

387
00:15:37,600 --> 00:15:40,280
没问题  怎么了
Of course. What's going on?

388
00:15:41,330 --> 00:15:42,950
路易已经失控了
Louis is out of control.

389
00:15:43,100 --> 00:15:44,780
是艾斯特婚姻问题那种失控
When Esther got married out of control,

390
00:15:44,790 --> 00:15:47,140
还是哈维当上高级合伙人那种
or when Harvey made senior partner out of control?

391
00:15:47,610 --> 00:15:48,550
还要糟
Worse.

392
00:15:48,860 --> 00:15:51,110
那糟了  他做了什么
Shit. What did he do?

393
00:15:51,110 --> 00:15:52,840
冲助理们发火去了
He just went off on the associates.

394
00:15:52,840 --> 00:15:55,590
异常狂暴  残忍而且可怕
He was abusive and cruel and ugly.

395
00:15:55,960 --> 00:15:58,220
唐娜  我从来没见过这样的路易
Donna, I have never seen Louis like this before.

396
00:15:58,220 --> 00:15:59,640
瑞秋  如果真如你所说
Rachel, if what you're saying is true,

397
00:15:59,640 --> 00:16:01,490
那我们就需要弄清楚原因
then we need to figure out why,

398
00:16:01,490 --> 00:16:02,920
因为路易这样从来都是为某件事...
because with Louis, there's always a reason--

399
00:16:02,920 --> 00:16:05,180
塔拉昨晚和他分手了
Tara broke up with him last night.

400
00:16:05,600 --> 00:16:08,390
-天哪  -他得知消息时我就在场
- Oh, my God. - I was there when it happened.

401
00:16:08,790 --> 00:16:12,090
这不是什么他能很快放下的事
This is not something that he's going to get over quickly.

402
00:16:12,710 --> 00:16:14,700
-你什么意见  -我建议
- So what are you saying? - I'm saying that

403
00:16:14,710 --> 00:16:16,480
应该由我接管助理
I think I should take over the associates

404
00:16:16,480 --> 00:16:19,450
直到他能控制好自己的情绪
until he's able to get his emotions under control.

405
00:16:19,450 --> 00:16:20,900
瑞秋  夺走他的助理
Rachel, taking the associates away

406
00:16:20,910 --> 00:16:22,540
可不是能稳定他的办法
isn't exactly gonna stabilize him.

407
00:16:22,540 --> 00:16:23,960
这是他仅剩的了
That's the one thing he has.

408
00:16:23,960 --> 00:16:25,410
我知道  但我必须说
Yeah, I know that, but I'm telling you,

409
00:16:25,420 --> 00:16:28,380
如果处理不好  肯定会有人报复他
if we're not careful, someone's gonna do something to him,

410
00:16:29,350 --> 00:16:31,560
到时候只是被告都得算他幸运了
and he'll be lucky if it's just suing him.

411
00:16:32,190 --> 00:16:33,240
这话你跟他说了吗
Did you tell him that?

412
00:16:33,240 --> 00:16:35,300
我去找他了  刚进他办公室
I tried to, and he bit my head off

413
00:16:35,300 --> 00:16:38,920
就被他一通痛骂  所以...
the minute I walked into his office, so...

414
00:16:39,200 --> 00:16:41,250
好  我去找他谈
Okay, I'll talk to him.

415
00:16:42,530 --> 00:16:45,330
但你得先把事情原原本本告诉我
But I'm gonna need you to tell me exactly what he did first.

416
00:16:53,630 --> 00:16:55,260
不管什么事我现在都没空  唐娜
Whatever it is, I don't have time, Donna.

417
00:16:55,260 --> 00:16:56,130
据我所知  你今早倒是有空
From what I heard, you had time

418
00:16:56,130 --> 00:16:57,680
去跟助理们发火呢
to go off on the associates this morning.

419
00:16:57,680 --> 00:16:58,970
谁跟你说的  胡扯
Who told you that? That's bullshit.

420
00:16:58,970 --> 00:17:00,830
你是说你没有冲布莱恩·阿特曼发火
Are you telling me you didn't go off on Brian Altman

421
00:17:00,830 --> 00:17:02,270
然后又对斯蒂芬妮·帕特尔的
and then make a horrible comment

422
00:17:02,270 --> 00:17:04,030
性生活进行了言辞激烈的评论吗
about Stephanie Patel's sex life?

423
00:17:04,030 --> 00:17:04,890
这叫管教  唐娜
It's called discipline, Donna.

424
00:17:04,890 --> 00:17:06,320
这叫可诉  路易
It's called actionable, Louis.

425
00:17:06,320 --> 00:17:07,440
你现在没有已经被告
You're lucky that there isn't a lawsuit

426
00:17:07,440 --> 00:17:08,310
已经是幸运了
on your desk right now.

427
00:17:08,310 --> 00:17:09,520
谢谢你的忠告
Well, thank you for your counsel.

428
00:17:09,520 --> 00:17:10,510
我知道我在做什么
I know what I'm doing.

429
00:17:10,510 --> 00:17:13,380
路易  我在努力体谅你
Louis, I am trying to be understanding,

430
00:17:14,250 --> 00:17:15,310
但我觉得
but I think Rachel should

431
00:17:15,310 --> 00:17:16,900
应该让瑞秋来负责助理们
handle the associates for right now.

432
00:17:16,900 --> 00:17:18,610
-你在开玩笑吗  -不  我没有
- Is that a joke? - No, it's not.

433
00:17:18,610 --> 00:17:20,410
那我来解释下
Well, then let me explain

434
00:17:20,410 --> 00:17:23,040
什么叫所谓的地位
a little something to you called pecking order.

435
00:17:23,480 --> 00:17:26,340
我在这里  瑞秋在这里
See, I am up here. Rachel's down here.

436
00:17:26,350 --> 00:17:28,500
你不能让处于这种低位置的人
And you don't give dominion over your associates

437
00:17:28,500 --> 00:17:29,650
来管理助理
to someone down here.

438
00:17:29,660 --> 00:17:30,970
我知道  但我还知道
I know that, but I also know that

439
00:17:30,980 --> 00:17:32,280
塔拉昨晚和你分手了
Tara broke up with you last night,

440
00:17:32,280 --> 00:17:33,290
所以你现在不在状态
and you're not in your right mind.

441
00:17:33,290 --> 00:17:34,310
我不想再听到这个名字了
I don't want to hear that name again.

442
00:17:34,310 --> 00:17:37,130
路易  我想说的是如果你解决此事
Louis, all I'm saying is if you don't deal with it,

443
00:17:37,130 --> 00:17:39,000
你会一直虐待助理们
you're gonna keep abusing the associates,

444
00:17:39,000 --> 00:17:39,660
-他们将会...  -唐娜  我告诉你
- and then we're gonna have-- - Hey, Donna, you know what,

445
00:17:39,660 --> 00:17:40,720
我本来不想这么做
I didn't want to do this,

446
00:17:40,720 --> 00:17:42,980
但刚才我没有提这件事
but I did leave one name off the chart.

447
00:17:42,980 --> 00:17:46,410
我  瑞秋  你
Me. Rachel. You.

448
00:17:46,420 --> 00:17:49,850
所以你也没资格告诉我我该怎么做
So don't you tell me what to do.

449
00:17:52,590 --> 00:17:53,500
路易  我就不揪着你这句话了
Louis, I'm gonna let that go,

450
00:17:53,500 --> 00:17:55,180
因为我知道你现在很受伤
because I know you're hurting,

451
00:17:56,440 --> 00:17:58,500
但是恰恰证明我说的是对的
but that right there is exactly why I'm right,

452
00:17:58,500 --> 00:18:01,090
因为如果你跟我都这么说话
because if you're willing to talk to me like that,

453
00:18:01,970 --> 00:18:03,900
那你对助理们的态度真的要惨不忍睹了
God help those associates.

454
00:18:19,410 --> 00:18:21,690
-喂  -是感觉良好医生吗
- Hello? - Yes, is this Dr. Feelgood?

455
00:18:21,690 --> 00:18:23,060
我想预约一次谈话
'Cause I'd like to schedule an appointment

456
00:18:23,060 --> 00:18:24,050
越快越好
as soon as possible.

457
00:18:24,050 --> 00:18:25,320
抱歉  你打错电话了
I'm sorry. You've got the wrong number.

458
00:18:25,320 --> 00:18:27,610
我是我有正事要做医生
This is Dr. I Have Work to Do.

459
00:18:27,610 --> 00:18:29,790
既然这样  我想预约一次谈话
Well, in that case, I'd like to schedule an appointment

460
00:18:29,790 --> 00:18:31,660
越快越好
as soon as possible.

461
00:18:32,790 --> 00:18:34,570
哈维  你到底为什么给我打电话
Harvey, why exactly are you calling me?

462
00:18:34,580 --> 00:18:35,900
首先  先回答我
First, answer me this:

463
00:18:35,900 --> 00:18:37,260
自从你答应我之后
how many times have you considered

464
00:18:37,260 --> 00:18:38,630
几次想要拿起电话
picking up the phone and telling me that

465
00:18:38,640 --> 00:18:41,100
告诉我你后悔了
you've reconsidered since you said yes?

466
00:18:41,100 --> 00:18:43,070
四次  如果不算现在这次的话
Four. If you don't count right now.

467
00:18:43,070 --> 00:18:44,810
这么说吧  我打给你的原因是
Then let's just say I'm calling to tell you

468
00:18:44,810 --> 00:18:47,830
我刚刚和一屋子模特待了一个小时
that I've been in a room full of models for the last hour,

469
00:18:47,840 --> 00:18:50,090
然而我脑海里想的都是你
and all I can think of is you.

470
00:18:51,070 --> 00:18:53,460
还在考虑拒绝我吗
Still thinking of cancelling on me?

471
00:18:53,470 --> 00:18:55,070
不  哈维
No, Harvey.

472
00:18:56,450 --> 00:18:58,670
我也期待我们的晚餐
I'm looking forward to our dinner as well.

473
00:19:11,560 --> 00:19:12,940
你是不是把我们的婚礼日子提前了
Did you move up the date of our wedding

474
00:19:12,940 --> 00:19:14,630
还忘了告诉我
and forget to tell me?

475
00:19:14,750 --> 00:19:16,840
不是  我打扮成这样是因为
No, I got to get dressed up for this thing

476
00:19:16,840 --> 00:19:18,900
我和哈维要去见个客户
that Harvey and I are going to for a client.

477
00:19:18,900 --> 00:19:21,930
为了一位客户打扮
A thing for a client.

478
00:19:21,930 --> 00:19:23,970
说的一点都不特别
That's not very specific.

479
00:19:23,970 --> 00:19:26,220
我的意思是  这事不好解释
Uh, yeah, I mean, it's just kind of hard to explain.

480
00:19:26,220 --> 00:19:27,820
这事是不是和三十六名模特
Hmm, does it involve three dozen models

481
00:19:27,820 --> 00:19:29,710
加一堆伏特加有关
and 1,000 bottles of vodka?

482
00:19:34,840 --> 00:19:36,970
看来也不没那么难解释
I guess it's not that hard to explain.

483
00:19:36,980 --> 00:19:38,050
你打算什么时候告诉我
When were you gonna tell me?

484
00:19:38,050 --> 00:19:41,800
如果不是提前说  那肯定是之后说
If not before, then definitely after...

485
00:19:42,020 --> 00:19:44,080
或者根本不说  不太好说
or never. It's hard to tell.

486
00:19:44,080 --> 00:19:45,950
我还没认真想过
I haven't really thought this through.

487
00:19:45,950 --> 00:19:48,680
-你知道我在开玩笑  对吧  -是的
- You know I'm kidding, right? - Yes.

488
00:19:49,870 --> 00:19:51,750
-你也应该来  -我去不了
- You should come. - I can't.

489
00:19:51,750 --> 00:19:54,100
我和卡特里娜忙着帮齐本德尔剧团上市
Katrina and I are taking the Chippendales public,

490
00:19:54,100 --> 00:19:55,960
我们要去见几位他们那里的首席舞者
so we're gonna meet with a few of their top dancers

491
00:19:55,960 --> 00:19:58,420
做一些文书工作  估计要忙一晚上
to go over some paperwork. Probably take all night.

492
00:19:58,420 --> 00:20:00,650
-一点意思都没有  -是的  没有
- So that's not funny. - Yes, it is.

493
00:20:01,130 --> 00:20:02,540
我认真的  瑞秋  你应该一起去
I'm serious, Rachel, you should come.

494
00:20:02,540 --> 00:20:04,490
哈维好像搞了一架直升机
I think Harvey got a helicopter.

495
00:20:04,490 --> 00:20:06,850
我们可以坐直升机环绕城市
We should take a ride around the city.

496
00:20:08,510 --> 00:20:10,350
我去不了  你去吧
I can't. You go.

497
00:20:10,350 --> 00:20:13,380
说来话长  短版本就是...
It's a long story. I ju--

498
00:20:13,890 --> 00:20:16,100
我可能要接管所有助理
I might be taking over the associates,

499
00:20:16,100 --> 00:20:18,480
果真能如此  我希望提前做好准备
and if I do, I just want to be prepared.

500
00:20:18,480 --> 00:20:20,320
太棒了  瑞秋  但你这是说
Rachel, that's amazing, but are you telling me

501
00:20:20,330 --> 00:20:22,380
路易真的愿意放手吗
that Louis is really ready to give that up?

502
00:20:22,380 --> 00:20:24,520
那个就是长版本
That's the long story.

503
00:20:24,620 --> 00:20:26,740
但是我晚一点会告诉你的
But I'll tell you about it later tonight.

504
00:20:27,680 --> 00:20:29,060
-我可以留下  -不  你应该去...
- I can stay. - No, you should go--

505
00:20:29,060 --> 00:20:30,890
太好了
Great, okay.

506
00:20:32,810 --> 00:20:34,970
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.

507
00:20:42,850 --> 00:20:45,000
唐娜  在你走之前  能和你说几句吗
Donna, before you leave, can I talk to you for a second?

508
00:20:45,000 --> 00:20:45,860
又怎么了
What is it now?

509
00:20:45,870 --> 00:20:47,900
公司的咖啡滤纸不够了吗
We're running low on coffee filters?

510
00:20:47,900 --> 00:20:49,170
找不到糖了吗
Can't find the Sweet 'n Low?

511
00:20:49,170 --> 00:20:51,430
还是路易终于因为太混蛋被告了
Or is Louis finally being sued for being an asshole?

512
00:20:51,430 --> 00:20:53,000
你想告诉我发生了什么
You want to tell me what's going on,

513
00:20:53,000 --> 00:20:54,640
还是你想一直继续
or you want to keep firing your pistol

514
00:20:54,640 --> 00:20:56,320
攻击同盟
in the wrong direction?

515
00:20:56,320 --> 00:20:57,880
抱歉  格蕾琴
I'm sorry, Gretchen.

516
00:20:59,320 --> 00:21:02,200
我真的厌烦了大家总来找我解决问题
I am just sick and tired of being everyone's go-to

517
00:21:02,200 --> 00:21:03,780
但我却得不到我想要的
and not getting what I ask for.

518
00:21:03,780 --> 00:21:05,590
我不想让你觉得我漠不关心
I don't mean to sound insensitive,

519
00:21:05,590 --> 00:21:07,470
但是你是企业秘书
but you're a corporate secretary.

520
00:21:07,470 --> 00:21:09,920
你到底期望些什么
What exactly did you expect?

521
00:21:10,620 --> 00:21:12,300
你真的想知道吗
You really want to know?

522
00:21:15,110 --> 00:21:17,370
我问哈维要了上桌的资格
I asked Harvey for a seat at the table.

523
00:21:17,380 --> 00:21:19,580
-什么桌子  -合伙人的桌子
- What table? - The partnership table.

524
00:21:19,580 --> 00:21:21,120
怪不得他拒绝了你
No wonder he shot you down.

525
00:21:21,120 --> 00:21:22,240
他没有拒绝我
He didn't shoot me down.

526
00:21:22,250 --> 00:21:23,370
他跟我说他要考虑一下
He told me he would think about it,

527
00:21:23,370 --> 00:21:25,810
但还没答复  我都不知道他还会不会答复
but I haven't heard anything, and I don't know now if I will.

528
00:21:25,810 --> 00:21:27,680
有个得到他注意的办法  是去他办公室
One way to get his attention is to go in there

529
00:21:27,680 --> 00:21:29,820
拿起你给他的支票  然后撕掉
and take that check you gave him and rip it the hell up.

530
00:21:29,830 --> 00:21:31,410
-什么支票  -你给他的入股公司
- What check? - The check you gave him

531
00:21:31,410 --> 00:21:33,610
做合伙人的资金
for your partnership money.

532
00:21:33,790 --> 00:21:35,790
-你没给他是吗  -没有
- You didn't give him one, did you? - No.

533
00:21:35,790 --> 00:21:37,470
红毛  我告诉你
Let me tell you something, Red.

534
00:21:37,470 --> 00:21:39,130
你想要上桌儿
You want a seat at the table,

535
00:21:39,130 --> 00:21:41,700
就得下点本儿
you got to put some skin in the game.

536
00:22:00,200 --> 00:22:02,360
终于来了  哈维
There he is. Hey, Harvey,

537
00:22:02,360 --> 00:22:03,560
这是个好主意
This was a great idea, huh?

538
00:22:03,570 --> 00:22:05,390
-很高兴我想出了这个点字  -开心吗
- Glad I thought of it. - Are we having fun?

539
00:22:05,390 --> 00:22:07,220
如果你觉得和一名叫斯维特拉娜的模特
If you call talking geopolitics

540
00:22:07,220 --> 00:22:08,950
聊地缘政治学算开心
with a model named Svetlana fun,

541
00:22:08,950 --> 00:22:11,230
那就没错  非常开心
then that would be a big, fat bowl of yes.

542
00:22:11,230 --> 00:22:14,310
镇定  小老虎  酒保在倒酒了
Easy, tiger. The bartender's pouring doubles.

543
00:22:14,710 --> 00:22:15,720
那你又是来干什么的
And what are you doing here?

544
00:22:15,720 --> 00:22:17,990
我要再来一杯  我是让你小心别醉了
I'm having another drink. I said for you to be careful.

545
00:22:17,990 --> 00:22:19,660
-我不会醉的  -好吧
- I can handle my liquor. - Okay.

546
00:22:19,660 --> 00:22:21,450
我举了几根手指
How many fingers am I holding up?

547
00:22:22,860 --> 00:22:24,070
你看不出来吧
You can't tell, can you?

548
00:22:24,070 --> 00:22:26,110
谁说不会醉来着
Who can't handle my liquor now?

549
00:22:26,760 --> 00:22:29,000
我想让你吃点东西  但不巧的是
I'd tell you to put food in your stomach, but unfortunately,

550
00:22:29,000 --> 00:22:30,240
我只点了些
I only ordered enough

551
00:22:30,240 --> 00:22:32,050
用来装点门面的食物
to give the appearance of having food.

552
00:22:32,050 --> 00:22:33,370
所以总的来说  你只想
So basically, you're just trying to get

553
00:22:33,370 --> 00:22:35,900
把这些家伙灌醉来让你哄抬标价
these guys hammered so you can drive up the bidding.

554
00:22:35,900 --> 00:22:36,970
不  我说过了
No. I told you,

555
00:22:36,980 --> 00:22:39,480
那些调戏模特的家伙都不是认真的
the guys hitting on the models aren't serious.

556
00:22:39,480 --> 00:22:41,090
-现在我告诉你...  -那些想把
- Now I'm telling you... - That the guys

557
00:22:41,090 --> 00:22:43,460
自己灌醉的家伙也不是认真的
who let themselves get drunk aren't serious,

558
00:22:43,460 --> 00:22:44,920
也就是说那些没醉的
which means whoever's left are the bids

559
00:22:44,930 --> 00:22:47,110
才是我们今晚要拿下的投标人
that we have in our hands at the end of the night.

560
00:22:47,530 --> 00:22:48,670
你早就知道了  对吗
You knew it the whole time, didn't you?

561
00:22:48,670 --> 00:22:50,020
不看看和你说话的是谁
Who do you think you're talking to?

562
00:22:50,020 --> 00:22:51,370
好伙计
Good man.

563
00:22:51,840 --> 00:22:53,800
有一个小问题
There's just one small problem.

564
00:22:54,140 --> 00:22:57,230
如果  我一不小心成了那些
What if, by accident, I happen to be one of the people

565
00:22:57,230 --> 00:22:59,610
灌醉自己的家伙怎么办
that let himself get too drunk?

566
00:23:00,060 --> 00:23:01,350
你只管放开了喝
You just might as well keep drinking,

567
00:23:01,350 --> 00:23:02,260
如果我们玩的不尽兴
'cause if we're not having fun,

568
00:23:02,260 --> 00:23:03,650
那何苦待在这里
what the hell are we doing here?

569
00:23:03,650 --> 00:23:05,330
好极了  明白
Yes! Copy that.

570
00:23:05,330 --> 00:23:06,820
斯维特拉娜
Svetlana...

571
00:23:15,510 --> 00:23:18,000
你清楚这间办公室不会自己收拾好的  对吧
You know this office isn't gonna pack itself up, right?

572
00:23:18,000 --> 00:23:19,290
还没收拾是因为我们其中之一
It's not packed because one of us

573
00:23:19,290 --> 00:23:20,910
之前三小时一直在工作
has been at work for the last three hours.

574
00:23:20,910 --> 00:23:22,590
另一个不过是为了昨晚的工作
The other one of us was sleeping off

575
00:23:22,590 --> 00:23:23,990
好好睡了一觉
all the work he did last night.

576
00:23:23,990 --> 00:23:26,170
你是说你伏特加喝的宿醉未醒
You mean you're hung over from all the vodka you drank?

577
00:23:26,170 --> 00:23:28,070
没错  我就是这个意思
Yeah, that's what I just said.

578
00:23:28,330 --> 00:23:29,810
我真不该请你回来
I never should have hired you back.

579
00:23:29,810 --> 00:23:31,950
现在想解雇我已经晚了
Well, it's too late to fire me now.

580
00:23:32,250 --> 00:23:33,030
是吗
Is it?

581
00:23:33,030 --> 00:23:35,320
因为如果你对得起你的薪资
Because if you were worth your salary,

582
00:23:35,320 --> 00:23:37,030
你会问我们找到几个投标人了
you'd ask how many bids we're sitting on.

583
00:23:37,030 --> 00:23:39,780
没必要问  我有脑子
I don't have to ask, because I've got this.

584
00:23:40,980 --> 00:23:42,720
访客名单上有500人
Guest list was 500,

585
00:23:42,720 --> 00:23:44,250
有一半是冲着模特来的
and half of them came for the girls.

586
00:23:44,250 --> 00:23:46,440
剩下的有一半没什么钱
Half of the other half don't have the capital,

587
00:23:46,440 --> 00:23:48,130
其中有百分之六十醒来后
and 60% of the rest of them woke up

588
00:23:48,140 --> 00:23:50,770
觉得他们并不想掺和酒业
realizing they don't want to work in the liquor business.

589
00:23:50,780 --> 00:23:52,400
就算  我不确定
Take, I don't know, what,

590
00:23:52,400 --> 00:23:54,980
最多47个来竞争
47 off the top for good measure?

591
00:23:54,980 --> 00:23:57,670
最后我们能收到的也就三个竞价
Leaves us with three bids.

592
00:23:59,050 --> 00:24:01,330
-唐娜跟你说了  对吗  -可能吧
- Donna told you, didn't she? - Probably.

593
00:24:01,330 --> 00:24:02,960
她有没有让你过来做点什么
Did she bother telling you what we're doing now?

594
00:24:02,960 --> 00:24:05,080
-不用她说  你可是哈维·斯佩克特
- She didn't have to, 'cause you're Harvey Specter.

595
00:24:05,080 --> 00:24:07,610
你也就那一招  几年前已经传授给我了
You've got one trick, and you taught it to me years ago,

596
00:24:07,620 --> 00:24:09,030
我们走吧
so let's go.

597
00:24:13,420 --> 00:24:15,110
你知道我可不只一招  对吧
You know I have more than one trick, right?

598
00:24:15,110 --> 00:24:16,440
不  我知道你以为是这样
No, I know you think you do,

599
00:24:16,440 --> 00:24:17,840
但是新瓶里装的
but just because you put on a different costume

600
00:24:17,840 --> 00:24:19,120
可不一定是新酒
doesn't make it a different trick.

601
00:24:19,120 --> 00:24:21,450
好吧  你还是喝醉时比较讨喜
Yeah, I liked you better when you were drunk.

602
00:24:21,450 --> 00:24:23,440
我喝醉时你也更讨喜
I liked you better when I was drunk too.

603
00:24:25,130 --> 00:24:26,730
我不管他们怎么说  都是胡扯
I don't care what they say. This is bullshit,

604
00:24:26,730 --> 00:24:28,140
我不想被耍的团团转
and I'm not gonna get played.

605
00:24:28,140 --> 00:24:30,930
先生们  不好意思  我第一天上班
Gentlemen, we're so sorry. It's my first day.

606
00:24:30,930 --> 00:24:32,350
很显然  我和哈维同一时间
Evidently, I booked the conference room

607
00:24:32,350 --> 00:24:34,100
-订了这间会议室  -胡说
- at the same time as Harvey. - Bullshit.

608
00:24:34,100 --> 00:24:35,370
你们以为我们不知道你们的打算吗
You think we don't know what's going on here?

609
00:24:35,370 --> 00:24:37,420
你们订一间会议室是想逼我们出更高的价
You double booked the room to scare us into overbidding.

610
00:24:37,420 --> 00:24:38,360
你说得对  我们早该想到
You're right. We should have known

611
00:24:38,360 --> 00:24:39,880
像你们这些精明人士
a couple of smart guys like you

612
00:24:39,890 --> 00:24:42,060
绝不会上这种愚蠢的当
would never fall for the banana in the tailpipe.

613
00:24:42,060 --> 00:24:43,300
我们带你们来这里是因为
We brought you down here just because you were

614
00:24:43,300 --> 00:24:45,550
只有你们两人出价一亿
the only two bidders who came in at 100 million,

615
00:24:45,560 --> 00:24:47,300
所以现在  你们两个好好看看
so now, you have to look each other in the eye

616
00:24:47,300 --> 00:24:48,450
旗鼓相当的对方
while you go head-to-head.

617
00:24:48,450 --> 00:24:49,910
接下来会这样
So here's what's gonna happen:

618
00:24:49,910 --> 00:24:53,160
你们有一次机会写下你们的最高竞价
you got one chance to write down your best bid.

619
00:24:53,160 --> 00:24:54,950
赢家通吃  输家走人
Winner takes all, loser goes home.

620
00:24:54,950 --> 00:24:56,280
我们15分钟后见
We'll be back in 15 minutes,

621
00:24:56,280 --> 00:24:58,780
希望能看到更高的竞价
and we better see some more zeroes.

622
00:24:59,170 --> 00:25:01,410
如果我们串通呢  就在这儿
What if we collude, right here?

623
00:25:01,410 --> 00:25:03,100
你们最多能拿到一亿
Stick at 100 and you're shit out of luck?

624
00:25:03,110 --> 00:25:04,330
顺便一说  这恰恰是
Which, by the way, is exactly why

625
00:25:04,330 --> 00:25:06,050
你们不订一间会议室的原因
you don't double book a conference room.

626
00:25:06,050 --> 00:25:07,450
这里只有一个问题
There's only one problem with that.

627
00:25:07,450 --> 00:25:08,290
当我们说只有你们
When we said you two were

628
00:25:08,290 --> 00:25:09,940
出价一亿时
the only ones that came in at 100,

629
00:25:09,940 --> 00:25:12,380
我们没说没人出更高的价
we didn't say there wasn't someone who put down more.

630
00:25:13,140 --> 00:25:14,720
-阿克谢罗德  -没错
- Axelrod. - Bingo.

631
00:25:14,720 --> 00:25:16,260
二次竞价20分钟前就来了
Second bid came in 20 minutes ago.

632
00:25:16,260 --> 00:25:18,490
所以如果你们想串通的话  请便
So if you two want to collude, go right ahead,

633
00:25:18,490 --> 00:25:21,590
但是你们最好出价远超过一亿
but it better be for a hell of a lot more than 100 million.

634
00:25:26,000 --> 00:25:28,070
-进展如何  -这要看情况了
- How'd it go? - That depends.

635
00:25:28,070 --> 00:25:31,820
-阿克谢罗德二次竞价是多少  -两亿
- What was Axelrod's second bid? - 200 million.

636
00:25:31,820 --> 00:25:32,960
这样的话进展如何都不重要了
Well, then it doesn't really matter how it went,

637
00:25:32,970 --> 00:25:35,080
因为不管这些小丑出价多少
because whatever those clowns come up with,

638
00:25:35,080 --> 00:25:37,080
尼尔·斯蒂尔曼都会抱回大笔现金
Neil Stillman's walking away with a boatload of cash.

639
00:25:37,080 --> 00:25:39,160
说到大笔现金...
Speaking of boatloads of cash...

640
00:25:44,100 --> 00:25:45,230
这是张50万的支票
It's a check for half a million dollars.

641
00:25:45,230 --> 00:25:46,480
我告诉过你我是真的想要
I told you I was serious about

642
00:25:46,480 --> 00:25:47,730
成为合伙人  我也真的是认真的
becoming a partner, and I am.

643
00:25:47,730 --> 00:25:49,070
-唐娜...  -哈维  说实话
- Donna... - Harvey, be honest.

644
00:25:49,070 --> 00:25:50,080
你还没考虑过我们
You haven't given one thought to

645
00:25:50,080 --> 00:25:51,200
昨天讨论过的事
what we talked about yesterday.

646
00:25:51,200 --> 00:25:52,040
我最近有点忙
I've been a little busy.

647
00:25:52,040 --> 00:25:53,550
你总想岔开这个话题
And you've also been avoiding the subject.

648
00:25:53,550 --> 00:25:55,520
这么一来  你就得认真对待了
This way, you have to take me seriously.

649
00:25:55,520 --> 00:25:57,040
我有认真对待此事
I do take you seriously.

650
00:25:57,040 --> 00:25:58,530
那就去路易的办公室
Then walk the hell down to Louis' office

651
00:25:58,540 --> 00:25:59,550
告诉他我要当合伙人
and tell him I'm a partner.

652
00:25:59,560 --> 00:26:01,880
唐娜  我不能把每个决定直接
Donna, I can't just ram every decision

653
00:26:01,880 --> 00:26:03,170
-通知给他  -每个决定
- down his throat. -Every decision?

654
00:26:03,170 --> 00:26:04,600
你到现在还没告诉他你要坐上
You haven't even told him that you're stepping

655
00:26:04,600 --> 00:26:05,920
杰西卡的位置
into Jessica's shoes yet.

656
00:26:05,920 --> 00:26:07,140
我在等合适的时机
I'm waiting for the right time.

657
00:26:07,140 --> 00:26:08,410
如果我是合伙人的话  我会告诉你
And if I were a partner, I would tell you that

658
00:26:08,410 --> 00:26:10,220
-昨天就是绝佳时机  -唐娜... 
- the right time was yesterday. - Donna...

659
00:26:10,220 --> 00:26:12,770
哈维  你觉得我在要你可怜我吗  我没有
Harvey, you think I'm asking for charity, I'm not.

660
00:26:12,770 --> 00:26:14,460
我要你为我这些年做过的事
I am asking for you to make official

661
00:26:14,460 --> 00:26:16,720
给我个交代
what I have been doing for years anyway,

662
00:26:16,720 --> 00:26:18,560
也就是给你出谋划策  就像你需要
which is giving you advice, like you need to step

663
00:26:18,560 --> 00:26:20,440
去告诉路易你是这儿的老大
the hell up and tell Louis that you're in charge,

664
00:26:20,440 --> 00:26:22,560
现在  不管你接不接受
and right this second, you're either gonna take that advice,

665
00:26:22,560 --> 00:26:25,450
这个建议  现在你应该
or you're not, but it is time

666
00:26:26,190 --> 00:26:28,110
对我的工作
that you recognize me

667
00:26:28,600 --> 00:26:30,220
予以认可了
for what I do.

668
00:26:40,220 --> 00:26:42,300
我哥哥托马斯比我聪明
My brother Thomas is the clever one.

669
00:26:42,560 --> 00:26:43,780
在剑桥教书
Teaches at Cambridge.

670
00:26:43,780 --> 00:26:46,220
一周工作20小时  暑假休息
20 hours a week, summers off.

671
00:26:47,330 --> 00:26:49,630
你没在听我说话  对吗
You're not listening to a word I'm saying, are you?

672
00:26:52,690 --> 00:26:54,840
-我很抱歉  -你是该道歉
- I'm sorry. - Well, you should be.

673
00:26:55,700 --> 00:26:58,060
大家都说我还挺招人喜欢的
I've been told I'm actually quite delightful.

674
00:26:58,430 --> 00:27:00,840
你确实是  我只是有点分心了
You are. I'm just a little distracted.

675
00:27:00,840 --> 00:27:02,470
开胃菜才吃了一半
Halfway through appetizers.

676
00:27:02,470 --> 00:27:04,150
等到酒浸烧烤端上桌来
Doesn't bode very well for how you'll be feeling

677
00:27:04,150 --> 00:27:06,000
-就不知道你会怎样了  -不是你想的那样
- when our flambé arrives. - It's not that.

678
00:27:06,000 --> 00:27:07,850
杰西卡上个月离开了事务所
Jessica left the firm last month.

679
00:27:07,850 --> 00:27:09,680
大家都认为我是继承人
Everyone assumes that I'm next in line,

680
00:27:09,680 --> 00:27:11,550
而现在唐娜又来告诉我  如果我不快点
and now I've got Donna telling me that if I don't step up...

681
00:27:11,550 --> 00:27:13,520
等等  我以为你有一天早上说过
Wait a second, I thought you told me as of the other morning

682
00:27:13,520 --> 00:27:14,730
你现在已经是公司老大了
that you're now head of the firm.

683
00:27:14,730 --> 00:27:16,500
确实是  只是我还没告诉路易
I am. I just haven't told Louis yet,

684
00:27:16,500 --> 00:27:18,100
而唐娜逼着不放
and Donna won't let it go.

685
00:27:18,370 --> 00:27:20,310
我觉得这次见面就是个错误
I think this may have been a mistake.

686
00:27:20,310 --> 00:27:22,250
-什么  -你不是来和我约会的
- What? - You didn't come to me to date me,

687
00:27:22,250 --> 00:27:23,480
你来找我是因为你正处于另一场危机
you came to me because you're in the middle

688
00:27:23,480 --> 00:27:25,850
而你需要我来帮你度过它
of another crisis and you need me to walk you through it.

689
00:27:25,850 --> 00:27:26,500
才不是这样
That's not true.

690
00:27:26,500 --> 00:27:27,570
你当然不这样想
Of course you don't think it's true.

691
00:27:27,570 --> 00:27:28,920
如果你这样想  你就会给我办公室打电话
If you did, you would have called my office

692
00:27:28,920 --> 00:27:31,100
-来预约治疗了  -我不需要预约
- and made an appointment. - I don't need an appointment.

693
00:27:31,100 --> 00:27:33,080
我是要和你分享生活中的事情
I'm sharing things about my life.

694
00:27:33,080 --> 00:27:35,420
据我所知  人们约会的时候就是这样做的
Last time I checked, that's what people do on dates.

695
00:27:35,420 --> 00:27:37,900
这没错  哈维  但是第一次约会的时候
Yes, it's what they do, Harvey, but on first dates,

696
00:27:37,900 --> 00:27:40,830
人们也会尽力让对方感觉到他们很特别
they also try to make the other person feel special

697
00:27:40,830 --> 00:27:42,880
-而且有人愿意听他们说话  -宝拉
- and listened to. - Paula--

698
00:27:42,880 --> 00:27:44,820
你知道为什么  心理医生与客户约会
Do you know why it's unethical for a therapist

699
00:27:44,830 --> 00:27:46,180
是违反职业道德的吗  哈维
to go out with her client, Harvey?

700
00:27:46,180 --> 00:27:47,310
当然知道了
Yeah, of course I do.

701
00:27:47,310 --> 00:27:49,410
因为客户会自然而然地
It's because it's natural for a client

702
00:27:49,410 --> 00:27:50,810
将不真实的情感和爱意
to transfer feelings of desire

703
00:27:50,820 --> 00:27:52,500
转移到心理医生身上
onto his therapist that aren't real.

704
00:27:52,500 --> 00:27:54,130
-我知道这一点  -但你不知道的是
- I know that. - What you may not know

705
00:27:54,130 --> 00:27:55,570
心理医生有这样的移情
is that it's not unnatural

706
00:27:55,570 --> 00:27:58,060
也是再正常不过的
for a therapist to feel the same way.

707
00:27:58,720 --> 00:28:01,040
你以为我对你就没抱过幻想吗
You don't think I've had fantasies about you?

708
00:28:01,040 --> 00:28:02,900
幻想着有一天  当我晚上准备回家的时候
That one day you'd show up at my office

709
00:28:02,900 --> 00:28:04,260
你会出现在我的办公室
as I was heading home for the night,

710
00:28:04,260 --> 00:28:06,670
我一转头就会看见你
and I turn around, and you'd be there.

711
00:28:06,770 --> 00:28:08,780
你什么都不说
You wouldn't say a word, but...

712
00:28:08,950 --> 00:28:11,470
把我拥入怀中  开始吻我
you'd take me in your arms and kiss me, and...

713
00:28:13,000 --> 00:28:15,420
而那将是一段特别的感情的开端
it would actually be the start of something special.

714
00:28:15,430 --> 00:28:16,430
我有过这些幻想
Well, I have,

715
00:28:17,390 --> 00:28:18,830
所以  虽然我有更好的判断力
which is why despite my better judgment,

716
00:28:18,830 --> 00:28:20,120
我还是来和你约会了
I'm here with you right now.

717
00:28:20,220 --> 00:28:22,980
-所以说问题在哪  -问题是在这些幻想中
- So what's the problem? - The problem is those fantasies

718
00:28:22,980 --> 00:28:24,530
我不应该是你的心理医生
weren't of me being a therapist to a man

719
00:28:24,530 --> 00:28:26,870
而你害怕到不敢承认自己需要帮助
who's still too afraid to admit that he needs help,

720
00:28:26,890 --> 00:28:29,520
更别说是掌控一家以你冠名的事务所了
much less take control of a firm that bears his name.

721
00:28:31,360 --> 00:28:33,050
谢谢你的晚餐  哈维
Thank you for dinner, Harvey.

722
00:28:33,200 --> 00:28:35,250
如果你需要治疗  请给我办公室打电话
If you need a session, call my office.

723
00:28:35,250 --> 00:28:37,250
遗憾的是  我不能再当你的治疗师了
Unfortunately, I can't see you anymore,

724
00:28:37,810 --> 00:28:39,040
但我可以给你推荐一些
but I can give you a recommendation

725
00:28:39,040 --> 00:28:40,190
可能的人选
for someone who can.

726
00:28:54,520 --> 00:28:55,940
-路易  我能做什么  -为我吗
- Louis, what can I do-- - Do for me?

727
00:28:55,940 --> 00:28:57,940
你可以告诉我  今后你对我再有什么不满
You could tell me from now on if you have a problem with me,

728
00:28:57,940 --> 00:29:00,570
你可以和我当面说  别在我背后捣鼓
you'll take it up with me instead of going behind my back.

729
00:29:00,570 --> 00:29:01,480
-什么  -这就对了
- What? - That's right.

730
00:29:01,480 --> 00:29:02,620
你以为我不知道这件事吗
You think I don't know the whole

731
00:29:02,620 --> 00:29:04,460
"瑞秋应该负责我的助理律师"这种狗屁
"Rachel should be in charge of my associates"

732
00:29:04,460 --> 00:29:06,380
是你说的  而不是唐娜
bullshit came from you and not Donna?

733
00:29:06,410 --> 00:29:08,530
没错  是我说的
You're right. It was from me.

734
00:29:08,960 --> 00:29:12,290
我最先来找的你  而你把我凶惨了
And I came to you first, and you bit my head off.

735
00:29:12,940 --> 00:29:15,020
那我就换种
Well, then let me tell you in a way

736
00:29:15,130 --> 00:29:17,380
不会伤害你这小可人的方式来说
that won't harm your pretty little head,

737
00:29:17,380 --> 00:29:20,690
我都忘了你有多娇贵了
because I clearly forgot what a delicate little flower you are.

738
00:29:20,690 --> 00:29:22,400
这些助理都是我的
Those associates are mine,

739
00:29:22,400 --> 00:29:23,900
除非等我死了那天  你来从我手里撬走
and the only way you're ever gonna get them

740
00:29:23,900 --> 00:29:26,760
否则你永远别想拿到
is if you pry them from my cold, dead hands.

741
00:29:44,730 --> 00:29:46,600
唐娜  除非是紧急情况
Donna, unless it's an emergency--

742
00:29:46,600 --> 00:29:47,700
这就是紧急情况
It is an emergency.

743
00:29:47,700 --> 00:29:49,640
我需要知道我的事你办得怎么样了  哈维
Harvey, I need to know what you're doing about me.

744
00:29:49,640 --> 00:29:51,810
唐娜  现在时机不对
Donna, right this second is not the time.

745
00:29:51,810 --> 00:29:53,340
时机正对  要是没人尽快
It is the time, because if somebody doesn't

746
00:29:53,340 --> 00:29:55,280
对路易采取行动
do something about Louis soon,

747
00:29:55,290 --> 00:29:58,140
事务所就要被自己的助理起诉了
this firm is gonna end up being sued by our own associates.

748
00:29:58,140 --> 00:30:00,140
我没有权限做什么
I don't have the authority to do anything,

749
00:30:00,140 --> 00:30:02,080
而你都不知道我说的是怎么回事
and you don't even know what I'm talking about.

750
00:30:03,720 --> 00:30:04,800
好吧  唐娜
Okay, Donna.

751
00:30:05,770 --> 00:30:08,160
你赢了  你是合伙人了
You win. You're a partner.

752
00:30:21,110 --> 00:30:21,910
哈维
Harvey.

753
00:30:22,940 --> 00:30:23,820
我们有麻烦了
We got a problem.

754
00:30:25,680 --> 00:30:26,630
这次又是什么
What is it now?

755
00:30:26,850 --> 00:30:27,750
你看一下
Take a look.

756
00:30:30,240 --> 00:30:31,360
你是从哪儿拿到的
Where'd you get this?

757
00:30:31,950 --> 00:30:33,440
我从哪拿到的不是重点
It doesn't matter where I got it.

758
00:30:33,440 --> 00:30:34,390
重点是文件已经传出来了
It's out there.

759
00:30:34,920 --> 00:30:36,560
你又不能确定尼尔知道
You can't be sure Neil knew this.

760
00:30:36,560 --> 00:30:37,580
这有什么区别吗
What difference does that make?

761
00:30:37,580 --> 00:30:38,910
因为如果他不知道的话
Because if he didn't know,

762
00:30:38,910 --> 00:30:41,570
-就只是倒霉了  -哈维  他可是首席执行官
- it's just bad luck. - Harvey, he's the goddamn CEO.

763
00:30:41,580 --> 00:30:43,190
他知道  他瞒着我们
He knew. He kept it from us,

764
00:30:43,190 --> 00:30:44,800
而且他还瞒着那些收购他公司的人
and he kept it from the guys buying his company.

765
00:30:44,800 --> 00:30:46,460
-这你可不知道  -我知道的
- You don't know that. - Yes, I do.

766
00:30:46,460 --> 00:30:48,050
我也知道你还有时间去阻止
I also know you still have time to go stop

767
00:30:48,050 --> 00:30:49,900
-这次收购  -你是在开玩笑吧
- this sale from going through. - Are you kidding?

768
00:30:49,900 --> 00:30:52,240
文件已经签了  收购已经完成了
They signed the documents. It's already gone through.

769
00:30:52,240 --> 00:30:53,730
款项还没转手
Money hasn't changed hands yet,

770
00:30:53,730 --> 00:30:55,530
所以你还有时间
so you still have time to stop it.

771
00:30:56,500 --> 00:30:58,380
-迈克  -哈维  如果你不过去
- Mike-- - Harvey, if you don't get over there

772
00:30:58,380 --> 00:31:01,720
-在转手之前找到  -好了  我会处理的
- and find out before-- - All right. I'll handle it.

773
00:31:02,170 --> 00:31:05,490
-你要去哪儿  -我要和路易谈谈
- And where are you going? - I need to talk to Louis.

774
00:31:05,490 --> 00:31:07,470
不管是什么事  都要等到明天
Whatever it is, it's gonna have to wait until tomorrow,

775
00:31:07,470 --> 00:31:08,680
因为如果你不在钱款转手前
because if you don't get over there

776
00:31:08,680 --> 00:31:10,120
赶到那里
before that money changes hands,

777
00:31:10,120 --> 00:31:12,710
那就是置我们于各种危险之前了
you are opening us up to a shitload of trouble.

778
00:31:22,540 --> 00:31:24,800
这里晚上有点吓人  是吧
Kind of creepy in here at night, isn't it?

779
00:31:25,530 --> 00:31:29,130
还好吧  我倒觉得挺平静的
Oh, I don't know. I find it kind of peaceful.

780
00:31:29,200 --> 00:31:31,370
那干嘛要卖掉它  而且最重要的
Then why get rid of it? And more importantly,

781
00:31:31,610 --> 00:31:33,630
你为什么想要交易这么快就完成
why'd you need the sale to go through so quickly?

782
00:31:33,630 --> 00:31:36,370
我说过  我有个收购机会
I told you, I have another opportunity.

783
00:31:36,370 --> 00:31:38,290
如果要我说  真正的原因是
And what if I said the real reason was

784
00:31:38,290 --> 00:31:40,490
你知道你的伏特加生意要被起诉了
you knew you vodka business was about to be sued

785
00:31:40,490 --> 00:31:42,400
因为你用了另一个品牌的配方
for using another brand's recipe?

786
00:31:42,400 --> 00:31:44,410
而我会说我不知道这些
I would say I did not know that.

787
00:31:44,500 --> 00:31:46,860
-而你其实知道  -又不能改变什么
- Well, now you do. - It doesn't change a thing.

788
00:31:46,860 --> 00:31:49,370
那两个笨蛋已经签了合同
Those two dipshits already signed the agreement.

789
00:31:49,370 --> 00:31:51,780
尼尔  这看着就像是你要我
Neil, this looks a hell of a lot like you're asking me

790
00:31:51,780 --> 00:31:54,970
-跟你合伙诈骗  -我是要你做好本职工作
- to be a party to fraud. - I'm asking you to do your job.

791
00:31:55,100 --> 00:31:58,330
为我谋取利益  相信我说的话
Look out for my interests, and take me at my word.

792
00:31:58,330 --> 00:32:00,460
如果我有理由相信你在说谎  而我确实相信...
If I have reason to believe that you're lying to me, which I do--

793
00:32:00,460 --> 00:32:01,790
唯一一件你要相信的事是
The only thing you have

794
00:32:01,790 --> 00:32:04,050
如果你不这样做  我就会炒了你
reason to believe is that I will fire you

795
00:32:04,050 --> 00:32:07,000
如果你不答应我  我会另找他人
if you don't do this for me and then find someone who will,

796
00:32:07,560 --> 00:32:09,900
没有你地球照样转
so this thing is gonna get done whether you do it or not.

797
00:32:09,900 --> 00:32:11,690
唯一确定的是如果你不答应
The only thing that happens if you don't

798
00:32:11,750 --> 00:32:14,960
外界会坚定此前的风言风语
is that the world will know what people suspect already:

799
00:32:14,960 --> 00:32:17,710
也就是你无法代替杰西卡
that you can't fill Jessica's shoes.

800
00:32:17,820 --> 00:32:19,850
如此一来你认为多长时间
How long do you think it's gonna take after that

801
00:32:19,850 --> 00:32:22,680
你的每位客户会开始离你而去
before every one of your clients starts to leave you?

802
00:32:23,080 --> 00:32:25,070
所以现在告诉我答案
So you tell me right now,

803
00:32:26,060 --> 00:32:27,340
你加入还是退出
are you in or not?

804
00:32:36,690 --> 00:32:37,660
见鬼  奥利佛
Shit. Oliver.

805
00:32:37,660 --> 00:32:38,990
最近怎样  迈克
What's up, Mike?

806
00:32:39,000 --> 00:32:40,690
-新工作还好吗  -我很抱歉
- How's your new job? - I'm sorry.

807
00:32:40,690 --> 00:32:41,860
我发誓我准备告诉你的
I swear I was gonna tell you.

808
00:32:41,860 --> 00:32:43,030
是啊  我听说了
Yeah, I heard,

809
00:32:43,030 --> 00:32:44,660
但我想你的确往前走了  对吗
but I guess when you move on, you move on, right?

810
00:32:44,660 --> 00:32:45,680
拜托  不是这样的
Come on, it's not like that.

811
00:32:45,680 --> 00:32:46,910
胡扯  不是这样的
Bullshit, it's not like that.

812
00:32:46,910 --> 00:32:48,900
你离开了  迈克  扔下此前一切承诺
You left, Mike, after everything you said.

813
00:32:48,900 --> 00:32:49,780
你能让我解释下吗
Would you please just let me explain?

814
00:32:49,780 --> 00:32:51,530
我曾竭力为你挽回那份工作
I fought for your goddamn job.

815
00:32:51,540 --> 00:32:53,700
我明白  我会永远心存感激
I know that, and I will always be grateful for it,

816
00:32:53,700 --> 00:32:54,140
但实不相瞒
but I am telling you,

817
00:32:54,150 --> 00:32:55,490
现在这样更好  因为...
it's better this way, because--

818
00:32:55,490 --> 00:32:57,350
对谁更好  因为你不得不挣钱
Better for who? Based on that extra cash

819
00:32:57,350 --> 00:32:58,930
向纳森上交罚金吗
that you had to throw at Nathan?

820
00:32:59,300 --> 00:33:00,440
照我说这是为你自己好
I'd say it's better for you.

821
00:33:00,440 --> 00:33:01,380
对每个人都好
For everybody.

822
00:33:01,380 --> 00:33:03,390
我还是可以帮法律诊所处理案子
I can still have cases with the clinic.

823
00:33:03,390 --> 00:33:04,870
我们还能一起工作
You and I can still work together.

824
00:33:04,880 --> 00:33:05,350
我真幸运
Lucky me.

825
00:33:05,350 --> 00:33:06,950
奥利佛  我回来的唯一原因是
Oliver, the only reason I went back

826
00:33:06,950 --> 00:33:09,050
哈维承诺会做公益法律服务
is that Harvey committed to doing pro bonos, all right?

827
00:33:09,050 --> 00:33:10,420
我处理的一半案子
Half of my cases,

828
00:33:10,420 --> 00:33:12,160
和我在诊所时做的一样  只是这一次
the kind the clinic does, only this time,

829
00:33:12,160 --> 00:33:14,420
我们有大律所的资源支持
with the resources of a big firm behind us.

830
00:33:14,420 --> 00:33:16,380
是吗  那你现在手头是什么工作  迈克
Oh, really? What are you working on right now, Mike?

831
00:33:16,380 --> 00:33:16,940
什么
What?

832
00:33:16,940 --> 00:33:18,180
你回来后做的第一件事是什么
What's your first case back?

833
00:33:18,180 --> 00:33:20,830
关于土地征用权还是侵犯公民权
Eminent domain? Civil rights violation?

834
00:33:20,830 --> 00:33:21,710
奥利佛  别这样
Oliver, come on,

835
00:33:21,710 --> 00:33:23,630
不是这样的  告诉我你回来的第一件事
It's not that-- - Tell me your first case back

836
00:33:23,630 --> 00:33:25,790
如果不是为公司权贵端茶倒水
isn't carrying water for some corporate big shot,

837
00:33:25,790 --> 00:33:27,580
我就马上闭嘴
and I'll shut my mouth right now.

838
00:33:30,690 --> 00:33:31,760
玛莉莎说对了
Marissa was right.

839
00:33:31,820 --> 00:33:34,540
你和我们共事只是为了等待时机
All you were doing with us was biding your time.

840
00:33:49,920 --> 00:33:52,620
-这怎么回事  -你说什么
- What the fu-- is going on? - What do you mean?

841
00:33:52,820 --> 00:33:54,600
案子结束了  你说过你会进行下一步
Case is over. You said you'd move.

842
00:33:54,710 --> 00:33:56,190
我只是在推动进度
I'm just getting the ball rolling.

843
00:33:56,190 --> 00:33:58,740
我如果没有自己的办公室无法处理案件
I can't work on my own cases if I don't have my own office.

844
00:33:58,740 --> 00:33:59,360
听着  迈克
Listen, Mike.

845
00:33:59,360 --> 00:34:01,070
你让那笔交易继续了
You let the goddamn sale go through.

846
00:34:01,070 --> 00:34:03,120
-你不明白  -我不明白你说过
- You don't understand. - I understand that you said

847
00:34:03,120 --> 00:34:05,850
你想在上位前和我最后一起做一个案子
that you wanted one last case together before you stepped up,

848
00:34:05,850 --> 00:34:08,210
但你明显还未准备好要做领导
but you clearly are not ready to step up,

849
00:34:08,210 --> 00:34:10,660
所以我得在这件律所消失之前
so I got to get my pro bono cases in

850
00:34:10,660 --> 00:34:12,930
多花点时间处理我的公益案件
before this place doesn't even exist anymore.

851
00:34:12,930 --> 00:34:15,650
你说完了吗  有空听我说说
Are you finished, or do you have a minute to hear

852
00:34:15,660 --> 00:34:16,960
为什么我继续了交易吗
why I let the sale go through?

853
00:34:16,960 --> 00:34:18,140
不  我不在乎
Oh, no, I don't care.

854
00:34:18,140 --> 00:34:20,210
迈克  他知道我没有证据
Mike, I have no proof he knew.

855
00:34:20,210 --> 00:34:21,930
他是杰西卡的委托人
He's Jessica's client.

856
00:34:21,930 --> 00:34:23,780
如果他把我们再也无法处理他事务的事
How's it gonna look if he tells the world

857
00:34:23,780 --> 00:34:25,210
公诸于众  会怎么样
that we can't handle his business anymore?

858
00:34:25,210 --> 00:34:26,810
我现在告诉你会怎么样
Well, I'll tell you how it looks right now.

859
00:34:26,810 --> 00:34:29,290
看起来你在害怕  而且说了不算
It looks like you're afraid and you're not in charge.

860
00:34:29,290 --> 00:34:31,180
好吧  你要是这样跟我说话
Okay, you say something like that to me,

861
00:34:31,180 --> 00:34:32,490
你最好做好挨揍的准备
you better get ready for a hit,

862
00:34:32,500 --> 00:34:34,300
因为我一直在尽力而为
because I am doing the best I can.

863
00:34:34,300 --> 00:34:36,180
不  哈维  你什么都没做
No, Harvey, you're not doing shit.

864
00:34:36,180 --> 00:34:37,780
你在逃避  因为你害怕
You're hiding, 'cause you're afraid.

865
00:34:37,780 --> 00:34:40,590
你害怕挑起这件律所的担子
You're afraid to take responsibility for this firm,

866
00:34:40,590 --> 00:34:42,250
你也不会对自己承认这一点
and you won't admit it to yourself.

867
00:34:42,250 --> 00:34:43,210
我不必听这些
I don't have to listen to this.

868
00:34:43,210 --> 00:34:44,580
你必须听
Well, you're going to,

869
00:34:46,630 --> 00:34:48,230
因为回想以前  你出于关心
'cause way back when, you cared enough about me

870
00:34:48,230 --> 00:34:49,800
当着我的面说出了同样的话
to tell me the same thing to my face,

871
00:34:49,800 --> 00:34:51,610
我现在只是在投桃报李
and I'm just returning the favor.

872
00:34:57,990 --> 00:34:59,190
我不是她  迈克
I'm not her, Mike.

873
00:35:00,920 --> 00:35:03,460
-我不是她  -你不必成为她
- I'm not her. - You don't have to be her.

874
00:35:05,190 --> 00:35:07,380
你只用做回你自己
You just have to go back to being you.

875
00:35:08,460 --> 00:35:10,720
我们第一次见面  聘用我的那个哈维
The Harvey I met the day you hired me,

876
00:35:10,720 --> 00:35:12,440
他会走到尼尔·斯蒂尔曼面前
he would have gone in there and told Neil Stillman

877
00:35:12,440 --> 00:35:14,070
告诉他去他妈的
to go fu-- himself.

878
00:35:15,190 --> 00:35:16,210
所以由你决定
So it's up to you.

879
00:35:17,530 --> 00:35:19,690
你可以继续躲在杰西卡阴影之下
You can keep hiding out in Jessica's shadow,

880
00:35:19,980 --> 00:35:21,190
也可以走出阴影
or you get out of it

881
00:35:21,200 --> 00:35:23,940
做一个霸道的哈维·斯佩克特
and start being Harvey goddamn Specter.

882
00:35:44,180 --> 00:35:46,390
你也发现这里白天特别平静是吗
Do you find it peaceful here in the day too?

883
00:35:47,410 --> 00:35:48,770
你带了我的支票过来
You're here to bring me my check,

884
00:35:48,770 --> 00:35:50,440
那我的答案是肯定的
then the answer's yes.

885
00:35:50,440 --> 00:35:52,690
我来这里告诉你我们终止了出售
I'm here to tell you that we stopped the sale.

886
00:35:53,960 --> 00:35:55,050
你刚才说什么
What did you just say?

887
00:35:55,830 --> 00:35:57,470
我们不参与你的骗局
We're not taking part in your fraud

888
00:35:57,470 --> 00:35:59,550
所以你可以关掉你的烂公司了
so that you can dump your shitty company.

889
00:35:59,550 --> 00:36:01,970
你这个混蛋  我不记得我给过你选项
You son of a bitch, I don't remember giving you a choice.

890
00:36:01,970 --> 00:36:04,160
你给了  因为你的原话是
Well, you did, because your exact words were,

891
00:36:04,160 --> 00:36:05,760
"要么同意  要么被解雇"
"Do it, or you're fired."

892
00:36:05,760 --> 00:36:06,900
那你他妈被解雇了
Then you're goddamn fired.

893
00:36:06,900 --> 00:36:09,120
你可以解雇我们  但一旦被解雇
You can let us go if you want, but the second you do,

894
00:36:09,120 --> 00:36:10,610
我们会发一篇通讯稿声明
we're putting out a press release saying

895
00:36:10,620 --> 00:36:13,210
皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特不再代理
Pearson Specter Litt no longer represents clients

896
00:36:13,210 --> 00:36:16,780
我们认为资产剥离中有不道德行为的委托人
we feel are unethical in their divestiture practices.

897
00:36:16,780 --> 00:36:17,450
你不能这么做
You can't do that,

898
00:36:17,450 --> 00:36:19,340
这触犯了律师-委托人的保密特权
that's attorney-client privilege.

899
00:36:19,340 --> 00:36:22,040
不  因为我们不会对你指名点姓
No, it's not, because we're not gonna name you.

900
00:36:22,040 --> 00:36:23,710
但你用屁股想都能猜到
But you can bet your ass the whole world

901
00:36:23,710 --> 00:36:25,670
全世界都会知道我们说的是谁
is gonna know who we're talking about.

902
00:36:26,950 --> 00:36:28,170
你想要什么
What do you want from me?

903
00:36:28,590 --> 00:36:29,660
你是作为我的委托人在询问我吗
Are you asking me as my client?

904
00:36:29,660 --> 00:36:31,570
因为我不提供免费法律建议
Because I don't give free legal advice.

905
00:36:31,570 --> 00:36:34,060
是的  好吧  你还是我的律师
Yes, okay. You're still my attorney.

906
00:36:34,060 --> 00:36:36,310
这样的话  接下来要做的是
In that case, here's what's gonna happen:

907
00:36:36,310 --> 00:36:37,600
你去和你盗用配方的对象
you're gonna go into business

908
00:36:37,600 --> 00:36:39,580
做一笔交易
with the guys whose process you stole.

909
00:36:39,600 --> 00:36:41,970
你私下交给他们10%的公司股权
You're gonna quietly give them 10% of your company,

910
00:36:41,970 --> 00:36:43,390
把商品售价提高两倍
you're gonna triple your price, and you're gonna have

911
00:36:43,390 --> 00:36:47,220
两家公司就谁家的伏特加味道更好进行公开竞争
a very public feud over whose vodka tastes better.

912
00:36:47,490 --> 00:36:49,440
然后在这相同产品的两大品牌间的战争中
And then we both profit from a war

913
00:36:49,440 --> 00:36:52,670
我们均能从中获利
between two brands that have the exact same product.

914
00:36:52,680 --> 00:36:53,800
达成双赢
Win-win.

915
00:36:55,130 --> 00:36:56,630
或许你和杰西卡一样厉害
Maybe you are as good as Jessica.

916
00:36:56,630 --> 00:36:58,570
或许是  或许不是
Maybe I am. Maybe I'm not.

917
00:36:58,720 --> 00:37:00,000
但我和她的共识是
But the thing we have in common is

918
00:37:00,000 --> 00:37:02,700
我们再也不会受任何委托人的摆布
we're never gonna be bullied by any of our clients.

919
00:37:25,290 --> 00:37:26,960
好了  路易  我一直尽力做到通情达理
All right, Louis, I've tried to be reasonable,

920
00:37:26,960 --> 00:37:29,220
但我不会再坐视不管
but I'm not gonna sit around and watch this anymore.

921
00:37:29,230 --> 00:37:30,330
从现在起  你不再
As of this moment, you're no longer

922
00:37:30,340 --> 00:37:32,750
-负责管理新律师  -这是你和谁的意思
- in charge of the associates. - Says you and what army?

923
00:37:32,750 --> 00:37:33,950
抱歉  我没听懂
I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.

924
00:37:33,950 --> 00:37:36,210
-我说你做不到  -不  我可以
- I said you can't do that. - Oh, yes, I can,

925
00:37:36,220 --> 00:37:38,020
因为即使哈维明显还未告诉你
because even though Harvey clearly didn't tell you,

926
00:37:38,020 --> 00:37:40,000
从昨晚开始  我成为了高级合伙人
as of last night, I'm a senior partner.

927
00:37:40,000 --> 00:37:41,150
-你成为什么  -你没听错
- You're what? - That's right.

928
00:37:41,160 --> 00:37:43,140
我给了哈维一张五十万美元的支票
I gave Harvey a check for half a million dollars.

929
00:37:43,150 --> 00:37:44,700
我现在是高级合伙人  路易
I'm a partner now, Louis,

930
00:37:44,700 --> 00:37:46,340
这意味着你那套
which means your whole

931
00:37:46,350 --> 00:37:48,930
"你高高在上  我俯首称臣"的屁话
"You're up here and I'm down here" bullshit,

932
00:37:49,070 --> 00:37:49,980
行不通了
not anymore.

933
00:37:49,980 --> 00:37:50,660
合伙人
Partner?

934
00:37:50,660 --> 00:37:51,670
你甚至都不是律师
You're not even a lawyer.

935
00:37:51,670 --> 00:37:53,680
世界最顶尖的9家律所中  有4家的首席运营官
Neither are the Chief Operating Officers of four

936
00:37:53,680 --> 00:37:55,450
也都不是律师
of the top nine firms in the world.

937
00:37:55,450 --> 00:37:57,510
这简直是胡闹  我根本没同意
This is bullshit. I didn't agree to any of this.

938
00:37:57,510 --> 00:37:59,280
我不管你同意还是不同意
I don't care whether you agreed to it or not.

939
00:37:59,280 --> 00:38:00,330
你都得忍着
You're gonna live with it.

940
00:38:00,330 --> 00:38:02,790
我也不管你的头衔是什么
And I don't give a shit what your supposed title is.

941
00:38:02,790 --> 00:38:04,200
我是不会放手我的律师的
I'm not giving up my associates.

942
00:38:04,200 --> 00:38:05,970
如果你觉得你可以就这样离开这间洗手间
And if you think you're gonna leave this bathroom

943
00:38:05,970 --> 00:38:07,880
而不对我表示出我应得的尊重...
without giving me the respect I deserve--

944
00:38:07,880 --> 00:38:09,530
我是不会放手我的律师的
I'm not giving up my associates.

945
00:38:09,530 --> 00:38:10,400
够了
That's enough.

946
00:38:10,410 --> 00:38:12,310
哈维  你这做的是什么狗屁决定
Harvey, what the hell kind of shit did you pull?

947
00:38:12,310 --> 00:38:13,650
闭嘴听我说  路易
Shut up and listen, Louis.

948
00:38:13,650 --> 00:38:15,250
唐娜要求在管理层有一席之位
Donna asked for a seat at the table,

949
00:38:15,250 --> 00:38:16,520
而我同意了
and I gave her one,

950
00:38:16,520 --> 00:38:19,040
因为先前为我工作时  她一直支持着我
because when she worked for me, she had my back,

951
00:38:19,040 --> 00:38:21,040
愿意为我大杀四方
and would kill anyone coming for me,

952
00:38:21,040 --> 00:38:23,680
而她先前为你工作时  一样尽心尽力
and when she worked for you, she did the same exact thing,

953
00:38:23,680 --> 00:38:25,530
更别提如果她离开了
not to mention if she left tomorrow,

954
00:38:25,530 --> 00:38:28,040
这家律所15分钟之内就会变为一滩散沙
this firm would be a pile of rubble within 15 minutes.

955
00:38:28,040 --> 00:38:29,550
那就给她加薪啊
So then give her a raise.

956
00:38:29,550 --> 00:38:31,410
但你不能就这样把她抬为高级合伙人
You don't make her goddamn senior partner.

957
00:38:31,420 --> 00:38:33,970
假如杰西卡在  她也会和我做法一样的
If Jessica were here, she'd tell you to do the same exact thing.

958
00:38:33,970 --> 00:38:35,810
但是  路易  杰西卡不在了
Well, Louis, Jessica isn't here,

959
00:38:36,570 --> 00:38:37,610
但我在
but I am.

960
00:38:41,510 --> 00:38:43,340
-谢谢你  哈维  -先别急着谢我
- Thank you, Harvey. - Don't thank me yet.

961
00:38:43,340 --> 00:38:45,510
你要求大家投票表决  没问题
You asked for a vote. You got it.

962
00:38:45,930 --> 00:38:49,320
但决定什么时候发起投票的人是我
But the person who's gonna decide when that vote is is me,

963
00:38:49,330 --> 00:38:51,780
而我认为我们要做的第一件事
and I say our first order of business

964
00:38:51,780 --> 00:38:55,130
是对外公布哈维·斯佩克特是新的管理合伙人
is putting out word that Harvey Specter is the new managing partner.

965
00:38:55,130 --> 00:38:57,570
你们想对这个决定投票表决吗  来吧
Now, you want to vote on that? Let's do it.

966
00:38:57,570 --> 00:38:59,270
但假如我们不能达成一致
But if it's not unanimous,

967
00:38:59,270 --> 00:39:00,570
那就有大麻烦了
we're gonna have a big problem.

968
00:39:01,980 --> 00:39:03,150
我没意见
No problem here.

969
00:39:06,510 --> 00:39:07,580
你呢  路易
What about you, Louis?

970
00:39:07,890 --> 00:39:09,770
你对我当老大有意见吗
You got a problem with me calling the shots?

971
00:39:10,280 --> 00:39:11,300
没有  哈维
No, Harvey.

972
00:39:12,800 --> 00:39:14,660
没意见  管理合伙人是你
No problem. You're managing partner.

973
00:39:14,660 --> 00:39:16,640
很好  那我建议你们两个
Good. Then I suggest the two of you

974
00:39:16,650 --> 00:39:18,070
在明天之前收拾好心情
get your shit together before tomorrow,

975
00:39:18,070 --> 00:39:20,440
因为此时此刻  我还有事要忙
because right now, I've got some things to take care of.

976
00:39:35,440 --> 00:39:36,720
我现在不想理你  路易...
I don't want to talk to you right now, Louis--

977
00:39:36,720 --> 00:39:38,140
我想让你来接手那些律师
I want you to have the associates.

978
00:39:39,640 --> 00:39:41,170
无论你对唐娜说了什么  你都没说错
Whatever you said to Donna, you were right.

979
00:39:41,170 --> 00:39:42,800
-路易...  -瑞秋  让我说完
- Louis... - Rachel, just let me finish

980
00:39:42,800 --> 00:39:44,170
趁着我还能说得出口
while I'm still able to get it out.

981
00:39:45,520 --> 00:39:46,980
我知道我对他们是严厉了点...
I know I can be rough on them...

982
00:39:49,770 --> 00:39:51,100
但那只是因为我希望看到他们
but it's only because I want to see them

983
00:39:51,100 --> 00:39:53,060
成为他们能成为的最好的律师
become the best lawyers they can be.

984
00:39:53,280 --> 00:39:55,490
但如今我不在最佳状态
But I'm not in the best headspace right now,

985
00:39:55,600 --> 00:39:57,530
我如果一直把气撒在他们头上
and if I keep taking my anger out on them,

986
00:39:57,530 --> 00:39:59,360
他们是无法成为伟大的律师的
they will not become great lawyers.

987
00:39:59,420 --> 00:40:01,980
说不定他们都要直接退出法律界了  所以...
They might not stay in the law at all, so...

988
00:40:04,270 --> 00:40:06,420
最好还是有别人暂时来接手一下
it's better that someone else takes over for a while,

989
00:40:06,420 --> 00:40:08,510
而我想不到比你更合适的人选了
and I cannot think of a better person than you.

990
00:40:08,760 --> 00:40:11,180
很抱歉我背着你行事了  路易
I'm sorry that I went behind your back, Louis.

991
00:40:11,180 --> 00:40:12,270
你没做错
You were right to.

992
00:40:12,520 --> 00:40:13,740
如果你当着我的面提出
If you had asked me face-to-face,

993
00:40:13,740 --> 00:40:15,230
我都不知道我会做出什么
I don't even know what I would have done,

994
00:40:15,230 --> 00:40:19,320
那种场景...光是想想都让我不舒服了
and that--just thinking about that makes me sick.

995
00:40:20,360 --> 00:40:21,530
瑞秋  你就像是我的亲人
Rachel, you're family,

996
00:40:23,170 --> 00:40:24,640
假如我连你都失去了...
and if I lose you too...

997
00:40:24,640 --> 00:40:26,870
路易  你不会失去我的
Louis, you're not going to lose me,

998
00:40:27,220 --> 00:40:29,220
但我觉得我知道你可能需要些什么
but I think I know what you may need.

999
00:40:29,220 --> 00:40:30,460
你可千万别说是"假期"
Please don't say vacation.

1000
00:40:30,460 --> 00:40:32,640
如果再来一个人和我提玛莎葡萄园岛
If someone else mentions Martha's Vineyard one more time,

1001
00:40:32,640 --> 00:40:35,330
-我对天发誓...  -我想说的词是"终结"
- I swear to God... - I was gonna say closure.

1002
00:40:36,790 --> 00:40:38,980
假如你是想说我得去和塔拉谈谈...
If you're telling me that I need to talk to Tara--

1003
00:40:38,980 --> 00:40:41,300
路易  你本来都要结婚了
Louis, you were gonna get married.

1004
00:40:41,540 --> 00:40:43,140
你本来都要当父亲了
You were gonna be a father.

1005
00:40:44,870 --> 00:40:48,130
不能仅凭一通语音留言就结束这一切
That can't all end over a voicemail.

1006
00:40:53,180 --> 00:40:54,160
好好对他们
Treat them well.

1007
00:41:06,560 --> 00:41:07,500
我就知道
I knew it.

1008
00:41:09,720 --> 00:41:10,380
知道什么
Knew what?

1009
00:41:10,380 --> 00:41:12,480
你没种把哈维的旧办公室填满
You don't have the balls to fill Harvey's office.

1010
00:41:13,810 --> 00:41:15,420
好吧  唐娜  声明一下
Okay, Donna, just to be clear,

1011
00:41:15,500 --> 00:41:16,990
光看种可算不得男人
balls do not make the man.

1012
00:41:16,990 --> 00:41:19,490
-瑞秋可不是这么说的  -这话是什么意思
- That's not what Rachel says. - What does that even mean?

1013
00:41:19,490 --> 00:41:20,930
我觉得咱俩都明白这是什么意思
I think we both know what that means.

1014
00:41:20,930 --> 00:41:21,750
唐娜  和你声明一下
Donna, for the record,

1015
00:41:21,750 --> 00:41:24,540
我的"种"尺寸正常
my balls are within normal parameters.

1016
00:41:24,540 --> 00:41:26,100
所以你下来就是为了调侃我
So you just come down here to give me shit,

1017
00:41:26,100 --> 00:41:27,590
还是说有其他什么事情
or was there maybe another reason?

1018
00:41:27,590 --> 00:41:28,970
还能有什么事情
What other reason would I have?

1019
00:41:28,970 --> 00:41:30,180
我一个都想不出来
I can't think of a single one.

1020
00:41:30,180 --> 00:41:31,600
-那我来这里的任务就完成了  -很好
- Then my work here is done. - Good.

1021
00:41:31,600 --> 00:41:33,590
因为我显然不是下来告诉你
Because I certainly didn't come down here to tell you

1022
00:41:33,590 --> 00:41:36,580
我还记得你第一次进这间办公室的情景
I remember the first time you were in this office,

1023
00:41:37,080 --> 00:41:38,770
而我从没想到我会有
and I never thought I'd see the day

1024
00:41:38,770 --> 00:41:41,380
对你道喜的这一天  迈克
when I told you congratulations, Mike.

1025
00:41:42,320 --> 00:41:43,790
这一切都是你应得的
You deserve it as your own.

1026
00:41:44,660 --> 00:41:47,250
-谢谢你  唐娜  -不客气  迈克
- Thanks, Donna. - You're welcome, Mike.

1027
00:41:50,100 --> 00:41:51,400
你确定你不一起吗
Are you sure you don't come with it?

1028
00:41:52,470 --> 00:41:54,070
我是说  那边有张桌子
I mean, there is a desk right there

1029
00:41:54,070 --> 00:41:55,830
上面可是真真切切写着你的名字的
that literally has your name on it.

1030
00:41:55,940 --> 00:41:57,130
抱歉  我也希望我能来
Sorry, I wish I could,

1031
00:41:57,130 --> 00:41:59,080
但实际上我也分到了一间新办公室
but I actually got a new office too.

1032
00:41:59,080 --> 00:42:00,170
-真的吗  -必须得有一间
- You did? - Needed one,

1033
00:42:00,170 --> 00:42:01,310
因为等到明天
because as of tomorrow,

1034
00:42:01,310 --> 00:42:04,660
我就正式是这家律所最新一位高级合伙人了
I am officially the firm's newest senior partner.

1035
00:42:04,660 --> 00:42:06,420
我勒个去  你是认真的吗
Holy shit. Are you serious?

1036
00:42:06,420 --> 00:42:08,460
是的  而且从现在开始
Yes. And from now on,

1037
00:42:08,460 --> 00:42:10,610
你得说"您是认真的吗  女士"
it's, "are you serious, ma'am?"

1038
00:42:11,570 --> 00:42:13,820
-清楚了吗  小帅哥  -天啊
- Have you got that, pretty boy? - My God.

1039
00:42:13,820 --> 00:42:15,830
哈维造出了一个怪物是吧
Harvey's created a monster, hasn't he?

1040
00:42:15,830 --> 00:42:17,270
你无法想象
You have no idea.

1041
00:42:18,320 --> 00:42:19,090
唐娜...
Donna...

1042
00:42:21,110 --> 00:42:21,970
这也是你应得的
it's about time.

1043
00:42:36,420 --> 00:42:39,100
喂  我知道我们一直没谈过
Hey. I know we haven't spoken,

1044
00:42:40,680 --> 00:42:43,020
我们也没有好好地结束
and we didn't exactly leave things off well,

1045
00:42:44,480 --> 00:42:45,480
但是...
but...

1046
00:42:47,620 --> 00:42:49,350
我今天真的很需要见你一面
I just really need to see you tonight

1047
00:42:49,750 --> 00:42:50,890
假如还有一丝可能的话
if at all possible.

1048
00:43:14,260 --> 00:43:17,050
看来你终于做了投入了
Guess you got some skin in the game after all.

1049
00:43:19,390 --> 00:43:20,630
确实  格蕾琴
Sure did, Gretchen.

1050
00:43:23,370 --> 00:43:24,300
确实
Sure did.

