1
00:00:00,100 --> 00:00:01,620
《訴訟雙雄》前情提要

2
00:00:01,620 --> 00:00:04,900
你是通過向外國政府行賄來獲得輸油管道
You're guilty of bribing a foreign government to get your pipeline.

3
00:00:04,930 --> 00:00:06,200
罪名完全成立
Guilty as charged.

4
00:00:06,290 --> 00:00:07,680
你覺得自己不可替代嗎
You think you're not replaceable?

5
00:00:07,690 --> 00:00:09,260
認識你之前我就這樣
I've been doing this before I met you,

6
00:00:09,260 --> 00:00:11,910
在我把你完全忘了之后  我還會一直這么做
and I'll be doing it long after I've forgotten all about you.

7
00:00:12,670 --> 00:00:13,710
拜托不要這么做
Please don't do this.

8
00:00:13,710 --> 00:00:16,450
你親愛的助理們都歸我了
Your beloved associates are mine.

9
00:00:16,450 --> 00:00:18,790
你想要的是一場曠日持久的官司
What you want is a long, drawn-out trial

10
00:00:18,790 --> 00:00:20,490
讓我們的股票跌至谷底
that puts our stock in the toilet.

11
00:00:20,550 --> 00:00:21,270
我是來告訴你
I'm here to tell you

12
00:00:21,270 --> 00:00:22,810
他準備退出此案了
he's recusing himself from the case.

13
00:00:22,810 --> 00:00:25,010
所以他指派了一名特別檢察官
So he appointed a special prosecutor.

14
00:00:25,010 --> 00:00:27,760
我要是贏了  你要支持我成為執行合伙人
I win, you back me for managing partner.

15
00:00:27,770 --> 00:00:29,660
你想扳倒杰西卡
You want to take down Jessica.

16
00:00:29,690 --> 00:00:31,590
正是如此
Yes, I do.

17
00:00:34,710 --> 00:00:36,350
我勒個去
Holy shit.

18
00:00:36,600 --> 00:00:39,190
這話是好是壞啊
Was that a good "holy shit" or a bad "holy shit"?

19
00:00:39,190 --> 00:00:41,380
哈維  你剛告訴我你計劃政變
Harvey, you just told me that you're planning a coup.

20
00:00:41,380 --> 00:00:42,900
讓我消化一下
Give me a second to figure that out.

21
00:00:42,920 --> 00:00:45,790
不是政變  是行動
Not a coup. It's a move.

22
00:00:45,890 --> 00:00:47,460
等你講完大道理...
And when you're done with your lecture--

23
00:00:47,460 --> 00:00:48,690
不  不講大道理
No. No lecture.

24
00:00:48,960 --> 00:00:50,230
我只有一個問題
I just have one question.

25
00:00:52,540 --> 00:00:53,720
我能有自己的辦公室嗎
Do I get my own office?

26
00:00:55,060 --> 00:00:57,080
哈維  如果你想做執行合伙人
Harvey, if you want to be managing partner

27
00:00:57,080 --> 00:00:58,210
達比也答應會支持你
and Darby agreed to back you,

28
00:00:58,210 --> 00:01:00,070
那我會追隨你到世界盡頭
then I'll follow you to the ends of the earth.

29
00:01:00,070 --> 00:01:02,060
但在行動之前  我要確定
But before we start, I want to make sure

30
00:01:02,060 --> 00:01:03,880
你真準備好這么對杰西卡了
you're ready to do this to Jessica.

31
00:01:04,790 --> 00:01:05,830
我準備好了
I am.

32
00:01:06,450 --> 00:01:08,850
那就去把卡梅隆·丹尼斯打個屁滾尿流吧
Then let's go beat the shit out of Cameron Dennis.

33
00:01:10,410 --> 00:01:11,740
我知道你不想見我
I know you don't want to see me.

34
00:01:11,810 --> 00:01:12,710
那你還來
And yet--

35
00:01:14,100 --> 00:01:15,370
我就想讓你知道我拿到了
I just wanted to let you know that I got

36
00:01:15,370 --> 00:01:17,400
杰西卡用來勒索我的信件副本
a copy of the letter that Jessica blackmailed me with,

37
00:01:17,400 --> 00:01:18,860
我清楚地告訴她  要是她再威脅我
and I made it clear to her that I would take it

38
00:01:18,860 --> 00:01:20,220
我就把信送到地檢手里
to the D.A. if she ever threatened me,

39
00:01:20,220 --> 00:01:22,290
我之前做的事絕不會再犯
so what I did will never happen again.

40
00:01:22,690 --> 00:01:24,490
你原本就不該那么做
Never should have happened in the first place.

41
00:01:24,840 --> 00:01:26,200
出去時把門帶上
Close the door on your way out.

42
00:01:26,260 --> 00:01:27,410
我和唐娜有活要干
Donna and I have work to do.

43
00:01:32,170 --> 00:01:36,790
邁克·羅斯
律師助理

44
00:01:34,150 --> 00:01:36,080
我得告訴你們一個殘酷的事實
There's a harsh reality I need to inform you of,

45
00:01:37,710 --> 00:01:39,620
你們會難以接受
and it's a bitter pill to swallow.

46
00:01:40,080 --> 00:01:42,890
但事實是  大錯已經鑄成
But the truth is, a mistake was made.

47
00:01:44,030 --> 00:01:45,100
致命的錯誤
A fatal mistake.

48
00:01:45,220 --> 00:01:47,190
盡管我很不情愿承認
And as much as I hate to admit it,

49
00:01:47,470 --> 00:01:49,690
但我們共同奮斗的日子到頭了
our time together is done.

50
00:01:50,960 --> 00:01:51,890
沒有共事
No more work,

51
00:01:53,770 --> 00:01:54,930
沒有歡聲笑語
no more laughter.

52
00:01:56,310 --> 00:01:57,460
記得嗎
Remember?

53
00:01:59,690 --> 00:02:00,920
沒有師徒關系
No more mentorship

54
00:02:01,040 --> 00:02:03,570
什么都沒了
and, um, no more anything.

55
00:02:04,580 --> 00:02:06,930
我飛得太高  跌得太重
See, I reached too high, and I fell.

56
00:02:07,230 --> 00:02:09,680
對我的懲罰就是  我作為律師助理主管的
And my punishment is the end of my tenure

57
00:02:09,680 --> 00:02:11,060
任期結束了
as head of the associates.

58
00:02:12,750 --> 00:02:15,260
我留給你們的是
So I would like to leave you

59
00:02:15,280 --> 00:02:17,760
羅賓·威廉姆斯的
with the immortal sentiment

60
00:02:17,760 --> 00:02:18,860
不朽觀點
of Robin Williams.

61
00:02:20,930 --> 00:02:22,780
在你們之前也有過很多律師助理
There have been other associates before you.

62
00:02:23,550 --> 00:02:26,360
他們堅信自己是來干大事的
They believed they were destined for great things,

63
00:02:26,360 --> 00:02:27,390
正如你們一樣
just like you.

64
00:02:27,550 --> 00:02:30,330
若是你們認真聆聽
If you just listen,

65
00:02:32,850 --> 00:02:34,920
還能聽到他們低語著自己的寶貴感悟
you can hear 'em whisper their legacy to you.

66
00:02:36,460 --> 00:02:37,790
及時行樂[拉丁語]
Carpe diem.

67
00:02:40,100 --> 00:02:42,180
及時行樂  各位
Seize the day, people.

68
00:02:43,510 --> 00:02:45,130
讓你們的法律生涯非凡出彩
Make your legal lives extraordinary.

69
00:02:46,760 --> 00:02:48,260
哦  船長  我的船長
Oh, captain, my captain.

70
00:02:46,760 --> 00:02:48,260
出自沃爾特·惠特曼《哦，船長!我的船長!》

71
00:02:53,550 --> 00:02:54,830
曾經的我看到這一幕一定會松口氣
There was a time I would've been relieved

72
00:02:54,830 --> 00:02:57,400
因為再也不用看路易的臉色了
to see that-- no more Louis.

73
00:02:57,400 --> 00:02:58,410
這樣不對
It's just wrong.

74
00:02:58,780 --> 00:03:00,320
整個合并的事就不對
This whole merger is wrong.

75
00:03:00,800 --> 00:03:02,090
哈維那邊怎么樣了
How'd it go with Harvey?

76
00:03:02,200 --> 00:03:03,240
不怎么樣
It didn't.

77
00:03:03,480 --> 00:03:04,490
你跟他說杰西卡的事了嗎
Did you tell him about Jessica?

78
00:03:04,500 --> 00:03:06,550
說了  他不管
Yeah. He didn't care.

79
00:03:09,350 --> 00:03:10,180
什么
What?

80
00:03:10,180 --> 00:03:12,520
真希望現在能抱抱你
I just wish I could give you a hug right now,

81
00:03:12,580 --> 00:03:15,390
但不行  因為我們還要低調行事
but I can't because we still want to keep us quiet.

82
00:03:15,390 --> 00:03:17,230
來吧  你可以抱抱我啊
Well, come on. You can give me a hug.

83
00:03:17,230 --> 00:03:18,820
可能發生了一些事
Something could've happened.

84
00:03:18,820 --> 00:03:20,270
一些壞事  比如...
Something bad, like a...

85
00:03:22,050 --> 00:03:22,900
我家的狗可能死了
My dog could've died.

86
00:03:22,900 --> 00:03:24,160
你居然還養狗了
Oh, you have a dog now?

87
00:03:25,170 --> 00:03:27,170
我跟這條狗真的很親近
I was really close to this dog.

88
00:03:27,710 --> 00:03:29,670
忘記愛狗之死的最好辦法
Well, the best way to get over the death of a dog

89
00:03:29,670 --> 00:03:31,160
就是再養一條
is to get a new one.

90
00:03:31,320 --> 00:03:32,310
-不要嗎  -不要
- No? - No.

91
00:03:32,310 --> 00:03:33,770
我太難過了
I'm just-- I'm just too upset.

92
00:03:33,770 --> 00:03:35,730
不知道現在能不能
I'm-- I don't know if I'm ready

93
00:03:35,730 --> 00:03:37,230
去接受一條新的假狗
for a new fake dog right now.

94
00:03:37,880 --> 00:03:39,270
好吧
Okay.

95
00:03:39,370 --> 00:03:41,510
就這樣放著我不管
Just leave me like this.

96
00:03:46,630 --> 00:03:47,640
怎么樣
How did it go?

97
00:03:52,810 --> 00:03:54,320
不知道  難受
I don't know. Awful.

98
00:03:55,290 --> 00:03:56,930
這在我被迫為之的事情中可能是最難的
Probably the hardest thing I ever had to do.

99
00:03:57,100 --> 00:03:58,460
路易  我們剛合并
Louis, we just merged,

100
00:03:58,460 --> 00:04:01,520
我也希望能恢復你律師助理主管的職位
and I wish I could undo you losing the associates,

101
00:04:01,530 --> 00:04:02,570
但我不能
but I can't.

102
00:04:02,580 --> 00:04:03,590
我只能
What I can do

103
00:04:04,380 --> 00:04:06,190
讓你把這么久以來
is take what you've been giving

104
00:04:06,190 --> 00:04:08,500
給予這么多人的東西
to so many for so long

105
00:04:08,790 --> 00:04:10,770
集中給一個人
and have you channel it into one.

106
00:04:12,200 --> 00:04:12,880
你是說...
You mean...

107
00:04:12,880 --> 00:04:14,740
我希望你培養自己的律師助理
I want you to mentor your own associate.

108
00:04:19,950 --> 00:04:21,030
終于啊
Finally.

109
00:04:21,920 --> 00:04:25,230
阿多斯  波爾朵斯和阿拉密斯是我達達尼昂的好兄弟
The D'Artagnan to my Athos, Porthos, and Aramis.

110
00:04:21,920 --> 00:04:25,230
出自大仲馬《三個火槍手》

111
00:04:25,520 --> 00:04:27,390
人人為我  我為人人
All for one and one for all.

112
00:04:27,530 --> 00:04:28,670
預備[法語]
En garde!

113
00:04:30,360 --> 00:04:31,300
抱歉
Sorry.

114
00:04:32,170 --> 00:04:33,250
杰西卡  等等
Jessica, wait.

115
00:04:36,040 --> 00:04:37,190
我挑誰做助理都行嗎
I can have anyone?

116
00:04:37,720 --> 00:04:39,540
路易  你隨便選
Louis, take your pick of the litter.

117
00:04:44,250 --> 00:04:45,780
-早上好  保爾森女士  -有話快說
- Good morning, Ms. Paulsen. - Spit it out.

118
00:04:46,340 --> 00:04:47,580
一大清早就這么咄咄逼人啊
Is that any way to start the day?

119
00:04:47,660 --> 00:04:48,640
你有事相求
You want something.

120
00:04:48,680 --> 00:04:50,130
我需要他倆分手的小道消息
I need the 411 on the breakup.

121
00:04:50,130 --> 00:04:52,210
-這兒難道還是高中嗎  -生活就是高中
- Are we in high school? - Life is high school.

122
00:04:52,210 --> 00:04:53,410
我得知道舞會國王
And I need to know if the prom king

123
00:04:53,410 --> 00:04:55,120
和他的神奇小子還是不是一對兒
and his boy wonder are still an item.

124
00:04:55,770 --> 00:04:56,970
你是哪所高中畢業的
What high school did you go to?

125
00:04:56,980 --> 00:04:58,460
唐娜  問題很簡單
Donna, it's a simple question.

126
00:04:59,400 --> 00:05:01,180
邁克和哈維是真分手了
Did Mike and Harvey break up break up,

127
00:05:01,180 --> 00:05:03,900
還是雙方冷靜一下  就是那種跟對方說
or did they take a time-out and, like, say to each other,

128
00:05:03,900 --> 00:05:05,400
"我們試著跟別人約會吧
"Hey, let's see other people

129
00:05:05,570 --> 00:05:06,560
看看感情是否真的不在了"
and make sure that we're sure."

130
00:05:06,560 --> 00:05:07,880
我知道怎么回事了
I see what's going on here.

131
00:05:08,840 --> 00:05:10,110
杰西卡可憐你
Jessica feels sorry for you,

132
00:05:10,110 --> 00:05:11,600
于是讓你給自己選個律師助理
so she's given you your pick of the liter.

133
00:05:11,680 --> 00:05:13,090
你就來這里打探
And now you're sniffing around here,

134
00:05:13,090 --> 00:05:15,180
想背著哈維對邁克發起攻勢
trying to put the moves on Mike behind Harvey's back.

135
00:05:15,180 --> 00:05:17,090
不不不  我絕不會這么做
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I would never do that.

136
00:05:17,440 --> 00:05:19,190
所以我才來征求同意
No, that's why I'm here to ask permission.

137
00:05:19,910 --> 00:05:20,730
那就去啊
So ask him.

138
00:05:20,750 --> 00:05:22,000
這話出自第三人之口
Well, I think it might go better

139
00:05:22,010 --> 00:05:23,210
效果可能會好一點
coming from a different source.

140
00:05:23,300 --> 00:05:24,580
-你想讓我去問  -對
- You want me to ask him. - Yeah.

141
00:05:24,580 --> 00:05:25,510
-可以嗎  -不行
- Would you please? - No.

142
00:05:25,510 --> 00:05:26,240
為什么
Why?

143
00:05:26,240 --> 00:05:27,600
因為我想聽你去問
Because it would be so much more fun

144
00:05:27,600 --> 00:05:29,320
一定會非常有意思
for me to listen to you ask him.

145
00:05:30,400 --> 00:05:31,630
好吧  說白了就是
Well, let me get this straight.

146
00:05:31,630 --> 00:05:33,320
你想把邁克從我身邊奪走
You want my permission to take Mike

147
00:05:33,320 --> 00:05:35,190
然后強迫他做你的助理
and force him to be your associate.

148
00:05:35,190 --> 00:05:36,720
不  我絕對不會強迫他做任何事
No, I would never force him to do anything.

149
00:05:36,770 --> 00:05:37,800
一定要以自愿為前提
It has to be consensual.

150
00:05:38,040 --> 00:05:40,200
不能像和薩莉·瓊斯在畢業舞會上那次
Not like Sally Jones and senior prom.

151
00:05:41,210 --> 00:05:43,270
等等  你剛才是承認自己犯罪了嗎
Wait a second. Did you just admit to a crime?

152
00:05:43,480 --> 00:05:45,690
不是  是別人對我犯罪
No, a crime was committed upon me.

153
00:05:46,050 --> 00:05:47,850
我不想問的  但必須得問一下
Okay, I don't want to, but I have to.

154
00:05:48,100 --> 00:05:49,050
什么罪名
What crime?

155
00:05:49,710 --> 00:05:52,410
我媽媽覺得薩莉很可憐  所以強迫我接受她
My mom felt bad for Sally, so she forced me to take her.

156
00:05:52,870 --> 00:05:54,790
她有什么可憐之處
Well, what was so bad about her?

157
00:05:56,450 --> 00:05:57,730
她有四個乳頭
She had four nipples.

158
00:06:00,210 --> 00:06:02,290
好吧  如果那次約會那么糟糕
Okay, if that date was so bad,

159
00:06:02,970 --> 00:06:04,830
你是怎么發現的
I mean, how did you find that out?

160
00:06:04,830 --> 00:06:05,940
行了  哈維
Okay, you know what, Harvey,

161
00:06:05,940 --> 00:06:07,100
你到底同不同意
do I have your blessing or not?

162
00:06:07,840 --> 00:06:09,160
盡管去吧  路易
Knock yourself out, Louis.

163
00:06:09,250 --> 00:06:10,460
不不  不對
See, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.

164
00:06:10,480 --> 00:06:12,490
你敢這么說是因為你覺得他會拒絕我
You're just saying that because you think he's gonna say no.

165
00:06:12,490 --> 00:06:14,810
-我是知道他會拒絕  -不  你錯了
- Oh, I know he'll say no. - Well, I know you're wrong.

166
00:06:15,410 --> 00:06:16,890
所以你最好考慮清楚
So you better think about this very carefully,

167
00:06:16,890 --> 00:06:17,990
否則你一旦答應
because once permission is given,

168
00:06:18,000 --> 00:06:19,200
就不能反悔了
you cannot go back.

169
00:06:20,800 --> 00:06:22,470
要么現在說  要么永遠別出聲
Speak now, or forever hold your peace.

170
00:06:23,090 --> 00:06:25,050
行  人我給你
Fine. He's yours.

171
00:06:25,330 --> 00:06:27,230
你們兩個肯定會合作愉快的
I'm sure you two will be very happy together.

172
00:06:27,230 --> 00:06:29,940
很好  完事之后
Good, 'cause when I'm done with him,

173
00:06:30,120 --> 00:06:32,040
邁克·羅斯一定會求著來當我的助理的
Mike Ross will be begging to be my associate.

174
00:06:35,630 --> 00:06:38,630
人人影視
YYeTs.com

175
00:06:35,630 --> 00:06:38,630
原創翻譯  雙語字幕

176
00:06:35,630 --> 00:06:38,630
■

177
00:06:35,630 --> 00:06:38,630
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com

178
00:06:38,630 --> 00:06:43,630
 翻譯：鳥  圈圈  阿囧  chelfi  貓咪賜我速死    Reginamoon

179
00:06:38,630 --> 00:06:43,630
■

180
00:06:43,630 --> 00:06:48,630
時間軸：Sinagujia  aaaBao  校對：swears  噎死青春  賀天天

181
00:06:43,630 --> 00:06:48,630
■

182
00:06:48,630 --> 00:06:53,630
 翻譯：珞小娘  小小   后期 & 特效：倉鼠sama     總監：swears

183
00:06:48,630 --> 00:06:53,630
■

184
00:07:00,290 --> 00:07:02,460
第三季 第二集

185
00:07:00,290 --> 00:07:02,460
訴 訟 雙 雄

186
00:07:08,430 --> 00:07:11,140
真是稀客啊
Well, well, a surprise.

187
00:07:11,140 --> 00:07:12,140
杰西卡
Jessica.

188
00:07:12,330 --> 00:07:13,650
咱倆上次見面的時候
Last time we saw each other,

189
00:07:13,650 --> 00:07:15,560
你以丟掉飯碗來要挾我
you were blackmailing me out of my job.

190
00:07:15,780 --> 00:07:16,710
這次又要故技重施嗎
Here to do it again?

191
00:07:17,400 --> 00:07:18,810
你手上掌握的把柄可是都給我了
Because you gave me what you had on me.

192
00:07:18,810 --> 00:07:20,260
我來只想說清楚一件事
I just want to make one thing clear.

193
00:07:20,510 --> 00:07:23,120
我對你的所作所為  責任在我
What I did to you, I did to you.

194
00:07:23,670 --> 00:07:24,870
不要拿哈維出氣
Don't take it out on Harvey.

195
00:07:25,120 --> 00:07:26,550
你還真貼心啊
Oh, that's sweet.

196
00:07:27,040 --> 00:07:29,030
跟護犢子一樣
Like a mother protecting her cub.

197
00:07:29,170 --> 00:07:31,120
有什么事盡管朝我來
Take me on anytime you want,

198
00:07:31,470 --> 00:07:34,070
不要因為我的所作所為去懲罰哈維的客戶
but don't punish Harvey's client for what I did.

199
00:07:34,480 --> 00:07:35,420
你的所作所為
You did?

200
00:07:36,380 --> 00:07:39,740
你在他就職地檢辦公室的時候
You just happened on evidence from his time

201
00:07:39,740 --> 00:07:40,890
恰好發現了證據
at the D.A.'s office?

202
00:07:45,570 --> 00:07:46,900
對了  那個紅發女人
Ah. The redhead.

203
00:07:47,290 --> 00:07:48,110
反正都無所謂了
Well, it doesn't matter,

204
00:07:48,110 --> 00:07:50,530
雖然背叛我的可能不是他
because he may not have been the one to betray me,

205
00:07:50,530 --> 00:07:51,670
但他也沒及時阻止
but he didn't stop it.

206
00:07:51,670 --> 00:07:53,890
你把他推進火坑  我救出了他
So after you threw him under the bus and I saved him,

207
00:07:53,890 --> 00:07:55,590
他應該自己再跳回火坑嗎
he should have thrown himself back under the bus?

208
00:07:55,590 --> 00:07:57,060
你怎么就是不明白
You just don't get it.

209
00:07:57,060 --> 00:07:57,990
我明白
Yes, I do.

210
00:07:58,720 --> 00:07:59,930
真正讓你生氣的
What you're really pissed at

211
00:07:59,930 --> 00:08:01,600
是他選了我  沒選你
is that he chose me over you.

212
00:08:01,610 --> 00:08:03,130
不是你  而是你的為人
Not you. What you are.

213
00:08:03,420 --> 00:08:05,000
我去解決壞人
I put bad guys away.

214
00:08:05,100 --> 00:08:06,150
而你卻在想辦法
You try to figure out

215
00:08:06,150 --> 00:08:07,230
讓他們為所欲為
how to let them do whatever they want.

216
00:08:07,230 --> 00:08:08,220
所以你沒資格來跟我說
So don't come in here telling me

217
00:08:08,220 --> 00:08:11,160
我把氣撒在了哈維的客戶身上
that I'm taking something out on Harvey's client,

218
00:08:11,370 --> 00:08:12,570
實話跟你說
because I'll tell you something--

219
00:08:13,470 --> 00:08:14,660
她確實有罪
She did this.

220
00:08:19,500 --> 00:08:20,850
你還給我做了張光盤
You made me a mixed tape.

221
00:08:20,940 --> 00:08:23,300
回去看看  然后跟我談條件
Watch it, and then make me an offer,

222
00:08:23,300 --> 00:08:25,260
當然  我會拒絕的  因為...
which I'll reject because...

223
00:08:26,020 --> 00:08:28,050
我吃定你們的客戶了
I got your client dead to rights.

224
00:08:35,170 --> 00:08:36,200
怎么樣
Well?

225
00:08:36,940 --> 00:08:38,820
我以前從沒吃過這么好的牛排
This is the best steak I've ever had in my life.

226
00:08:38,940 --> 00:08:40,960
你此生再也不會吃到
That is the best steak you will ever have

227
00:08:40,960 --> 00:08:41,880
這么好吃的牛排了
in your life.

228
00:08:42,660 --> 00:08:43,940
我很感激你讓我脫離了
As much as I appreciate for once

229
00:08:43,940 --> 00:08:46,030
在熱狗攤前吃午餐的苦海
not having to eat my lunch from the hot dog stand,

230
00:08:47,280 --> 00:08:48,280
但我們到底來這里干什么
what are we doing here?

231
00:08:49,490 --> 00:08:50,860
一個男人難道就不能帶另一個男人
Can't a man just take out another man

232
00:08:50,860 --> 00:08:52,410
在中午的時候出來吃吃牛排  喝喝葡萄酒
in the middle of the day for some steak and some wine

233
00:08:52,410 --> 00:08:54,700
再吃點好吃到爆的奶酪蛋糕嗎
and some cheesecake that's gonna knock your socks off?

234
00:08:55,220 --> 00:08:57,510
某類男人是可以的
Uh, some men could.

235
00:08:57,580 --> 00:08:59,890
但你我都清楚
But I think you and I both know

236
00:08:59,890 --> 00:09:01,390
你不屬于那類人
that you are not one of those men.

237
00:09:01,530 --> 00:09:02,620
這倒是真的
True that.

238
00:09:02,680 --> 00:09:03,750
還想來點葡萄酒嗎
Want some more wine?

239
00:09:03,750 --> 00:09:04,890
來點吧
Don't mind if I do.

240
00:09:05,020 --> 00:09:06,260
來嘗嘗這個奶酪蛋糕
And you gotta try this cheesecake.

241
00:09:06,270 --> 00:09:07,730
不用了  路易  我...
Oh, no, Louis, I'm-- mm--

242
00:09:08,430 --> 00:09:10,140
你知道我的意思對吧  你覺得怎么樣
You know what I mean, right? What do you think of that?

243
00:09:10,140 --> 00:09:11,780
路易  牛排怎么樣
Hey, Louis! How was the steak?

244
00:09:11,840 --> 00:09:12,990
-只應天上有  -你覺得呢
- Heaven. - How about you?

245
00:09:12,990 --> 00:09:13,980
是你吃過的最好的牛排嗎
Best steak you ever had?

246
00:09:13,980 --> 00:09:17,270
我此生再也吃不到這么好的牛排了
Uh, best steak I will ever have.

247
00:09:17,460 --> 00:09:18,560
你調教得不錯啊
You taught him well.

248
00:09:18,560 --> 00:09:20,060
你們是什么關系  兄弟嗎
What are you guys, brothers?

249
00:09:21,520 --> 00:09:22,580
開個玩笑
Oh, I'm just kidding.

250
00:09:22,580 --> 00:09:24,140
我知道路易有一個可愛的妹妹  埃斯特
Louis here's got a lovely sister, Esther,

251
00:09:24,150 --> 00:09:25,440
還有很棒的父母
two wonderful parents.

252
00:09:25,460 --> 00:09:26,910
那你到底是誰
Who the hell are you?

253
00:09:26,910 --> 00:09:29,570
我是邁克·羅斯  和路易是同事
I am Mike Ross. Louis and I work together.

254
00:09:29,570 --> 00:09:31,020
我想讓他知道他要為誰工作
I wanted him to know who he was working for.

255
00:09:31,120 --> 00:09:32,990
我也想讓你知道
And I would like you to know

256
00:09:33,080 --> 00:09:34,000
誰要為你工作
who's working for you.

257
00:09:34,010 --> 00:09:34,900
這里這位邁克
'Cause Mike here,

258
00:09:35,250 --> 00:09:36,660
絕對是你此生擁有的最棒的"牛排"
he's the best steak you'll ever have.

259
00:09:36,670 --> 00:09:38,120
想知道你工作的意義嗎
You want to know what you're working for?

260
00:09:39,210 --> 00:09:41,350
蒂娜  吉娜  安德麗安
Tina, Gina, Adrian.

261
00:09:41,890 --> 00:09:43,520
他們在這里待了大約有五十年了
They've been here 50 years between them.

262
00:09:43,520 --> 00:09:44,820
他們是我的家人
They are my family.

263
00:09:47,540 --> 00:09:48,730
這就是你工作的意義
That's what you're working for.

264
00:09:50,500 --> 00:09:51,750
我明白了
I-I understand.

265
00:09:55,500 --> 00:09:56,710
其實我不明白
I do not understand.

266
00:09:57,670 --> 00:09:58,710
土地征用權
Eminent domain.

267
00:09:59,380 --> 00:10:01,250
-我去  -最終聽證會在周二
- Shit. - Final hearing's Tuesday.

268
00:10:01,260 --> 00:10:03,290
如果我們輸了  這里要改建成購物中心
If we don't win, this place becomes a shopping center.

269
00:10:03,290 --> 00:10:04,630
那就讓這里改建成購物中心好了
Then this place becomes a shopping center,

270
00:10:04,630 --> 00:10:06,920
沒人能贏下涉及土地征用權的案件
because nobody wins eminent domain cases.

271
00:10:06,920 --> 00:10:08,140
要是我們贏了呢  邁克
But what if we did, Mike?

272
00:10:09,370 --> 00:10:10,840
那他就可以留住自己的餐館了
Then he'd get to keep his restaurant.

273
00:10:10,860 --> 00:10:12,280
他可以繼續實現自己的夢想
He would get to keep his dream,

274
00:10:12,980 --> 00:10:15,870
我也可以繼續實現的我夢想
and I would get to keep my dream.

275
00:10:17,630 --> 00:10:19,670
-你的夢想是什么  -重寫法律
- And what is that? - To rewrite the law.

276
00:10:19,860 --> 00:10:20,900
要想實現這個夢想
And the way to do that

277
00:10:20,900 --> 00:10:22,590
就得贏下這個看似無法取勝的案子
is to win an un-winnable case.

278
00:10:22,810 --> 00:10:23,830
你想讓我干什么
What do you need me to do?

279
00:10:27,200 --> 00:10:28,290
你去見卡梅隆了嗎
You went to see Cameron?

280
00:10:28,290 --> 00:10:29,900
我是來向你道歉的
I was just coming to apologize.

281
00:10:29,900 --> 00:10:31,350
因為你介入了我的案子嗎
For interfering on my case.

282
00:10:31,350 --> 00:10:32,130
他對你很生氣
He's pissed at you.

283
00:10:32,130 --> 00:10:33,470
他會把氣都撒到艾娃身上
He's going to take it out on Ava.

284
00:10:33,500 --> 00:10:34,680
我想讓他知道
I wanted to let him know the person

285
00:10:34,680 --> 00:10:35,940
他應該氣的是我
he should be pissed at is me.

286
00:10:35,940 --> 00:10:38,430
但這也沒法讓他不往艾娃身上撒氣
Well, it's not gonna stop him from taking it out on Ava.

287
00:10:38,490 --> 00:10:40,050
所以我才來道歉
Which is why I was coming to apologize.

288
00:10:40,050 --> 00:10:41,410
那你打不打算和我道歉
Are you also going to apologize

289
00:10:41,410 --> 00:10:42,850
告訴我我需要你
for sending the message that I need you

290
00:10:42,850 --> 00:10:44,290
才能打贏官司
to help me fight my battles for me?

291
00:10:44,290 --> 00:10:45,800
我不想為了你對抗卡梅隆
I don't want to fight Cameron for you.

292
00:10:45,850 --> 00:10:47,220
我要和你一起對抗卡梅隆
I want to fight Cameron with you.

293
00:10:47,510 --> 00:10:49,030
當證據對你不利時
When the evidence is stacked against you,

294
00:10:49,030 --> 00:10:51,580
你就學O.J.  請個夢幻團隊
you do what O.J. did-- you hire the dream team.

295
00:10:49,030 --> 00:10:51,580
O.J.辛普森  辛普森案被告方

296
00:10:51,580 --> 00:10:53,670
是說我們常去的酒吧O.J.嗎
Oh, that's our bar? O.J.?

297
00:10:53,760 --> 00:10:55,690
你說他到底能不能無罪釋放
Did he walk or not?

298
00:10:56,280 --> 00:10:57,180
好吧
Fine.

299
00:10:57,180 --> 00:10:58,670
但我可是約翰尼·科克倫
But I'm Johnnie Cochran.

300
00:10:57,180 --> 00:10:58,670
辛普森案辯方

301
00:11:02,690 --> 00:11:04,590
-你知道了  -我當然知道
- You know. - You know I know.

302
00:11:04,590 --> 00:11:05,650
邁克告訴我的
Mike told me.

303
00:11:05,650 --> 00:11:07,110
自從你讓我玩命去追《美國舞男》之后
Nobody had to tell me after you sent me

304
00:11:07,110 --> 00:11:09,820
這一切我都心知肚明了
on that wild goose chase after American Gigolo.

305
00:11:07,110 --> 00:11:09,820
理查·基爾主演

306
00:11:09,820 --> 00:11:10,690
對不起
Oh, I'm sorry.

307
00:11:10,690 --> 00:11:13,930
你不是褻瀆了我們神圣的友誼
You know, it's not that you violated the sanctity of our friendship.

308
00:11:14,440 --> 00:11:16,790
而是褻瀆了神圣的理查·基爾
It's that you violated the sanctity of Richard Gere--

309
00:11:17,340 --> 00:11:18,400
這種事我也愿意做
something I would like to do,

310
00:11:18,410 --> 00:11:19,590
但也不是像你這樣
but not the way you did it.

311
00:11:19,590 --> 00:11:21,750
聽著  我只是想讓邁克和哈維重歸于好
Look, I was just trying to get Mike back with harvey.

312
00:11:21,780 --> 00:11:22,860
我明白
I understand.

313
00:11:22,860 --> 00:11:24,970
因為我不想讓他們的恩怨影響到我們
Because I never want their thing to be our thing.

314
00:11:24,970 --> 00:11:25,810
當然了
It's not.

315
00:11:25,940 --> 00:11:27,470
不影響到我們的方法
And the way to keep it from becoming our thing

316
00:11:27,480 --> 00:11:29,300
-就是別再說他們了  -沒問題
- is to stop talking about them. - Done.

317
00:11:30,360 --> 00:11:31,750
你和邁克啊
So you and mike.

318
00:11:31,750 --> 00:11:33,890
是啊  費盡周折
I know. It's a lot.

319
00:11:33,890 --> 00:11:35,800
-你想談談嗎  -當然
- Do you want to talk about it? - Of course I do.

320
00:11:36,190 --> 00:11:37,320
那么我們就先從
Okay, I think we should start

321
00:11:37,320 --> 00:11:40,270
-最重要的感情問題開始  -好
- with the most important emotional question. - Okay.

322
00:11:45,600 --> 00:11:46,830
我開始擔心你了
I'm actually getting worried for you.

323
00:11:46,830 --> 00:11:48,200
你根本不了解情況
You don't know the half of it.

324
00:11:55,650 --> 00:11:57,710
路易  你說五點開始  現在才四點半
Louis, you said 5:00. It's only 4:30.

325
00:11:57,800 --> 00:11:59,290
我吃完飯后就來這了
I've been here since we ate.

326
00:11:59,650 --> 00:12:01,370
我在找所有有關征用權的案子
I've been researching every eminent domain case

327
00:12:01,370 --> 00:12:03,150
最早從1905年開始
ever tried, starting with 1905.

328
00:12:03,150 --> 00:12:03,790
克拉克和納什
Clark v. Nash.

329
00:12:03,790 --> 00:12:06,360
-你不是讓我去查嗎  -是啊
- I thought you wanted me to be doing the research? - I did.

330
00:12:06,360 --> 00:12:07,960
但我要是不一起找  要怎么幫你
But if I don't do it too, how can I help you?

331
00:12:09,710 --> 00:12:12,210
-你幫我  -是啊  幫你來幫我
- You're helping me? - Yeah. I help you help me.

332
00:12:12,210 --> 00:12:13,080
我們就這么合作
That's how it works.

333
00:12:14,070 --> 00:12:16,880
-你幫我我幫你  -什么
- Help me help you. - What?

334
00:12:16,880 --> 00:12:20,300
幫我...  是出自《甜心先生》里的
Help me help-- it's Jerry Maguire.

335
00:12:20,300 --> 00:12:22,890
-杰里什么  -你
- Jerry Mc-what? - You--

336
00:12:23,180 --> 00:12:24,730
如果你看完了所有訴訟文件
Okay, if you've gone over every case file,

337
00:12:24,730 --> 00:12:26,210
那你就會明白沒人能勝訴
then you know that the reason nobody wins

338
00:12:26,210 --> 00:12:28,400
是因為根本沒有漏洞可鉆
is because there is no chink in the armor.

339
00:12:28,460 --> 00:12:30,560
那我們就自己造一個
Well, then we make a chink of our own.

340
00:12:38,820 --> 00:12:39,860
如果我在陪審團
If I'm on a jury,

341
00:12:39,990 --> 00:12:42,050
我肯定會針對賄賂這一點
I'm looking at a bribe, plain as day.

342
00:12:42,120 --> 00:12:43,760
因為事實就是這樣
Because that's exactly what it is.

343
00:12:43,760 --> 00:12:45,330
我才不在乎
I don't care what it looks like.

344
00:12:45,330 --> 00:12:46,360
反正他們又沒音頻
There's no audio.

345
00:12:46,460 --> 00:12:47,950
就看陪審信我們還是信他們了
It's our story versus theirs.

346
00:12:47,950 --> 00:12:50,040
見不得人的交易  又處處和金錢有關
It's a shady deal and a case full of cash.

347
00:12:50,040 --> 00:12:51,710
他們的說法更有信服力
Their story is going to be more compelling.

348
00:12:51,710 --> 00:12:53,860
沒有更多證據卡梅倫庭審時不會冒險的
Cameron's not going to risk trial without more.

349
00:12:53,860 --> 00:12:55,010
你覺得他有這段音頻嗎
Do you think he has audio?

350
00:12:55,010 --> 00:12:55,960
這段音頻講什么的
What would it say?

351
00:12:56,290 --> 00:13:00,010
這位男士是馬加里上校
It would have this gentleman, Colonel Mariga,

352
00:13:00,010 --> 00:13:01,360
他問我們有沒有帶錢過來
asking if we had the money

353
00:13:01,360 --> 00:13:03,590
我的副手尼克·豪厄爾就把錢給了他
and my number two, Nick Howell, showing it to him.

354
00:13:03,630 --> 00:13:07,940
然后他感謝我們支付污染整治費
Then he would thank us for paying a pollution remediation fee.

355
00:13:07,940 --> 00:13:09,810
聽起來可真夠環保的
That sounds environmentally sound.

356
00:13:09,810 --> 00:13:13,390
但是該整治的我們都整治過了
Except we'd already remediated everything that needed to be remediated.

357
00:13:13,560 --> 00:13:16,560
-于是你知道這是賄賂  -是的
- Which is how you knew it was a bribe. - Yes.

358
00:13:17,040 --> 00:13:18,070
問題是
The question is,

359
00:13:18,070 --> 00:13:19,910
你在那個房間里有提到這個詞嗎
did you ever use that word in that room?

360
00:13:20,010 --> 00:13:21,540
我也許厚顏無恥  斯佩克特先生
I may be brazen, Mr. Specter,

361
00:13:21,540 --> 00:13:22,900
但我不蠢
but I am not a fool.

362
00:13:22,980 --> 00:13:24,810
那音頻對他們毫無用處
Then the audio won't help them anyway.

363
00:13:26,060 --> 00:13:26,980
那個上校呢
The Colonel?

364
00:13:26,980 --> 00:13:29,650
不對  他們還是占上風  他沒有被控告
No, they're still in power. He's not getting indicted.

365
00:13:35,500 --> 00:13:36,560
什么意思
What?

366
00:13:36,780 --> 00:13:38,170
卡梅倫搞定了你的副手
Cameron's got your protege.

367
00:13:38,770 --> 00:13:39,810
不可能
No.

368
00:13:40,300 --> 00:13:42,240
我培養了尼克十年了
I've been grooming Nick for ten years.

369
00:13:42,240 --> 00:13:43,980
我教會了他所有東西
I've taught him everything he knows.

370
00:13:44,100 --> 00:13:45,800
比如如何賄賂外國政府
Like how to bribe a foreign government?

371
00:13:45,860 --> 00:13:49,110
這可不是一回事  他永遠不會背叛我的
That is not the same. He would never turn on me.

372
00:13:49,110 --> 00:13:50,850
當你發現你最信賴的人
You'd be surprised what people you trust

373
00:13:50,850 --> 00:13:52,960
在被迫無奈的情況下背叛你
would do when someone puts them in a position

374
00:13:52,970 --> 00:13:54,610
你一定會很驚訝的
where they think they don't have a choice.

375
00:13:57,470 --> 00:13:58,500
哈維說得對
Harvey's right.

376
00:13:59,310 --> 00:14:02,790
一旦把別人推到違法的道路上
Once someone puts another person down the path of bending the law,

377
00:14:03,670 --> 00:14:05,840
-相互背叛就會滋生  -你不了解他
- people tend to turn on each other. - You don't know him.

378
00:14:06,460 --> 00:14:08,030
你最后一次和他說話是什么時候
When's the last time you spoke to him?

379
00:14:08,170 --> 00:14:09,260
幾天前
A few days ago.

380
00:14:09,400 --> 00:14:11,280
打電話給他  他肯定不會接
Call him. He won't take your call.

381
00:14:11,700 --> 00:14:12,780
這你就錯了
You're wrong.

382
00:14:12,900 --> 00:14:14,550
我的電話他一定接
He always takes my calls.

383
00:14:16,200 --> 00:14:17,930
嗨  我是尼克  請留言
Hi, it's nick. Leave a message.

384
00:14:18,880 --> 00:14:20,820
我來告訴你這是什么意思吧
Let me tell you what that message really said.

385
00:14:20,910 --> 00:14:22,540
"嗨  艾娃  我是尼克
"Hi, Ava. It's Nick.

386
00:14:22,540 --> 00:14:25,740
我現在不在  因為我打算毀約出賣你
I'm not here right now because I'm cutting a deal to sell you out."

387
00:14:35,510 --> 00:14:36,750
和路易合作得怎樣
How's it going with Louis?

388
00:14:36,780 --> 00:14:39,060
感覺還不錯
You know, it's actually not bad.

389
00:14:39,630 --> 00:14:42,270
但事實是  我更想...
But the truth is, I would rather be--

390
00:14:42,430 --> 00:14:43,750
-別想  -拜托
- No. - What? Come on.

391
00:14:43,760 --> 00:14:44,870
都已經午夜了
It's the middle of the night.

392
00:14:44,940 --> 00:14:46,160
路易隨時都可能回來
Louis could be back at any minute.

393
00:14:46,170 --> 00:14:47,630
-我可以速戰速決  -我知道
- I can be fast. - I know.

394
00:14:48,700 --> 00:14:50,240
就那一次而已啦
That was a one-time thing.

395
00:14:53,500 --> 00:14:56,420
好了好了
Mm, mm, mm. Enough, enough.

396
00:14:56,420 --> 00:14:58,760
但我...  好吧
But I-- okay.

397
00:14:59,630 --> 00:15:00,830
也許你說得對
Yeah, you're probably right.

398
00:15:01,450 --> 00:15:03,180
我們最不想被路易抓現形
The last person we want catching us is louis.

399
00:15:03,180 --> 00:15:05,320
你有沒有想過他在試著挖走你
Did it ever occur to you that's he's trying to recruit you?

400
00:15:05,320 --> 00:15:06,500
我們就不能
Can we just for once assume

401
00:15:06,500 --> 00:15:08,340
別揣測路易的動機嗎
that Louis doesn't have an ulterior motive?

402
00:15:09,590 --> 00:15:11,460
我準備了些茶點
I got us some refreshments.

403
00:15:13,010 --> 00:15:15,090
我就不打攪你倆工作了
I will leave you two to your work.

404
00:15:16,600 --> 00:15:18,040
-好了嗎  -搞定
- So? - Yeah.

405
00:15:18,720 --> 00:15:20,250
路易  這都大半夜了
Louis, it's the middle of the night.

406
00:15:20,250 --> 00:15:21,450
你在哪買到的
Where did you get all this?

407
00:15:21,560 --> 00:15:23,430
我可是新任采購主管  不記得了嗎
I'm the new quartermaster, remember?

408
00:15:25,060 --> 00:15:26,030
好吧
Okay.

409
00:15:26,160 --> 00:15:27,260
給你  看看這個
Here, check this out.

410
00:15:31,510 --> 00:15:33,100
沒想到是從這里突破
Whoa, no one's thought to come at it this way.

411
00:15:33,100 --> 00:15:34,300
邁克  這太厲害了
Mike, this is outstanding.

412
00:15:34,510 --> 00:15:36,250
其實是一部電影啟發了我
I actually got the idea from a movie.

413
00:15:36,760 --> 00:15:38,990
-《點球成金》  -你不是討厭體育嗎
- Moneyball. - I thought you hated sports.

414
00:15:39,070 --> 00:15:40,250
《點球成金》跟體育沒關系
Moneyball isn't about sports.

415
00:15:40,250 --> 00:15:41,380
-是關于數學的  -沒錯
- It's about math. - Exactly.

416
00:15:41,380 --> 00:15:43,410
有個問題  這是違法的
One problem. It's outside the scope.

417
00:15:43,410 --> 00:15:45,780
-如果不違法呢  -如果能不被發現呢
- What if it weren't? - What if I could fly?

418
00:15:45,780 --> 00:15:46,570
這我幫不了你
Well, I can't help you with that.

419
00:15:46,570 --> 00:15:47,840
但要想讓它不違法
But if we want to get it in the scope,

420
00:15:48,170 --> 00:15:50,250
只要讓對方幫我們做到就行了
we just have to get the other side to put it there for us.

421
00:16:02,260 --> 00:16:03,510
早啊
Morning.

422
00:16:04,760 --> 00:16:06,290
這輛福特野馬不錯  哈維
Nice Mustang, Harvey.

423
00:16:06,690 --> 00:16:08,680
你還想變成史蒂夫·麥奎因啊
I see you're still trying to be Steve Mcqueen.

424
00:16:06,690 --> 00:16:08,680
美國演員  曾在電影《警網鐵金剛》中駕駛福特野馬

425
00:16:08,680 --> 00:16:09,740
不是想變成
Not trying.

426
00:16:10,740 --> 00:16:11,800
已經是了
Being.

427
00:16:12,070 --> 00:16:14,350
現在就是他圍堵大惡棍的那一幕
This is the scene where he corners the asshole.

428
00:16:14,740 --> 00:16:17,920
談到電影  我寄給你的那部你喜歡嗎
Speaking of movies, did you enjoy the one that I sent over?

429
00:16:18,210 --> 00:16:20,440
很少有電影拍到整個犯罪過程啊
It's not often we get the whole crime on film.

430
00:16:20,440 --> 00:16:23,710
你寄來的不過是無法證明任何東西的默片
All you have is a silent film with no proof of anything.

431
00:16:23,710 --> 00:16:25,450
順便告訴你  我要因隱瞞證據
And by the way, I'm going to have you sanctioned

432
00:16:25,450 --> 00:16:26,490
對你申請制裁
for withholding evidence.

433
00:16:26,490 --> 00:16:29,030
我錄像寄得很及時啊
I gave you that video in a timely manner.

434
00:16:29,030 --> 00:16:30,160
你給我們錄像
You gave us that video,

435
00:16:30,160 --> 00:16:31,770
只是為了讓我們不去留意尼克
so we'd take our eyes off Nick.

436
00:16:32,090 --> 00:16:32,990
哪個尼克
Nick who?

437
00:16:33,870 --> 00:16:36,620
被你藏在某個酒店房間的那個
The Nick you have stashed in a hotel room somewhere.

438
00:16:36,740 --> 00:16:38,130
那個尼克啊
Oh, that Nick.

439
00:16:38,130 --> 00:16:39,230
多虧你提到他
Now that you mention it,

440
00:16:39,230 --> 00:16:43,680
我好像該把他列為證人
I probably should put him on my witness list.

441
00:16:44,930 --> 00:16:46,370
我都有點不熟練了
I'm a little out of practice.

442
00:16:49,750 --> 00:16:50,780
給你
There you go.

443
00:16:51,690 --> 00:16:53,700
趕緊把你的
Now... why don't you get

444
00:16:53,700 --> 00:16:55,800
這坨垃圾從我的車道上移開
that piece of shit out of my driveway, okay?

445
00:16:59,690 --> 00:17:01,520
我第一次吃到真正的牛排
The first time I ever had steak,

446
00:17:01,900 --> 00:17:03,010
就是在彼得的餐館
It was at Peter's.

447
00:17:04,310 --> 00:17:05,790
我之前吃過牛排
I mean, I'd had steak before...

448
00:17:06,700 --> 00:17:09,910
但那些都不算真正的牛排
but I never had steak before.

449
00:17:10,300 --> 00:17:11,700
這不是我今天站在這的原因
But that's not why I'm here today.

450
00:17:12,060 --> 00:17:13,620
吃到一半的時候
You see, halfway through the meal,

451
00:17:13,640 --> 00:17:14,710
彼得走到我的桌前
Peter came over to my table,

452
00:17:14,710 --> 00:17:15,820
問我喜不喜歡
and he asked how I'd liked it.

453
00:17:17,710 --> 00:17:19,380
他想了解  因為他在乎
He wanted to know because he cared.

454
00:17:20,200 --> 00:17:21,290
他在乎我
He cared about me.

455
00:17:21,580 --> 00:17:24,110
我朋友不多
I don't make friends very easily,

456
00:17:24,530 --> 00:17:26,700
但是我一走進彼得的牛排屋
but the second I set foot in Peter's steakhouse,

457
00:17:26,760 --> 00:17:28,880
我便交到了一生的摯友
I had made a friend for life.

458
00:17:29,230 --> 00:17:31,320
而彼得對牛排屋的每一個顧客
And that is how Peter treats every single person

459
00:17:31,320 --> 00:17:32,370
都是如此
who walks through his door.

460
00:17:32,740 --> 00:17:34,310
所以我不在乎大家怎么說
So I don't care what they say.

461
00:17:34,310 --> 00:17:37,200
法官大人  這不算是公眾利益
Your honor, this is not a public benefit.

462
00:17:37,680 --> 00:17:41,010
法官大人  我很感動
Your honor, I'm... I'm touched.

463
00:17:41,540 --> 00:17:43,100
他讓我想現在就奔去
He makes me want to run right over there

464
00:17:43,380 --> 00:17:44,490
來一塊牛排
and get a steak.

465
00:17:44,560 --> 00:17:46,740
但根據最高法院對凱洛案的判決
But as for the supreme court decision in Kelo,

466
00:17:46,740 --> 00:17:48,570
公眾利益要以數量
public benefit is determined on a quantitative,

467
00:17:48,570 --> 00:17:50,010
而非質量衡量
not qualitative basis.

468
00:17:50,540 --> 00:17:51,790
很高興你提到凱洛案
Well, I'm glad you brought up Kelo,

469
00:17:51,790 --> 00:17:55,280
我們這里剛好有量化證據
because we happen to have some quantitative evidence right here.

470
00:17:55,430 --> 00:17:57,550
凱洛案于2005年判決
Kelo was decided in 2005.

471
00:17:57,550 --> 00:17:59,200
八年過去了
Eight years later and still,

472
00:17:59,200 --> 00:18:01,140
我們沒有看到任何成效
nothing has been built on this land.

473
00:18:01,140 --> 00:18:02,280
沒有產生就業崗位
No jobs created,

474
00:18:02,280 --> 00:18:03,990
或稅收收入  經濟效益
no taxes collected, no money made.

475
00:18:03,990 --> 00:18:06,050
毫無量化利益
Zero quantitative benefit.

476
00:18:06,800 --> 00:18:08,710
他們說會有所改善
Just because they say it will be better

477
00:18:08,710 --> 00:18:10,080
并不意味真的會有改善
Doesn't mean it actually will be.

478
00:18:10,080 --> 00:18:13,560
即便如此  我們還是有權這樣做
Even if it were true, we have every right to do it.

479
00:18:14,130 --> 00:18:16,140
利益由政府決定  而非法院
The state determines benefit, not the court,

480
00:18:16,150 --> 00:18:17,670
直到法律修訂前
and until such time as the law is changed,

481
00:18:17,670 --> 00:18:19,320
您無權改變政府的決定
you have no authority to affect the state's determination.

482
00:18:19,320 --> 00:18:21,010
法官大人  您今天就可以建立新的判例
Uh, your honor, you can establish authority today.

483
00:18:21,010 --> 00:18:22,120
這樣做沒有依據
There's no basis for that.

484
00:18:22,120 --> 00:18:23,760
您只能繼續維持
You have no choice but to uphold

485
00:18:23,760 --> 00:18:25,400
政府征用權的原有機制
the established practice of eminent domain.

486
00:18:26,360 --> 00:18:28,300
抱歉  對方律師說的沒錯
I'm afraid opposing counsel is right.

487
00:18:28,570 --> 00:18:30,210
下周開始拆遷
Demolition begins next week.

488
00:18:33,320 --> 00:18:35,360
我剛想到在《點球成金》里
I just remembered something about Moneyball.

489
00:18:36,160 --> 00:18:38,620
奧克蘭運動家隊就沒贏過世界大賽
The A's never actually won the world series.

490
00:18:40,720 --> 00:18:41,770
抱歉  路易
I'm sorry, Louis.

491
00:18:41,770 --> 00:18:43,000
現在不是抱歉的時候
Now is not the time to be sorry.

492
00:18:43,000 --> 00:18:44,220
那要干什么
What is it the time for?

493
00:18:45,930 --> 00:18:46,980
進來
Get in.

494
00:18:47,580 --> 00:18:48,660
不用了  我站這兒挺好
Nah, I think I'm good.

495
00:18:50,020 --> 00:18:52,470
邁克  沒什么好怕的
Mike, there's nothing to be afraid of.

496
00:18:52,470 --> 00:18:54,090
不過是干凈的泥罷了
It's just good, clean mud.

497
00:18:54,220 --> 00:18:55,950
怎么會有這種東西
That doesn't make any sense.

498
00:18:55,950 --> 00:18:57,540
是因為我裸體嗎
Is this about the fact that I'm in the nude?

499
00:18:57,730 --> 00:18:58,970
拜托別提這茬了
Please don't harp on that.

500
00:18:59,220 --> 00:19:00,190
說說而已  我明白
Yeah, I'm just saying, I know

501
00:19:00,190 --> 00:19:02,180
現在的年輕人都特矜持
how the younger generation gets hung up on that stuff.

502
00:19:02,250 --> 00:19:02,950
不用擔心
But you don't have to worry

503
00:19:02,950 --> 00:19:04,240
你有你自己的浴池
because you have your own self-contained unit.

504
00:19:04,240 --> 00:19:06,290
我進去了  你能閉嘴嗎
Okay, if I get in, will you stop saying words?

505
00:19:17,260 --> 00:19:18,200
你要是穿著短褲進去
You know, if you go in with boxers,

506
00:19:18,200 --> 00:19:19,250
出來就沒法穿了
you're not gonna have them later.

507
00:19:19,250 --> 00:19:20,410
你得光屁股了
You're gonna have to go smokeless.

508
00:19:33,080 --> 00:19:35,940
這個兩面派的人渣
That disloyal piece of filth.

509
00:19:35,940 --> 00:19:37,370
相信我  我理解你的感受
Believe me, I know how you feel.

510
00:19:37,380 --> 00:19:38,290
你理解
Do you?

511
00:19:39,040 --> 00:19:41,400
我聽說你喜歡獨來獨往
Because I've heard you prefer to work alone.

512
00:19:41,400 --> 00:19:42,530
我可不喜歡
Well, I don't.

513
00:19:43,550 --> 00:19:45,170
剛開始或許我是他的上級
I may have been above him when we started,

514
00:19:45,180 --> 00:19:46,200
但過去兩年里
but for the last two years,

515
00:19:46,200 --> 00:19:48,400
我們一直并肩作戰
we worked together side by side.

516
00:19:48,790 --> 00:19:51,150
我不多愁善感  但這對我很重要
I'm not a sentimental person, but it meant something to me,

517
00:19:51,150 --> 00:19:52,770
我以為他也覺得如此
and I thought it meant something to him.

518
00:19:53,210 --> 00:19:55,810
-他該死  -沒錯
- He deserves to be shot. - He does.

519
00:19:56,480 --> 00:19:58,660
但我想要不要給他升職
But I suggest we promote him instead.

520
00:19:58,790 --> 00:20:01,460
你想給他升職來封他的口嗎
You want to give him a new title to keep him from testifying?

521
00:20:01,500 --> 00:20:04,280
我覺得還得給他大幅加薪
I believe it will require a substantial raise as well.

522
00:20:04,280 --> 00:20:05,860
我不是這個意思
You know that's not what I meant.

523
00:20:05,870 --> 00:20:07,480
你想通過賄賂別人
You're suggesting bribing a man

524
00:20:07,480 --> 00:20:09,210
來擺脫賄賂指控
to get you out of your bribery charge.

525
00:20:09,260 --> 00:20:10,980
一不做  二不休
In for a penny, in for a pound.

526
00:20:10,980 --> 00:20:12,120
我母親總是這么說
Mother always said.

527
00:20:13,550 --> 00:20:14,900
這就是卡梅隆的目的
This is what Cameron wanted.

528
00:20:14,900 --> 00:20:17,070
那盤錄像不是為了讓我們放過尼克
He didn't give us that video so we wouldn't find Nick.

529
00:20:17,070 --> 00:20:19,370
他用尼克引誘你去行賄
He gave us Nick, so you'd try to bribe him.

530
00:20:19,610 --> 00:20:20,740
你怎么知道
Well, how can you know that?

531
00:20:20,740 --> 00:20:22,890
因為卡梅隆知道本性難移的道理
Because Cameron knows people are who they are.

532
00:20:23,140 --> 00:20:25,140
一日行賄  終身難改
You bribed once, you'll bribe again.

533
00:20:25,140 --> 00:20:26,640
那你說怎么辦
Well, then what are you suggesting I do?

534
00:20:26,640 --> 00:20:28,130
我可打算試著說服他了
Because I'm going to make a run at him.

535
00:20:28,130 --> 00:20:30,540
不  我去找他
No, I'm gonna make a run at him.

536
00:20:37,790 --> 00:20:38,760
路易
Louis.

537
00:20:39,620 --> 00:20:40,640
干嗎
Yeah?

538
00:20:41,410 --> 00:20:43,960
這是我洗過的最棒的泥漿浴
This is the best damn mud I've ever had.

539
00:20:44,700 --> 00:20:45,870
我
Hey, I--

540
00:20:48,560 --> 00:20:50,250
我知道你為什么選我做這個案子
I know why you picked me for this case.

541
00:20:51,000 --> 00:20:52,530
你要是不知道我也不會選你
I wouldn't have picked you if you didn't.

542
00:20:52,860 --> 00:20:54,340
如果你想要我做你的助理
If you wanted me to be your associate,

543
00:20:54,340 --> 00:20:55,500
為什么不直接問我
why didn't you just ask?

544
00:20:56,020 --> 00:20:57,350
因為你會拒絕的
Because you would've said no.

545
00:20:57,520 --> 00:20:59,750
-路易  拜托  -不  麥克
- Louis, come on. - no, Mike.

546
00:21:00,150 --> 00:21:01,440
我知道大家是怎么看我的
I know what people think of me,

547
00:21:01,440 --> 00:21:02,960
我知道你是怎么看我的
and I know what you think of me.

548
00:21:03,300 --> 00:21:04,400
我知道你還記得
I knew you'd remember

549
00:21:04,400 --> 00:21:06,090
和我工作時候的糟糕事兒
all the bad things about working with me.

550
00:21:06,090 --> 00:21:07,880
我只是想讓你記起一些好的回憶
I just wanted to remind you of some of the good ones.

551
00:21:07,890 --> 00:21:09,530
我記得那些美好的回憶
I remember all the good ones,

552
00:21:09,530 --> 00:21:11,540
但我也記得在那過后
but I also remember after those things,

553
00:21:11,540 --> 00:21:12,720
你又變成了
you going back to being

554
00:21:12,720 --> 00:21:15,110
我第一天工作所見到的路易
the same Louis I met the first day of work.

555
00:21:15,110 --> 00:21:17,840
那個當著我的面炒人魷魚
The Louis who fired someone right in front of my face

556
00:21:17,840 --> 00:21:21,060
只為教我恐懼的路易
for the sole purpose of teaching me to be afraid.

557
00:21:21,760 --> 00:21:22,650
你說得對
You're right.

558
00:21:24,210 --> 00:21:27,190
我記得你有一次說我的所作所為也很重要
I remember you once said that my actions matter

559
00:21:27,190 --> 00:21:29,530
并不能一筆勾銷那么簡單
and that it's not water under the bridge.

560
00:21:29,530 --> 00:21:30,830
你改變了我
You've changed me.

561
00:21:31,050 --> 00:21:33,010
你讓我想要成為更出色的人
You make me want to be a better man.

562
00:21:33,320 --> 00:21:35,840
等等  你是說我讓你更完整嗎
Wait, are you saying I complete you?

563
00:21:35,840 --> 00:21:37,260
你看過《甜心先生》嘛
You have seen Jerry Maguire.

564
00:21:37,270 --> 00:21:38,860
不  我在引用我最愛電影主角的臺詞
no, I'm quoting my cinema hero,

565
00:21:38,860 --> 00:21:40,270
梅爾文·尤德爾的角色
the character of Melvin Udall,

566
00:21:38,860 --> 00:21:42,680
《盡善盡美》的男主角

567
00:21:40,270 --> 00:21:42,680
杰克·尼克爾森將其演繹得淋漓盡致
expertly portrayed by Jack Nicholson as good as it gets.

568
00:21:42,680 --> 00:21:45,450
-沒看過  -好吧  你挺幸運
- Oh. Never saw it. - Oh, well, then you're lucky.

569
00:21:45,450 --> 00:21:46,360
為什么這么說
Why is that?

570
00:21:46,360 --> 00:21:48,130
因為你還可以享受第一次觀影
Because you can still see it for the first time.

571
00:21:52,370 --> 00:21:53,190
第一次
The first time.

572
00:21:53,190 --> 00:21:55,330
就是這個  第一次
That's it, the first time.

573
00:21:55,330 --> 00:21:56,880
-怎么了  -法官
- What? - The judge.

574
00:21:56,880 --> 00:21:59,090
當時你申辯說這將是第一次
You were making your argument about the first time.

575
00:21:59,090 --> 00:22:00,880
他想做出對我們有利的判決  但是不行
He wanted to rule in our favor, but he couldn't.

576
00:22:00,880 --> 00:22:02,590
我知道  所以我們需要他修改法律
I know, that's why we need him to rewrite the law.

577
00:22:02,590 --> 00:22:04,260
不  我們不用  因為法律中
No, we don't, because there's already

578
00:22:04,260 --> 00:22:06,330
已經有對我們有利的條款了
a provision in the law that works for us.

579
00:22:06,330 --> 00:22:07,700
-它在第...  -不不不
- It's in section-- - No, no, no, no.

580
00:22:07,700 --> 00:22:11,770
首先  我泥浴的時候不談工作  好嗎
First of all, I cannot mix work with mudding, okay?

581
00:22:11,980 --> 00:22:13,360
我們好好沐浴一番
Let's hit the showers.

582
00:22:13,360 --> 00:22:15,810
我等不及要大戰對方律師了
I can't wait to stick it to opposing counsel.

583
00:22:15,820 --> 00:22:17,370
需要我拉你一把嗎
Do you need me to give you a hand out of there?

584
00:22:25,530 --> 00:22:26,720
我知道你是誰
I know who you are.

585
00:22:26,920 --> 00:22:28,080
你不該來這里
You shouldn't be here.

586
00:22:28,080 --> 00:22:30,140
不  尼克  不該在這的是你
No, Nick. You shouldn't be here.

587
00:22:30,140 --> 00:22:30,920
你走吧
I'd like you to go.

588
00:22:30,920 --> 00:22:32,970
不  你不會想我走的
No. You wouldn't.

589
00:22:33,210 --> 00:22:34,600
你最好給我五分鐘
You'd like to give me five minutes

590
00:22:34,600 --> 00:22:36,600
看看在你出賣靈魂之前
to see if I can get you out of the box you're in

591
00:22:36,600 --> 00:22:38,130
我能否拯救你
before you sell your soul.

592
00:22:44,400 --> 00:22:45,740
我不想這么做的
I didn't want to do this.

593
00:22:47,930 --> 00:22:49,360
如果你想的話  就不會讓我進來了
You wouldn't let me in if you did.

594
00:22:49,360 --> 00:22:50,740
我別無選擇
I had no choice.

595
00:22:50,790 --> 00:22:52,730
不管我是否作證  艾娃都有麻煩了
Ava's in trouble whether I testify or not.

596
00:22:52,740 --> 00:22:54,380
那正是卡梅隆想讓你相信的
That's what Cameron wants you to believe.

597
00:22:54,380 --> 00:22:55,300
你沒看過錄像嗎
You haven't seen the video?

598
00:22:55,300 --> 00:22:57,350
我看到的是一場交易
I saw a business transaction.

599
00:22:57,350 --> 00:22:59,360
-你不相信  -我可以讓別人相信
- You don't believe that. - I can sell that.

600
00:22:59,360 --> 00:23:01,150
你只要保持冷靜  閉上嘴就行
You just got to keep your head and shut your mouth.

601
00:23:01,160 --> 00:23:02,320
有話直說吧
Just do what you're here to do,

602
00:23:02,320 --> 00:23:03,670
恐嚇我  或者提交易
threaten me, or offer me a deal.

603
00:23:03,680 --> 00:23:05,940
-兩者我都考慮過  -卡梅隆說過你會的
- I've considered both. - Cameron said you would.

604
00:23:05,940 --> 00:23:07,150
卡梅隆錯了
Cameron's wrong.

605
00:23:08,010 --> 00:23:08,900
兩者我都不會做
I'm not going to do either

606
00:23:08,900 --> 00:23:10,860
因為我認為你關心艾娃
because I think you care about Ava.

607
00:23:11,710 --> 00:23:12,590
是的
I do.

608
00:23:13,450 --> 00:23:14,810
那就考慮下這點
Then think about this.

609
00:23:15,490 --> 00:23:17,410
無論卡梅隆向你提什么協議
Whatever deal cameron offered you,

610
00:23:17,410 --> 00:23:19,930
都是假的  他沒有任何把柄
it's based on a lie. He doesn't have anything.

611
00:23:20,120 --> 00:23:21,790
他只是想利用你的恐懼
He's just trying to use your fear

612
00:23:21,800 --> 00:23:23,200
坑你對付艾娃
to pit you against Ava.

613
00:23:23,200 --> 00:23:24,750
我曾經見識過這一招
Look, I've seen it happen before,

614
00:23:24,750 --> 00:23:26,580
我對你唯一的忠告就是
And the one thing I can tell you is

615
00:23:27,070 --> 00:23:28,810
如果你這么做  你一輩子
you go through with it, you'll regret it

616
00:23:28,810 --> 00:23:30,260
都會活在悔恨中
for the rest of your life.

617
00:23:30,430 --> 00:23:32,000
因為她永遠不會原諒我
Because she'll never forgive me.

618
00:23:32,010 --> 00:23:34,040
因為你永遠不會原諒你自己
Because you'll never forgive yourself.

619
00:23:37,370 --> 00:23:39,210
好吧  什么事情如此重要
Okay, what is so important that

620
00:23:39,210 --> 00:23:40,820
我們非得開個緊急聽證會
we need to have an emergency hearing?

621
00:23:40,820 --> 00:23:41,890
法官大人  在拆遷開始之前
Your honor, we need to be heard

622
00:23:41,890 --> 00:23:43,020
你需要聽聽我們的想法
before demolition starts.

623
00:23:43,020 --> 00:23:43,780
這次又是什么
What's he going to do now,

624
00:23:43,780 --> 00:23:45,390
告訴我們他的第一次行動嗎
tell us about his first demolition?

625
00:23:45,390 --> 00:23:47,330
非常精彩  但我想說的不是這個
It was riveting, but this has nothing to do that.

626
00:23:47,330 --> 00:23:48,630
法官大人  基于針對他們的工程
Your honor, based on the new zoning

627
00:23:48,630 --> 00:23:49,890
通過的區域重劃分
put through for their project,

628
00:23:49,890 --> 00:23:52,080
我們僅僅請求對他們納入的地產
We're simply asking for a revised valuation

629
00:23:52,090 --> 00:23:53,910
進行重新評估
of the property that they're taking.

630
00:23:57,380 --> 00:23:58,670
一億美元
$100 million?

631
00:23:58,670 --> 00:24:00,160
這樣的評估毫無根據
That valuation has no basis.

632
00:24:00,160 --> 00:24:01,790
這個結果有確實的數理根據
It has a mathematical basis.

633
00:24:01,800 --> 00:24:04,050
具體來說  未來現金流量的現值
Specifically, the present value of future cash flow,

634
00:24:04,050 --> 00:24:04,980
如那上面所述
as shown right there.

635
00:24:04,990 --> 00:24:06,880
胡扯  你聽說過巫毒經濟學吧
Bullshit. You've heard of voodoo economics.

636
00:24:04,990 --> 00:24:07,880
巫毒經濟學  
里根總統實行的"供給面經濟學"的批評說法

637
00:24:06,880 --> 00:24:07,990
這就是巫毒數學
This is voodoo math.

638
00:24:07,990 --> 00:24:10,160
他們作出各種瘋狂推論來抬高自己的身價
They're making crazy assumptions to inflate their value.

639
00:24:10,160 --> 00:24:10,990
就像凱洛訴新倫敦市案  但是
just like Kelo, but that

640
00:24:10,160 --> 00:24:13,070
美國著名經濟案件  法院允許政府為了經濟發展的需要征用私有財產

641
00:24:11,000 --> 00:24:13,070
當那對你們有利的時候  你們倒不在乎
really didn't seem to bother you when it was in your favor.

642
00:24:13,070 --> 00:24:14,460
法官大人  這太荒唐了
Your honor, this is ludicrous.

643
00:24:14,460 --> 00:24:15,450
他們選這個數字
They're only picking that number

644
00:24:15,450 --> 00:24:16,590
就是因為他們知道這會使我們的項目
because they know it makes our project

645
00:24:16,590 --> 00:24:17,850
因為太昂貴而不可行
too expensive to be feasible.

646
00:24:17,850 --> 00:24:19,510
根據對方律師所言
Well, in the words of opposing counsel,

647
00:24:19,510 --> 00:24:22,830
就算他說的沒錯  我們也完全有權這么做
Even if that were true, we have every right to do it.

648
00:24:25,110 --> 00:24:27,350
嗨  唐娜  我喜歡你的裙子
Hi, Donna. I love your dress.

649
00:24:27,450 --> 00:24:28,710
我喜歡你有求于我的時候
And I love when you compliment me

650
00:24:28,710 --> 00:24:29,850
恭維我
before you ask for something.

651
00:24:29,850 --> 00:24:31,190
你真是目光如炬
You're so insightful.

652
00:24:31,920 --> 00:24:32,990
我知道我們說過
Look, I know we said

653
00:24:32,990 --> 00:24:34,700
哈維和麥克的問題與我們無關
Harvey and Mike's problem isn't our problem,

654
00:24:34,700 --> 00:24:36,240
但路易想偷走麥克
but Louis is stealing Mike.

655
00:24:36,240 --> 00:24:38,760
如果某人完全自由  那就不是偷
It's not stealing when someone's available for the taking.

656
00:24:39,470 --> 00:24:40,520
你知道
You knew?

657
00:24:40,520 --> 00:24:41,960
我什么時候不知道
When do I not know?

658
00:24:42,460 --> 00:24:44,580
路易向哈維征求同意  想要麥克
Louis asked for Harvey's blessing with Mike,

659
00:24:44,580 --> 00:24:45,410
他就同意了
and he gave it.

660
00:24:45,410 --> 00:24:46,660
你怎么沒告訴我
Why didn't you tell me?

661
00:24:46,660 --> 00:24:48,650
因為我們說過他們的問題與我們無關
Because we agreed that their problem isn't our problem.

662
00:24:48,650 --> 00:24:50,700
我知道  但哈維并不想這樣
I know. But Harvey doesn't really want this,

663
00:24:50,700 --> 00:24:53,440
-而且你知道是因為  -因為他不能
- and you know that because-- - because he can't.

664
00:24:53,710 --> 00:24:55,760
他需要你做你該做的
Look, he needs you to do your Donna thing

665
00:24:55,760 --> 00:24:57,340
幫他忘掉這事
and help him get over it.

666
00:24:58,130 --> 00:25:00,350
哈維聽我的是因為我告訴他我的想法
Harvey listens to me because I tell him what I believe.

667
00:25:00,350 --> 00:25:01,810
你怎么想的
What do you believe?

668
00:25:08,420 --> 00:25:10,130
我認為麥克背叛了哈維
That Mike betrayed Harvey.

669
00:25:10,130 --> 00:25:12,590
-麥克被要挾了  -然后他背叛了哈維
- Mike was blackmailed. - and then he betrayed Harvey.

670
00:25:12,590 --> 00:25:15,200
-唐娜  你怎么能  -我怎么能什么
- Donna, how can you-- - how can I what?

671
00:25:15,360 --> 00:25:17,980
去年我一直在幫你男友掩飾他的雙重生活
I just spent the last year hiding your boyfriend's double life.

672
00:25:17,980 --> 00:25:19,960
我得說我是個通情達理的人
I'd say I'm a pretty understanding person.

673
00:25:19,980 --> 00:25:21,230
但我不能理解的是
But what I don't understand is

674
00:25:21,240 --> 00:25:22,810
有的人對待這樣的忠誠
when someone takes loyalty like that,

675
00:25:22,810 --> 00:25:24,130
就把它隨手扔掉
and they throw it in the garbage.

676
00:25:24,850 --> 00:25:26,520
你想讓我這么和哈維說嗎
Would you like me to say that to Harvey?

677
00:25:27,960 --> 00:25:30,680
抱歉  我不會再問了
Sorry I asked. Won't happen again.

678
00:25:31,360 --> 00:25:33,400
-太棒了  -干得好  麥克
- Yeah, that was awesome. - That was a great job, Mike.

679
00:25:33,400 --> 00:25:35,040
-謝謝  路易  -瑞秋
- Thanks, Louis. - Rachel.

680
00:25:35,440 --> 00:25:38,050
-看來你贏了  -法官明天判決
- Looks like you won. - The judge is ruling tomorrow.

681
00:25:38,770 --> 00:25:40,550
那你們在慶祝什么
Then what were you just celebrating?

682
00:25:40,830 --> 00:25:42,380
我們本來死定了
Well, we were dead in the water,

683
00:25:42,380 --> 00:25:43,910
而如今我們有了一個翻身的機會
and now we have a fighting chance.

684
00:25:44,310 --> 00:25:45,330
真替你高興
I'm glad.

685
00:25:47,660 --> 00:25:48,710
發生了什么嗎
Is something wrong?

686
00:25:49,000 --> 00:25:51,190
我剛剛和唐娜吵了一架
Oh, I just got into a fight with Donna.

687
00:25:51,740 --> 00:25:52,270
因為什么
About what?

688
00:25:52,270 --> 00:25:53,690
我和她說了你跟路易的事
I went to tell her about you and Louis,

689
00:25:53,690 --> 00:25:55,900
-但是她  -你去找唐娜說了我跟路易的事
- and she just-- - You went to Donna about me and Louis?

690
00:25:55,900 --> 00:25:57,660
-我以為她能幫上忙的  -你說什么
- I thought she could help. - You what?

691
00:25:57,670 --> 00:25:58,620
我以為要是她知道了這件事
I thought if she knew,

692
00:25:58,620 --> 00:25:59,420
就會去和哈維說
she'd go to harvey,

693
00:25:59,420 --> 00:26:00,430
然后他們會阻止這件事的發生
and they'd just put an end to it.

694
00:26:00,430 --> 00:26:02,050
如果有人插手這件事并告訴他該做什么
Someone butting in and telling him what to do

695
00:26:02,050 --> 00:26:03,630
只會把他推得更遠
is only going to push him further away.

696
00:26:03,630 --> 00:26:05,230
我可沒告訴他該做什么
I didn't tell him what to do.

697
00:26:05,230 --> 00:26:07,400
-我找的是唐娜  -假如唐娜和他說了
- I went to donna. - If Donna tells him,

698
00:26:07,400 --> 00:26:08,620
就只能說明我太弱了
all it says is that I'm too weak

699
00:26:08,620 --> 00:26:09,930
沒有能力獨自作戰
to fight my own battles.

700
00:26:09,930 --> 00:26:11,320
上帝  假如消息是從你這里傳出的
God, if it's coming from you,

701
00:26:11,320 --> 00:26:12,250
就會讓整件事變得更糟
that makes it so much worse.

702
00:26:12,250 --> 00:26:13,080
為什么
Why?

703
00:26:14,890 --> 00:26:15,690
怎么了
What?

704
00:26:22,480 --> 00:26:24,720
哈維禁止我和你透露任何消息
Harvey forbid me to tell you anything.

705
00:26:25,310 --> 00:26:26,920
你和哈維談論過我
You and Harvey talked about me?

706
00:26:26,930 --> 00:26:28,270
我們開始約會之后  我去找了哈維
After we went out, I went to him,

707
00:26:28,270 --> 00:26:29,370
我和他說我想告訴你
I said I wanted to tell you--

708
00:26:29,370 --> 00:26:31,200
然后他和你說我不值得信任
And he said I wasn't trustworthy.

709
00:26:31,200 --> 00:26:32,050
不是這樣的
It's not that.

710
00:26:32,050 --> 00:26:33,180
她不希望我倆約會
He didn't want you to go out with me.

711
00:26:33,180 --> 00:26:34,210
不  也不對
No, it's not that either.

712
00:26:34,210 --> 00:26:36,430
他對我倆約會的事沒有任何意見  他
He didn't have a problem with us going out, he--

713
00:26:36,540 --> 00:26:38,780
這么說來只要你能瞞著我
Oh, so it's okay if you screwed me

714
00:26:38,780 --> 00:26:40,280
那么你和我上床也沒關系
so long as you lied.

715
00:26:40,280 --> 00:26:41,450
瑞秋
Rachel.

716
00:26:42,340 --> 00:26:42,860
我總算知道了
Oh, my god.

717
00:26:42,860 --> 00:26:44,490
這就是你和我分手的原因
That's why you cut things off with me.

718
00:26:44,490 --> 00:26:45,550
我不是有意要瞞著你的
I didn't want to lie to you.

719
00:26:45,550 --> 00:26:46,420
我無法相信他
I can't believe him.

720
00:26:46,420 --> 00:26:47,850
瑞秋  他不止一次地為了我
Rachel, he didn't just risk everything

721
00:26:47,850 --> 00:26:49,300
而賭上自己的一切
he had for me once.

722
00:26:49,510 --> 00:26:51,140
當杰西卡發現的時候  他又一次為我
When Jessica found out, he put everything

723
00:26:51,140 --> 00:26:53,110
賭上了一切
he had on the line for me again.

724
00:26:53,170 --> 00:26:55,180
但愿你意識到了在你為他辯護時
I hope you know as you stand here defending him,

725
00:26:55,180 --> 00:26:57,840
他卻連原諒你的意思都沒有
he has no intention of ever forgiving you.

726
00:26:57,840 --> 00:27:00,440
因為我發現當路易向哈維征求同意的時候
Because I found out when Louis asked Harvey for his blessing,

727
00:27:00,440 --> 00:27:02,390
哈維說  "帶走他吧  他是你的了"
he said, "Take him. He's all yours."

728
00:27:02,390 --> 00:27:03,830
所以說與其在這里對我發火
So instead of getting mad at me

729
00:27:03,830 --> 00:27:05,510
只為了求得哈維的原諒
for trying to get Harvey to forgive you,

730
00:27:05,510 --> 00:27:07,170
不如去對哈維發火
maybe you should get pissed at Harvey

731
00:27:07,170 --> 00:27:08,720
并想想該如何繼續生活
and think about moving on.

732
00:27:17,630 --> 00:27:19,180
你他媽到底有什么問題
What the hell is wrong with you?

733
00:27:20,450 --> 00:27:21,440
我說過了我很抱歉
I said I was sorry,

734
00:27:21,440 --> 00:27:22,800
我把辦公室還回去了
I gave back the office,

735
00:27:22,800 --> 00:27:25,320
我協助你辦案子  我甚至要挾了杰西卡
I helped you with your case, I even blackmailed Jessica.

736
00:27:25,320 --> 00:27:27,160
哈維我知道你很生我的氣
Harvey, I get that you are pissed off at me,

737
00:27:27,160 --> 00:27:28,000
但是最終
but eventually,

738
00:27:28,000 --> 00:27:29,370
你還是得原諒我
you are going to have to forgive me.

739
00:27:29,370 --> 00:27:31,490
原諒你什么  是讓我雇用了卡特里娜
Forgive you for what, making me hire Katrina?

740
00:27:31,490 --> 00:27:33,480
還是在你工作的第一周就嗑嗨了
Getting high on the job your first week?

741
00:27:33,750 --> 00:27:35,420
是和杰西卡一起背叛了我
Betraying me with Jessica?

742
00:27:35,420 --> 00:27:38,180
又或者是告訴了瑞秋你的秘密
Or for telling Rachel about your secret?

743
00:27:40,400 --> 00:27:41,920
你拋棄我了
You cut me loose.

744
00:27:42,790 --> 00:27:43,990
行了吧  你炒了我魷魚
Okay? You fired me.

745
00:27:43,990 --> 00:27:45,100
我當時處于人生最低谷
I was at my lowest point.

746
00:27:45,100 --> 00:27:46,130
而她就在那兒守著我
She was there for me.

747
00:27:46,130 --> 00:27:47,380
她如今還在守著我
She's still there for me.

748
00:27:47,390 --> 00:27:48,250
恭喜
Congratulations.

749
00:27:48,250 --> 00:27:49,610
我祝你倆幸福
I hope you two are happy together.

750
00:27:49,610 --> 00:27:51,740
所以你為了懲罰我就把我扔給路易
So you're gonna punish me by giving me to Louis?

751
00:27:51,740 --> 00:27:53,050
好吧  讓我和你實話實說吧
Well, let me tell you something.

752
00:27:53,630 --> 00:27:54,650
你失算了
It failed.

753
00:27:54,650 --> 00:27:56,540
我實際上挺喜歡和路易一起工作的
I actually like working for Louis.

754
00:27:56,540 --> 00:27:58,670
他讓我覺得自己是在和他一起工作
He makes me feel like I'm working with him,

755
00:27:58,670 --> 00:27:59,610
而不是為他工作
not for him.

756
00:27:59,610 --> 00:28:00,200
好吧  我很高興聽到你這么說
Well, I'm glad to hear that.

757
00:28:00,200 --> 00:28:01,960
因為我不是為了懲罰你而把你給路易的
Because I didn't give you to Louis as punishment.

758
00:28:01,960 --> 00:28:03,990
我把你給路易是因為咱倆之間玩完了
I gave you to Louis because you and I are done.

759
00:28:06,740 --> 00:28:08,420
哈維  我很后悔我所做的事情
Harvey, I regret what I did.

760
00:28:09,750 --> 00:28:10,520
但是我現在告訴你
But I'm telling you right now,

761
00:28:10,520 --> 00:28:11,970
你會因為拋棄我而后悔的
you're gonna regret this.

762
00:28:12,960 --> 00:28:14,310
可能你還沒有聽清楚我的話
Maybe you didn't hear me.

763
00:28:15,660 --> 00:28:17,230
我說  咱倆之間
I said you and I...

764
00:28:18,630 --> 00:28:19,680
玩完了
We're done.

765
00:28:29,360 --> 00:28:32,180
不管你要干什么  我現在都沒心情奉陪
Whatever it is, I'm not really in the mood right now.

766
00:28:32,520 --> 00:28:35,290
哈維  我了解卡梅隆的行事風格
Harvey, I know how Cameron works.

767
00:28:35,810 --> 00:28:37,240
他現在一定在計劃著什么
He's setting something up.

768
00:28:37,550 --> 00:28:39,100
你以為我不知道嗎
You think I don't know that?

769
00:28:39,120 --> 00:28:41,100
他在設計艾娃讓她去賄賂尼克
He's setting Ava up to bribe Nick.

770
00:28:41,100 --> 00:28:43,620
-這不是你剛剛干的事嗎  -我沒這么干
- Isn't that what you just did? - No.

771
00:28:43,620 --> 00:28:45,140
我去找他  然后告訴他
I went to him and told him

772
00:28:45,150 --> 00:28:46,630
他會因為對艾娃不忠而后悔的
he'd regret being disloyal to her.

773
00:28:46,630 --> 00:28:48,190
這種事我有稍許經驗
Something I know a little bit about.

774
00:28:48,750 --> 00:28:53,250
迷你劇《血仇》中的兩大家族

775
00:28:48,750 --> 00:28:51,430
哈維  你知道哈特菲爾德家族和麥科伊家族
Harvey, do you know what started it

776
00:28:51,430 --> 00:28:53,250
之間的恩怨是如何產生的嗎
between the Hatfields and the McCoys?

777
00:28:53,280 --> 00:28:56,330
我沒看那部迷你劇  但我聽說科斯特納毀了那部劇
I didn't catch the miniseries, but I heard Costner killed it.

778
00:28:56,710 --> 00:28:57,380
無關緊要
Doesn't matter.

779
00:28:57,380 --> 00:28:58,760
因為不管哪一方說是對方挑的事
Because whoever they say started it,

780
00:28:58,760 --> 00:29:00,360
我敢說
I guarantee you,

781
00:29:00,360 --> 00:29:03,040
另一方都會說  "扯淡"
The other side says, "Bullsh--."

782
00:29:03,660 --> 00:29:06,700
你為了這次合并  背著我去找達比
You went to Darby for this merger behind my back.

783
00:29:06,770 --> 00:29:09,990
然后你也背著我和他挑起了戰爭
And then you picked a fight with him behind my back.

784
00:29:09,990 --> 00:29:12,180
你還背著我要挾邁克
And then you blackmailed mike behind mine.

785
00:29:12,180 --> 00:29:13,960
我之所以能這么做
And I was only able to do that

786
00:29:13,960 --> 00:29:17,500
是因為你一開始就把一個騙子帶進了我的事務所
because you brought a fraud into my firm in the first place.

787
00:29:17,510 --> 00:29:19,200
你真的覺得這是我的錯了
So you do think it's my fault?

788
00:29:19,620 --> 00:29:23,140
我只是很后悔我們要倒戈相向
What I think is I regret where we are,

789
00:29:23,140 --> 00:29:26,110
我一直想修復我們之間的關系
And I've been trying to get us back to where we were.

790
00:29:26,110 --> 00:29:28,120
你有什么證據這么說
And what would the evidence of that be?

791
00:29:28,170 --> 00:29:29,730
你想要什么證據
What evidence would you like?

792
00:29:29,730 --> 00:29:31,130
不如告訴我真相
Why don't you tell me the truth

793
00:29:31,130 --> 00:29:34,020
到底為什么讓我接手這個案子
about why the hell I'm on this case?

794
00:29:34,240 --> 00:29:35,530
好吧  哈維
All right, harvey.

795
00:29:36,040 --> 00:29:37,650
我對你撒謊了
I lied to you.

796
00:29:38,030 --> 00:29:41,030
我之前說是我努力幫你爭取到的
When I told you I fought to get you on this case,

797
00:29:41,030 --> 00:29:42,110
但并不是這樣
I didn't.

798
00:29:42,220 --> 00:29:43,570
是達比做的決定
Darby made that call.

799
00:29:43,570 --> 00:29:47,190
而我只是利用這個機會來向你求和
And I used it as an opportunity to reach out to you.

800
00:29:47,190 --> 00:29:49,630
-"利用"  -為了向你求和
- "Used." - To reach out to you.

801
00:29:49,650 --> 00:29:51,760
而這正是我現在在做的事情
Which I am now here doing

802
00:29:51,770 --> 00:29:53,390
沒有利用任何事情
without using anything.

803
00:29:53,390 --> 00:29:55,400
所以你到底要不要讓這件事過去
So do you want to let it go or not?

804
00:29:55,570 --> 00:29:57,200
我只想知道一件事
I want to know one thing.

805
00:29:57,210 --> 00:29:58,750
假如有機會重來
If you had it to do over,

806
00:29:58,750 --> 00:30:00,140
你還會不會這么做
would you do it again?

807
00:30:02,530 --> 00:30:05,580
明天和卡梅隆的取證寫好了
Deposition's on the books with Cameron tomorrow.

808
00:30:06,760 --> 00:30:08,450
你想不想我到場
You want me there or not?

809
00:30:18,450 --> 00:30:20,720
哈維  我本想介紹你給尼克
Harvey, I'd introduce you to Nick.

810
00:30:20,720 --> 00:30:22,580
但是我知道在你干預證人的時候
But I understand you two already met

811
00:30:22,580 --> 00:30:23,960
你倆已經見過了
when you witness-tampered.

812
00:30:24,160 --> 00:30:25,690
尼克是海辛頓石油的員工
Nick works for Hessington Oil.

813
00:30:25,690 --> 00:30:26,720
我們是他的律師
We're their lawyers.

814
00:30:26,720 --> 00:30:28,610
因此  我沒有干預證人
Therefore, I didn't witness-tamper.

815
00:30:28,610 --> 00:30:29,470
并且如果你這么再說一次
And if you say it again,

816
00:30:29,470 --> 00:30:31,220
我就要控告你誹謗
I'm gonna slap you with a slander suit.

817
00:30:31,220 --> 00:30:32,810
讓我先打擊打擊你
Well, let me slap you with something.

818
00:30:32,810 --> 00:30:35,340
托尼·揚諾普洛斯不知如何拿到了那盤錄像
Tony Gianopolous got a hold of that video somehow,

819
00:30:35,340 --> 00:30:36,980
然后他把錄像給了你的股東
and he gave it to your shareholders.

820
00:30:36,990 --> 00:30:38,440
他們貌似在申請什么訴訟
They're filing some sort of lawsuit.

821
00:30:38,440 --> 00:30:39,870
我覺得他在試圖控制你們的公司
I think he's trying to take over the company.

822
00:30:39,870 --> 00:30:42,230
你個狗娘養的  是你把錄像泄露出去的
You son of a bitch. You leaked it.

823
00:30:42,230 --> 00:30:43,350
我可要否認這點
I deny that.

824
00:30:43,620 --> 00:30:45,060
假如你的客戶再這么說一遍
And if your client says that again,

825
00:30:45,060 --> 00:30:47,470
我就要控告她誹謗
I will slap her with a slander suit

826
00:30:47,470 --> 00:30:49,620
和控告她行賄一起
to go alongside her bribery charges.

827
00:30:49,620 --> 00:30:50,660
順便說一句
And by the way,

828
00:30:52,270 --> 00:30:53,270
尼克的態度
Nick wasn't swayed

829
00:30:53,280 --> 00:30:55,850
并沒有因為你的話而動搖
by your attempt to tug at his heartstrings.

830
00:30:55,850 --> 00:30:57,510
曉之以情
Emotional pleas?

831
00:30:57,780 --> 00:30:59,460
你對他做了什么  杰西卡
What did you do to him, Jessica?

832
00:30:59,460 --> 00:31:01,070
這不是我教出來的孩子
This is not the kid I mentored.

833
00:31:01,070 --> 00:31:02,130
等一下
Hold on a sec.

834
00:31:03,080 --> 00:31:06,190
你從來都不是我的導師  杰西卡才是
You were never my mentor. Jessica was.

835
00:31:06,200 --> 00:31:08,090
你只是個耍嘴皮子的汽車推銷員
You're just a fast-talking car salesman

836
00:31:08,090 --> 00:31:10,450
一直躲在安全線后吹噓著"我很棒"
that hides behind the line, "I do good."

837
00:31:10,450 --> 00:31:13,760
離我遠點  我要去和委托人協商了
Now get out of my face while I confer with my client.

838
00:31:18,500 --> 00:31:20,530
你告訴我你了解這個人
You told me you knew this man.

839
00:31:20,530 --> 00:31:22,160
我以為那對我們有好處
I thought that was an advantage.

840
00:31:22,160 --> 00:31:24,850
然而  你卻刺激他處心積慮
Instead, you've goaded him into orchestrating

841
00:31:24,850 --> 00:31:26,880
試圖奪走我的公司
an attempt to take over my company.

842
00:31:26,880 --> 00:31:28,630
你知道有時候醫生會說
You know how sometimes the doctor says

843
00:31:28,630 --> 00:31:30,790
在病情好轉之前你會覺得更難受
you're gonna feel worse before you feel better?

844
00:31:30,790 --> 00:31:33,070
-你是什么意思  -他的意思是
- What are you saying? - What he's saying is

845
00:31:33,070 --> 00:31:35,240
半小時后再告訴我們你的想法
let us know how you feel in half an hour.

846
00:31:45,290 --> 00:31:45,890
你有空嗎
Do you have a second?

847
00:31:45,890 --> 00:31:47,630
我想跟你談談我們之前的問題
I want to talk to you about how we left things.

848
00:31:47,630 --> 00:31:49,480
我不知道  你先跟哈維說過了嗎
I don't know, did you run it by Harvey first?

849
00:31:50,350 --> 00:31:51,540
-什么  -我理解
- What? - I understand

850
00:31:51,540 --> 00:31:54,350
他員工的交往對象最后是他說了算
that he has final say onwho his employees fraternize with.

851
00:31:55,560 --> 00:31:56,320
聽著
Look.

852
00:31:56,890 --> 00:31:59,560
哈維不僅僅是在保護他自己
Harvey wasn't just trying to protect himself,

853
00:31:59,570 --> 00:32:01,010
邁克  杰西卡  還有我
Mike, Jessica, and me.

854
00:32:01,010 --> 00:32:02,370
他也在試圖保護你
He was also trying to protect you.

855
00:32:02,370 --> 00:32:05,380
對  保護我是哈維的頭等大事
Right, my protection's at the top of Harvey's agenda.

856
00:32:05,380 --> 00:32:07,120
-他幾乎都不知道我是誰  -瑞秋
- He barely knows who I am. - Rachel.

857
00:32:07,120 --> 00:32:08,510
如果他了解我的話
And if he did know me,

858
00:32:08,510 --> 00:32:10,550
他會知道我不絕會告訴任何人的
He would know that I would never tell anyone.

859
00:32:10,550 --> 00:32:11,060
好吧  聽著
Okay, look.

860
00:32:11,060 --> 00:32:12,580
你想生哈維的氣  可以
You want to be mad at Harvey, fine.

861
00:32:12,580 --> 00:32:13,870
但你也生我的氣好了
But you might as well be mad at me,

862
00:32:13,870 --> 00:32:15,700
因為我也跟邁克說了同樣的話
because I told mike the same thing.

863
00:32:16,920 --> 00:32:17,790
什么
What?

864
00:32:18,900 --> 00:32:20,340
我把邁克拽到哈維的辦公室
I dragged Mike into Harvey's office,

865
00:32:20,340 --> 00:32:22,090
然后我告訴他哈維是對的
And I told him that Harvey was right.

866
00:32:22,920 --> 00:32:25,250
-說邁克應該對我撒謊  -不
- That Mike should lie to me? - No.

867
00:32:25,580 --> 00:32:27,590
我告訴他  他應該忘了你
I told him that he should get over you.

868
00:32:34,030 --> 00:32:36,100
那是在我去跟你說
Was that before or after

869
00:32:36,100 --> 00:32:38,790
我吻了他而且打電話告訴他
I came to you and told you that I kissed him

870
00:32:38,790 --> 00:32:41,480
我的感受之前還是之后
and that I called him and told him how I felt?

871
00:32:42,570 --> 00:32:43,710
是在那之后
It was after.

872
00:32:44,650 --> 00:32:45,920
你告訴他不要跟我在一起
You told him not to be with me,

873
00:32:45,920 --> 00:32:48,400
然后你又讓我覺得他不在乎我
and then you let me think that he didn't care about me.

874
00:32:48,400 --> 00:32:50,780
不  我告訴他了我的想法
No, I told him what I thought,

875
00:32:50,790 --> 00:32:51,900
然后我試著
and then I tried

876
00:32:51,900 --> 00:32:53,460
幫你走出來  因為他們的真相
to help you move on because their truth

877
00:32:53,460 --> 00:32:54,570
不應該由我來告訴你
wasn't mine to tell you.

878
00:32:54,570 --> 00:32:55,770
我以為你是我的朋友
I thought you were my friend.

879
00:32:55,770 --> 00:32:56,720
我是
I am.

880
00:32:56,720 --> 00:32:58,270
比起保護我  你更在乎
You cared more about protecting Harvey

881
00:32:58,270 --> 00:32:59,360
保護哈維
than protecting me.

882
00:32:59,360 --> 00:33:01,560
是的  瑞秋  那是我的工作
Yes, Rachel! That's my job.

883
00:33:04,740 --> 00:33:07,560
我知道所有人的工作都很重要
I get that everyone's jobs are important.

884
00:33:09,090 --> 00:33:11,150
但對我來說  這事與工作無關
This wasn't about a job for me.

885
00:33:11,640 --> 00:33:13,650
這關乎我的生活
It was about having a life.

886
00:33:14,140 --> 00:33:16,350
但我猜你不會明白的
But I guess you wouldn't understand that.

887
00:33:18,920 --> 00:33:19,970
瑞秋
Rachel...

888
00:33:21,560 --> 00:33:24,540
在事情無法挽回之前  我要轉身走掉
I'm going to walk away before you and I can't go back.

889
00:33:27,470 --> 00:33:31,620
美國司法部

890
00:33:29,400 --> 00:33:31,050
那是過去十年間發現的
It's the second largest oil deposit

891
00:33:31,050 --> 00:33:32,390
第二大儲量的石油礦床
found in the last decade.

892
00:33:32,390 --> 00:33:35,250
我們有合同  但為了繞過環境影響報告
We had the contract for it, but to get it out of the E.I.R.,

893
00:33:35,250 --> 00:33:38,390
-我們需要管道  -你被告知了什么
- We needed the pipeline. - what were you told?

894
00:33:38,390 --> 00:33:39,540
是誰說的
And by whom?

895
00:33:39,680 --> 00:33:41,150
馬里加上校告訴我們
We were told by Colonel Mariga

896
00:33:41,160 --> 00:33:42,920
如果我們支付污染治理費
we could build the pipeline if we paid

897
00:33:42,920 --> 00:33:45,410
-就可以鋪設管道  -但是
- a pollution remediation fee. - But?

898
00:33:45,410 --> 00:33:46,900
我們已經治理了所有
We'd already remediated everything

899
00:33:46,900 --> 00:33:48,600
需要治理的東西
that needed to be remediated.

900
00:33:48,600 --> 00:33:51,430
所以  那些費用有何用處
So what was the fee for?

901
00:33:51,700 --> 00:33:53,030
那是一份賄賂
It was a bribe.

902
00:33:53,260 --> 00:33:56,310
而在明知那是賄賂的情況下
And Ava Hessington paid this fee

903
00:33:56,310 --> 00:33:58,600
艾娃·海辛頓交了那筆費用
with the full knowledge that it was a bribe?

904
00:33:58,600 --> 00:34:00,960
是的
Yes, she did.

905
00:34:01,300 --> 00:34:03,460
在這個屏幕上  尼克
On this screen here, Nick,

906
00:34:03,460 --> 00:34:06,700
你是在把一個裝滿現金的公文包
are you sliding a briefcase full of cash

907
00:34:06,700 --> 00:34:08,720
從桌上推給馬里加上校嗎
across the table to Colonel Mariga?

908
00:34:09,300 --> 00:34:10,220
是的
Yes.

909
00:34:10,250 --> 00:34:13,290
而且你知道那是賄賂
And you were aware it was a bribe?

910
00:34:13,340 --> 00:34:14,050
是的  但是...
Yes, but--

911
00:34:14,050 --> 00:34:16,140
海辛頓女士是個怎樣的老板
How was Ms. Hessington as a boss?

912
00:34:17,400 --> 00:34:18,920
她教會我許多東西
She taught me a great deal.

913
00:34:19,180 --> 00:34:21,370
-她信任你嗎  -我認為是的
- Did she trust you? - I believe so.

914
00:34:21,370 --> 00:34:23,020
-信賴你嗎  -是的
- Rely on you? - Yes.

915
00:34:23,020 --> 00:34:25,980
你做的每件事她都會監督著你嗎
Did she look over your shoulder on everything you did?

916
00:34:25,980 --> 00:34:27,070
不
No.

917
00:34:27,070 --> 00:34:29,350
你做的每件事她都知道嗎
Was she aware of everything you did?

918
00:34:29,350 --> 00:34:30,270
她知道這件事
She was aware of this.

919
00:34:30,280 --> 00:34:32,430
但我們有的只是你的一面之詞
Yet all we have is your word on that.

920
00:34:32,430 --> 00:34:33,810
讓我直說吧
So let me get this straight.

921
00:34:33,810 --> 00:34:36,510
她培養了你  讓你晉升
She groomed you, promoted you,

922
00:34:36,510 --> 00:34:39,720
給了你權力  然后你進行了一次賄賂
gave you autonomy, then you engineered a bribe.

923
00:34:39,730 --> 00:34:41,300
當你被抓到的時候
And when you got caught,

924
00:34:41,300 --> 00:34:42,840
你做了個交易
you cut a deal

925
00:34:42,920 --> 00:34:45,210
把這次賄賂歸罪于你的導師
to lay that bribe on your mentor.

926
00:34:45,210 --> 00:34:46,280
我說的對嗎
Is that correct?

927
00:34:46,280 --> 00:34:47,320
她知道的
She knew.

928
00:34:47,490 --> 00:34:49,840
是  你之前說過了
Yes. You claimed that before.

929
00:34:49,840 --> 00:34:52,580
如果艾娃·海辛頓被確認有罪
If Ava Hessington were convicted of this crime,

930
00:34:52,580 --> 00:34:54,170
那誰會是下一個呢
who would be considered next in line?

931
00:34:54,170 --> 00:34:55,310
那還不確定
That's speculative.

932
00:34:55,310 --> 00:34:57,200
有可能是你嗎
Is it at all possible it would be you?

933
00:34:57,770 --> 00:34:58,610
是的
Yes.

934
00:35:00,450 --> 00:35:03,980
聽起來你會失去很多
Wow, sounds like you have a lot to lose

935
00:35:03,980 --> 00:35:05,430
但得到的更多
and even more to gain.

936
00:35:05,430 --> 00:35:06,490
我們現在不在庭上
We're not in court.

937
00:35:06,490 --> 00:35:08,970
你們的證詞沒有任何幫助
Your testimony doesn't help you here.

938
00:35:08,980 --> 00:35:10,640
是的  但我們想讓你們嘗嘗
No, but we wanted to give you a taste

939
00:35:10,640 --> 00:35:12,160
尼克在背后捅她刀子
of what it would be like in court

940
00:35:12,160 --> 00:35:14,520
在法庭上卻依然無法直視她的眼睛時
when nick still won't be able to look her in the eye

941
00:35:14,520 --> 00:35:16,160
是什么滋味
when he stabs her in the back.

942
00:35:22,070 --> 00:35:23,040
我們贏了
We won.

943
00:35:23,520 --> 00:35:25,490
-真的嗎  -真的
- We did? - We did.

944
00:35:27,890 --> 00:35:29,410
我只想說一件事
I just want to say one thing.

945
00:35:29,710 --> 00:35:30,950
如果哈維有能力
You know, if Harvey had the power

946
00:35:30,950 --> 00:35:33,120
成為馬里亞諾·里維拉  他會的
to become Mariano Rivera, he would,

947
00:35:33,550 --> 00:35:35,560
因為哈維不熱愛法律
because Harvey doesn't love the law.

948
00:35:36,200 --> 00:35:38,480
法律只是他為了勝利而
It's just his vehicle for forcing

949
00:35:38,480 --> 00:35:40,800
將自己的意愿強加在對手身上所用的工具
his will on his opponents, for winning.

950
00:35:41,940 --> 00:35:43,670
但是  邁克  那不是我對法律的感受
But you see, Mike, that's not how I feel about the law.

951
00:35:43,670 --> 00:35:44,910
我熱愛法律
I love the law.

952
00:35:46,050 --> 00:35:47,730
我永遠都不會用它交換任何東西
And I'd never trade it for anything.

953
00:35:47,730 --> 00:35:50,710
我也愛法律  我還愛勝利
I love it too. I also like winning.

954
00:35:50,720 --> 00:35:51,680
我知道
I know.

955
00:35:52,950 --> 00:35:54,190
你知道我怎么想嗎
You know what I think?

956
00:35:55,960 --> 00:35:58,070
我覺得你一半是哈維一半是我
I think you're half Harvey and you're half me.

957
00:35:59,000 --> 00:36:00,400
你已經和他共事過
You've had your time with him.

958
00:36:00,840 --> 00:36:02,360
現在該跟我共事了
Now have your time with me.

959
00:36:08,510 --> 00:36:09,790
-哈維  -你是來面試的嗎
- Harv... - You're here for an interview?

960
00:36:09,790 --> 00:36:10,890
他們這么快就讓你出來了
They let you go already?

961
00:36:10,890 --> 00:36:11,910
你說的夠清楚了
You made your point.

962
00:36:11,910 --> 00:36:14,510
如果上法庭  你會把尼克挖得體無完膚
If we go to trial, you eviscerate nick.

963
00:36:14,550 --> 00:36:15,920
但我們有那段視頻
But we still have that video,

964
00:36:15,920 --> 00:36:18,910
里面有她  而且他說她知道
She's on it, and he says she knew.

965
00:36:19,540 --> 00:36:22,050
知道嗎  事實上  我相信他
And you know what? The truth is I believe him.

966
00:36:22,550 --> 00:36:24,170
我也會讓別人都相信他
And I'll make them believe him.

967
00:36:24,810 --> 00:36:25,960
那你還來這干嘛
Then why are you here?

968
00:36:27,520 --> 00:36:29,580
好樣的  哈維  被你發現了
Nice job, harvey. You got me.

969
00:36:29,960 --> 00:36:31,100
他們要你跟我達成協議
They want you to cut a deal.

970
00:36:31,860 --> 00:36:33,180
我也很被動
Against my recommendation.

971
00:36:33,630 --> 00:36:35,040
我猜他們掌握了些你不知道的內幕
I guess they know what you don't.

972
00:36:35,730 --> 00:36:37,450
-你奈何不了我  -我們的條件是
- You can't beat me. - Here are our terms.

973
00:36:37,450 --> 00:36:38,850
不  輪不到你提條件
No, here are my terms.

974
00:36:39,370 --> 00:36:41,020
我們依然堅持原始協議
Our original offer stands.

975
00:36:41,020 --> 00:36:42,900
海辛頓石油接受無爭辯答辯
Hessington Oil pleads no contest.

976
00:36:41,020 --> 00:36:43,900
無爭辯答辯  
被告方無法推翻指控  但控方也無有力證據證明被告有罪

977
00:36:42,900 --> 00:36:44,710
我們賠償50萬美元
We pay a $50-million fine.

978
00:36:44,920 --> 00:36:47,610
你們要撤回所有針對艾娃的刑事指控
And all criminal charges against ava are dropped.

979
00:36:48,220 --> 00:36:49,680
他們本來同意的
They were going to go for that,

980
00:36:49,680 --> 00:36:52,000
不過我說服他們做了個小改變
but I convinced them to make one change.

981
00:36:52,010 --> 00:36:53,080
已經板上釘釘了
Nonnegotiable.

982
00:36:53,660 --> 00:36:56,140
艾娃·海辛頓不能無爭辯答辯
Ava Hessington doesn't plead no contest.

983
00:36:57,210 --> 00:36:58,300
她需要認罪
She pleads guilty.

984
00:36:59,600 --> 00:37:00,990
你就能把這當作一次勝利
And you get to call it a win.

985
00:37:02,100 --> 00:37:03,590
記錄上會顯示她有罪
Well, the record is going to say guilty.

986
00:37:03,590 --> 00:37:04,490
我是贏了
It is a win.

987
00:37:05,320 --> 00:37:06,540
我能奈何得了你
I can beat you,

988
00:37:06,950 --> 00:37:08,040
你看我做到了
And I did,

989
00:37:08,510 --> 00:37:10,410
會讓你痛心疾首的
And it's going to eat you up.

990
00:37:11,070 --> 00:37:12,220
丹尼斯  得一分
Dennis, one.

991
00:37:12,680 --> 00:37:15,160
斯佩克特  零蛋
Specter, zero.

992
00:37:16,560 --> 00:37:17,630
接不接受隨你
Take it or leave it.

993
00:37:20,750 --> 00:37:22,720
-這算什么狗屁協議  -哈維
- This deal is bullshit. - Harvey.

994
00:37:22,940 --> 00:37:24,650
不用管卡梅隆說什么
Cameron can say what he wants.

995
00:37:24,650 --> 00:37:26,300
達比讓你接的案子
Darby asked you to take this case.

996
00:37:26,300 --> 00:37:27,890
這對他來說絕對算勝利了
No way he doesn't consider this a win.

997
00:37:27,890 --> 00:37:29,160
我可不覺得是勝利
I don't consider it a win.

998
00:37:29,240 --> 00:37:31,700
那你就想拿她的五年時間來賭
Do you really want to gamble five years of her life,

999
00:37:31,700 --> 00:37:33,300
只為了證明你比卡梅隆強
So you can prove you're better than cameron?

1000
00:37:33,300 --> 00:37:35,530
你我都明白  他這么做
You know as well as I do, he's only offering this

1001
00:37:35,530 --> 00:37:37,000
是因為他知道他會輸
'cause he knows he's got a loser.

1002
00:37:37,000 --> 00:37:39,040
這就是我們提出的協議
It's the exact same deal we offered

1003
00:37:39,040 --> 00:37:40,640
只有一個小小的改動而已
With one technical change.

1004
00:37:40,640 --> 00:37:42,400
你知道他們怎么讓一次技術擊倒[拳擊術語]
Do you know how they enter a technical knockout

1005
00:37:42,400 --> 00:37:43,400
進入記錄簿嗎
in the record books?

1006
00:37:43,620 --> 00:37:44,970
用一次貨真價實的技術擊倒
As a knockout.

1007
00:37:48,640 --> 00:37:49,770
我會的
I would.

1008
00:37:51,180 --> 00:37:51,840
什么
What?

1009
00:37:51,840 --> 00:37:53,700
之前你問我會不會故技重施
You asked me before if I'd do it again.

1010
00:37:54,900 --> 00:37:55,960
我會
I would.

1011
00:37:58,040 --> 00:37:59,740
如果你讓我再次陷入如此境地
You put me in that position again,

1012
00:37:59,790 --> 00:38:01,640
我會不擇手段地去贏
And I'll do whatever I have to do to win.

1013
00:38:02,690 --> 00:38:03,910
因為我們注定該贏
Because we win.

1014
00:38:05,220 --> 00:38:07,610
你是說我們毀約  跟他玩狠的
Are you saying screw this deal, let's kick his ass?

1015
00:38:07,620 --> 00:38:08,610
不是
No.

1016
00:38:08,650 --> 00:38:10,140
我們答應他的條件
I'm saying take the deal.

1017
00:38:10,650 --> 00:38:11,740
本來也已如此
We already did.

1018
00:38:23,280 --> 00:38:24,420
我很抱歉
Sorry.

1019
00:38:24,970 --> 00:38:26,090
我也是
Me too.

1020
00:38:26,830 --> 00:38:28,170
你只是想幫我
You were just trying to help me.

1021
00:38:28,170 --> 00:38:29,420
是  但我不該為了停止爭吵
Yeah, but I shouldn't have said something

1022
00:38:29,420 --> 00:38:31,410
就說些傷害你的話
I knew would hurt you just to end an argument.

1023
00:38:32,650 --> 00:38:34,180
我想對你毫無保留
I don't want to keep secrets from you.

1024
00:38:34,180 --> 00:38:35,250
你不必保留什么
You don't have to.

1025
00:38:37,190 --> 00:38:39,350
路易讓我跟著他干
So Louis asked me.

1026
00:38:40,530 --> 00:38:41,880
你怎么回答的
And what did you say?

1027
00:38:42,490 --> 00:38:44,460
我說我需要考慮考慮
I told him I needed some time to think about it,

1028
00:38:44,460 --> 00:38:45,900
然后就直接來找你了
and then I came straight here.

1029
00:38:47,490 --> 00:38:49,040
所以你來道歉
So you're really just apologizing

1030
00:38:49,040 --> 00:38:50,760
只是為了聽我的建議
because you need my advice.

1031
00:38:51,370 --> 00:38:52,400
我還想要點愛愛
Well, I also want sex.

1032
00:38:52,400 --> 00:38:53,700
你只能選一樣
You can have one or the other.

1033
00:38:53,840 --> 00:38:55,060
那我不要什么建議了
I really don't need any advice.

1034
00:39:07,280 --> 00:39:09,280
這協議對你有好處  艾娃
It's a good deal, Ava.

1035
00:39:09,280 --> 00:39:10,450
別遲疑了
Don't second-guess yourself.

1036
00:39:10,600 --> 00:39:13,060
我可不是喜歡遲疑的人
I'm not in the habit of second-guessing myself.

1037
00:39:13,930 --> 00:39:16,020
只是我想  等我回到倫敦
No, I just realized when I get back to London,

1038
00:39:16,020 --> 00:39:17,730
我就失去我的得力助手了
my right hand is going to be gone.

1039
00:39:17,810 --> 00:39:19,460
你的得力助手出賣了你
Your right hand sold you out.

1040
00:39:19,500 --> 00:39:22,150
以你的說法  他是為了自己
You made it seem like he did it for his own personal gain.

1041
00:39:22,340 --> 00:39:24,400
可他是為了生存迫不得已
But he did it for his own survival.

1042
00:39:24,400 --> 00:39:25,490
那他也是做了
He still did it.

1043
00:39:26,090 --> 00:39:26,750
但這不代表
But that doesn't mean

1044
00:39:26,750 --> 00:39:27,910
我不會想他
I'm not going to miss him.

1045
00:39:33,880 --> 00:39:35,020
再見  哈維
Good-bye, Harvey.

1046
00:39:35,330 --> 00:39:36,400
再會  艾娃
Good-bye, Ava.

1047
00:39:42,920 --> 00:39:44,570
要我給達比發一份文件嗎
Do you want me to send a copy to Darby?

1048
00:39:44,570 --> 00:39:45,520
需要
I do.

1049
00:39:45,950 --> 00:39:47,320
我還以為  跟杰西卡共事
I thought maybe working with Jessica

1050
00:39:47,320 --> 00:39:49,040
會動搖你接手律所的主意
Would change your mind about taking over the firm.

1051
00:39:49,590 --> 00:39:51,450
-并沒有  -為什么
- It didn't. - Why not?

1052
00:39:51,450 --> 00:39:53,020
因為如果要她重新來過的話
Because if she had it to do all over again,

1053
00:39:53,020 --> 00:39:54,290
她也會那樣做
she would.

1054
00:39:57,460 --> 00:39:58,540
哈維  如果從頭到尾
Harvey, if this whole thing

1055
00:39:58,540 --> 00:39:59,980
都是杰西卡的錯
is really Jessica's fault,

1056
00:40:00,690 --> 00:40:02,690
那我們也許該原諒邁克了
Maybe it's time we considered forgiving Mike.

1057
00:40:09,930 --> 00:40:11,960
她打掃不干凈的話  就趕她走好了
If she's not vacuuming properly, then just fire her.

1058
00:40:12,040 --> 00:40:12,980
沒關系的
It doesn't matter.

1059
00:40:13,230 --> 00:40:14,390
再找別人
You'll get someone--

1060
00:40:14,420 --> 00:40:15,850
媽媽我先掛了  再見
Mom, I gotta go. Bye.

1061
00:40:20,190 --> 00:40:22,190
你讓我想要成為更出色的人
You make me want to be a better man.

1062
00:40:23,020 --> 00:40:24,510
-你看了《盡善盡美》  -很喜歡
- You watched it? - Loved it.

1063
00:40:24,800 --> 00:40:28,130
一見面我就愛上你了
Well, you had me at Hello.

1064
00:40:28,230 --> 00:40:29,380
你看了《甜心先生》
You watched Jerry Maguire?

1065
00:40:29,980 --> 00:40:31,980
杰里  你知道人腦有3.6公斤重嗎
Jerry, did you know the human head weighs 8 pounds?

1066
00:40:29,980 --> 00:40:37,210
《甜心先生》臺詞

1067
00:40:31,980 --> 00:40:34,120
我很在意這種事  寶貝
These are the ABC's of me, baby.

1068
00:40:34,300 --> 00:40:37,210
讓我賺大錢
Show me the money!

1069
00:40:40,680 --> 00:40:42,160
我一般不喜歡破壞氣氛
You know, normally, I wouldn't want to jinx anything,

1070
00:40:42,400 --> 00:40:43,920
-不過我給咱倆弄了點東西  -好吧
- But I got us something. - Okay.

1071
00:40:43,920 --> 00:40:45,530
正好配我們的完美聯手
The perfect way to consummate our relationship.

1072
00:40:45,530 --> 00:40:46,470
等我一下  我去廚房拿
So just wait right here. It's in the kitchen.

1073
00:40:46,470 --> 00:40:47,500
好的
Sure.

1074
00:40:59,640 --> 00:41:01,180
我可不能放任你這么做
I can't let you do this.

1075
00:41:05,000 --> 00:41:06,220
放任我
Let me?

1076
00:41:06,760 --> 00:41:07,930
別這么做
Don't do this.

1077
00:41:11,120 --> 00:41:12,710
我都答應他了
I already said yes.

1078
00:41:14,850 --> 00:41:16,340
我不能食言
I can't go back on my word.

1079
00:41:17,080 --> 00:41:18,740
你不用食言
You're not going back on your word.

1080
00:41:19,430 --> 00:41:21,620
回你該待的地兒就行了
You're going back where you belong.

1081
00:41:26,530 --> 00:41:27,700
我一直在
I am.

1082
00:41:30,920 --> 00:41:31,950
對不起
I am sorry.

1083
00:41:33,680 --> 00:41:34,770
我知道
I know.

1084
00:41:35,620 --> 00:41:38,440
你不如今晚休個假
Look, why don't you take tonight off

1085
00:41:38,870 --> 00:41:40,330
陪陪你女朋友
and go out with your girlfriend?

1086
00:41:51,390 --> 00:41:52,390
謝謝  哈維
Thanks, Harvey.

1087
00:41:52,530 --> 00:41:53,950
不行  我們要擊掌
No, we're going up top.

1088
00:41:55,430 --> 00:41:56,470
-真的嗎  -是的
- Oh, really? - Yeah.

1089
00:41:56,470 --> 00:41:59,570
但你明天膽敢遲到的話  我就炒了你
But if you come in late tomorrow, you're fired.

1090
00:41:59,570 --> 00:42:00,570
瞧好吧你
We'll see.

1091
00:42:11,060 --> 00:42:15,680
歡迎加入利特團隊

