1
00:00:13,130 --> 00:00:14,650
什么情况  你三连胜了
What is that, three in a row?

2
00:00:14,900 --> 00:00:16,470
实际上已经四连胜了
That would be four, actually.

3
00:00:16,530 --> 00:00:17,840
不是吧  
Oh, God.

4
00:00:17,900 --> 00:00:19,630
要不九局五胜  你看怎样
Come on. What do you say, we go five outta nine?

5
00:00:19,630 --> 00:00:20,900
那样你就能继续虐我了是吧
So you can keep abusing me?

6
00:00:20,900 --> 00:00:22,060
不用了  谢谢  我不玩了
No, thank you. I'm done.

7
00:00:22,060 --> 00:00:23,930
来嘛  我让你三局
Oh, come on. I'll spot you three.

8
00:00:24,000 --> 00:00:26,030
游戏时间结束了  怀亚特  他们来了
Game time's over, Wyatt. They're here.

9
00:00:26,040 --> 00:00:26,840
他们到了吗
They're here?

10
00:00:26,920 --> 00:00:28,270
你可以去会议室准备了
You can set up in the conference room.

11
00:00:28,270 --> 00:00:29,790
我只是...
Yeah. No, I'm just...

12
00:00:29,790 --> 00:00:31,410
快去会议室准备
Get set up in the conference room.

13
00:00:33,970 --> 00:00:35,690
-你故意让他的吧  -这还真不容易
-You did let him win, right?  -It wasn't easy.

14
00:00:35,750 --> 00:00:37,880
这家伙的协调能力跟两岁小孩似的
The guy has the coordination of a two-year-old.

15
00:00:37,880 --> 00:00:40,120
我知道  上次风险投资人来的时候
I know, the last time these venture capitalists came in,

16
00:00:40,190 --> 00:00:41,650
为了让他冷静  我还带他去打拳击
I took him boxing to calm him down.

17
00:00:41,720 --> 00:00:44,420
我基本上得打自己的脸  才能让他赢
I basically had to punch myself in the face to let him win.

18
00:00:45,690 --> 00:00:47,610
我不懂  如果他真是个天才
I don't get it. I mean, if he's such a genius,

19
00:00:47,610 --> 00:00:50,030
为什么在投资人面前那么紧张
why does he get so nervous around a bunch of investors?

20
00:00:50,030 --> 00:00:51,580
要是你花了整整两年 
Eh, you spend two years working on

21
00:00:51,580 --> 00:00:52,970
研发袖珍卫星电话
a satellite phone that fits in your pocket

22
00:00:53,030 --> 00:00:54,870
还把整个公司都赌上了
and then bet the company on it.

23
00:00:55,100 --> 00:00:56,850
我看你也会紧张的
You'd be a little nervous too, I think.

24
00:00:56,890 --> 00:00:58,040
那个样机...
The prototype...

25
00:00:58,040 --> 00:01:00,180
我找不到了  我不知道放在哪...
I can't find it. I don't know where I--

26
00:01:00,180 --> 00:01:01,420
是这个吗
You mean this?

27
00:01:01,880 --> 00:01:03,590
没有你我真不知道怎么办
I don't know what I'd do without you.

28
00:01:03,590 --> 00:01:05,710
-惨败  -那是必然
- Fail miserably. - I would.

29
00:01:05,710 --> 00:01:08,430
-这是...  -没错  两千万的样机
- Is that the...  - $20 million prototype, yes.

30
00:01:08,500 --> 00:01:10,430
今天交易谈成之前
And you don't even get to look at this bad boy

31
00:01:10,430 --> 00:01:11,830
你看都别想看
until after we close the deal today.

32
00:01:11,900 --> 00:01:14,360
哇  他们像纳粹党的冲锋队似的
Wow, they're like storm troopers.

33
00:01:14,360 --> 00:01:16,910
冲锋队可不会开支票
Storm troopers don't write checks.

34
00:01:16,960 --> 00:01:18,440
现在你只需要走进去
Now all you gotta do is walk in there,

35
00:01:18,510 --> 00:01:19,910
告诉他们电话怎么用
show them how the phone works...

36
00:01:19,980 --> 00:01:22,200
然后尚德电子公司
Right, and Suntech Digital

37
00:01:22,200 --> 00:01:24,500
就会成为全球通讯的新生力量
will be a new force in global communications.

38
00:01:24,500 --> 00:01:26,010
一举秒杀他们吧
Let's knock 'em dead.

39
00:01:27,390 --> 00:01:28,700
好
All right.

40
00:01:30,390 --> 00:01:32,030
停住  你这是要去哪里
Wait, wait. Where do you think you're going?

41
00:01:32,030 --> 00:01:34,090
进房间  和大家见面
Into the room with the people.

42
00:01:34,090 --> 00:01:36,300
不行  那是专业人士的谈判场所
Wrong, that's the adult table in there.

43
00:01:36,300 --> 00:01:38,230
你还不够级别
And you haven't earned the privilege yet.

44
00:01:38,230 --> 00:01:39,740
但我都跟他玩过桌上冰球了
But I played air hockey with him--

45
00:01:39,740 --> 00:01:40,610
你得回办公室
You need to go back to the office

46
00:01:40,670 --> 00:01:42,230
申请这个电话的专利
and file a patent for the phone.

47
00:01:42,230 --> 00:01:43,980
专利吗  我不知道怎么申请
A patent? I don't know how to file a patent.

48
00:01:44,040 --> 00:01:45,810
-自己想办法  -我们能不能先...
- Figure it out.  - Can't we do that after--

49
00:01:45,880 --> 00:01:47,810
不行  你再说一句  我就要开始计费了
No, and you keep talking, I'm gonna start billing you.

50
00:01:47,880 --> 00:01:50,020
我的价位是每小时一千美元
And my time runs $1,000 an hour.

51
00:01:50,020 --> 00:01:52,390
时间不是你我共享的吗  汉德先生
But isn't this our time, Mr. Hand?

52
00:01:50,020 --> 00:01:52,390
汉德先生:电影《开放的美国学府》中角色

53
00:01:53,430 --> 00:01:55,010
我接受指正
I stand corrected.

54
00:01:55,050 --> 00:01:56,760
你会引用《开放的美国学府》的台词
Your Fast Times at Ridgemont High quote,

55
00:01:56,820 --> 00:01:59,490
证明你可以进行专业谈判了[反语]
that proves you belong at the adult table.

56
00:01:59,560 --> 00:02:01,830
那电影相当不错
Hey, that's a great movie.

57
00:02:01,890 --> 00:02:03,560
道出了一代人的心声...
And it spoke to a generation...

58
00:02:15,040 --> 00:02:16,270
你在忙吗
Hey, you busy?

59
00:02:20,620 --> 00:02:22,790
好吧  你以前申请过专利吗
Okay, have you ever filed a patent before?

60
00:02:22,850 --> 00:02:24,350
我刚从哈维那里回来
I just got back from this meeting with Harvey

61
00:02:24,420 --> 00:02:25,720
他让我申请专利
and he wants me to file this patent,

62
00:02:25,790 --> 00:02:27,660
但我完全不知道怎么填
but I have no idea what that paperwork looks like.

63
00:02:27,720 --> 00:02:30,990
你要是能给我些帮助的话...
So...any help in this arena would be re--

64
00:02:33,340 --> 00:02:35,390
是哈维打电话叫你这么做的吗
Did Harvey call you and tell you to do that?

65
00:02:44,280 --> 00:02:46,450
这不是金童吗
If it isn't the golden boy.

66
00:02:46,480 --> 00:02:48,550
你是哈维的手下  对吧
You're Harvey's project, right?

67
00:02:48,550 --> 00:02:51,410
-你叫什么  -迈克  迈克·罗斯
- What's your name? - Mike, Mike Ross.

68
00:02:51,410 --> 00:02:52,590
我是格雷戈里·布恩
Gregory Boone.

69
00:02:52,610 --> 00:02:54,290
你怎么在这里待着
So what are you doing here?

70
00:02:54,430 --> 00:02:57,180
你今天下午不是要到市中心签一笔大生意吗
Weren't you signing some big deal this afternoon downtown?

71
00:02:57,180 --> 00:02:59,420
显然我还不够格
Well, evidently I haven't earned the privilege yet.

72
00:02:59,420 --> 00:03:01,170
说你不能参与专业谈判是吧
Get the adult table speech?

73
00:03:04,280 --> 00:03:06,200
是啊  我不但看不到谈判的过程
Yeah, instead of watching the deal close,

74
00:03:06,200 --> 00:03:07,710
还得申请专利
I get to file the patent.

75
00:03:07,710 --> 00:03:09,610
是啊  真悲剧
Yeah, those suck.

76
00:03:11,490 --> 00:03:14,180
等等  你以前做过专利申请吗
Wait, you-- You've done one of these before?

77
00:03:14,180 --> 00:03:16,550
有上百次了  怎么了
Like 100. Why?

78
00:03:24,420 --> 00:03:25,450
说吧
Now.

79
00:03:26,100 --> 00:03:27,920
没事  你不用道歉
It's okay, you don't have to apologize.

80
00:03:27,990 --> 00:03:29,220
我搞定了
I took care of it.

81
00:03:29,890 --> 00:03:31,160
那个专利申请
Patent claim.

82
00:03:31,240 --> 00:03:33,060
我做了个交易就搞定了
I negotiated a deal to get it done.

83
00:03:33,060 --> 00:03:34,300
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?

84
00:03:34,300 --> 00:03:36,420
格雷戈里  他答应帮我申请
Gregory. He agreed to file it for me.

85
00:03:36,420 --> 00:03:38,330
我只要帮他校对班布里奇案的摘要就行
And all I have to do is proof his Bainbridge briefs.

86
00:03:38,400 --> 00:03:41,620
难怪他让我把这个给你
Ah. That explains why he said to give you this.

87
00:03:43,980 --> 00:03:45,660
还叫你蠢蛋
And why he called you a sucker.

88
00:03:46,940 --> 00:03:48,200
他叫我什么
He called me a what?

89
00:03:50,610 --> 00:03:54,300
迈克·罗斯  请允许我向你介绍班布里奇一案
Mike Ross, allow me to introduce the Bainbridge briefs.

90
00:03:55,340 --> 00:03:57,280
-哪一摞  -全部都是
- Which stack? - All of them.

91
00:03:58,530 --> 00:03:59,820
等等  这些都是...
Wait a minute, are these all--

92
00:03:59,890 --> 00:04:02,030
还在打印呢  还要半个小时吧
Still printing, yeah. I'd give it about a half hour.

93
00:04:03,340 --> 00:04:05,760
6台打印机  每分钟打印23页  共30分钟
That's six printers, 23 pages a minute, 30 minutes.

94
00:04:05,830 --> 00:04:09,470
-总共有4140页  -再加上这些
- That's 4,140 pages.  -Plus all this.

95
00:04:09,530 --> 00:04:11,530
所以说下次做交易的时候
Which means the next time you negotiate a deal,

96
00:04:11,600 --> 00:04:13,370
我建议你先搞清楚状况
I would suggest to get your facts straight.

97
00:04:14,880 --> 00:04:16,530
我真是个蠢蛋
I am a sucker.

98
00:04:19,680 --> 00:04:21,240
什么时候变蠢的
When did that happen?

99
00:04:22,000 --> 00:04:26,000
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
 更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

100
00:04:22,000 --> 00:04:26,000
■

101
00:04:26,000 --> 00:04:30,000
翻译：圆圆  桃乐  马蒂  米苏  菜根莫莫  HenryYang

102
00:04:26,000 --> 00:04:30,000
■

103
00:04:30,000 --> 00:04:34,000
时间轴：小怡子 潘叔  校对：饿得慌 地瓜  后期：飞飞  总监：丢丢

104
00:04:30,000 --> 00:04:34,000
■

105
00:04:46,760 --> 00:04:48,930
诉 讼 双 雄

106
00:04:46,760 --> 00:04:48,930
第一季 第二集

107
00:04:55,800 --> 00:04:57,710
你早上能过来真好
Nice of you to join us this morning.

108
00:04:57,710 --> 00:04:59,500
向你报告  阳光先生
For your information, Mr. Sunshine,

109
00:04:57,710 --> 00:04:59,500
《阳光先生》:ABC喜剧  讲述了男主角陷入中年危机的故事

110
00:04:59,500 --> 00:05:00,680
我一整夜都在校对
I've been here all night proofing.

111
00:05:00,750 --> 00:05:02,520
这杯是...  好吧
That belongs to-- Okay.

112
00:05:02,520 --> 00:05:04,110
我要的确认书呢
Where's my confirmation?

113
00:05:04,360 --> 00:05:05,200
什么
What?

114
00:05:05,260 --> 00:05:07,000
你竟然忘了  我很担心
The fact that you don't know already concerns me.

115
00:05:07,070 --> 00:05:08,690
你指专利申请吗
Oh, you mean the patent thing?

116
00:05:09,350 --> 00:05:11,270
就因为没有专利申请的那张纸
"The patent thing" is the only piece of paper

117
00:05:11,340 --> 00:05:13,360
昨天的交易被耽搁了
that's holding up our deal from yesterday.

118
00:05:14,190 --> 00:05:15,170
那张纸在哪里
Where is it?

119
00:05:15,170 --> 00:05:16,590
在我桌上
It's on my desk.

120
00:05:16,710 --> 00:05:18,970
我回来的时候要是还没放到我桌上
Well, if it's not on mine by the time I get back,

121
00:05:18,970 --> 00:05:20,430
我就把你交给路易处理
I'm gonna feed you to Louis.

122
00:05:21,590 --> 00:05:22,560
没问题
No problem.

123
00:05:29,860 --> 00:05:31,160
你已经提交了...
Please tell me that you filed that--

124
00:05:31,220 --> 00:05:33,100
专利申请吗  还没有
Patent? No, not yet.

125
00:05:33,100 --> 00:05:34,160
我昨天就给你了
I gave it to you yesterday.

126
00:05:34,230 --> 00:05:36,380
我昨天也把班布里奇案的摘要给你了
At the same time I gave you my Bainbridge briefs,

127
00:05:36,380 --> 00:05:37,440
你不也没做完嘛
which you haven't finished.

128
00:05:37,440 --> 00:05:39,060
我熬了一整晚  也只看完了一半
I was here all night, and I barely got through half.

129
00:05:39,130 --> 00:05:41,000
我也纠结了11分钟
And I was on hold for almost 11 minutes

130
00:05:41,000 --> 00:05:42,680
才放弃了你的专利申请
before I gave up on your patent,

131
00:05:42,680 --> 00:05:43,220
你想说什么
so what's your point?

132
00:05:43,220 --> 00:05:44,600
我保证我会看完那些摘要
I swear I will finish those filings,

133
00:05:44,670 --> 00:05:46,580
但在哈维回来之前
but you have to give me this patent confirmation

134
00:05:46,580 --> 00:05:47,840
你一定要把确认书给我
before Harvey gets back.

135
00:05:47,870 --> 00:05:50,650
抱歉了  金童  我们有言在先
Sorry, golden boy. Deal's a deal.

136
00:06:07,840 --> 00:06:08,890
你在做什么呢
What do you think you're doing?

137
00:06:10,430 --> 00:06:13,690
我在校对摘要  怎么了
Uh...I'm proofing briefs. Why?

138
00:06:13,690 --> 00:06:15,520
-有问题吗  -有
- Is there a problem? - Yeah, there is.

139
00:06:15,520 --> 00:06:17,630
那是格雷戈里的事  为什么你在做
That's Gregory's responsibility, why are you handling it?

140
00:06:17,630 --> 00:06:20,150
我自愿帮忙的
Oh, I...volunteered.

141
00:06:21,020 --> 00:06:22,840
不是他推给你的吗
He didn't pawn it off on you?

142
00:06:23,130 --> 00:06:24,630
不  不是
No. No.

143
00:06:24,630 --> 00:06:27,030
我是说  他没想让我帮忙
I mean, he didn't even want me to do it,

144
00:06:27,030 --> 00:06:30,110
但是我正好有点空
but you know, I-I-I had some extra time.

145
00:06:30,110 --> 00:06:31,940
所以我坚持要帮他
So I insisted.

146
00:06:38,000 --> 00:06:39,500
恭喜你
Congratulations.

147
00:06:40,090 --> 00:06:42,630
你表现了对同事的忠诚
You've shown loyalty to your fellow associates.

148
00:06:42,960 --> 00:06:45,090
我知道是格雷戈里下套让你做的
I know Gregory tricked you into doing his work.

149
00:06:45,090 --> 00:06:47,180
我只是想看你被逼问时会作何反应
I wanted to see how you react when pressed about it.

150
00:06:47,230 --> 00:06:48,410
你顶住了
You held up.

151
00:06:49,250 --> 00:06:50,700
我很欣赏你那点
I respect that.

152
00:06:51,500 --> 00:06:52,270
谢谢
Thanks?

153
00:06:52,420 --> 00:06:53,980
但我不明白的是
See, but I don't understand something now.

154
00:06:53,980 --> 00:06:55,430
既然你不知道怎么申请专利
If you didn't know how to file a patent,

155
00:06:55,430 --> 00:06:57,050
为什么不去问哈维
then why didn't you just run to Harvey?

156
00:06:58,600 --> 00:07:00,050
他很忙
He was busy.

157
00:07:00,910 --> 00:07:01,710
知道吗  迈克
But you see, Mike,

158
00:07:01,710 --> 00:07:03,440
这就是为什么让你有事来找我
that's why you come to see me.

159
00:07:06,400 --> 00:07:11,070
迈克  我知道有时候我有点...
Look, Mike, I know... I can come across a bit...

160
00:07:12,290 --> 00:07:13,150
刺头
prickly.

161
00:07:14,900 --> 00:07:16,230
但我们是个团队
But we're a team here.

162
00:07:16,650 --> 00:07:18,530
我过来是为了帮你
That means I'm here to help.

163
00:07:21,400 --> 00:07:23,390
好  行啊
Okay, all right.

164
00:07:23,720 --> 00:07:25,260
那你现在能帮我吗
So can you help me now?

165
00:07:27,090 --> 00:07:28,350
我说到做到
I already have.

166
00:07:31,130 --> 00:07:32,020
这...
Are--

167
00:07:32,660 --> 00:07:34,130
谢谢你  路易
Thank you, Louis.

168
00:07:40,770 --> 00:07:43,070
唐娜  蓝色真配你 
Donna, blue is your color.

169
00:07:43,070 --> 00:07:44,260
哈维回来了吗
Is Harvey back?

170
00:07:44,800 --> 00:07:45,340
没有
No.

171
00:07:45,590 --> 00:07:46,960
我可以把这个放在他桌上吗
Can I put this on his desk?

172
00:07:47,030 --> 00:07:48,080
可以
Yes.

173
00:07:48,410 --> 00:07:51,070
你能告诉他我很早就放过去了吗
Will you tell him I put it there hours ago?

174
00:07:52,050 --> 00:07:53,550
你想让我说几点
What time you want me to say?

175
00:07:54,320 --> 00:07:56,730
-上午十一点行吗  -没问题
- 11 a.m.?  - Absolutely.

176
00:07:58,090 --> 00:08:00,370
那说不定我还可以用他的银行账户
And then maybe I can use my access to his bank accounts

177
00:08:00,370 --> 00:08:02,430
在汉普顿给自己买栋别墅呢
to buy myself a house in the Hamptons.

178
00:08:03,500 --> 00:08:04,950
-两点一刻呢  -没门
- 2:15?  - No.

179
00:08:14,810 --> 00:08:15,820
你找我吗
You wanted to see me?

180
00:08:19,630 --> 00:08:20,680
先坐下
Sit down.

181
00:08:28,170 --> 00:08:30,530
我看了你校对的班布里奇案的摘要
I looked through your work on the Bainbridge briefs.

182
00:08:35,490 --> 00:08:36,740
非常出色
Spectacular.

183
00:08:39,360 --> 00:08:42,500
你发现了上市资产和潜在资产间的不符之处
You caught the discrepancies between listed assets and potential assets.

184
00:08:42,500 --> 00:08:43,950
迈克  这之间差距可不小
That had a huge impact, Mike.

185
00:08:43,950 --> 00:08:45,470
是  我知道  差上百万
Yeah, I know. Millions.

186
00:08:45,470 --> 00:08:48,120
不过谁都能发现那个问题  对吧
But anyone would've caught that, right?

187
00:08:48,150 --> 00:08:50,530
我们这里的五十个助理
Um, out of the 50 associates that are under purview,

188
00:08:50,530 --> 00:08:52,090
没有一人发现得了那个问题
not one of them would've caught that.

189
00:08:52,460 --> 00:08:53,980
迈克  你对细节观察入微
You just have this eye for detail, Mike.

190
00:08:53,980 --> 00:08:55,670
难怪哈维这么器重你
I mean, no wonder Harvey's so crazy about you.

191
00:08:55,740 --> 00:08:56,840
你很厉害  说真的
It's amazing. I mean, I really,

192
00:08:56,910 --> 00:08:58,660
我非常欣赏这一点
really, seriously appreciate that.

193
00:08:58,660 --> 00:09:01,040
谢谢你  路易
Hey, thank you, Louis.

194
00:09:02,440 --> 00:09:03,750
你客气了
That's nice.

195
00:09:03,750 --> 00:09:05,020
你知道的吧
You know that I pick a...

196
00:09:05,820 --> 00:09:07,760
我每年都会从马群里挑出一匹良驹
pony out of the herd every year, don't you?

197
00:09:07,780 --> 00:09:09,830
-良驹  -是的
- A pony?  - Oh, yeah.

198
00:09:09,830 --> 00:09:11,320
就是有潜力的人
Someone who shows potential.

199
00:09:11,370 --> 00:09:13,120
将其纳入我的麾下
Stamp my own little brand on him.

200
00:09:14,920 --> 00:09:16,450
迈克  你会是那匹良驹吗
Are you that pony, Mike?

201
00:09:21,040 --> 00:09:23,730
我...是为哈维工作的
I...work for Harvey.

202
00:09:24,470 --> 00:09:25,470
那是应该的
As you should.

203
00:09:25,710 --> 00:09:26,740
那就好
Good.

204
00:09:26,800 --> 00:09:28,190
我现在手头还有工作要做
Well, listen, I have some work to get to.

205
00:09:28,190 --> 00:09:31,410
明天我们可以在俱乐部一起吃个午饭
So maybe we can meet for lunch tomorrow at the club.

206
00:09:31,470 --> 00:09:33,540
-一点怎么样  -明天可能...
- 1 p.m.?  -Uh, you know, tomorrow...

207
00:09:33,610 --> 00:09:34,880
我虽然用的是问句
I know I just posed that as a question,

208
00:09:34,940 --> 00:09:36,390
但其实我没想征求你的意见
but I really didn't mean it that way.

209
00:09:44,180 --> 00:09:45,560
有事吗
Hey, what's up?

210
00:09:45,810 --> 00:09:47,440
我刚从怀亚特那里得到消息
We just heard from Wyatt.

211
00:09:47,830 --> 00:09:50,040
他从专利局收到了回复
He got a response from the patent office.

212
00:09:50,150 --> 00:09:51,090
然后呢
And?

213
00:09:52,250 --> 00:09:53,600
申请没有通过
It's been denied.

214
00:09:53,740 --> 00:09:54,720
什么
What?

215
00:09:54,870 --> 00:09:56,780
很显然  有人申请了相似的专利
Evidently, there was a similar claim.

216
00:09:56,990 --> 00:09:57,850
等等  这什么意思
Wait, what do you mean?

217
00:09:57,850 --> 00:09:58,890
有人抢在我们前面了吗
Somebody beat us to it?

218
00:09:58,890 --> 00:10:00,950
不  是抢在你前面了
No, someone beat you to it.

219
00:10:00,990 --> 00:10:03,010
他们只比你早申请不到24小时
They filed less than 24 hours ago,

220
00:10:03,010 --> 00:10:05,930
也就是说你的专利申请迟交了一天
which means you filed a day later than you said you would.

221
00:10:05,930 --> 00:10:07,710
我跟你说了  我不会填申请
I tried to tell you that I didn't know how to do that.

222
00:10:07,710 --> 00:10:09,140
我也跟你说了  自己去想办法
And I told you to figure it out.

223
00:10:09,140 --> 00:10:10,250
我想了呀  而且申请也交上去了
And I did, and it got filed.

224
00:10:10,310 --> 00:10:13,690
那是在你谎称已经完成以后的事了
After you lied and said you'd already followed through.

225
00:10:16,670 --> 00:10:18,290
那现在怎么办
Okay, what's gonna happen now?

226
00:10:19,750 --> 00:10:20,960
我建议你现在拿起电话
I suggest you get on the phone,

227
00:10:21,030 --> 00:10:23,360
打给专利局  搞清楚是谁抢了先
call the patent office, and find out who beat us to it.

228
00:10:23,430 --> 00:10:26,270
然后让唐娜找个愿意听我们解释的法官
Then you're gonna have Donna find any judge who will listen,

229
00:10:26,270 --> 00:10:27,460
这样我们就能申请强制令
so we can get an injunction,

230
00:10:27,530 --> 00:10:30,120
阻止对方抢先把产品投放到市场
and stop whoever it is from launching their product first.

231
00:10:30,120 --> 00:10:31,000
好  明白了
Okay, got it.

232
00:10:31,070 --> 00:10:32,870
我现在要打给怀亚特  稳定他的情绪
Now I've gotta call Wyatt and calm him down.

233
00:10:32,870 --> 00:10:34,510
肯定不止在公园散散步那么简单
You think that's gonna be a walk in the park?

234
00:10:36,570 --> 00:10:38,180
哈维
Hey, Harvey...

235
00:10:39,480 --> 00:10:41,500
你有没有告诉他是我搞砸的
Did you tell him it was me?

236
00:10:42,750 --> 00:10:44,480
为什么要告诉他  我要为你的行为负责
Why would I do that? I'm responsible for you.

237
00:10:44,550 --> 00:10:45,770
搞砸的人是我
It was me.

238
00:11:07,850 --> 00:11:09,970
怀亚特  他们已经签了文件
They signed the paperwork, Wyatt.

239
00:11:09,970 --> 00:11:11,060
不可能撤回了
They can't pull out.

240
00:11:11,190 --> 00:11:13,710
好了  专利之争不是重点
The patent dispute is not an issue, okay?

241
00:11:13,840 --> 00:11:16,650
不  他们已经写好支票了  就这么简单
No, they cut the check. End of story.

242
00:11:16,650 --> 00:11:18,910
我要上法庭了  一会再打给你
I'm in court right now, let me call you back.

243
00:11:20,240 --> 00:11:22,020
抢注专利的是极速数据处理公司
So it's Velocity Data Solutions.

244
00:11:22,080 --> 00:11:23,750
你通知他们参加审讯了吗
Did you serve them with notice of the hearing?

245
00:11:23,820 --> 00:11:25,530
他们公司市值有数十亿美元
They are a billion dollar company.

246
00:11:25,530 --> 00:11:27,830
公司越大  输得越惨
The bigger they are, the harder they fall.

247
00:11:30,530 --> 00:11:32,390
你没看见庭外的告示吗
Did you not see the sign outside?

248
00:11:32,450 --> 00:11:33,870
我现在就放好  法官大人
I'm just putting it away, your honor.

249
00:11:33,870 --> 00:11:35,630
手机早该放进口袋了
It should already be in your pocket.

250
00:11:35,700 --> 00:11:38,640
不过这也许解释了你为何会迟到
But you were already running late, so perhaps that's why it wasn't.

251
00:11:39,540 --> 00:11:41,670
请记录  控方律师因违反上庭条例
Let the records show that the counsel is fined $1,000

252
00:11:41,740 --> 00:11:43,720
罚款一千美元
for failing to follow the posted rules of the court.

253
00:11:43,720 --> 00:11:44,830
法官大人  我不是故意...
Your honor, I didn't mean--

254
00:11:44,830 --> 00:11:47,250
-外加顶嘴  -顶嘴
- And for mouthing off. - Mouthing off?

255
00:11:47,250 --> 00:11:51,050
再多说一句废话  我就把你赶出法庭
Another outburst like that, and you will be escorted out.

256
00:11:56,090 --> 00:11:57,370
萨林格先生
Mr. Salinger?

257
00:11:57,540 --> 00:11:59,350
法官大人  这是在浪费您的宝贵时间
Your honor, this is a waste of your time.

258
00:11:59,420 --> 00:12:02,060
美国专利局才是解决这种争端的
The U.S. Patent office is the only judicial body

259
00:12:02,060 --> 00:12:04,410
唯一法定机构
that should be handling this dispute.

260
00:12:04,500 --> 00:12:07,650
极速数据处理公司要求驳回上诉
Velocity Data Solutions requests dismissal.

261
00:12:08,910 --> 00:12:11,420
法官大人  我能发言吗
Your honor. If I may?

262
00:12:12,070 --> 00:12:13,910
这份强制令申请书指明了...
This injunction request--

263
00:12:13,910 --> 00:12:15,050
律师上前
Counsel approach.

264
00:12:23,180 --> 00:12:24,670
这是要提交的证据吗
That's the exhibit filing?

265
00:12:26,050 --> 00:12:28,040
我怎么连份像样的副本都没收到
Why wasn't I given a courtesy copy?

266
00:12:28,130 --> 00:12:30,180
因为这次审讯的准备时间仓促
Given the expedited nature of this hearing, I--

267
00:12:30,250 --> 00:12:32,270
给我  递给我
Hand it to me. Hand it to me.

268
00:12:39,560 --> 00:12:44,020
在我看来  律师应该比法官早到庭
And I would've assumed that a lawyer appearing before a judge would come on time,

269
00:12:44,020 --> 00:12:47,570
另外还要微言慎行  准备好副本
with his mouth shut, and prepared with a courtesy brief.

270
00:12:49,850 --> 00:12:52,300
-我深表歉意  -驳回上诉
- My apologies.  - Request denied.

271
00:12:52,480 --> 00:12:53,910
休庭
Court adjourned for morning.

272
00:12:55,300 --> 00:12:57,570
祝你下次好运  哈维  
Better luck next time, Harvey.

273
00:13:00,880 --> 00:13:04,080
从现在起  和你打官司  我就找这个法官
From now on, I want him when I go against you.

274
00:13:07,990 --> 00:13:09,110
在这等着
Wait here.

275
00:13:13,010 --> 00:13:14,940
-法官大人  -让他进来
- Your honor, I have--  - Send him in.

276
00:13:25,980 --> 00:13:27,070
有事吗  律师
Counselor?

277
00:13:27,810 --> 00:13:29,470
你要求见我
You asked to see me.

278
00:13:29,620 --> 00:13:31,380
应该有话对我说吧
You must have something to say.

279
00:13:31,380 --> 00:13:33,220
除了我的朋友  助理
Excluding friends, associates,

280
00:13:33,290 --> 00:13:34,930
和委托人
and the clients that I represent,

281
00:13:34,930 --> 00:13:37,540
很少有人和我的交情好到直呼名字的地步
there are very few people that I'm on a first name basis with.

282
00:13:37,540 --> 00:13:40,130
我也从没碰到过
And I've never had anyone,

283
00:13:40,130 --> 00:13:42,170
任何一个我从未见过的法官
let alone a judge I've never met,

284
00:13:42,220 --> 00:13:44,910
在法庭上直呼我为哈维
address me as Harvey in open court.

285
00:13:45,420 --> 00:13:46,600
但你要是想存心整我
But if you're gonna screw me,

286
00:13:46,600 --> 00:13:49,240
那你对我直呼姓名就不奇怪了
I guess it's only fair that you call me by name.

287
00:13:49,870 --> 00:13:51,480
依你刚才对我说话的态度
I could have you brought up on review

288
00:13:51,480 --> 00:13:52,590
我可以让你去接受复审
for talking to me like that.

289
00:13:52,590 --> 00:13:54,250
那样我们就可以把谈话内容记录在案了
Then we can get it all on record.

290
00:13:54,530 --> 00:13:55,630
什么内容
Get what?

291
00:13:55,630 --> 00:13:59,360
你无故针对我的原因
Whatever it is that you seem to have against me for no apparent reason.

292
00:13:59,440 --> 00:14:00,910
我的证据充足  
I have a solid argument

293
00:14:00,910 --> 00:14:03,490
任何讲理的法官都会批准我的强制令 
for any reasonable judge to grant my injunction.

294
00:14:03,490 --> 00:14:04,960
这就让我不禁想问
So solid it begs the question,

295
00:14:04,960 --> 00:14:06,540
你为何要针对我
why do you have it in for me?

296
00:14:06,740 --> 00:14:08,880
我却连你的名字都不知道
And I don't even know your first name.

297
00:14:08,930 --> 00:14:09,950
真的吗
Really?

298
00:14:10,300 --> 00:14:12,820
-我老婆没提起过吗  -你老婆
- My wife never mentioned it?  - Your wife?

299
00:14:12,930 --> 00:14:15,480
上个月和你偷情的那个
The woman you had an affair with last month?

300
00:14:21,100 --> 00:14:22,450
等等  你在里面干了什么
Wait, what happened in there?

301
00:14:22,450 --> 00:14:25,620
唐娜  给我找出上个月搞慈善的那个画廊地址
Donna, the address for that fundraiser at the gallery last month,

302
00:14:25,690 --> 00:14:28,080
发到我手机上  并推掉我下午的日程
I need you to text it to me, and clear my afternoon.

303
00:14:29,740 --> 00:14:31,040
我们这是去哪里
Hey, where are we going?

304
00:14:31,200 --> 00:14:33,220
你马上回办公室去
You're going back to the office to file

305
00:14:33,220 --> 00:14:35,260
向专利局递交一份抵触声明
an interference claim with the patent office.

306
00:14:35,260 --> 00:14:37,370
好的  慢着  那是什么
Okay. Wait, what's that?

307
00:14:37,370 --> 00:14:39,720
他们用来认定谁拿到专利权的依据
It's how they determine who wins these situations.

308
00:14:39,720 --> 00:14:41,020
并不是谁申请得早  谁就赢
It's not always who filed first,

309
00:14:41,020 --> 00:14:41,820
所以我们还有机会
so we have a chance.

310
00:14:41,820 --> 00:14:43,190
那为什么不一开始就这样做呢
So why didn't we do that in the first place?

311
00:14:43,190 --> 00:14:44,280
因为那得等很长时间
Because it takes longer,

312
00:14:44,280 --> 00:14:46,430
而我想在这种问题上  速战速决
and I wanted to head velocity off at the pass.

313
00:14:46,830 --> 00:14:48,140
你要去哪里啊
Hey, where you going?

314
00:14:48,240 --> 00:14:49,860
摆平麻烦
To iron out a wrinkle.

315
00:14:55,600 --> 00:14:58,510
如果你真的感兴趣  就明天一点左右过来
If you're really interested, come back tomorrow around 1:00.

316
00:14:58,620 --> 00:15:01,660
午后的阳光会让这幅油画变得栩栩如生
The afternoon light really makes this canvas come alive.

317
00:15:01,680 --> 00:15:02,470
打扰一下  
Pardon me.

318
00:15:02,470 --> 00:15:04,900
作为你外遇的对象 
I was wondering, would I get a discount for being the guy

319
00:15:04,900 --> 00:15:06,770
这幅画能给我打个折吗
you cheated on your husband with?

320
00:15:08,760 --> 00:15:11,000
失陪一下
Can you excuse me for a second?

321
00:15:12,970 --> 00:15:14,250
你过来干什么
What are you doing here?

322
00:15:14,470 --> 00:15:16,650
今早的审讯  我碰到了个法官
I had a hearing in front of the judge this morning,

323
00:15:16,650 --> 00:15:17,890
处处针对我
it didn't go very well.

324
00:15:17,950 --> 00:15:20,410
-你为什么跟他说谎  -你说什么
- Why did you lie to him? - I'm sorry.

325
00:15:20,450 --> 00:15:22,560
你那天晚上是有点醉
I mean, I recall you being tipsy that night,

326
00:15:22,560 --> 00:15:25,280
但我不相信  你的记忆会模糊到
but I'm finding it hard to believe that your memory is so cloudy,

327
00:15:25,350 --> 00:15:27,030
忘记我叫车送你回家了
you forgot I sent you home in a cab.

328
00:15:27,080 --> 00:15:28,560
那是在你羞辱了我之后
After humiliating me.

329
00:15:28,560 --> 00:15:29,740
我可绅士了
I was the perfect gentleman.

330
00:15:29,740 --> 00:15:31,100
是啊  没错
Yes, exactly.

331
00:15:31,140 --> 00:15:33,360
我使出浑身解数勾引你
I fall all over myself making a pass,

332
00:15:33,420 --> 00:15:35,890
你却无动于衷  叫车送我回家
and you do the right thing and send me home.

333
00:15:35,890 --> 00:15:37,390
抱歉这让你蒙羞了
I'm sorry you felt humiliated,

334
00:15:37,460 --> 00:15:39,840
但我说过  我不和已婚女士上床
but I told you, I don't sleep with married women.

335
00:15:39,840 --> 00:15:42,080
是啊  严守道德准则
Right. The moral code.

336
00:15:42,120 --> 00:15:44,530
不  是因为这会后患无穷 
No. It's too big of a pain in the ass

337
00:15:44,530 --> 00:15:46,820
今早的审讯就是最好的例证
as evidenced by my experience in court this morning.

338
00:15:46,820 --> 00:15:48,180
你要我怎样  哈维
What do you want from me, Harvey.

339
00:15:48,180 --> 00:15:50,130
我要你跟他说实话
I need you to tell him the truth.

340
00:15:50,130 --> 00:15:51,620
-我不能  -你能
- I can't. - Yes, you can.

341
00:15:51,640 --> 00:15:52,970
你为什么不自己告诉他  
Why didn't you just tell him?

342
00:15:52,970 --> 00:15:53,860
他才不会信我
He's never gonna believe me.

343
00:15:53,860 --> 00:15:55,880
那他凭什么会相信我
And what makes you think he'll believe me?

344
00:15:58,610 --> 00:16:00,100
因为他愿意相信你
Because he'd want to.

345
00:16:02,680 --> 00:16:04,050
在我们的婚姻里  
Our whole marriage,

346
00:16:04,050 --> 00:16:05,870
唐纳德只在乎一件事
Donald's only cared about one thing.

347
00:16:05,990 --> 00:16:08,150
就是他至高无上的名誉
His sterling reputation.

348
00:16:08,660 --> 00:16:10,370
这点从未改变过
Never overturned.

349
00:16:11,210 --> 00:16:15,240
所以我...  当他发现你和我有...
I was... When he found out you and I had...

350
00:16:15,760 --> 00:16:17,340
他变了
He changed.

351
00:16:18,250 --> 00:16:20,610
他又开始正视我了
He looked at me for the first time again.

352
00:16:20,610 --> 00:16:22,070
很关心的样子
Like I mattered.

353
00:16:23,800 --> 00:16:26,130
对不起  我不会告诉他的
I'm sorry. I can't tell him.

354
00:16:31,430 --> 00:16:34,390
不  这是申请人所提出的要求
No, this is a request from the applicant for--

355
00:16:34,710 --> 00:16:37,360
我知道  但最多不能超过一年
Yes, but I have up to a year before you--

356
00:16:37,360 --> 00:16:39,880
-不  我等不了...  -可以走了吗
- Hello-- No, I can't hold... - You ready?

357
00:16:40,180 --> 00:16:41,140
我去不成俱乐部了  
I can't go to the club,

358
00:16:41,140 --> 00:16:42,520
我得帮哈维把这事处理好
I have to do this for Harvey.

359
00:16:42,520 --> 00:16:44,170
没错  你之前那人说了 
Yes, the person before you said

360
00:16:44,170 --> 00:16:44,870
让我填写蓝色的表格
that I had to file the blue form--

361
00:16:44,870 --> 00:16:46,220
停  停  停  场地已经预定好了
No, no, no, no. We have a court reserved

362
00:16:46,220 --> 00:16:47,350
定在30分钟之后   我们现在就得走
in 30 minutes, we have to go now.

363
00:16:47,350 --> 00:16:49,000
是的  我一直在申请口头审理
Yes, I'm trying to file the oral hearing.

364
00:16:49,000 --> 00:16:51,430
但你们一直在...  喂
But what you people keep doing is trans-- Hello?

365
00:16:51,780 --> 00:16:52,880
喂
Hello?

366
00:16:56,990 --> 00:16:58,090
你也是我的手下
You work for me, too.

367
00:16:58,090 --> 00:17:00,340
所以哈维不在的时候
And that means when Harvey is not here,

368
00:17:00,570 --> 00:17:02,210
你就得听我的  迈克
you gotta listen to what I say, Mike.

369
00:17:02,210 --> 00:17:04,720
路易  我今天必须把这份声明提交上去
Louis, this claim needs to be filed today.

370
00:17:04,720 --> 00:17:06,020
这是哈维的命令
Harvey's orders.

371
00:17:06,900 --> 00:17:08,720
既然如此  格雷戈里 
In that case... Gregory!

372
00:17:08,720 --> 00:17:10,320
我和你一帮的  没忘吧
I'm on your side, remember?

373
00:17:10,360 --> 00:17:12,070
-看好了  -在  
- Watch this. - Yes?

374
00:17:12,070 --> 00:17:13,820
专利抵触声明
Hi. Patent interference claim...

375
00:17:13,820 --> 00:17:15,460
你能在我们回来之前提交吗
Can you have it filed before we get back?

376
00:17:15,460 --> 00:17:17,000
没问题吧  谢了  我们走
Cool? Thanks. Let's go.

377
00:17:18,700 --> 00:17:20,550
这动作是什么...
What's with the...?

378
00:17:39,520 --> 00:17:40,730
谁领先
Who's winning?

379
00:17:42,070 --> 00:17:44,350
-你要热身吗  -不用了
- You need to warm up? - No, I'm good.

380
00:17:44,870 --> 00:17:45,650
你先发球  
You serve first.

381
00:17:45,650 --> 00:17:47,320
来吧  让我见识下你的实力
Come on, show me what you got.

382
00:17:47,960 --> 00:17:48,910
15比0
15-love.

383
00:17:49,230 --> 00:17:50,490
玩认真的是吧
All right, you wanna play like that?

384
00:17:50,490 --> 00:17:51,860
我乐意奉陪  来吧
Let's do this thing. Come on.

385
00:17:59,160 --> 00:18:00,430
慢点  慢点
Wait, wait.

386
00:18:05,060 --> 00:18:05,960
来啦  汤姆  
Hey, Tom.

387
00:18:07,370 --> 00:18:09,060
结束
Game.

388
00:18:10,490 --> 00:18:11,950
我见识过你的压线球
I mean, I have seen your approach shot, man.

389
00:18:12,020 --> 00:18:13,250
你水平大有提升啊  说真的
You have really improved. I'm not kidding.

390
00:18:13,320 --> 00:18:14,590
我们现在就来一局吧
You know, maybe you can play now,

391
00:18:14,660 --> 00:18:16,260
我和我助理刚开始打
me and my associate were just starting up.

392
00:18:16,330 --> 00:18:17,390
你们俩二打一怎么样  
How about you two against me,

393
00:18:17,390 --> 00:18:18,730
我一人...
I'll just play--

394
00:18:18,800 --> 00:18:19,960
汤姆  说真的  我可以...
Tom, seriously, I'll even--

395
00:18:20,030 --> 00:18:21,860
我可以让你三局
I'll spot you three sets.

396
00:18:22,370 --> 00:18:23,820
好吧  那过会见
All right, I'll see you later then.

397
00:18:25,400 --> 00:18:26,110
他是不是... 
Isn't that, uh...?

398
00:18:26,110 --> 00:18:27,420
汤姆·凯勒
It's Tom Keller.

399
00:18:27,640 --> 00:18:30,450
就是《梦幻体育》的创始人吗
Yeah, the premiere Fantasy Sports guy, right?

400
00:18:27,640 --> 00:18:30,450
虚拟网络游戏  玩家扮演经理人操纵整个球队

401
00:18:30,610 --> 00:18:31,710
没错  就是他  
That's him.

402
00:18:31,710 --> 00:18:32,950
我过去一年常玩这游戏
Yeah, I play it ever a year.

403
00:18:32,950 --> 00:18:33,930
是啊  何止是你  
Yeah, you and five million

404
00:18:33,930 --> 00:18:35,220
那游戏玩家超过五百万
other Fantasy Footballers.

405
00:18:35,220 --> 00:18:38,170
这家伙每年能赚两亿  对吧
I mean, the guy generates 200 million per annum, right?

406
00:18:38,170 --> 00:18:41,390
却还雇他兄弟会的哥们当法律顾问
And he still uses his fraternity brother as a general counsel.

407
00:18:41,390 --> 00:18:43,930
这种家财万贯的人  看了就觉得恶心
I mean, someone with that many assets just makes me sick.

408
00:18:44,210 --> 00:18:45,520
好吧
Okay.

409
00:18:45,740 --> 00:18:46,800
轮到我发球了吧  
So is it my serve?

410
00:18:46,800 --> 00:18:47,760
该冲澡了
Let's hit the showers.

411
00:18:49,630 --> 00:18:50,470
但是...
But, wait...

412
00:18:51,950 --> 00:18:52,950
抱歉  先生  但...
Sorry, sir, but--

413
00:18:52,950 --> 00:18:54,130
不用介绍了
No introductions necessary,

414
00:18:54,130 --> 00:18:55,750
我们熟到都可以直呼对方大名了
we're on a first name basis.

415
00:18:56,020 --> 00:18:57,140
我给你带了份礼物
I brought you a present.

416
00:18:57,140 --> 00:18:59,990
签了这份强制令  它就归你了
Yours to keep, after you sign my injunction.

417
00:18:59,990 --> 00:19:01,640
-就一支笔  -是专门订制的
- A pen.  - It's custom.

418
00:19:01,830 --> 00:19:03,710
法国制造  利比克牌  
French. Le bic.

419
00:19:03,780 --> 00:19:05,950
我之前的裁决你没听清吗
Oh, my earlier ruling wasn't clear enough for you?

420
00:19:05,990 --> 00:19:08,440
相当清楚  但我不想让你为此麻烦缠身
Crystal, but I didn't want you to suffer for it.

421
00:19:08,510 --> 00:19:10,580
要知道  要是你不签了这份强制令
You see, if you don't sign my injunction,

422
00:19:10,580 --> 00:19:12,250
我就会起诉你
there's gonna be a lawsuit.

423
00:19:12,270 --> 00:19:14,330
等下一位法官调查清楚后
And when the next judge sees all the facts,

424
00:19:14,940 --> 00:19:16,330
就会撤销你的裁决
he's gonna overturn your ruling.

425
00:19:16,330 --> 00:19:17,340
你也许说得对
You may be right.

426
00:19:17,370 --> 00:19:19,110
但到时候你的委托人已经炒你鱿鱼了
But by then your clients will have dumped you.

427
00:19:19,110 --> 00:19:20,130
你也可能说得没错 
You may be right,

428
00:19:20,130 --> 00:19:23,400
但到时你视之如命的名誉
but that sterling reputation that you value so highly...

429
00:19:23,400 --> 00:19:24,290
就会一落千丈
down the tubes.

430
00:19:24,290 --> 00:19:26,600
换做从前  这话也许能威胁到我
Which would matter, except for one thing.

431
00:19:26,760 --> 00:19:28,800
但现在我已决定辞职了
I've decided to leave the bench.

432
00:19:29,840 --> 00:19:32,420
想改行做律师
Try my hand at litigation.

433
00:19:32,680 --> 00:19:34,550
这是你审理的最后一案
And I'm your last case.

434
00:19:34,700 --> 00:19:37,950
离婚就是这样   让人想改头换面
Divorce will do that. Make you wanna change your life.

435
00:19:37,950 --> 00:19:40,730
-你已经提出离婚了吗  -快了吧
- You filed for divorce?  - Soon enough.

436
00:19:41,650 --> 00:19:43,910
不过在此之前
Perhaps we could discuss

437
00:19:43,910 --> 00:19:46,450
我们可以谈谈条件
a little quid pro quo before I do.

438
00:19:47,080 --> 00:19:48,300
洗耳恭听
I'm listening.

439
00:19:48,550 --> 00:19:51,530
只要你白纸黑字写清楚和我老婆上过床
You sign a document that says you slept with my wife.

440
00:19:51,620 --> 00:19:53,180
我就批准你的强制令
I'll give you your injunction.

441
00:19:53,180 --> 00:19:54,860
你为什么要我那样做
And why would you want me to do that?

442
00:19:54,860 --> 00:19:57,570
以免她分走我一半的财产
To prevent her from taking me for half of everything I own.

443
00:19:58,210 --> 00:20:01,280
所以说  你是想勒索我
So what you're saying is you'd like to blackmail me.

444
00:20:01,280 --> 00:20:04,010
我是说  我们可以双赢
I'm saying we could both benefit.

445
00:20:04,140 --> 00:20:06,210
另外  既然是你毁我在先
And since you're the one who screwed me,

446
00:20:06,240 --> 00:20:08,340
这是你欠我的
I'd say you owe me one.

447
00:20:18,140 --> 00:20:19,140
哈维·斯佩克特
Harvey specter.

448
00:20:19,140 --> 00:20:20,600
你有什么瞒着我吗  哈维
What are you hiding from me, Harvey?

449
00:20:20,630 --> 00:20:23,570
怀亚特  还记不记得六个月前你紧张得要命
Wyatt, do you remember six months ago when you got all nervous

450
00:20:23,640 --> 00:20:25,180
觉得一切都没戏了
and you thought everything was falling apart?

451
00:20:25,180 --> 00:20:26,840
记得  但这次不一样
Yeah, yeah. But this is a little different.

452
00:20:26,840 --> 00:20:27,910
当时你也这样说
That's what you said then.

453
00:20:27,910 --> 00:20:30,060
1年前和18个月前你也是这么说的
And a year ago, and 18 months ago.

454
00:20:30,060 --> 00:20:32,240
我们不是说好  要是你再那么想
And we agreed that when this happens again,

455
00:20:32,360 --> 00:20:34,430
我会提醒你之前都是瞎操心
I'll remind you of those times

456
00:20:34,430 --> 00:20:36,030
-我要挂了  -好吧  哈维
- and I'll hang up. - Okay, Harvey--

457
00:20:36,030 --> 00:20:37,350
相信我  这是为了你好
Trust me, it's for your own good.

458
00:20:37,350 --> 00:20:38,660
哈维  别挂电话
Harvey, please don't hang up--

459
00:20:46,440 --> 00:20:48,440
汤姆  你刚错过了一场精彩的比赛
Hey, Tom. You just missed a great game.

460
00:20:48,440 --> 00:20:49,930
我们...我们刚才...
We were, uh... We were just re--

461
00:20:49,930 --> 00:20:51,040
我打了他个落花流水
I was beating him.

462
00:20:55,410 --> 00:20:56,690
你知道吗  十年前
You know, ten years ago,

463
00:20:56,740 --> 00:20:59,280
在这些靠网络起家的百万富翁出现之前
before these dot-com millionaires,

464
00:20:59,400 --> 00:21:00,990
这个俱乐部里可都是名副其实的富贾
there were men of substance in this club.

465
00:21:00,990 --> 00:21:03,810
他们真正懂得如何经商
You know, men who understood how business gets done.

466
00:21:04,170 --> 00:21:05,570
也许他只是不喜欢
Well, maybe he's just not interested in

467
00:21:05,570 --> 00:21:07,530
围着浴巾谈生意
talking business while he's in a towel.

468
00:21:07,540 --> 00:21:09,780
他之所以不想谈  是因为觉得我不够酷
Like, he's not interested because he doesn't think I'm cool.

469
00:21:10,230 --> 00:21:11,280
他是个瘾君子
And he's a pothead

470
00:21:11,280 --> 00:21:13,890
所以觉得不吸毒的人都是土老帽
who thinks that anybody who doesn't smoke is a nerd.

471
00:21:14,080 --> 00:21:15,030
我是说...
I mean...

472
00:21:16,390 --> 00:21:17,810
我像敬神一样珍惜身体
So I treat my body like a temple.

473
00:21:17,990 --> 00:21:19,610
那样就不够酷吗  我可不这么想
Does that make me uncool? I don't think so.

474
00:21:21,170 --> 00:21:21,930
不
No.

475
00:21:24,110 --> 00:21:25,060
但从另一方面来看
But on the other hand...

476
00:21:25,890 --> 00:21:27,240
你似乎和他很搭调
You kinda seem his type.

477
00:21:28,550 --> 00:21:30,110
-为什么那么说  -因为你年轻
- Why do you say that? - Because you're young.

478
00:21:30,920 --> 00:21:33,380
而且你认为自己很时髦
And you think of yourself as...hip.

479
00:21:34,030 --> 00:21:34,780
不管怎么说
Whatever, I guess.

480
00:21:34,780 --> 00:21:37,430
我觉得你偶尔抽上几口肯定很享受
You know, I'm sure you enjoyed the occasional bong hit.

481
00:21:40,090 --> 00:21:42,470
不  我不抽大麻
No. No, I don't smoke.

482
00:21:45,990 --> 00:21:47,190
这就有点奇怪了
I mean, that's just a little strange.

483
00:21:47,390 --> 00:21:48,230
哪里奇怪
Why is it strange?

484
00:21:48,400 --> 00:21:50,600
因为你上次做的那次药检结果...
I mean, because the drug test that you took--

485
00:21:50,600 --> 00:21:51,920
就是我逼你去做的那次
Well, that I made you take--

486
00:21:51,920 --> 00:21:53,810
和你的说法不符
would indicate otherwise.

487
00:22:03,100 --> 00:22:04,980
证据摆在眼前  没什么好狡辩的了吧
You're not gonna dispute it now, are you?

488
00:22:06,520 --> 00:22:07,670
放轻松  麦克
Relax, Mike.

489
00:22:08,290 --> 00:22:09,330
放轻松
Relax.

490
00:22:09,860 --> 00:22:10,800
我不生气
I'm not offended.

491
00:22:11,080 --> 00:22:12,250
我甚至都不觉得吃惊
I'm not even surprised.

492
00:22:12,450 --> 00:22:14,090
事实上  在这个案子中
And in fact, in this instance,

493
00:22:14,280 --> 00:22:15,600
我们还能利用你吸毒这点
we can use this to our advantage.

494
00:22:15,780 --> 00:22:16,520
你这是什么意思  路易
What are you talking about, Louis?

495
00:22:16,520 --> 00:22:18,550
我只是说  你知道  在过去
I'm just saying, you know, back in the day,

496
00:22:18,720 --> 00:22:20,850
要想赢得客户  你可以请他吃饭
to woo a client you would take him to dinner,

497
00:22:21,040 --> 00:22:21,830
请他喝酒
you would buy him a drink.

498
00:22:22,010 --> 00:22:23,130
但是那些对汤姆都不管用
But that's not gonna work with Tom.

499
00:22:23,570 --> 00:22:25,490
永远没戏  反正跟我是肯定不行
Not in a million years. Not with me, anyway.

500
00:22:25,710 --> 00:22:27,490
但是和一个与他年龄相当
But with someone of his generation

501
00:22:27,670 --> 00:22:28,970
有共同喜好的人呢
who shares the same proclivities?

502
00:22:29,760 --> 00:22:31,130
你是说想让我和他一起吸大麻
You saying you want me to smoke pot with him?

503
00:22:31,320 --> 00:22:33,610
我是说你可以帮我拿下这个客户
I'm saying you can help me land him as a client.

504
00:22:36,490 --> 00:22:37,930
你就是为了这事才叫我过来的吧
That's the only reason I'm here, isn't it?

505
00:22:38,140 --> 00:22:39,210
不  麦克  别这样
No, Mike. Stop.

506
00:22:39,500 --> 00:22:40,730
别胡思乱想  好吗
Just stop, okay?

507
00:22:40,930 --> 00:22:43,290
我向你保证  当我看到你的药检结果时
I assure you, no one was more disappointed than me

508
00:22:43,470 --> 00:22:46,020
我比任何人都失望  明白吗
when I found out the results of your drug test, okay?

509
00:22:46,260 --> 00:22:47,010
我还不得不告诉自己
Then I had to say to myself,

510
00:22:47,010 --> 00:22:49,640
"路易  发挥你的特长  化腐朽为神奇"
"Louis, do what you do, make lemonade."

511
00:22:51,700 --> 00:22:52,380
如果我不同意呢
And if I don't?

512
00:22:54,980 --> 00:22:56,010
你是个聪明孩子
You're a smart kid.

513
00:22:57,930 --> 00:22:59,790
我也真心想看到你出人头地
And I really wanna see you succeed.

514
00:23:08,910 --> 00:23:09,770
自己把握吧
Ball's in your court.

515
00:23:12,910 --> 00:23:15,150
汤姆  我正打算告诉你  我想...
Hey, Tom, I was just gonna tell you, I wanted to--

516
00:23:16,380 --> 00:23:17,230
好吧
Okay.

517
00:23:22,010 --> 00:23:23,060
他真吓人  兄弟
Dude creeps me out, man.

518
00:23:23,650 --> 00:23:25,250
而且他从来不围浴巾  从来不围
And he never wears a towel, ever.

519
00:23:25,520 --> 00:23:26,640
没错  可不是嘛
Yeah, tell me about it.

520
00:23:31,130 --> 00:23:33,110
我知道你一定经常听别人这么说
Hey, I know you must hear this all the time,

521
00:23:33,280 --> 00:23:35,280
我真的喜欢你的网游  哥们
but totally addicted to your website, man.

522
00:23:36,730 --> 00:23:39,170
那么去年的传球码数  谁排第六
All right, who placed sixth in passing yards last year?

523
00:23:40,230 --> 00:23:41,190
卡森·帕默
Carson Palmer.

524
00:23:41,490 --> 00:23:42,810
共3970码
3,970.

525
00:23:43,000 --> 00:23:44,350
詹姆斯·霍尔几次擒杀四分卫
How many sacks did James Hall have?

526
00:23:45,500 --> 00:23:46,140
11次
11?

527
00:23:46,500 --> 00:23:47,880
10次半
Ten and a half.

528
00:23:48,490 --> 00:23:49,710
我知道  我四舍五入了
Yeah, I know, I rounded up.

529
00:23:49,710 --> 00:23:52,210
游戏里可不是那么算的  否则我就进前20了
Well, your league doesn't or I would've come in better than 20th.

530
00:23:55,300 --> 00:23:57,260
你是"罗斯的入侵者"  对吗
You'r Ross's raiders, right?

531
00:23:58,150 --> 00:23:59,210
对  我叫迈克·罗斯
Yeah, Mike Ross.

532
00:23:59,400 --> 00:24:01,510
-我是汤姆·凯勒  -很高兴见到你
- Tom Keller. - Good to meet you.

533
00:24:01,700 --> 00:24:03,560
恭喜你  兄弟  你有个很棒的队伍
Congratulations, man, you got a nice little team there.

534
00:24:03,770 --> 00:24:04,460
一般
Yeah.

535
00:24:04,640 --> 00:24:05,880
不  如果罗兹力斯伯格没让你失望的话
No, if Roethlisberger hadn't let you down,

536
00:24:06,070 --> 00:24:07,300
你肯定能进前十  肯定能
you'd have been top ten for sure, I'm telling you.

537
00:24:07,490 --> 00:24:08,420
如果上场前你抽高了
Yeah, well, that's what happens

538
00:24:08,600 --> 00:24:09,960
就难免会失手  不是吗
when you get high before the draft, right?

539
00:24:11,490 --> 00:24:12,100
你会抽吗
You get high?

540
00:24:50,760 --> 00:24:51,700
跟哈维相处得怎么样
How's it going with Harvey?

541
00:24:54,810 --> 00:24:55,600
我吗
Me?

542
00:24:56,390 --> 00:24:59,360
那个...还不错
Uh...It's... You know, it's good.

543
00:24:59,680 --> 00:25:00,590
我在学习
I'm learning.

544
00:25:02,530 --> 00:25:04,320
要学的真不少  再见
A lot of learning. Bye.

545
00:25:39,320 --> 00:25:41,710
什么白纸黑字会让你付出巨大代价
What's black and white and gonna cost you dearly?

546
00:25:45,570 --> 00:25:47,380
我花了一个上午才写好  金童
Took me all morning to file this, golden boy.

547
00:25:47,570 --> 00:25:49,070
你欠我的  我不会忘记的
You owe me and I won't forget it.

548
00:25:49,310 --> 00:25:51,190
天啊  谢谢你
Oh, God! Thank you.

549
00:25:52,690 --> 00:25:53,850
你身上有纸的味道
You smell papery.

550
00:25:57,720 --> 00:25:59,160
怀亚特  不可能马上就好
Wyatt, it doesn't happen immediately.

551
00:25:59,370 --> 00:26:00,820
书面文件很快就下来了
The paperwork's coming.

552
00:26:01,960 --> 00:26:03,250
别担心好吗
Don't worry about it, okay?

553
00:26:03,430 --> 00:26:05,080
行了  看看那个
There you go, look at that.

554
00:26:06,280 --> 00:26:07,860
怀亚特  我一会回给你  好吗
Wyatt, let me call you back, okay?

555
00:26:08,360 --> 00:26:09,850
五分钟后  再见
Five minutes. Bye.

556
00:26:11,240 --> 00:26:13,190
-这是什么  -这是什么
- What's this? - What is this?

557
00:26:13,370 --> 00:26:14,980
这是抵触声明的确认书
That's confirmation of the interference claim

558
00:26:15,370 --> 00:26:17,160
我已经用心校对过了
which I proofed. Up top.

559
00:26:17,740 --> 00:26:19,370
干嘛  你以为你在兄弟会工作吗
What, you think you're working in a fraternity?

560
00:26:19,560 --> 00:26:21,090
我打电话的时候你不能这么闯进来
You don't barge in here when I'm on the phone.

561
00:26:22,170 --> 00:26:23,340
你为什么面红耳赤的
And why you so flushed?

562
00:26:24,440 --> 00:26:26,580
-我怎么了  -你的脸发红
- Why am I so what? - Your face is red.

563
00:26:26,580 --> 00:26:28,500
好像经过暴晒似的
It looks like you've been in the sun.

564
00:26:28,750 --> 00:26:29,880
是的
Yeah, I--

565
00:26:30,090 --> 00:26:34,170
早上  路易带我去了网球俱乐部
I-- This morning, Louis took me to the tennis club.

566
00:26:34,650 --> 00:26:36,520
他没跟你谈那个关于...
He didn't give you the speech about the, um,

567
00:26:37,050 --> 00:26:38,640
-马驹的问题吧  -我的天
- the ponies, did he?  - Oh, my God.

568
00:26:38,640 --> 00:26:40,330
说他会从马群中千里挑一
How he likes to cut one from the herd.

569
00:26:41,030 --> 00:26:42,270
马驹
The ponies.

570
00:26:42,270 --> 00:26:43,410
他戴着发带吗
Was he wearing the headband?

571
00:26:43,410 --> 00:26:45,700
你知道发带的事  还有...
You know about the headband? With the...

572
00:26:45,990 --> 00:26:47,700
天啊  那家伙太让人无语了
Oh, my God, are you kidding me with that guy?

573
00:26:47,890 --> 00:26:49,510
如果你们一上午都在打网球
Hey, if you guys were playing tennis all morning,

574
00:26:49,970 --> 00:26:51,890
你怎么有时间提交确认书
how'd you have time to file this?

575
00:26:56,800 --> 00:26:58,190
他...今天早上
He-- It was this morning--

576
00:26:58,370 --> 00:27:00,040
实际上  我当时正和他们打着电话
Actually, I was on the phone with them,

577
00:27:00,240 --> 00:27:02,660
-然后路易帮我...  -看着我
- and Louis helped me-- - Look at me.

578
00:27:03,210 --> 00:27:05,290
他一打响指  然后格雷戈里...
And he did this snapping thing, and Gregory--

579
00:27:05,520 --> 00:27:06,300
看着我
Look at me.

580
00:27:13,400 --> 00:27:14,170
你抽高了
You're high.

581
00:27:17,490 --> 00:27:18,290
滚出去
Get out.

582
00:27:20,970 --> 00:27:22,510
哈维  你不了解  路易他...
Harvey, you don't understand. Louis--

583
00:27:22,720 --> 00:27:23,500
滚
Out.

584
00:27:37,260 --> 00:27:37,870
唐娜
Donna?

585
00:27:38,970 --> 00:27:40,030
再帮我接通怀亚特的电话
Get Wyatt back on the line?

586
00:27:58,330 --> 00:27:59,210
你在这里干什么
What are you doing in here?

587
00:28:00,070 --> 00:28:01,150
这是女洗手间
It's the ladies room.

588
00:28:04,890 --> 00:28:05,500
抱歉
I'm sorry.

589
00:28:06,160 --> 00:28:08,080
能帮我个忙吗  你能不能...
Look, can you do me a favor? Can we--

590
00:28:09,060 --> 00:28:11,100
能不能帮我保守这个秘密
Can we just keep this our little secret?

591
00:28:11,620 --> 00:28:13,350
你眼睛为什么这么红
Why are your eyes so red?

592
00:28:17,270 --> 00:28:17,990
我需要点新鲜空气
I need some air.

593
00:28:20,870 --> 00:28:22,390
你今天带迈克·罗斯去实地考察了吗
You took Mike Ross on a field trip today?

594
00:28:22,390 --> 00:28:24,090
-对  -除了让他围着浴巾
- Yep. - Aside from subjecting him

595
00:28:24,270 --> 00:28:25,710
听你指挥  你还做了什么
to you in a towel, what happened?

596
00:28:26,420 --> 00:28:28,180
我直落三盘获胜  你问的是这个...
Well, I beat him in straight sets, if that's what you're get...

597
00:28:28,180 --> 00:28:30,210
别装傻充愣  路易  告诉我你把他怎么样了
Don't play dumb, Louis. Tell me what you did to him.

598
00:28:30,210 --> 00:28:31,080
怎么  你嫉妒了吗
What, are you jealous?

599
00:28:31,260 --> 00:28:33,580
哈维  别这样  那个孩子急缺导师
Harvey, come on, the kid is starving for a mentor,

600
00:28:33,850 --> 00:28:34,840
缺一个可以给他建议的人
someone to give him some advice.

601
00:28:34,840 --> 00:28:35,620
也许如果你有时间...
So maybe if you just took the time--

602
00:28:35,620 --> 00:28:37,870
我现在告诉你  你要是再试图靠近他
I'm telling you right now, you try to move in on him--

603
00:28:37,870 --> 00:28:39,400
哈维  这话从何说起
Harvey, where is this coming from?

604
00:28:39,600 --> 00:28:42,900
哈维  极速公司的外部法律顾问在线上等你
Harvey, I've got the outside counsel for Velocity on the line.

605
00:28:42,900 --> 00:28:43,700
接进来
Put them through.

606
00:28:51,490 --> 00:28:52,750
和那家伙吸完毒之后发生了什么
What happened after you smoked with that guy?

607
00:28:53,280 --> 00:28:54,790
我变得很焦虑
I just got paranoid.

608
00:28:54,970 --> 00:28:57,170
为对他撒谎而感到内疚
I felt bad for lying to him,

609
00:28:58,030 --> 00:28:59,890
我告诉他是路易让我那么做的
I told him that Louis put me up to it

610
00:29:00,070 --> 00:29:01,030
让他不要相信路易
and that he couldn't trust him.

611
00:29:01,200 --> 00:29:01,910
那他说了什么
So what did he say?

612
00:29:02,970 --> 00:29:05,130
他说路易本来也让他觉得不舒服
He said that Louis gave him the creeps anyway.

613
00:29:05,320 --> 00:29:06,470
他永远不会聘请他
You know, he's never gonna hire him.

614
00:29:06,690 --> 00:29:08,090
你得告诉哈维
Okay, you have to tell Harvey.

615
00:29:09,580 --> 00:29:10,900
我试了  但他不听
I tried, he wasn't listening.

616
00:29:11,100 --> 00:29:12,750
那就先回家  明天再告诉他
So then go home and tell him tomorrow.

617
00:29:13,380 --> 00:29:14,990
天啊  你真该看看他的脸色
Oh, God, you should've seen his face.

618
00:29:15,230 --> 00:29:16,960
-我们说好的  -说好什么
- We had a deal. - What deal?

619
00:29:21,920 --> 00:29:22,980
谢谢听我讲了那么多  
Thanks for hearing me out.

620
00:29:22,980 --> 00:29:23,690
你到底在说什么
No, what're you talking about?

621
00:29:23,870 --> 00:29:25,050
-说好什么了  -没什么
- What deal? - It's nothing.

622
00:29:25,210 --> 00:29:26,390
我保证过  不会...
I just promised that I wouldn't...

623
00:29:28,250 --> 00:29:30,780
做任何傻事让他失望  但我却做了
Do anything stupid and let him down, and I did.

624
00:29:30,960 --> 00:29:31,990
等等  你让他失望
Wait, you let him down?

625
00:29:32,460 --> 00:29:34,330
在我看来  是他让你失望
No, the way I see it, he let you down.

626
00:29:35,230 --> 00:29:35,800
什么
What?

627
00:29:35,990 --> 00:29:37,600
他知道路易会对你做什么
He's gotta know what Louis is capable of,

628
00:29:37,780 --> 00:29:39,160
所以即使他真的不听你解释
so if he didn't listen to what happened

629
00:29:39,340 --> 00:29:40,320
也只是因为他不想听
it's 'cause he didn't want to.

630
00:29:40,980 --> 00:29:42,490
迈克  你应该告诉他
Mike, you need to tell him.

631
00:29:42,680 --> 00:29:44,310
我不知道你有多了解哈维
I don't know how often you come across Harvey,

632
00:29:44,490 --> 00:29:46,280
他绝不是个好的倾听对象
but he's not exactly the listening type.

633
00:29:47,030 --> 00:29:47,790
好吧
Right.

634
00:29:48,070 --> 00:29:50,230
但他也是第一个告诉你
But he's also the first person that would tell you

635
00:29:50,410 --> 00:29:52,830
永不言弃的人
never to take no for an answer from anyone.

636
00:30:01,560 --> 00:30:03,450
哈维  今天过得怎么样
Harvey, how you doing this fine day?

637
00:30:04,210 --> 00:30:06,860
正准备听你的条件呢  乔治
I'm ready to hear your settlement offer, George.

638
00:30:07,070 --> 00:30:08,370
直切主题  我喜欢
Cutting to the chase, I like that.

639
00:30:08,760 --> 00:30:09,670
你准备给多少
What's the number?

640
00:30:12,330 --> 00:30:13,000
一千万
Ten million.

641
00:30:14,650 --> 00:30:17,240
那只是开发样机费用的一半
That's half what we spent developing the prototype.

642
00:30:17,240 --> 00:30:18,670
据目前的情况看来
And ten million more than you'll get,

643
00:30:18,670 --> 00:30:19,800
一千万不少了  
the way the wind's blowing.

644
00:30:19,800 --> 00:30:21,400
情况有变
Yeah, well, winds can change.

645
00:30:21,590 --> 00:30:22,610
你我都知道  如果上诉的话
And you and I both know the injunction

646
00:30:22,610 --> 00:30:24,000
禁止令会被撤销
will get overturned on appeal.

647
00:30:24,000 --> 00:30:25,410
我怎么不知道有那回事
I don't know anything of the kind.

648
00:30:25,690 --> 00:30:27,270
那你打过来干吗
Then why are you calling with an offer at all?

649
00:30:32,410 --> 00:30:33,880
一千五百万  不能再多了
15, that's as high as I'll go.

650
00:30:34,370 --> 00:30:35,830
好了  我要挂了  
Okay, I'm hanging up now.

651
00:30:35,830 --> 00:30:37,040
两千万  就这样
20 million, that's it.

652
00:30:37,290 --> 00:30:39,040
24小时内有效
The offer's good for 24 hours.

653
00:30:39,240 --> 00:30:40,440
我想不用提醒你
And I'm sure I don't have to remind you

654
00:30:40,650 --> 00:30:43,050
依法要把这消息告诉你的客户吧
that you're legally required to present this to your client.

655
00:30:54,390 --> 00:30:55,050
他有空吗
Is he free?

656
00:30:55,730 --> 00:30:56,740
他不会见你的
Not for you.

657
00:30:57,650 --> 00:30:58,500
他告诉你什么了
How much did he tell you?

658
00:30:59,600 --> 00:31:01,670
他不必告诉我  他脸上都写着呢
He didn't have to tell me, I read it on his face.

659
00:31:02,770 --> 00:31:03,400
你也听到了
You heard him.

660
00:31:03,400 --> 00:31:04,720
也许他也做了对不起我的事
Maybe he did the same to me.

661
00:31:09,030 --> 00:31:09,680
去吧
Get in there.

662
00:31:11,760 --> 00:31:12,550
小心点
And be careful.

663
00:31:18,470 --> 00:31:19,190
哈维
Harvey.

664
00:31:20,040 --> 00:31:22,190
我跟你说过  别随便进我的办公室
We talked about this, right? Barging into my office.

665
00:31:22,400 --> 00:31:23,580
你不听我解释  我就不走
I'm not leaving until you hear me out.

666
00:31:23,800 --> 00:31:25,520
-想打赌吗  -你欠我的
- Wanna bet? - You owe it to me.

667
00:31:25,740 --> 00:31:27,130
-我欠你的  -对
- Oh, I owe it to you? - Yeah.

668
00:31:27,690 --> 00:31:29,010
这不是我的错  好吧
Look, this is not my fault, all right?

669
00:31:29,210 --> 00:31:29,980
是路易逼我做的  
Louis made me do it.

670
00:31:29,980 --> 00:31:30,820
他逼你了  好吧
Louis did, right.

671
00:31:31,010 --> 00:31:32,950
他拿枪指着你  逼你抽大麻
He put a gun to your head and made you smoke pot.

672
00:31:33,150 --> 00:31:35,010
对  他拿出药检报告
Yeah, he did. He pulled out the drug test--

673
00:31:35,010 --> 00:31:36,340
我没通过
which I failed, by the way.

674
00:31:36,340 --> 00:31:38,110
然后他告诉我  如果我不抽大麻
And then he told me that if I didn't smoke pot

675
00:31:38,290 --> 00:31:40,700
帮他搞定新客户  他就要炒了我
to help him land this new client, that he'd fire me.

676
00:31:43,980 --> 00:31:44,620
拜托
Come on.

677
00:31:44,820 --> 00:31:46,070
这和请人喝酒
It's not so different than asking someone

678
00:31:46,280 --> 00:31:48,260
-没什么区别吧  -我们说好的
- out for drinks, is it? - You and I had a deal.

679
00:31:48,440 --> 00:31:49,210
对不起
I'm sorry.

680
00:31:49,820 --> 00:31:51,660
如果下次路易让你做什么
And if next time Louis asks you to do something

681
00:31:51,850 --> 00:31:54,350
我不允许你做的事  怎么办
that I told you not to do, what then?

682
00:31:54,530 --> 00:31:56,250
我说了我别无选择
I told you that I did not have a choice.

683
00:31:56,250 --> 00:31:57,330
因为他拿枪指着你
Oh, because he had a gun to your head.

684
00:31:57,330 --> 00:32:00,350
-对  -万一真的有人拿枪指着你呢
- Yes! - What are your choices if someone puts a gun to your head?

685
00:32:00,560 --> 00:32:01,850
你想什么呢  当然是照他们说的做啊
What are you talking about? You do what they say

686
00:32:02,030 --> 00:32:03,020
-不然就没命了  -错了
- or they shoot you. - Wrong.

687
00:32:03,490 --> 00:32:05,300
你应该把枪夺走  或掏出把更大的枪
You take the gun, or you pull out a bigger one,

688
00:32:05,510 --> 00:32:06,790
或是说他们虚张声势 
or you call their bluff.

689
00:32:06,990 --> 00:32:09,880
你还有很多选择
Or you do any one of 146 other things.

690
00:32:10,050 --> 00:32:11,090
如果你想不出
If you can't think for yourself,

691
00:32:11,280 --> 00:32:12,360
说明你不适合当律师
maybe you aren't cut out for this.

692
00:32:12,550 --> 00:32:14,700
我能想出来  我已经尽我所能了
No, I can and I am. Look, I did what I had to do.

693
00:32:14,900 --> 00:32:16,660
我知道该怎么绝处逢生
I made the best out of a bad situation.

694
00:32:16,860 --> 00:32:17,860
那是我的特长
Which is what I am good at.

695
00:32:18,030 --> 00:32:19,630
你就是因为看重我那点才雇佣了我
Which is what you hired me to do in the first place.

696
00:32:19,830 --> 00:32:21,980
对  我雇你的时候以为你会很忠诚
Yeah, I hired you and I expect your loyalty.

697
00:32:22,180 --> 00:32:24,210
如果路易让你做那种事
So if Louis asks you to do something like that,

698
00:32:24,430 --> 00:32:26,060
-你应该先来找我  -对
- you come to me first. - Oh, right.

699
00:32:26,250 --> 00:32:28,070
我上次找你的时候  你告诉我
Like when I came to you and you told me

700
00:32:28,240 --> 00:32:29,740
我没有资格参加专业谈判
that I couldn't sit at the adult table, right.

701
00:32:29,930 --> 00:32:31,580
我可没忘  你还让我
I remember that. Or-or when you told me

702
00:32:31,760 --> 00:32:33,670
自己去申请专利  找你有什么用
to go file the patent by myself, like that?

703
00:32:33,850 --> 00:32:35,390
-你说什么  -你知道吗
- Excuse me? - You know what?

704
00:32:35,600 --> 00:32:37,540
也许这次该让我看看你的忠心了
Maybe it's time you showed me some loyalty.

705
00:32:40,820 --> 00:32:41,670
你知道我花了多久
Do you know how long it was

706
00:32:41,860 --> 00:32:43,690
才有资格上桌谈判的吗
before I got to sit at the adult table?

707
00:32:45,080 --> 00:32:46,840
直到我有了第一个客户
It was when I brought in my first client.

708
00:32:47,040 --> 00:32:48,840
我记得你好像一个也没有
Which I don't recall you having done.

709
00:32:49,740 --> 00:32:51,180
在你申请专利失败以后
And when you screwed up that patent

710
00:32:51,360 --> 00:32:53,220
怀亚特冲我发火
and Wyatt went ape shit on me,

711
00:32:53,400 --> 00:32:55,700
我可没有把责任推卸给你  我自己扛了
I didn't put that on you, I took it on myself.

712
00:32:55,890 --> 00:32:57,020
因为那是我的职责
Because that's my job.

713
00:32:57,340 --> 00:32:59,900
而你的职责就是按我说的去做
And it's your job to do what I say when I say it.

714
00:33:00,150 --> 00:33:01,860
如果想谈什么忠诚
So if you're talking about loyalty,

715
00:33:02,490 --> 00:33:03,850
你只能自己去争取
you better goddamn earn it.

716
00:33:07,880 --> 00:33:08,530
你说得对
You're right.

717
00:33:11,430 --> 00:33:12,920
我向你道歉的时候是真心的
I said I'm sorry and I meant it.

718
00:33:15,980 --> 00:33:16,650
哈维...
Harvey...

719
00:33:17,550 --> 00:33:20,650
我希望...我需要你相信我  好吗
I want you to tr-- I need you to trust me, okay?

720
00:33:20,840 --> 00:33:22,260
我会加班加点
And I will work as long as I can,

721
00:33:22,450 --> 00:33:24,520
尽一切努力赢得你的信任
as hard as it takes to make that happen.

722
00:33:24,710 --> 00:33:27,190
你可以不用给我报酬  好吗
I mean, you don't even have to pay me, all right?

723
00:33:27,360 --> 00:33:28,490
我免费给你干活
I'll work for free.

724
00:33:31,110 --> 00:33:31,770
免费
For free.

725
00:33:32,470 --> 00:33:34,070
也不是一直不要报酬
What, I meant...not forever.

726
00:33:34,300 --> 00:33:35,510
只是在试用期内
Just as, like, a probationary thing.

727
00:33:35,700 --> 00:33:37,130
唐娜  告诉怀亚特我马上过去
Donna, tell Wyatt I'm on my way over.

728
00:33:37,340 --> 00:33:38,540
你不用按键就能直接通话吗
Do you never have to press a button?

729
00:33:38,720 --> 00:33:39,950
收到  杰西卡要麦克
Got it. And Jessica wants to see

730
00:33:40,140 --> 00:33:41,140
立刻去办公室见她
Mike in her office right now.

731
00:33:44,160 --> 00:33:45,500
路易告诉我俱乐部的事了
Louis told me what you did at the club.

732
00:33:47,760 --> 00:33:49,030
我猜他没把全部实情告诉你
I bet he didn't tell you the whole story.

733
00:33:51,470 --> 00:33:52,680
那些已足以令我钦佩了
He told me enough to impress me.

734
00:33:56,770 --> 00:33:57,740
临时动议不好处理
Your new business is hard.

735
00:33:59,040 --> 00:34:00,380
对方会对你夸下海口
People will promise you the world

736
00:34:00,610 --> 00:34:02,590
但在签合同之前
but until they sign that engagement letter,

737
00:34:02,850 --> 00:34:03,870
那毫无意义
it means nothing.

738
00:34:05,990 --> 00:34:08,570
我不知道你对汤姆·凯勒说了什么
Now I don't know what you told Tom Keller,

739
00:34:09,180 --> 00:34:11,060
但你年纪轻轻就能拉到客户...
but bring a client in at your age...

740
00:34:12,330 --> 00:34:13,560
你让我想起了哈维
That reminds me of Harvey.

741
00:34:15,810 --> 00:34:17,370
杰西卡  签合同之前
Jessica, before we get started,

742
00:34:17,560 --> 00:34:19,690
汤姆对聘金方面有点意见
there's something in the retainer that Tom pointed out.

743
00:34:19,890 --> 00:34:21,150
其实没什么的
It's not a big deal, really.

744
00:34:21,350 --> 00:34:22,610
-我们只是  -不  不  不
- We were just-- - No, no, no, no, no, no.

745
00:34:22,790 --> 00:34:24,440
我说过  我们得让你满意
Like I said, we're here to make you happy.

746
00:34:24,840 --> 00:34:25,640
对吗
Right?

747
00:34:32,010 --> 00:34:33,540
我以为你不想和他有任何瓜葛
I thought you wanted nothing to do with him?

748
00:34:33,780 --> 00:34:35,770
的确不想  但是后来我仔细一想
I didn't. But then I thought about it.

749
00:34:36,210 --> 00:34:37,770
他虽然不是什么好人
And he might not be a very good person,

750
00:34:37,960 --> 00:34:39,100
但好的律师
but a little deviousness

751
00:34:39,310 --> 00:34:40,910
就应该具备狡猾的特质
is the sort of thing you look for in a good lawyer.

752
00:34:41,320 --> 00:34:43,300
我以前的律师  人太老实了
I mean, the other guy I was with, he was too nice.

753
00:34:43,490 --> 00:34:45,590
我们是兄弟  一起上过学
We were buddies, we went to school together.

754
00:34:45,810 --> 00:34:47,580
是时候找个专业的律师了
It's time I grew up, got a real shark.

755
00:34:48,310 --> 00:34:51,700
我不是故意那么做来拉拢你做我们的客户
Well, I had no intention of being that way to get your business.

756
00:34:51,930 --> 00:34:54,230
所以我才要坚持让你做首席律师
That's exactly why I insisted that you be my point man.

757
00:34:55,180 --> 00:34:57,110
我希望有人帮我算计别人
I want someone being devious for me,

758
00:34:57,350 --> 00:34:58,320
而不是算计我
not to me.

759
00:35:00,740 --> 00:35:02,370
-怎么了  -只是...
- What? - It's just...

760
00:35:02,600 --> 00:35:04,620
要不是你要求的话  路易根本不会
Louis would've never told Jessica that I existed,

761
00:35:04,800 --> 00:35:06,730
向杰西卡提起我  更不可能说我帮过他
let alone that I helped him if you hadn't done that.

762
00:35:07,460 --> 00:35:09,980
在我看来  我们三个精诚合作
Hey, the way I see it, the three of us stick together,

763
00:35:10,160 --> 00:35:11,190
可以做到所向披靡
we'll make a pretty good team.

764
00:35:14,720 --> 00:35:16,010
我有个更好的主意
You know, I got a better idea.

765
00:35:16,680 --> 00:35:17,900
二千万美元
$20 million?

766
00:35:18,100 --> 00:35:19,670
他们说这是最终价格了
They claim it's their final offer.

767
00:35:20,230 --> 00:35:22,060
我光做样机就花了两千万
That's what it cost to make the prototype.

768
00:35:22,360 --> 00:35:26,190
我还搭上了全部积蓄和两年的心血
Not to mention my entire savings and two years of my life.

769
00:35:26,360 --> 00:35:27,170
怀亚特...
Wyatt...

770
00:35:28,230 --> 00:35:30,240
他们知道我们的禁止令还没通过
They know we're stalled on our injunction.

771
00:35:30,520 --> 00:35:33,330
所以说  为了避免你们拿下专利
Which means, to them, they're giving you a fair price

772
00:35:33,330 --> 00:35:35,590
而带来的损失 
as an insurance policy against the risk of

773
00:35:35,590 --> 00:35:37,990
他们的出价还是很合理的
possibly losing the interference claim.

774
00:35:38,370 --> 00:35:39,540
我才懒得管他们
I don't care what it is to them.

775
00:35:40,660 --> 00:35:41,630
这不公平
It's not fair.

776
00:35:44,400 --> 00:35:46,100
不管公平与否  都是他们的最终出价了
Fair or not, it's their final offer.

777
00:35:50,940 --> 00:35:51,790
你觉得我该接受吗
You think I should take it?

778
00:35:54,500 --> 00:35:56,640
我觉得你可以让他们去死
I think you should tell them to shove it up their ass.

779
00:36:00,200 --> 00:36:02,540
女士们先生们  非常抱歉
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm terribly sorry,

780
00:36:02,720 --> 00:36:03,560
我们遇到了麻烦
but we have a problem.

781
00:36:04,680 --> 00:36:05,600
什么麻烦
What problem?

782
00:36:05,830 --> 00:36:06,590
我们之所以过来  
We came down here

783
00:36:06,590 --> 00:36:07,720
是因为你告诉我们
because you led us to believe that

784
00:36:07,720 --> 00:36:10,380
你的委托人愿意接受我们的和解协议
your client was ready to accept - our settlement agreement.

785
00:36:10,380 --> 00:36:11,460
我原本也那么认为
And I thought he would.

786
00:36:11,970 --> 00:36:13,140
我把出价告诉了他
Look, I took him the offer.

787
00:36:13,690 --> 00:36:16,580
向他做了解释  并建议他接受
I presented it to him, and recommended that he take it.

788
00:36:16,780 --> 00:36:17,930
事实上  我强烈要求他接受
In fact, I urged him to take it.

789
00:36:18,120 --> 00:36:19,190
你知道他让我怎么做吗
You know what he told me to do?

790
00:36:19,720 --> 00:36:21,730
他让我告诉你们可以去死了
He told me to tell you to shove it up your ass.

791
00:36:26,050 --> 00:36:27,840
你让我们大老远跑过来 
Now I know you didn't have me come all the way

792
00:36:27,840 --> 00:36:29,460
要说的远不止那些吧
down here just to tell me that.

793
00:36:30,040 --> 00:36:32,190
没错  怀亚特的想法不止这些
You're right. That's not all Wyatt said.

794
00:36:32,390 --> 00:36:35,150
他说与其长时间地和你们在法庭上纠缠 
He said rather than spending years fighting this out in court,

795
00:36:35,150 --> 00:36:39,650
倒不如在48小时内把这些放到网上
in 48 hours he's gonna put this online.

796
00:36:41,910 --> 00:36:44,980
做得有点粗糙  不过你们懂的
That's a little rough, but you get the idea.

797
00:36:45,180 --> 00:36:46,680
这播的是什么  是个网站吗
What are you showing us? Is this a website?

798
00:36:46,880 --> 00:36:49,360
以尚德的域名注册的
Available at the Suntech domain name.

799
00:36:49,570 --> 00:36:51,890
所有设计蓝图和计算数据都已上传
All the design plans and calculations have been uploaded.

800
00:36:52,070 --> 00:36:53,520
-已经放到网上了吗  -马上就能
- Is this online now? - Can be.

801
00:36:53,710 --> 00:36:56,210
也就意味着全世界都能看到我的设计
Which means the whole world will have access to my designs.

802
00:36:56,390 --> 00:36:58,060
在你们还没来得及打车回到总部之前
They'll be ten knock-offs of that phone

803
00:36:58,240 --> 00:37:00,510
市面上就会出现十几部盗版机了
before you can catch a cab back to your headquarters.

804
00:37:00,710 --> 00:37:03,350
-我们可以申请禁止令  -那也得等到明天
- We could file an injunction. - Not before tomorrow.

805
00:37:03,550 --> 00:37:05,370
而一旦技术泄露出去
And once that technology is out there,

806
00:37:05,720 --> 00:37:07,510
就覆水难收了
good luck putting that genie back in the bottle.

807
00:37:07,710 --> 00:37:08,570
那我们就起诉你们
Well, then we'll sue.

808
00:37:08,790 --> 00:37:10,390
我的委托人可没什么积蓄
But my client won't have any money.

809
00:37:10,760 --> 00:37:13,390
他有的只是原设计的版权而已
What he will have is credit for the initial design.

810
00:37:13,570 --> 00:37:16,150
他用别的名字对产品进行注册之后
Which, after he incorporates under a different name,

811
00:37:16,460 --> 00:37:18,180
会比你们提供的二千万美元
will be worth a hell of a lot more money

812
00:37:18,360 --> 00:37:20,200
值钱得多
than the $20 million that you're offering.

813
00:37:24,600 --> 00:37:27,240
你还说这些都是你客户的鬼主意
And you're saying that this was all your client's idea.

814
00:37:30,400 --> 00:37:31,100
对
Yes.

815
00:37:32,180 --> 00:37:33,000
我就是这么说的
That's what I'm saying.

816
00:37:49,000 --> 00:37:49,920
以为你不会来了
Thought you weren't coming.

817
00:37:50,190 --> 00:37:51,510
得先解决个案子
I had to settle a case first.

818
00:37:53,600 --> 00:37:55,110
说好的文件带了吗
You have the paperwork we talked about?

819
00:38:05,160 --> 00:38:05,860
这是什么
What is this?

820
00:38:06,600 --> 00:38:08,810
《法官行为准则》的副本
It's a copy of the Judicial Conduct Codes.

821
00:38:09,020 --> 00:38:11,000
是我一个在司法部长办公室工作的朋友
A friend of mine works at the Attorney General's office

822
00:38:11,180 --> 00:38:12,600
给我的  我们聊你聊得可欢了
gave it to me. We had a nice chat about you.

823
00:38:13,130 --> 00:38:16,110
我告诉他  既然你这次想勒索我
I told him if you were willing to blackmail someone once,

824
00:38:16,320 --> 00:38:17,880
很有可能你之前就有过前科
chances are you'd done it before.

825
00:38:18,520 --> 00:38:19,780
他非常想见你
He's very anxious to meet you.

826
00:38:20,130 --> 00:38:21,960
你认为睡了我老婆之后  你能侥幸逃脱
You think you can get away with screwing my wife

827
00:38:22,160 --> 00:38:23,380
并让我接受审查吗
and then have me investigated?

828
00:38:23,610 --> 00:38:25,220
其实你从头到尾都搞错了
You actually have it the wrong way around.

829
00:38:25,440 --> 00:38:26,570
到目前为止  我所做的
The only thing I've done so far

830
00:38:27,550 --> 00:38:29,250
只是让你接受审查而已
is have you investigated.

831
00:38:30,190 --> 00:38:30,980
什么
What?

832
00:38:31,460 --> 00:38:33,340
我没跟劳伦上过床
I never actually slept with Lauren.

833
00:38:33,950 --> 00:38:35,060
但我知道你不会相信我
But I knew you'd never believe me

834
00:38:35,240 --> 00:38:36,470
所以我就没说
so I kept my mouth shut.

835
00:38:36,720 --> 00:38:38,460
现在既然她都要跟你离婚了
But now that she's getting a divorce,

836
00:38:38,660 --> 00:38:40,560
我就没必要再忍下去了
my policy no longer applies.

837
00:38:40,740 --> 00:38:43,870
当然  她中意谁  就可以跟谁约会
And of course, she's free to date whoever she pleases.

838
00:38:45,060 --> 00:38:46,010
而她中意的是我
And she pleases me.

839
00:38:48,130 --> 00:38:49,660
长夜漫漫  好好享受  唐纳德
Enjoy your evening, Donald.

840
00:39:13,450 --> 00:39:14,700
我总是听说这个地方
I've always heard about this place.

841
00:39:16,420 --> 00:39:17,700
《超级巨人》在哪个房间
Which room is Hoffa buried in?

842
00:39:18,850 --> 00:39:19,680
不清楚  但是...
Not sure, but...

843
00:39:20,050 --> 00:39:22,120
《盟约之弧》就在过道尽头左拐
The Arc of the Covenant's just down the hall on the left.

844
00:39:24,250 --> 00:39:25,270
这边忙完之后
When you're finished down here,

845
00:39:25,460 --> 00:39:26,450
你上楼来一趟
I'd like you to come upstairs

846
00:39:26,620 --> 00:39:28,470
给我整理一下和解笔录
and start putting together a settlement memorandum.

847
00:39:30,190 --> 00:39:32,390
-他们同意和解了吗  -多亏了你的主意
- They went for it? - Thanks to your idea.

848
00:39:33,410 --> 00:39:34,390
其实那也算不上是我的...
Well, I mean, it wasn't really my idea--

849
00:39:34,390 --> 00:39:36,220
他们同意出四亿美元进行和解
They're settling for 400 million.

850
00:39:36,410 --> 00:39:37,740
对  那的确是我的主意
Okay, yeah, that was my idea.

851
00:39:40,110 --> 00:39:41,700
这也意味着我保住工作了吧
So does this mean I get to keep my job?

852
00:39:41,930 --> 00:39:42,730
正想跟你谈这个
I wanna talk to you about that.

853
00:39:42,730 --> 00:39:43,570
在你开口之前  哈维  
Before you do, Harvey--

854
00:39:43,570 --> 00:39:44,500
我说话的时候
Do we have to have a conversation

855
00:39:44,500 --> 00:39:46,220
能不能不要一直打断我
about how you keep interrupting me?

856
00:39:48,350 --> 00:39:51,150
有些时候  人们拿枪指着你时
Look, sometimes when someone pulls a gun on you,

857
00:39:51,810 --> 00:39:54,270
枪里很可能根本没有子弹
instead of bullets it's filled with blanks.

858
00:39:55,260 --> 00:39:56,090
这是什么
What's this?

859
00:39:56,650 --> 00:39:58,200
你药检结果的副本
It's a copy of your drug test results.

860
00:39:59,330 --> 00:40:00,500
这上面说我通过药检了
But this says I passed.

861
00:40:00,660 --> 00:40:01,420
是通过了
You did.

862
00:40:03,560 --> 00:40:04,750
路易拿给我看的是伪造的
Louis showed me a fake?

863
00:40:05,520 --> 00:40:06,580
我打算去找他好好谈谈
I'm gonna go have a talk with him.

864
00:40:09,100 --> 00:40:11,390
不如让我自己去吧
You know what, why don't you let me do it?

865
00:40:12,740 --> 00:40:14,160
你觉得你有能力上桌谈判了吗
You think you're ready for the adult table?

866
00:40:14,770 --> 00:40:17,360
你没听说吗  我已经签下首位客户了
What, didn't you hear? I just landed my first client.

867
00:40:17,950 --> 00:40:19,220
没听说的话  我会直接去找路易
Why do you think I'm showing you this now

868
00:40:19,390 --> 00:40:20,850
而不是拖到现在才把这个给你
and not going straight to Louis?

869
00:40:24,640 --> 00:40:25,870
-友善点  -想得美
- Go easy on him. - Nope.

870
00:40:27,080 --> 00:40:27,910
孩子真棒
Good boy.

871
00:40:32,110 --> 00:40:32,830
你骗我
You lied.

872
00:40:33,350 --> 00:40:35,430
那天你给我看的药检结果是假的
That other drug test you showed me was a fake.

873
00:40:35,640 --> 00:40:36,570
你怎么发现的
How'd you figure that out?

874
00:40:36,820 --> 00:40:38,390
有人曾经告诉过我  对于重要文件
Someone once told me I have an eye for detail

875
00:40:38,580 --> 00:40:40,350
一定要关注细节
when it comes to important paperwork.

876
00:40:40,690 --> 00:40:42,100
或许你远不如自己所想的那么优秀
Well, maybe you're not as good as you think you are,

877
00:40:42,310 --> 00:40:43,350
要不然早就发现了
or you would've caught it sooner.

878
00:40:43,810 --> 00:40:45,510
好吧  这又算是哪门子测试
Okay, so this was all some sort of test?

879
00:40:46,320 --> 00:40:48,030
你威胁我  害我差点丢掉工作
You blackmail me, you jeopardize my job?

880
00:40:48,200 --> 00:40:50,060
迈克  停  停
Mike, stop. Stop.

881
00:40:50,250 --> 00:40:51,740
我们都获利了  不是吗
We all came out ahead, didn't we?

882
00:40:52,290 --> 00:40:53,890
新客户会给我们带来大笔收入
That new client's gonna bring us millions.

883
00:40:54,090 --> 00:40:55,530
而且杰西卡现在认识你这个人了
Jessica knows your name now.

884
00:40:55,720 --> 00:40:57,230
这是双赢
It's a win-win.

885
00:41:00,030 --> 00:41:00,810
话是没错
You're right.

886
00:41:02,050 --> 00:41:03,050
她确实知道我这个人了
She does know my name.

887
00:41:04,110 --> 00:41:05,970
所以我去告诉她实情的时候
Which is why she'll listen when I tell her

888
00:41:06,230 --> 00:41:07,640
她会听的
exactly what happened.

889
00:41:09,660 --> 00:41:10,900
好吧  但在那之前
Okay, but before you do that

890
00:41:11,590 --> 00:41:13,990
又到了...那什么的时间了
it is...That time again, isn't it?

891
00:41:15,350 --> 00:41:16,080
什么时间
What time?

892
00:41:16,860 --> 00:41:17,600
尿检时间
Pee in a cup time.

893
00:41:20,740 --> 00:41:21,950
你明知道我通不过的
And now you know I'd fail.

894
00:41:22,310 --> 00:41:23,420
当然  你可以选择去她那里
Of course, you can run to mommy,

895
00:41:23,610 --> 00:41:25,100
告知实情  碰碰运气
tell her your story, and take your chances.

896
00:41:25,300 --> 00:41:27,390
或是选择接受药检
Or you can take the test and trust

897
00:41:27,570 --> 00:41:30,580
信任我会对结果保密  以对你聊表谢意
that I'll keep it to myself as my way of thanking you.

898
00:41:43,150 --> 00:41:45,090
不过我也研究过
Ah, you know, I actually did some reading

899
00:41:45,280 --> 00:41:47,850
皮尔森·哈蒙药检政策
of the Pearson-Harmon Drug Policy as well.

900
00:41:48,510 --> 00:41:50,840
我发现两次药检之间
It turns out that you have to wait three months

901
00:41:51,020 --> 00:41:52,700
要间隔三个月
before you can request another drug test.

902
00:41:52,900 --> 00:41:54,540
瞧  这就是你漏掉的小细节
See, it's a little detail that you might've missed.

903
00:41:54,730 --> 00:41:55,900
一饮而尽吧
So, drink up.

904
00:41:58,900 --> 00:42:00,930
对了  我跟汤姆·凯勒谈过了
Oh, and I spoke to Tom Keller.

905
00:42:01,380 --> 00:42:03,100
他说  还是感觉由我和哈维
He says that he feels he'd be best served

906
00:42:03,290 --> 00:42:04,720
来做他的律师比较好
with a combination of me and Harvey.

907
00:42:05,500 --> 00:42:06,790
估计你明早就会接到电话了
I think you'll get that call in the morning.

