1
00:00:04,450 --> 00:00:05,620
我真搞不懂
I just don't understand.

2
00:00:05,620 --> 00:00:06,930
你搞不懂的事情多了
Yeah, there's a lot of things you don't understand.

3
00:00:06,930 --> 00:00:08,730
别人系的都是黑领带
Everyone is wearing a black tie.

4
00:00:08,800 --> 00:00:10,410
就你系了条灰的
You're wearing a gray tie.

5
00:00:10,410 --> 00:00:12,280
虽说这场合要求系黑领饰
This is acceptable at a black tie affair.

6
00:00:12,680 --> 00:00:14,460
但我这颜色也算不上出格
There's nothing wrong with the tie that I'm wearing.

7
00:00:14,460 --> 00:00:15,260
谢谢
Thank you.

8
00:00:16,230 --> 00:00:17,040
-您...  -好的  来一杯
- You-- - Yes, please.

9
00:00:17,040 --> 00:00:17,990
您要香槟吗  先生
Champagne, sir?

10
00:00:18,520 --> 00:00:22,800
这酒是法国产的吗
Is it? From the region? In France?

11
00:00:23,100 --> 00:00:25,010
如果不是  那就只能算是汽酒
Because if it's not, it's called sparkling wine,

12
00:00:25,040 --> 00:00:26,770
我可不喝汽酒
And I don't really drink sparkling wine.

13
00:00:27,120 --> 00:00:28,190
-算了  -别怪他
- Forget it. - Forgive him.

14
00:00:28,220 --> 00:00:31,090
他父母想生个女孩  他到现在都不能释怀
His parents really wanted a girl. Never got over it.

15
00:00:31,090 --> 00:00:32,600
产地不同  味道不同  能尝出来的
Wait a minute. You can taste the difference.

16
00:00:32,600 --> 00:00:33,530
我没瞧不起他
I'm not being a snob.

17
00:00:33,560 --> 00:00:34,540
没瞧不起他
Not a snob?

18
00:00:34,540 --> 00:00:35,790
你那语气和弗莱泽他弟弟似的
You sound like Frasier's brother.

19
00:00:34,540 --> 00:00:37,960
喜剧《欢乐一家亲》中的角色

20
00:00:35,830 --> 00:00:37,960
大家都误会奈尔斯·克雷恩了
Niles Crane was completely misunderstood.

21
00:00:37,960 --> 00:00:40,260
好了  二位  需要我叫个暂停吗
Okay, boys, you don't want me to give you a time-out now, do you?

22
00:00:40,260 --> 00:00:41,790
你要是能打他五十大板
Look, I'd be willing to stand in a corner

23
00:00:41,790 --> 00:00:43,490
我愿意去站墙角
if you agree to paddle his bottom.

24
00:00:43,660 --> 00:00:45,050
真搞笑  我觉得
That's hilarious. I'm just saying

25
00:00:45,050 --> 00:00:46,940
他们要是想让咱们捐钱
that if they want us to donate to their charity,

26
00:00:46,940 --> 00:00:48,150
起码也得有点诚意
they might as well step it up.

27
00:00:48,260 --> 00:00:49,830
让我甘愿掏腰包
You know, make me want to give away my money.

28
00:00:49,830 --> 00:00:50,610
你掏腰包
Your money?

29
00:00:50,800 --> 00:00:52,920
路易  你是代表律所出席的
You're here representing the firm, Louis.

30
00:00:52,990 --> 00:00:55,450
而且我们一直都热衷于慈善事业
And we've always been committed to giving back to the community.

31
00:00:55,560 --> 00:00:57,660
杰西卡  那不是...
Jessica, is that--

32
00:00:59,700 --> 00:01:01,700
是托莉  我一直都没联系她
Tori. Yes, and I owe her a call.

33
00:01:02,050 --> 00:01:03,110
失陪
Excuse me.

34
00:01:09,280 --> 00:01:10,870
我身上有香肠味吗
Do I smell like sausage?

35
00:01:11,400 --> 00:01:12,590
那不很正常吗  怎么了
No more than usual. Why?

36
00:01:12,630 --> 00:01:15,200
我要和未来的路易·利特太太见面了
Uh, because I'm about to meet the future Mrs. Louis Litt.

37
00:01:15,230 --> 00:01:16,730
我来之前吃了披萨  
I had pizza before I came and I just want to

38
00:01:16,730 --> 00:01:18,500
我怕身上会有味道
make sure I still am not emanating any aroma.

39
00:01:18,500 --> 00:01:20,210
你身上确实有种味道
Oh, you're emanating something.

40
00:01:20,720 --> 00:01:23,470
那叫信息激素  让女人无法抗拒
It's called pheromones and women find it irresistible.

41
00:01:26,270 --> 00:01:27,460
瞧好吧
Watch this.

42
00:01:32,440 --> 00:01:33,230
哈维
Harvey.

43
00:01:34,020 --> 00:01:35,360
你还记得托莉吗
You remember Tori?

44
00:01:35,450 --> 00:01:37,030
当然了  你好
Of course. Nice to see you.

45
00:01:37,030 --> 00:01:40,270
我跟杰西卡说  来参加慈善活动的时候
I told Jessica I don't really want to talk shop

46
00:01:40,270 --> 00:01:42,050
我不想谈公事
while we're here to support a good cause.

47
00:01:42,050 --> 00:01:43,790
预付佣金的好处就在于此
Well, that's the beautiful thing about a retainer.

48
00:01:43,820 --> 00:01:45,440
我们随时听你差遣
We're always on call when you need us.

49
00:01:45,560 --> 00:01:46,930
这次有什么要我们出马
So how can we help?

50
00:01:47,970 --> 00:01:51,040
这事牵扯到一位威信很高的高级副总裁
It involves one of our most trusted senior VPs.

51
00:01:51,040 --> 00:01:52,770
最近  他过去的一些事被人发现了
Something recently came to light about his past

52
00:01:52,800 --> 00:01:54,530
我真的非常震惊
and I'm shocked by it, really.

53
00:01:54,570 --> 00:01:57,500
你就说问题出在哪  我们会解决的
You tell us where it hurts and we'll make it go away.

54
00:02:10,330 --> 00:02:12,420
等等
Wait. Wait.

55
00:02:12,420 --> 00:02:13,530
-等等  -对
- Wait? - Yeah.

56
00:02:13,530 --> 00:02:14,820
只是...
Well, it's just...

57
00:02:15,720 --> 00:02:17,700
我觉得我们进度有点快了
This feels like it's moving really fast.

58
00:02:17,770 --> 00:02:19,150
要我慢点吗
I should slow down?

59
00:02:19,150 --> 00:02:20,460
不  我只是...我是说...
No, I just--I mean, like--

60
00:02:20,460 --> 00:02:23,360
我才结束一段感情...
I just got out of a relationship and...

61
00:02:23,360 --> 00:02:24,020
没错
Right.

62
00:02:24,130 --> 00:02:25,530
你也差不多
You kind of did too.

63
00:02:26,100 --> 00:02:27,780
我之前没有跟谁约会
I wasn't really seeing anyone.

64
00:02:27,810 --> 00:02:28,970
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.

65
00:02:30,560 --> 00:02:31,400
特雷弗
Trevor.

66
00:02:33,060 --> 00:02:33,670
对  特雷弗
Yeah, Trevor.

67
00:02:33,670 --> 00:02:35,170
对了  特雷弗
Right. Trevor.

68
00:02:37,880 --> 00:02:38,860
对  对  你说得对
Yeah, yeah, you're right.

69
00:02:38,860 --> 00:02:39,860
我们该慢点来
We should slow down.

70
00:02:42,120 --> 00:02:43,070
我去泡点茶
I should make us some tea.

71
00:02:43,070 --> 00:02:44,130
-想喝点茶吗  -想
- You want some tea? - Mm-hmm, yeah.

72
00:02:44,130 --> 00:02:45,100
好  我们喝茶吧
Yeah, let's drink some tea.

73
00:02:45,630 --> 00:02:46,480
谢谢
Thank you.

74
00:02:52,350 --> 00:02:53,920
法学院校友协会  诚邀您携伴前来参加
年度成员联谊会
时间  晚八点
地点  俱乐部壁炉室
着装  商业便装

75
00:02:52,900 --> 00:02:55,210
哈佛俱乐部是什么
What's the, uh, Harvard Club?

76
00:02:55,710 --> 00:02:59,730
就是...就是哈佛校友的俱乐部会所
Oh, it's, uh-- it's, like, this clubhouse for Harvard alumni.

77
00:03:00,030 --> 00:03:02,050
那个邀请函是...
Yeah, that invite is, uh--

78
00:03:02,470 --> 00:03:04,140
是为了律师之间联络感情的
It's for this networking thing for lawyers.

79
00:03:04,170 --> 00:03:05,370
我在公司拿到的
I got it at work.

80
00:03:05,410 --> 00:03:06,780
你会去吗
Hmm, would you go?

81
00:03:07,040 --> 00:03:08,450
什么  你开玩笑
What? Are you kidding me?

82
00:03:09,200 --> 00:03:10,050
不去
No.

83
00:03:10,210 --> 00:03:11,810
我在公司装相就够辛苦了
I have a hard enough time pretending at work.

84
00:03:11,850 --> 00:03:14,020
还要深入虎穴吗
It's not like I want to enter the lion's den.

85
00:03:17,880 --> 00:03:21,210
如果你要去的话...
Well, if you were gonna go...

86
00:03:22,580 --> 00:03:24,460
而你又打算带个伴去...
And you were gonna take a date--

87
00:03:24,460 --> 00:03:25,650
肯定是你
It would be you.

88
00:03:27,760 --> 00:03:29,160
我很乐意带你去
I'd love to take you.

89
00:03:35,420 --> 00:03:36,500
现在是谁进展得太快了
Who's moving too fast now?

90
00:03:36,540 --> 00:03:39,800
这是因为你说对了话
Oh, well, that's due to saying all the right things.

91
00:03:50,210 --> 00:03:51,660
什么事这么紧急
Hey, what's the emergency?

92
00:03:51,880 --> 00:03:53,440
没人跟你去舞会了吗
Couldn't find a date to the prom?

93
00:03:53,510 --> 00:03:55,080
我们要解雇斯坦·雅各布森
We're firing Stan Jacobson.

94
00:03:55,600 --> 00:03:56,230
谁
Who?

95
00:03:56,470 --> 00:03:58,470
雷贝克会计事务所的高级副总裁
Senior vice president, Drybeck Accounting.

96
00:03:59,160 --> 00:04:00,640
-我们的会计事务所吗  -没错
- Our accounting firm? - Yes.

97
00:04:00,640 --> 00:04:02,000
他们为我们做账  我们是他们的律师
They're our firm and our client.

98
00:04:02,030 --> 00:04:03,460
这怎么可能
How's that possible?

99
00:04:04,540 --> 00:04:06,380
他们签订了利益冲突弃权书
They signed a conflict of interest waiver.

100
00:04:06,390 --> 00:04:08,790
不错嘛  你小子终于懂法了
Look at that. He's actually learning how the law works.

101
00:04:09,160 --> 00:04:11,070
熟悉一下雷贝克的公司章程
Acquaint yourself with Drybeck's company charter

102
00:04:11,100 --> 00:04:13,140
和斯坦的原始雇佣合同
and Stan's original employment contract.

103
00:04:13,430 --> 00:04:15,180
-他做了什么  -撒谎
- What'd he do? - He lied.

104
00:04:15,650 --> 00:04:16,800
撒谎  在哪方面撒谎了
He lied? About what?

105
00:04:16,800 --> 00:04:19,070
等等  让我猜猜  他做假账了
Wait, let me guess. He cooked the books.

106
00:04:19,360 --> 00:04:20,580
天呐  现在华尔街还有人
God, doesn't anyone on Wall Street

107
00:04:20,580 --> 00:04:22,250
能诚诚恳恳地工作吗
put in an honest day's work anymore?

108
00:04:22,280 --> 00:04:25,300
实际上  他作为副总的工作非常出色
Actually, he's got a stellar record as a senior VP.

109
00:04:25,950 --> 00:04:27,620
他在简历里撒谎了
He lied on his resume.

110
00:04:27,890 --> 00:04:29,400
他没拿到注册会计师执照
Never got his CPA license.

111
00:04:29,400 --> 00:04:31,190
甚至没进过商学院
Never even went to business school.

112
00:04:32,070 --> 00:04:33,510
因为他在就读学校上撒了谎
He lied about where he went to school

113
00:04:33,510 --> 00:04:35,090
就要被解雇了吗
and now he's getting fired?

114
00:04:35,520 --> 00:04:38,230
雷贝克为半条华尔街做账
Drybeck does the books for half of Wall Street.

115
00:04:38,750 --> 00:04:40,960
如果高级职员是个骗子的事流传出去
Word gets out that a senior staff is a fraud,

116
00:04:40,960 --> 00:04:42,770
他们会损失客户
they're gonna start bleeding clients.

117
00:04:42,990 --> 00:04:45,240
我们得快速低调地解决这个问题
We have to do this fast and keep it quiet.

118
00:04:47,610 --> 00:04:48,590
放松
Relax.

119
00:04:48,970 --> 00:04:50,370
这不会发生在你身上
That's not gonna happen to you.

120
00:04:50,820 --> 00:04:53,140
但如果杰西卡知道了  我会被解雇的
But I would get fired if Jessica found out.

121
00:04:53,160 --> 00:04:54,150
知道什么
Found out what?

122
00:04:56,190 --> 00:04:57,750
他刚刚告诉我他是处男
Just told me he's a virgin.

123
00:04:58,410 --> 00:05:00,030
我一点不觉得惊奇呢
That doesn't surprise me one bit.

124
00:05:00,400 --> 00:05:01,770
该来的总会来  迈克
All in due time, Mike.

125
00:05:02,180 --> 00:05:03,730
你拿到遣散费的报价了吗
You have those severance quotes?

126
00:05:10,800 --> 00:05:14,800
■

127
00:05:10,800 --> 00:05:14,800
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
 更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

128
00:05:14,800 --> 00:05:18,800
■

129
00:05:14,800 --> 00:05:18,800
翻译：马蒂  草草  媛媛

130
00:05:18,800 --> 00:05:22,800
■

131
00:05:18,800 --> 00:05:22,800
时间轴：小怡子  潘叔  校对：饿得慌  桃乐

132
00:05:22,800 --> 00:05:26,800
■

133
00:05:22,800 --> 00:05:26,800
后期：飞飞是菇凉   总监：丢丢

134
00:05:34,890 --> 00:05:37,060
第一季 第十集

135
00:05:34,890 --> 00:05:37,060
诉 讼 双 雄

136
00:05:59,400 --> 00:06:00,640
你要去哪儿  美女
Oh, where you headed, doll?

137
00:06:01,090 --> 00:06:03,430
皮尔逊·哈德曼律所  找迈克·罗斯
Pearson Hardman to see Mike Ross.

138
00:06:03,670 --> 00:06:05,520
你们约好了吗
Uh, he expecting you?

139
00:06:05,870 --> 00:06:07,870
没有  我就是来给他送衣服的
No, I just was gonna drop this off.

140
00:06:07,920 --> 00:06:09,350
没预约  我不能放你上去
No appointment. I can't let you up.

141
00:06:10,370 --> 00:06:11,960
我长得像恐怖分子吗
Do I look like a terrorist?

142
00:06:11,960 --> 00:06:13,700
我长得像想丢掉饭碗吗
Do I look like I want to lose my job?

143
00:06:13,770 --> 00:06:14,510
珍妮
Jenny?

144
00:06:15,880 --> 00:06:16,460
瑞秋
Rachel.

145
00:06:16,460 --> 00:06:17,850
你是来找迈克的吗
Hey. You here to see Mike?

146
00:06:17,850 --> 00:06:18,770
差不多吧  我只是...
Sort of. I just--

147
00:06:18,770 --> 00:06:20,370
我本想把这套西装捎给他
I was gonna drop this suit off for him.

148
00:06:20,370 --> 00:06:21,780
哈维昨晚打电话找他
Harvey called late last night,

149
00:06:21,900 --> 00:06:23,050
出了什么紧急的大事
some big emergency,

150
00:06:23,080 --> 00:06:24,580
结果迈克一晚未归
And Mike ended up staying the night.

151
00:06:24,710 --> 00:06:26,720
你能帮帮我吗
Actually, could you help me out

152
00:06:26,720 --> 00:06:28,060
我上班要晚了
I'm running so late to work.

153
00:06:28,060 --> 00:06:28,810
没问题
Sure.

154
00:06:28,880 --> 00:06:30,010
我的天  谢谢你
Oh, my God. Thank you.

155
00:06:31,690 --> 00:06:32,430
谢谢
Thanks.

156
00:06:32,490 --> 00:06:33,480
-谢啦  -没问题
- Thank you. - Okay.

157
00:06:34,510 --> 00:06:37,460
你能告诉迈克我把钥匙留在垫子下面了吗
Oh! And can you tell Mike that I left the key under the mat?

158
00:06:37,930 --> 00:06:39,070
没问题
Absolutely.

159
00:06:39,370 --> 00:06:40,390
太感谢你了  瑞秋
Thank you so much, Rachel.

160
00:06:40,390 --> 00:06:41,590
-不客气  -你太好了
- You're welcome. - You're amazing.

161
00:07:03,540 --> 00:07:04,640
我起来了  起来了
I'm up. I'm up.

162
00:07:04,640 --> 00:07:06,110
你女朋友来过了
Your girlfriend stopped by.

163
00:07:06,430 --> 00:07:07,820
给你送这个来了
Dropped that off for you.

164
00:07:08,460 --> 00:07:09,200
女朋友
Girlfriend?

165
00:07:09,200 --> 00:07:10,660
你们都搬到一起住了吗
You guys move in together already?

166
00:07:10,880 --> 00:07:12,130
什么  没有
What? No.

167
00:07:12,130 --> 00:07:14,200
我们...她不是...你干嘛关心这个
We--she's not my-- why do you care?

168
00:07:14,200 --> 00:07:15,200
我不关心
I don't. What--

169
00:07:15,200 --> 00:07:16,890
昨晚出了什么重大的急事
What was the big emergency last night?

170
00:07:17,110 --> 00:07:18,500
哈维
Um, Harvey.

171
00:07:18,500 --> 00:07:21,320
他要解雇我们会计事务所的某个大副总
He's firing some big VP from our accounting firm this morning.

172
00:07:21,430 --> 00:07:23,070
斯坦·雅各布森吗
Stan Jacobson?

173
00:07:23,200 --> 00:07:24,820
没错  怎么  你认识他吗
Yeah, why? You know him?

174
00:07:24,850 --> 00:07:27,030
不  我到的时候  他刚好在接待处登记
No, he was just checking in at reception when I got there.

175
00:07:27,900 --> 00:07:29,730
天  我得换衣服了
Oh, God! I got to change.

176
00:07:30,790 --> 00:07:32,850
我告诉他你马上就到
I will let him know that you will be right there.

177
00:07:32,850 --> 00:07:33,960
谢谢
Thanks.

178
00:07:45,310 --> 00:07:47,520
业绩数据  人力资源方针
Performance numbers, HR guidelines,

179
00:07:47,520 --> 00:07:49,240
遣散费报价  斯坦在外面等着呢
severance quotes, and Stan's in the waiting room.

180
00:07:49,270 --> 00:07:50,290
你昨晚在这儿睡的吗
Did you sleep here last night?

181
00:07:50,290 --> 00:07:52,010
我觉得那不算是睡
I wouldn't exactly call it sleeping.

182
00:07:52,170 --> 00:07:53,200
西装哪来的
Where'd you get that suit?

183
00:07:53,200 --> 00:07:54,190
瑞秋拿来的
Uh, Rachel.

184
00:07:55,020 --> 00:07:57,660
不  是珍妮在楼下给瑞秋的
No, I mean Jenny gave it to Rachel downstairs.

185
00:07:57,680 --> 00:07:59,190
她昨晚去我家了
She slept over last night.

186
00:07:59,230 --> 00:08:00,660
珍妮  不是瑞秋
Jenny did, not Rachel.

187
00:08:01,030 --> 00:08:02,830
你解雇他的时候我真有必要在场吗
Do I really need to be here when you fire this guy?

188
00:08:02,830 --> 00:08:04,490
你想了解流程  不是吗
You want to learn how it's done, right?

189
00:08:04,820 --> 00:08:06,570
哈维  我读了这家伙的工作经历
I read this guy's employment records, Harvey.

190
00:08:06,570 --> 00:08:08,360
他聪明过人  才华横溢  忠心不二
He's smart, talented, loyal.

191
00:08:08,360 --> 00:08:09,440
你为他感到难过
Oh, and you feel bad for him.

192
00:08:09,440 --> 00:08:10,450
真让我震惊
I'm shocked.

193
00:08:10,800 --> 00:08:12,140
我要的铁证呢
Where's my smoking gun?

194
00:08:13,310 --> 00:08:15,880
能证明斯坦在文凭上撒谎的背景调查
Background check that confirmed Stan lied about his credentials.

195
00:08:15,880 --> 00:08:17,190
没拿到
It never came through.

196
00:08:18,230 --> 00:08:19,250
这就去
On it.

197
00:08:23,210 --> 00:08:23,950
进来  进来
Come in, come in.

198
00:08:23,950 --> 00:08:25,490
你能帮我个忙吗
Um, could you help me with something?

199
00:08:25,490 --> 00:08:27,080
我要帮哈维拿到一份传真
I need to get this fax for Harvey and it's--

200
00:08:27,110 --> 00:08:27,750
早上好
Good morning.

201
00:08:29,410 --> 00:08:30,920
早  他需要...
Good morning. He needs a--

202
00:08:30,920 --> 00:08:31,810
你能看出来  对吧
You can tell, can't you?

203
00:08:32,160 --> 00:08:33,390
我敢说大家都能看出来
I bet you everybody can.

204
00:08:34,530 --> 00:08:36,290
看得出什么
Tell what?

205
00:08:37,400 --> 00:08:39,960
你  修过眉毛了
You...wax your eyebrows?

206
00:08:39,990 --> 00:08:41,880
昨晚我和最美的女人共度良宵了
I was with the most beautiful woman last night.

207
00:08:43,640 --> 00:08:45,600
她帮你修眉毛吗
She wax your eyebrows?

208
00:08:45,640 --> 00:08:47,020
昨晚我们做了很多事
We did a lot of things last night

209
00:08:47,020 --> 00:08:49,460
但没修过眉毛
and waxing wasn't one of them,

210
00:08:49,470 --> 00:08:50,990
不知你是否明白我的意思
if you know what I mean.

211
00:08:51,930 --> 00:08:52,700
天呐
Oh, god.

212
00:08:52,700 --> 00:08:54,520
太棒了  我来是想问
That's great. I'm here to ask--

213
00:08:54,520 --> 00:08:56,750
她叫查丽丝  我们有很多相似之处
Her name's charisse and we have so much in common.

214
00:08:56,760 --> 00:08:58,490
迈克  这种感觉
And Mike, there was like this--

215
00:08:58,710 --> 00:08:59,840
感觉太美妙了
There was like this, "Mmm."

216
00:09:00,370 --> 00:09:02,190
爽翻了
Like a "Mmm."

217
00:09:02,190 --> 00:09:03,510
当我们身体接触时
Like a chemical thing would happen

218
00:09:03,510 --> 00:09:04,400
产生了化学反应
when our bodies would touch.

219
00:09:04,400 --> 00:09:06,630
不  我不想和你讨论这个问题
No, I really don't want to have this conversation with you.

220
00:09:06,630 --> 00:09:08,380
行了  我们都是爷们  不是吗
Oh, come on. We're both guys, right?

221
00:09:08,380 --> 00:09:09,890
在办公室讨论点私事
Little locker room talk around the office.

222
00:09:09,890 --> 00:09:11,230
就当是哥们之间促进感情
I mean, that creates a little male bonding.

223
00:09:11,230 --> 00:09:12,540
太诡异了  我好像听到有人喊我
That's crazy. I just heard my name.

224
00:09:12,650 --> 00:09:14,280
听到吗  有人在叫我
Did you hear that? Someone's calling me.

225
00:09:14,280 --> 00:09:16,320
我要  我去一下
I'm gonna-- just one second, okay?

226
00:09:18,010 --> 00:09:19,060
他八成还是个处男
He's probably still a virgin.

227
00:09:19,400 --> 00:09:21,030
雅各布森先生  你好
Mr. Jacobson, hi.

228
00:09:21,030 --> 00:09:22,240
迈克·罗斯  哈维助手
Mike Ross, Harvey's associate.

229
00:09:22,240 --> 00:09:23,300
抱歉让你等那么久
So sorry to keep you waiting.

230
00:09:23,300 --> 00:09:24,680
我马上就来  好吗
Just gonna be a couple more minutes, okay?

231
00:09:24,720 --> 00:09:26,020
很好  谢谢
Okay, great. Thank you.

232
00:09:27,620 --> 00:09:28,640
是的  我听到了
Yes, I hear you.

233
00:09:28,640 --> 00:09:30,150
你们公司找不到当时的复印件了
Your office couldn't find a copy.

234
00:09:30,440 --> 00:09:31,940
那能告诉我你们一般都找哪家保安公司
Can you tell me the name of the security firm

235
00:09:31,980 --> 00:09:33,580
来做背景调查吗
you guys used to do the background check?

236
00:09:34,950 --> 00:09:35,810
好的  很好
Okay, great.

237
00:09:35,810 --> 00:09:37,280
不用  很好
Nope. That's great.

238
00:09:37,280 --> 00:09:39,150
我自己找到电话号码了  谢谢 
I found the number myself. Thank you.

239
00:09:39,450 --> 00:09:40,530
莎莉  是的
Sally, yes.

240
00:09:40,530 --> 00:09:42,350
我是皮尔逊·哈德曼律所的迈克·罗斯
This is Mike Ross for Pearson Hardman.

241
00:09:42,350 --> 00:09:43,150
我打电话来是想
I'm calling regarding

242
00:09:43,150 --> 00:09:44,750
询问一下你们之前做的背景调查
a background check you guys did.

243
00:09:45,490 --> 00:09:46,460
当然
Sure.

244
00:09:46,460 --> 00:09:47,920
你可以拒绝透露任何信息
You could refuse to cooperate,

245
00:09:47,960 --> 00:09:50,420
但你可能会因此闯祸
but then you would be wrong.

246
00:09:50,420 --> 00:09:52,390
莎莉  稍等片刻
Sally, hold on one minute.

247
00:09:52,930 --> 00:09:53,590
喂
Yeah?

248
00:09:53,640 --> 00:09:57,300
不  斯坦两分钟后就到
No. Stan is going to be there in two minutes.

249
00:09:57,300 --> 00:09:59,020
他去厕所了  好的
He's in the bathroom. Okay.

250
00:10:01,890 --> 00:10:02,780
莎莉  还在吗
Sally, you there?

251
00:10:03,220 --> 00:10:04,140
这样吧
Let's do this.

252
00:10:04,140 --> 00:10:06,410
我现在把我手上的传票
I'm gonna fax you the subpoena

253
00:10:06,410 --> 00:10:08,000
传真给你
that I'm holding in my hand right now

254
00:10:08,000 --> 00:10:10,060
给你们老板看一下  然后...
And you can show that to your boss and then we--

255
00:10:12,390 --> 00:10:13,250
太好了
Great.

256
00:10:13,920 --> 00:10:16,050
我现在把我的传真号码发给你
Let me send you my fax number now.

257
00:10:17,650 --> 00:10:18,470
很好
Nice.

258
00:10:27,900 --> 00:10:28,740
斯坦
Stan.

259
00:10:29,250 --> 00:10:31,290
我们可以开始了吗
We ready?

260
00:10:31,320 --> 00:10:32,660
是的  我很抱歉
Yes. I'm sorry about that.

261
00:10:32,810 --> 00:10:33,650
没关系
No worries.

262
00:10:34,210 --> 00:10:35,370
顺便说一句  我认识你
I know you, by the way.

263
00:10:36,510 --> 00:10:38,500
7611053
7611053.

264
00:10:40,120 --> 00:10:41,270
你的员工编号
Your employee code.

265
00:10:41,490 --> 00:10:42,810
每个人在我脑子里都是一串号码
See, I remember everyone that way.

266
00:10:42,850 --> 00:10:45,100
好了  你要带我去见哈维吧
Anyway, you are taking me to see harvey.

267
00:10:45,100 --> 00:10:46,520
我等不及了
I have been dying to meet him.

268
00:10:47,270 --> 00:10:48,030
为什么
Why is that?

269
00:10:48,030 --> 00:10:49,080
他的球
His balls.

270
00:10:50,580 --> 00:10:52,410
他的明星签名棒球  我是个超级棒球粉丝
His autographed ones. I'm a huge baseball fan.

271
00:10:52,410 --> 00:10:53,840
没错  是吗
Right. Really?

272
00:10:53,840 --> 00:10:54,710
当然了
Oh, yeah, yeah. No.

273
00:10:54,710 --> 00:10:55,840
如果我不是会计的话
If I wasn't an accountant,

274
00:10:55,950 --> 00:10:57,350
我肯定会成为大联盟球探
I would be a major league scout.

275
00:10:57,350 --> 00:10:58,670
我只要看一眼相关数据
I can tell you anything you want to know

276
00:10:58,670 --> 00:11:00,440
就能知道他的底细
just by looking at somebody's numbers.

277
00:11:00,490 --> 00:11:01,830
比如  看一眼击球次数
For instance, slugging percentage

278
00:11:01,830 --> 00:11:03,900
再对比下春训三振出局次数
versus strikeouts during spring training--

279
00:11:03,900 --> 00:11:05,400
边走边说如何
Do you want to walk and talk maybe?

280
00:11:10,980 --> 00:11:11,830
斯坦·雅各布森
Stan Jacobson.

281
00:11:11,830 --> 00:11:14,070
斯佩克特先生  见到你很高兴
Mr. Specter, it is a pleasure.

282
00:11:14,070 --> 00:11:15,280
斯坦  很高兴见到你
Stan, it's nice to meet you.

283
00:11:15,280 --> 00:11:16,450
-迈克是不是  -我的天
- Has Mike alr-- - Oh, my god!

284
00:11:17,040 --> 00:11:19,290
我的老天  是它们吗
Oh, my god! Is that them?

285
00:11:19,830 --> 00:11:22,740
哇  基特
Oh! Jeter.

286
00:11:19,830 --> 00:11:22,740
德瑞克·基特:21岁时便成为美国职棒大联盟选手

287
00:11:22,960 --> 00:11:24,590
汉克·阿伦
Hank Aaron.

288
00:11:22,960 --> 00:11:24,590
汉克·阿伦:前美国职棒名将  全垒打王

289
00:11:24,590 --> 00:11:27,270
不会吧  马里斯
No way! Maris?

290
00:11:24,590 --> 00:11:27,270
罗杰·马里斯:前美国职棒名将  年度最有价值球员

291
00:11:27,270 --> 00:11:28,970
那不是61号球吧
That's not number 61, is it?

292
00:11:28,980 --> 00:11:30,340
不是  但上面的签名是特雷西
No, but it was signed by Tracy--

293
00:11:30,340 --> 00:11:32,160
斯塔勒德
Stallard.

294
00:11:30,340 --> 00:11:32,160
特雷西·斯塔勒德:前美国职棒名将

295
00:11:33,330 --> 00:11:34,800
超级棒球迷
Big baseball fan.

296
00:11:35,000 --> 00:11:36,960
斯坦  过来这边坐吧
Stan, why don't you have a seat over here?

297
00:11:37,110 --> 00:11:38,840
我去倒些水吧
Why don't I get us some waters?

298
00:11:39,450 --> 00:11:40,280
抱歉
Sorry.

299
00:11:40,780 --> 00:11:43,190
一说到棒球  我就停不下来了
I get talking about baseball, I cannot stop.

300
00:11:44,150 --> 00:11:46,100
我知道你的时间很宝贵
I know how valuable your time is.

301
00:11:46,100 --> 00:11:47,270
我查账非常专业
I do do the books.

302
00:11:48,280 --> 00:11:50,390
说到这个  你的助手告诉我
And speaking of which, your assistant tells me

303
00:11:50,390 --> 00:11:52,990
你想再核查一下你上一次的审计结果
you wanted to go over something from your last audits.

304
00:11:52,990 --> 00:11:54,420
我还是去倒水吧
I could really use a water.

305
00:11:56,380 --> 00:11:59,470
斯坦  请你来不是要让你来查账的
Stan, we're not here to go over any accounting business.

306
00:11:59,470 --> 00:12:01,180
而是要解雇你
You're here because you're being let go.

307
00:12:02,910 --> 00:12:03,610
什么
What?

308
00:12:04,170 --> 00:12:05,420
知道原因后
It's not gonna feel that surprising

309
00:12:05,420 --> 00:12:06,700
你就不会这么吃惊了
when you understand why.

310
00:12:07,070 --> 00:12:09,010
你公司最近调查了你的背景资料
The firm looked into your background recently.

311
00:12:09,010 --> 00:12:11,650
他们查到你根本没通过注册会计师考试
They know you lied about passing the CPA exam.

312
00:12:11,660 --> 00:12:14,490
他们雇佣你是因为你出色的证书成绩
You were hired because of your outstanding credentials

313
00:12:14,640 --> 00:12:16,890
而事实是  你根本没拿到证书
And the reality is they never existed.

314
00:12:21,640 --> 00:12:23,220
我已经在那工作九年了
I've been there for nine years.

315
00:12:24,180 --> 00:12:25,560
我的业绩都不算了吗
My work has been nothing but--

316
00:12:26,980 --> 00:12:28,100
证书有那么重要吗
I mean, why would this even matter now?

317
00:12:28,100 --> 00:12:30,600
你的整个职业生涯都在谎言中渡过
You have been committing fraud your entire career.

318
00:12:30,600 --> 00:12:31,360
由此带来的后果...
The liability it presents--

319
00:12:31,360 --> 00:12:32,970
不  我不接受这个
No! I don't accept this.

320
00:12:33,380 --> 00:12:34,470
好吧  深呼吸
Okay, take a deep breath.

321
00:12:34,550 --> 00:12:36,180
看一下遣散费的数目
Once you go over the severance numbers,

322
00:12:36,250 --> 00:12:38,610
你就知道我们的决策是相当公平的
you'll see that we've been more than fair.

323
00:12:39,920 --> 00:12:40,870
公平
Fair?

324
00:12:42,190 --> 00:12:43,530
你觉得这样公平吗
You think this is fair?

325
00:12:44,120 --> 00:12:46,730
我们知道你很难接受  斯坦
We understand how difficult this must be, Stan.

326
00:12:46,730 --> 00:12:48,100
我们理解你现在的感受
How you must feel right now.

327
00:12:48,100 --> 00:12:50,160
你们根本无法体会我此刻的心情
You have no idea what I feel right now.

328
00:12:52,660 --> 00:12:53,450
让我确认一下
Just so I'm clear--

329
00:12:53,450 --> 00:12:55,540
你不否认我们对你的举证吗
You're not denying what we're presenting you with?

330
00:12:56,860 --> 00:12:59,440
你是说雷贝克雇佣我的时候  
You mean that I lied back

331
00:12:59,440 --> 00:13:00,580
我对他们撒谎了吗
when Drybeck hired me?

332
00:13:04,750 --> 00:13:05,500
是的
No.

333
00:13:06,960 --> 00:13:08,320
但我也不完全是个骗子啊
But I'm not some scam artist either.

334
00:13:08,320 --> 00:13:09,220
我确实上过大学啊
I did go to college.

335
00:13:09,220 --> 00:13:12,040
我只是付不起学费  辍学罢了
I just couldn't afford to graduate.

336
00:13:12,040 --> 00:13:13,300
因为我在数字方面的突出才能
No one ever questioned it before

337
00:13:13,300 --> 00:13:14,730
从来没人怀疑过我
because I'm that good with numbers.

338
00:13:18,890 --> 00:13:20,280
然后就一下子东窗事发了
Then they find out all of a sudden.

339
00:13:22,040 --> 00:13:22,950
他们不是一下子发现的
They didn't.

340
00:13:25,490 --> 00:13:28,140
这份背景调查是五年前的了
This background check is five years old.

341
00:13:28,950 --> 00:13:29,830
什么
What?

342
00:13:30,360 --> 00:13:31,450
这说不通啊
That doesn't make sense.

343
00:13:32,300 --> 00:13:33,380
这份是原件吗
Is this the original?

344
00:13:33,380 --> 00:13:34,110
是的
Yeah.

345
00:13:35,020 --> 00:13:37,720
这么说托莉一直都知道
So Tori knew all this time?

346
00:13:40,530 --> 00:13:42,270
宝拉之前也是这个下场
This is the same thing that happened to Paula.

347
00:13:42,890 --> 00:13:44,380
-谁  -宝拉
- Who? - Paula.

348
00:13:44,900 --> 00:13:46,330
她发现了一些私密收益
Discovered some undisclosed income,

349
00:13:46,370 --> 00:13:48,560
却没记在账本上  她跟我说了这件事
the books weren't adding up, she brought it to me.

350
00:13:48,580 --> 00:13:50,320
紧接着  她就被辞了
The next thing I know, she is gone.

351
00:13:50,350 --> 00:13:51,360
我问过托莉这件事
I asked Tori about it,

352
00:13:51,360 --> 00:13:52,980
然后我就被踢出公司会议了
then I start getting shut out of meetings.

353
00:13:52,980 --> 00:13:53,810
他们有不可告人的秘密
They're trying to hide something

354
00:13:53,810 --> 00:13:55,460
所以要除掉我这块绊脚石
and they're firing me so they can.

355
00:13:55,810 --> 00:13:57,230
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?

356
00:13:57,230 --> 00:13:58,340
我不会签任何协议
I'm not signing some agreement.

357
00:13:58,340 --> 00:13:59,150
给我听清楚了
Are you kidding me?

358
00:13:59,620 --> 00:14:01,210
我会揭发他们的
I'm getting railroaded!

359
00:14:02,110 --> 00:14:03,910
-要我去追他吗  -不用
- Should I go after him? - No.

360
00:14:04,020 --> 00:14:05,520
你做得还不够多吗
You've done enough already.

361
00:14:11,970 --> 00:14:13,760
你就这么让他走了吗
So you let him leave?

362
00:14:13,930 --> 00:14:16,880
强制拘留不属于我的工作范畴
Physically restraining someone is not in my job description.

363
00:14:17,570 --> 00:14:19,160
那你的助手呢
What about your associate,

364
00:14:19,310 --> 00:14:21,230
泄露了背景调查资料的那家伙
the one who shared the background check?

365
00:14:21,270 --> 00:14:23,580
那可是内部保密文件
That was a confidential internal document.

366
00:14:23,580 --> 00:14:25,040
斯坦根本不该看到
Stan should have never seen it.

367
00:14:25,040 --> 00:14:26,340
你们又是怎么得到的
Why did you even have it?

368
00:14:26,340 --> 00:14:28,910
你也知道我们不可能无凭无据开除他
You didn't expect us to fire him without proof, did you?

369
00:14:28,910 --> 00:14:31,320
托莉说得对  斯坦不应该看到文件
Tori's right. Stan shouldn't have seen it.

370
00:14:31,320 --> 00:14:32,980
那你们是怪我做事太仔细了
Then I'm guilty of being thorough.

371
00:14:32,980 --> 00:14:35,500
我还是不明白  你为什么不告诉我事情的真相
I still don't understand why you haven't told us the whole truth.

372
00:14:35,500 --> 00:14:37,200
如果你五年前就查过他背景
I mean, if you knew five years ago,

373
00:14:37,200 --> 00:14:39,000
为什么还要搞得像是最近查的
why'd you make it sound like this is something recent?

374
00:14:39,000 --> 00:14:41,140
因为这事两天前才引起我的注意
Because it only came to my attention two days ago.

375
00:14:41,140 --> 00:14:42,470
那又是谁让做的背景调查
Then who ordered the background check?

376
00:14:42,470 --> 00:14:45,080
这是人力资源部的例行公事
It's routine. You check with human resources.

377
00:14:45,080 --> 00:14:46,910
人力资源部还负责
Is it routine for human resources

378
00:14:46,910 --> 00:14:49,550
向总裁隐瞒事实长达五年之久吗
to keep something from the ceo for half a decade?

379
00:14:49,570 --> 00:14:51,330
你这话什么意思
What are you insinuating?

380
00:14:52,730 --> 00:14:54,820
我想哈维是想说
I think what harvey is saying is given

381
00:14:54,820 --> 00:14:57,130
我们想尽快处理好这件事
how quickly we tried to accomplish this,

382
00:14:57,450 --> 00:14:59,360
可能被忽略了某些细节问题
some of the details might have gotten lost.

383
00:14:59,360 --> 00:15:02,460
你们还忘了  斯坦还没签离职补偿协议
What was also lost is that Stan never signed the severance package,

384
00:15:02,460 --> 00:15:04,530
包括里面的一份保密协议
which included the confidentiality agreement,

385
00:15:04,530 --> 00:15:06,220
他一旦想要把事情弄大
Which means if he decides to make waves,

386
00:15:06,220 --> 00:15:08,330
我们之前所说的避免公司形象受损就...
the whole point of avoiding negative publicity--

387
00:15:08,330 --> 00:15:10,460
哈维会找到斯坦
Harvey will track down Stan

388
00:15:10,460 --> 00:15:13,060
确保他今天就会签署离职补偿协议
and make sure that he signs the severance package

389
00:15:13,060 --> 00:15:15,450
和保密协议
and the confidentiality agreement today.

390
00:15:16,510 --> 00:15:17,700
我保证
You have my word.

391
00:15:19,570 --> 00:15:20,400
谢谢
Thank you.

392
00:15:20,680 --> 00:15:21,570
愿意效劳
Of course.

393
00:15:27,290 --> 00:15:28,900
没事的  托莉
It's allight, Tori.

394
00:15:33,120 --> 00:15:34,000
她在撒谎
She's lying.

395
00:15:34,060 --> 00:15:34,960
她知道斯坦的背景
She knew about Stan.

396
00:15:34,960 --> 00:15:36,330
很早就知道了
She's known for a long time.

397
00:15:36,330 --> 00:15:37,950
这关我们什么事
And that matters to us why?

398
00:15:37,950 --> 00:15:39,580
她在利用我们
Because she's taking advantage of us.

399
00:15:39,580 --> 00:15:41,550
我们无缘无故帮她解雇员工
We are being manipulated into firing

400
00:15:41,550 --> 00:15:44,070
还不准问问题
one of her employees and told not to ask questions.

401
00:15:44,070 --> 00:15:45,420
我问题可多着呢
Well, I have questions.

402
00:15:45,590 --> 00:15:47,790
答案是1000
And the answer is ten.

403
00:15:48,270 --> 00:15:50,840
雷贝克公司每年为我们公司
As in $10 million per year,

404
00:15:50,990 --> 00:15:54,320
谋得1000万的利润
the amount of business Drybeck generates for this firm.

405
00:15:54,420 --> 00:15:57,190
所以你得妥当处理此事
Which means you have to finish what you started.

406
00:15:57,380 --> 00:16:00,190
找到斯坦  说服他签署那些文件
Find Stan and get him to sign those documents.

407
00:16:00,920 --> 00:16:02,260
我个人认为
And as far as I'm concerned,

408
00:16:02,260 --> 00:16:04,570
你的助理要为这事负责
that little associate of yours is to blame for all of this.

409
00:16:04,570 --> 00:16:05,900
那是无心之过
That was an honest mistake.

410
00:16:05,900 --> 00:16:09,650
他明知那是客户的机密文件  还泄露了出去
He knowingly revealed the client's confidential document.

411
00:16:09,760 --> 00:16:11,740
那不叫失误
That is not a mistake.

412
00:16:13,160 --> 00:16:15,020
你还要给那孩子多少次机会
How many more chances are you gonna give that kid?

413
00:16:15,240 --> 00:16:17,440
我不知道我们还计分呢
Oh, I didn't realize we were keeping score.

414
00:16:17,790 --> 00:16:20,210
就算这么说  他也还是遥遥领先
But if that's the case, I still think he's coming out ahead.

415
00:16:31,180 --> 00:16:32,710
停下你手中的活
Whatever you're doing, stop.

416
00:16:32,710 --> 00:16:34,030
等等  这个你会感兴趣的
Wait, you're gonna want to see this.

417
00:16:34,280 --> 00:16:37,040
宝拉·奥尼尔  斯坦提到的那个雷贝克前雇员
Paula O'Neil, the former Drybeck employee that Stan mentioned,

418
00:16:37,040 --> 00:16:38,980
她控告公司不正当解雇
she filed a wrongful termination suit

419
00:16:38,980 --> 00:16:40,700
事情神秘地不了了之
that mysteriously went away.

420
00:16:40,840 --> 00:16:42,180
是吗  我看看
Really? Let me see that.

421
00:16:45,350 --> 00:16:46,300
跟我来
Come with me.

422
00:16:49,000 --> 00:16:51,210
等等  你不觉得这里面有猫腻吗
Wait. Do you not think something funny's going on?

423
00:16:51,210 --> 00:16:52,710
告诉你  我觉得现在的情况是
You know what? Here's what I think is going on.

424
00:16:52,710 --> 00:16:54,970
你同情斯坦  觉得你们同命相连
You're sympathizing with Stan because you think he's you.

425
00:16:54,970 --> 00:16:55,930
那也不代表...
That doesn't mean that--

426
00:16:55,930 --> 00:16:57,890
你要从刚刚发生的事中吸取教训
You need to learn something from what just happened,

427
00:16:57,890 --> 00:16:59,810
最起码也该明白  任何人
not the least of which is how anyone,

428
00:16:59,810 --> 00:17:01,840
不管多么有价值  都可能被解雇
no matter how valuable, can be let go.

429
00:17:01,840 --> 00:17:03,780
我可以把跟斯坦发生的小插曲
I can chalk up what happened with Stan

430
00:17:03,780 --> 00:17:06,290
归咎为你年轻气盛  但杰西卡不这么想
to youthful exuberance, but Jessica can't.

431
00:17:06,380 --> 00:17:08,430
你要是还想在这儿工作  现在就先回家
So if you want to work here, you better go home now,

432
00:17:08,430 --> 00:17:09,380
-她要是见到你  -慢着
- because if she sees you-- - Wait, wait.

433
00:17:09,380 --> 00:17:10,170
她要解雇我吗
Is she gonna fire me?

434
00:17:10,170 --> 00:17:12,720
你对每个客户都同情心泛滥的习惯
This habit of you empathizing with every client,

435
00:17:12,720 --> 00:17:14,180
对你没有好处
it's not getting you anywhere.

436
00:17:14,930 --> 00:17:16,280
你想在这家公司工作
You want to work in this firm?

437
00:17:16,380 --> 00:17:20,110
就得学会只和可靠的事实  证据和信息打交道
You need to deal in facts, evidence, information that can hold up.

438
00:17:20,760 --> 00:17:22,600
这才是真正的律师的做法
That's what a real lawyer does.

439
00:17:40,280 --> 00:17:41,160
斯坦
Stan.

440
00:17:43,690 --> 00:17:45,130
你跟踪我到这儿的吗
Did you follow me here?

441
00:17:45,360 --> 00:17:47,030
不用猜都知道
Doesn't take a sleuth to figure out

442
00:17:47,030 --> 00:17:49,320
你下一步要再找个律师
that your next step would be to see another lawyer.

443
00:17:49,810 --> 00:17:51,300
鲍珀·威廉姆斯律所
Bopal and Williams.

444
00:17:52,290 --> 00:17:54,650
这公司不错  不过不太友好
They're a good firm. Not the friendliest bunch.

445
00:17:54,740 --> 00:17:55,510
他们给你打电话了
They called you.

446
00:17:55,510 --> 00:17:56,900
那可违反律师委托人保密协议
That is against lawyer-client privilege.

447
00:17:57,000 --> 00:17:58,590
没人违反什么
No one's breaking any laws, okay?

448
00:17:58,590 --> 00:18:00,850
我的助理与其他的助理间有联系
My assistant has a network of other assistants

449
00:18:00,850 --> 00:18:02,510
他们什么都会跟她说
that tell her anything she wants to know,

450
00:18:02,510 --> 00:18:04,990
比如说有人打电话来做紧急预约
like when someone calls for an emergency appointment.

451
00:18:05,180 --> 00:18:06,730
你走的时候忘拿这个了
You forgot this when you left.

452
00:18:06,730 --> 00:18:08,380
我说了我什么都不签
I said I'm not signing anything.

453
00:18:08,380 --> 00:18:09,700
不是让你签
It's nothing to sign.

454
00:18:10,150 --> 00:18:11,220
这是诉讼
It's a lawsuit.

455
00:18:12,050 --> 00:18:14,120
你为雷贝克工作九年
You worked for Drybeck for 9 years,

456
00:18:14,180 --> 00:18:17,330
管理80位客户  做过数百份纳税申报单
oversaw 80 clients, filed hundreds of tax returns,

457
00:18:17,330 --> 00:18:19,010
并做过27次审计
and fought 27 audits.

458
00:18:19,210 --> 00:18:21,880
但鉴于你最近被发现的欺诈行为
Now, in light of your recently discovered fraud,

459
00:18:21,930 --> 00:18:24,090
这些都值得质疑
all of that can now be called into question.

460
00:18:24,090 --> 00:18:27,650
因此  我们要追回你这九年的欠薪
Therefore, you are being sued for nine years back pay,

461
00:18:27,810 --> 00:18:30,760
外加为弥补你的过失所消耗的经费
plus any expenses incurred to mitigate the damage you've done.

462
00:18:31,550 --> 00:18:32,390
那...
This is--

463
00:18:34,360 --> 00:18:35,520
那会让我破产的
This would bankrupt me.

464
00:18:35,520 --> 00:18:37,790
或者你可以走第二条路
Or you can take what's behind door number two.

465
00:18:41,870 --> 00:18:43,950
-是因为阿伯丁  -谁
- It's Aberdeen. - Who?

466
00:18:44,190 --> 00:18:45,540
那不是个人  而是家公司
It's not a "who." It's a "what."

467
00:18:45,640 --> 00:18:46,820
雷贝克在和他们做生意
Drybeck is doing business with them

468
00:18:46,820 --> 00:18:48,170
我觉得问题就出在那儿
and I think that's where the problem lies.

469
00:18:48,170 --> 00:18:49,270
你不懂
You don't get it, okay?

470
00:18:49,410 --> 00:18:51,210
你只有这两条路
I'm only leaving with one of these,

471
00:18:51,210 --> 00:18:52,680
你要是想上法庭
and if it's the lawsuit,

472
00:18:52,760 --> 00:18:54,360
你楼上的朋友
the first thing your friends upstairs

473
00:18:54,360 --> 00:18:56,630
首先就会让你付一笔高额聘金
are gonna ask you for is a big, fat retainer.

474
00:18:56,630 --> 00:18:57,380
而等你告诉他们
And when you tell them

475
00:18:57,380 --> 00:18:59,550
是哈维·斯佩克特要告你
that Harvey Specter is the one that's suing you,

476
00:18:59,550 --> 00:19:01,570
你就会看到他们瞬间面无血色
you're gonna watch the color drain from their faces.

477
00:19:01,570 --> 00:19:02,800
你到底想要怎么做
Now what would you like to do?

478
00:19:09,170 --> 00:19:10,540
这样可不太好
This is not cool.

479
00:19:10,800 --> 00:19:12,440
你整晚把我扔在你的公寓
You leave me in your apartment all night

480
00:19:12,440 --> 00:19:13,820
还说你会马上回来
and say you're gonna be right back.

481
00:19:13,830 --> 00:19:15,770
我去给你送西装你都不谢谢我
You don't even thank me for dropping off your suit.

482
00:19:15,770 --> 00:19:17,230
我今天不顺利  珍妮
I had a bad day, Jenny.

483
00:19:17,840 --> 00:19:19,060
那你就不能给我打个电话吗
So you couldn't call me?

484
00:19:19,060 --> 00:19:20,720
我差点被炒鱿鱼了
I almost got fired, okay?

485
00:19:21,410 --> 00:19:22,340
怎么回事
What happened?

486
00:19:23,000 --> 00:19:25,090
没什么好说的
It--it's not worth explaining.

487
00:19:27,090 --> 00:19:28,800
好吧  我需要找到证据
Okay. I need to find evidence

488
00:19:28,800 --> 00:19:30,290
证明我们的会计事务所图谋不轨
that our accounting firm is up to something,

489
00:19:30,290 --> 00:19:33,110
我找到了一个控告他们不正当解雇的女人
so I found this woman who filed a wrongful termination suit

490
00:19:33,110 --> 00:19:34,880
但她让我去找她的律师
against them, but then she referred me to her lawyer.

491
00:19:34,880 --> 00:19:36,010
你找过了吗
Did you call them?

492
00:19:36,010 --> 00:19:37,400
找了  可他们是家大事务所
Yeah, but they're this huge firm.

493
00:19:37,400 --> 00:19:38,570
安格·梅西律所
Unger and Macy.

494
00:19:38,570 --> 00:19:40,330
他们不接我电话
They wouldn't take my call.

495
00:19:40,510 --> 00:19:41,460
为什么
Why not?

496
00:19:41,870 --> 00:19:44,890
首先  和解条件里有保密条款
There's a confidentiality clause in the settlement, for one.

497
00:19:44,910 --> 00:19:45,720
那又如何
So?

498
00:19:46,220 --> 00:19:49,730
这就意味着他们不能泄露那类信息
So it means that they can't share details like that.

499
00:19:49,730 --> 00:19:52,190
我以为这些事律师都会私底下交流呢
You know, I thought all lawyers secretly shared that stuff.

500
00:19:52,700 --> 00:19:54,910
你们都去同一家俱乐部  不是吗
You're all in the same club, right?

501
00:19:56,970 --> 00:19:58,930
怎么了  这么想也不算傻吧
What? That's not a dumb thing to assume.

502
00:19:58,930 --> 00:19:59,770
不不不
No, no, no, no.

503
00:19:59,770 --> 00:20:02,240
一点也不傻
That's not dumb at all, because...

504
00:20:03,770 --> 00:20:05,780
年度成员联谊会

505
00:20:06,580 --> 00:20:08,710
安格·梅西律所的哈佛毕业生人数
Unger and Macy have almost as many Harvard grads

506
00:20:08,710 --> 00:20:09,980
跟我们差不多  这就是说...
as we do, which means--

507
00:20:09,980 --> 00:20:11,080
他们也会去今晚的联谊会
They're gonna be at the mixer tonight.

508
00:20:11,080 --> 00:20:13,460
而律师最爱做两件事
And there are two things that lawyers love to do.

509
00:20:13,460 --> 00:20:15,000
开怀畅饮  高谈阔论
Drink and talk.

510
00:20:17,680 --> 00:20:18,430
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.

511
00:20:18,430 --> 00:20:21,520
我叫迈克·罗斯  2011届毕业生
Uh, Mike Ross, class of 2011.

512
00:20:21,590 --> 00:20:22,300
罗斯
Ross.

513
00:20:22,790 --> 00:20:24,170
抱歉  你不在名单上
Sorry, I don't have you on here.

514
00:20:24,170 --> 00:20:24,980
你带身份证了吗
Do you have your I.D.?

515
00:20:24,980 --> 00:20:26,300
我可以在电脑里查一下
I can n it through the computer.

516
00:20:26,460 --> 00:20:28,260
我的哈佛证件吗
Uh, my Harvard I.D.?

517
00:20:28,520 --> 00:20:30,150
你说你叫什么来着
What did you say your name was again?

518
00:20:30,790 --> 00:20:33,390
皮尔逊·哈德曼律所的迈克·罗斯
Michael Ross of Pearson Hardman.

519
00:20:34,240 --> 00:20:35,690
天啊  你说哈维来时
Boy, you think they ask Harvey

520
00:20:35,690 --> 00:20:37,660
他们还会查他的身份证吗
for his I.D. when he comes to this place?

521
00:20:38,290 --> 00:20:39,290
哈维·斯佩克特
Harvey Specter?

522
00:20:39,900 --> 00:20:42,050
你跟哈维·斯佩克特一起工作吗
You work with Harvey Specter?

523
00:20:43,070 --> 00:20:44,530
是的
Uh, yeah, yes.

524
00:20:44,530 --> 00:20:45,610
我是他的助理律师
I'm his associate.

525
00:20:46,100 --> 00:20:47,460
如果你需要  我可以给他打个电话
I can call him if you like.

526
00:20:47,530 --> 00:20:50,040
不要告诉他我给你带来了不便  好吗
Just don't tell him I gave you any trouble, okay?

527
00:20:51,560 --> 00:20:52,440
请进
Welcome.

528
00:20:52,850 --> 00:20:53,800
谢谢
Thank you.

529
00:20:56,440 --> 00:20:58,480
天呐  我肯定会死得很难看
Oh, God. I'm never gonna survive this.

530
00:20:58,640 --> 00:21:00,950
深呼吸  不会有事的
Deep breaths. You'll be fine.

531
00:21:15,140 --> 00:21:17,120
我看到我桌上签好的离职补偿协议了
I saw the signed severance papers on my desk.

532
00:21:17,340 --> 00:21:19,390
-谢谢  -我给托莉也留言了
- Thank you. - I also left word for Tori.

533
00:21:19,560 --> 00:21:20,580
我知道  我们通过话了
Yes, we spoke.

534
00:21:20,760 --> 00:21:22,010
她如释重负  但我不敢说
She's relieved, but I wouldn't go so far

535
00:21:22,200 --> 00:21:23,630
她完全原谅我们的过失了
as to say completely forgiving.

536
00:21:24,050 --> 00:21:26,080
你听说过阿伯丁咨询公司吗
You ever heard of Aberdeen Solutions?

537
00:21:26,410 --> 00:21:28,450
雷贝克把他们列为顾问公司
Drybeck listed them as a consultant firm.

538
00:21:28,870 --> 00:21:31,690
他们每月向我们收取管理业务费用
They bill us every month for their management services.

539
00:21:31,870 --> 00:21:32,680
怎么了
Okay.

540
00:21:32,860 --> 00:21:33,670
这算什么费用
What does that mean?

541
00:21:34,110 --> 00:21:35,990
-去跟会计查查  -查了
- Check with accounting. - I did.

542
00:21:36,470 --> 00:21:38,040
他们只能说我们付了他们多少钱
They can only tell me how much we pay them,

543
00:21:38,590 --> 00:21:40,440
所以我直接打给阿伯丁
so I called Aberdeen directly.

544
00:21:40,630 --> 00:21:42,510
接电话的是自动答录系统
It's an automated answering system.

545
00:21:42,760 --> 00:21:44,930
我留了六条信息  毫无回音
I left six messages. No returns.

546
00:21:45,330 --> 00:21:46,360
这是斯坦提到的
Stan mentioned it.

547
00:21:46,690 --> 00:21:48,170
事情有些蹊跷
Something just doesn't feel right.

548
00:21:50,170 --> 00:21:51,890
你的意思是要调查我们的客户吗
Are you saying you want to investigate our client?

549
00:21:52,090 --> 00:21:53,400
他们还是我们的会计
They're also our accountants.

550
00:21:53,580 --> 00:21:55,120
托莉还是我的朋友
And Tori is also a friend.

551
00:21:57,110 --> 00:21:58,570
哈维  如果你被抓到...
Harvey, if you got caught--

552
00:21:58,760 --> 00:21:59,810
我不会被抓到
I wouldn't get caught.

553
00:22:02,820 --> 00:22:06,330
我很明确地告诉过你  不要这么做
I am explicitly telling you not to do this.

554
00:22:08,660 --> 00:22:09,940
那我会向你汇报我没做调查之后
Well, then I'll let you know what I don't find

555
00:22:09,940 --> 00:22:11,580
所没查到的证据
after I don't look into it.

556
00:22:27,450 --> 00:22:29,220
我们是不是该把其他的2010届毕业生
Hey, should we get the rest of the 2010 grads

557
00:22:29,410 --> 00:22:30,250
都找来照张相
with us for a pic?

558
00:22:30,840 --> 00:22:32,200
什么其他人  这是11届毕业生合照
The rest? This is 2011. No way.

559
00:22:32,710 --> 00:22:34,150
他不是10届的吗
Isn't he from the 2010 class?

560
00:22:39,160 --> 00:22:41,270
不  不  我是11届的
No, no. I was 2011.

561
00:22:42,230 --> 00:22:42,880
你不是我们班的
You're not with us.

562
00:22:43,850 --> 00:22:45,470
是啊  鲁迪  我是迈克啊
Yeah, Rudy... It's Mike.

563
00:22:45,690 --> 00:22:47,410
我们常一起出去呢
You know, we-- we hung out a bunch.

564
00:22:47,700 --> 00:22:48,460
去哪
Where?

565
00:22:49,740 --> 00:22:50,580
你猜怎么
Oh, you know what?

566
00:22:50,760 --> 00:22:51,990
我八成是把别人记成你了
Maybe I'm thinking about somebody else.

567
00:22:52,220 --> 00:22:52,960
抱歉
Sorry about that.

568
00:22:53,710 --> 00:22:54,950
有谁见过那个人吗
Has anyone seen that guy here before?

569
00:23:00,520 --> 00:23:01,540
我很不走运啊
I'm not having any luck.

570
00:23:01,740 --> 00:23:02,850
真希望能给你点好消息
Wish I could say different, love.

571
00:23:03,040 --> 00:23:05,180
可惜我这边也是毫无收获
But it's been a potter's field for me too.

572
00:23:06,170 --> 00:23:07,730
什么  你能装成另一个人
What? You get to pretend to be someone else.

573
00:23:07,930 --> 00:23:09,220
我也想试试  挺好玩的
I wanted to try. It's fun.

574
00:23:09,590 --> 00:23:11,020
装英国腔啊
Accent? Hmm.

575
00:23:12,530 --> 00:23:13,710
好吧  我不闹了
Okay, I'll stop.

576
00:23:14,890 --> 00:23:15,610
怎么了
What?

577
00:23:16,200 --> 00:23:17,110
你真是不可思议
You're amazing.

578
00:23:21,790 --> 00:23:23,030
那位是布莱恩·简宁斯
And that's Brian Jennings.

579
00:23:23,410 --> 00:23:24,670
布莱恩·简宁斯是谁
Who's Brian Jennings?

580
00:23:24,900 --> 00:23:26,760
我今天在安格·梅西律所的网站上看到他了
I saw his face on Unger and Macy's website today.

581
00:23:27,180 --> 00:23:28,550
你还等什么  冲啊
What are you waiting for? Go.

582
00:23:35,950 --> 00:23:36,650
你好
Hi.

583
00:23:37,770 --> 00:23:39,680
公共场合不当暴露监禁十日
Ten days for public exposure.

584
00:23:40,400 --> 00:23:42,020
下次你去时代广场感到内急
Next time you need a bathroom in Times Square,

585
00:23:42,020 --> 00:23:43,380
上旅馆找厕所
go into a hotel.

586
00:23:45,730 --> 00:23:47,260
休庭五分钟
Five-minute recess.

587
00:23:52,670 --> 00:23:53,690
哈维
Harvey.

588
00:23:54,090 --> 00:23:55,400
好久不见  安东尼
Long time, Anthony.

589
00:23:57,050 --> 00:23:59,720
你总跟中央大街上的款爷们为伍
You keep company with the high rollers on Center Street.

590
00:24:00,470 --> 00:24:01,890
屈尊来我这夜间法庭干什么
What are you doing down in night court?

591
00:24:02,750 --> 00:24:03,730
我需要你帮忙
I need a favor.

592
00:24:05,230 --> 00:24:06,320
什么样的忙
What kind of favor?

593
00:24:06,540 --> 00:24:09,250
我要看封存的法庭文件
One that requires access to sealed court documents.

594
00:24:09,480 --> 00:24:10,250
能等到明天吗
Can it wait till tomorrow?

595
00:24:10,450 --> 00:24:11,800
我这里有积压案件...
I got this backlog of case--

596
00:24:11,990 --> 00:24:13,630
你两年前大半夜来找我
When you came to me two years ago in the middle of the night,

597
00:24:14,180 --> 00:24:15,950
我让你等到第二天了吗
did I tell you it had to wait till tomorrow?

598
00:24:18,570 --> 00:24:19,580
去我办公室
My chambers.

599
00:24:22,970 --> 00:24:24,870
真没想到啊
So...this is quite a surprise.

600
00:24:25,880 --> 00:24:27,460
真想不到我们也会双重约会
Who'd ever think that you and I would on a double date?

601
00:24:28,210 --> 00:24:29,380
-什么  -别装了
- Excuse me? - Oh, come on.

602
00:24:29,580 --> 00:24:30,830
你一进屋就注意到了吧
You had to notice when you walked in the room.

603
00:24:31,040 --> 00:24:32,130
她绝对惊为天人啊
She's absolutely gorgeous.

604
00:24:32,470 --> 00:24:34,070
而且她非常喜欢你女朋友
And she's completely infatuated with your girlfriend.

605
00:24:36,840 --> 00:24:37,610
来吧
Come on.

606
00:24:37,800 --> 00:24:38,800
来  我介绍你们认识
Come on, I'll introduce you to her.

607
00:24:39,300 --> 00:24:40,740
查丽丝  亲爱的
Charisse, honey...

608
00:24:41,240 --> 00:24:43,310
这是我们一位助理律师  迈克·罗斯
Uh, this is one of my associates, Mike Ross.

609
00:24:43,510 --> 00:24:44,740
见到你很高兴
Oh, so nice to meet you.

610
00:24:44,950 --> 00:24:46,450
我爱上你的女朋友了
And I'm in love with your date.

611
00:24:47,030 --> 00:24:47,730
真的
Seriously.

612
00:24:47,920 --> 00:24:49,680
她刚刚在跟我讲她工作中接触到的猴子
She's just been telling me about her work with monkeys.

613
00:24:49,870 --> 00:24:51,110
听着真有趣
It's fascinating.

614
00:24:51,290 --> 00:24:52,880
他们真的跟我们一样聪明吗
So really, they're as smart as us?

615
00:24:53,540 --> 00:24:54,390
比我们聪明呢
Oh, smarter.

616
00:24:55,420 --> 00:24:56,860
我没机会跟他说话
I never had a chance with him.

617
00:24:58,540 --> 00:25:00,120
我得去趟洗手间
I need to use the ladies' room.

618
00:25:00,320 --> 00:25:01,390
失陪一下
Would you excuse me?

619
00:25:03,290 --> 00:25:05,030
猴子不比人类聪明  抱歉
Monkeys aren't smarter than humans, sorry.

620
00:25:05,840 --> 00:25:07,840
那要看是跟谁比了
That depends on which humans you're talking about, I guess.

621
00:25:08,140 --> 00:25:09,140
-什么  -什么
- What? - Huh?

622
00:25:09,920 --> 00:25:11,530
案件的名称  大体日期
Name of case and rough date?

623
00:25:11,920 --> 00:25:13,780
宝拉·奥尼尔起诉阿伯丁公司
Aberdeen versus Paula O'Neil,

624
00:25:13,970 --> 00:25:15,170
大概半年前
say six months ago.

625
00:25:16,360 --> 00:25:17,380
我查查
Oh, let's see.

626
00:25:17,980 --> 00:25:21,010
这里写他们是雷贝克的附属公司
Says here that they were listed as a subsidiary of Drybeck

627
00:25:21,010 --> 00:25:22,800
诉讼内容为不当解雇
in a wrongful termination suit.

628
00:25:23,000 --> 00:25:24,240
就是这个  我找的就是这个
That's it. That's what I'm looking for.

629
00:25:24,450 --> 00:25:26,290
我不能打印出来  会被追踪到
I can't print this out. I'll get tagged.

630
00:25:26,480 --> 00:25:27,420
过来自己看
Come around. Take a look.

631
00:25:29,050 --> 00:25:29,980
你找的是这个吗
Is that what you're after?

632
00:25:30,260 --> 00:25:31,380
没错  就是这个
Yeah, that's it.

633
00:25:31,740 --> 00:25:33,910
这是什么
But what's that?

634
00:25:37,020 --> 00:25:40,360
这是与阿伯丁相关的另一个法庭档案的链接
That links to another court filing in relation to Aberdeen.

635
00:25:40,680 --> 00:25:41,480
点开看看
Click on it.

636
00:25:42,780 --> 00:25:44,740
写着他们申请解散了
Says here that they filed for dissolution...

637
00:25:45,330 --> 00:25:46,280
就在今天早些时候
earlier today.

638
00:25:46,870 --> 00:25:47,870
整家公司吗
The whole company?

639
00:25:48,090 --> 00:25:49,400
白纸黑字
That's what it says.

640
00:25:49,610 --> 00:25:50,960
他们正式歇业了
They're officially shut down.

641
00:25:51,220 --> 00:25:52,570
我还得请你再帮个忙
I'm gonna need one more favor.

642
00:25:55,630 --> 00:25:57,120
我觉得你能找一个不在法律界
I think it's great that you found someone

643
00:25:57,310 --> 00:25:59,230
而在外面真实世界里工作的人很好
not in law who works out in the real world.

644
00:25:59,420 --> 00:26:00,380
为什么这么说
Why do you say that?

645
00:26:00,590 --> 00:26:02,150
因为我整日西装革履
Because I'm stuck in a suit all day

646
00:26:02,330 --> 00:26:04,090
不是在办公室就是在法庭
or an office or a courtroom.

647
00:26:04,300 --> 00:26:05,480
我觉得能回归自然是件好事
I think it'd be nice to be in nature.

648
00:26:05,690 --> 00:26:06,490
你说呢  迈克
Don't you, Mike?

649
00:26:06,700 --> 00:26:08,200
我很喜欢你律师的职业
Well, I love that you're a lawyer.

650
00:26:08,590 --> 00:26:12,030
事实上  我哪天还想看看你工作的地方
In fact, I'd love to see where you work sometime.

651
00:26:14,110 --> 00:26:14,870
你真的想去
You would?

652
00:26:16,310 --> 00:26:18,620
我突然有些不舒服
I'm not feeling so well all of a sudden.

653
00:26:18,800 --> 00:26:19,880
-不是吧  -是啊
- No. - Yeah.

654
00:26:20,100 --> 00:26:21,010
你觉得我们能走吗
You think we can go?

655
00:26:21,190 --> 00:26:21,820
-行啊  -现在就走
- Yeah. - Right now?

656
00:26:22,030 --> 00:26:22,930
现在  行啊
Now. Yeah.

657
00:26:23,130 --> 00:26:24,170
-认识你很高兴  -你也是
- So great to meet you. - Lovely to meet you.

658
00:26:24,360 --> 00:26:25,100
好好玩
Have good night.

659
00:26:27,700 --> 00:26:29,450
你怎么不早用这一招
Okay, why didn't you do that sooner?

660
00:26:29,650 --> 00:26:32,370
因为...我先去搞定这个了
Because... I had to get this first.

661
00:26:33,330 --> 00:26:34,630
就是那个公司的人的吧
That's the guy, right? From the firm.

662
00:26:34,840 --> 00:26:35,660
是他的雇员证件
That's his employee I.D.

663
00:26:35,880 --> 00:26:37,390
-他给你的吗  -我偷来的
- He gave this to you? - No, I stole it.

664
00:26:37,830 --> 00:26:39,220
什么
What?

665
00:26:39,480 --> 00:26:42,080
听着  你可以花一晚上功夫跟他套近乎
Listen, you could spend all night trying to get to the guy

666
00:26:42,260 --> 00:26:44,840
或者你干脆自己去他公司找找看
or you could just go into his firm yourself and look.

667
00:26:45,430 --> 00:26:45,940
走吧
Come on.

668
00:26:46,120 --> 00:26:46,910
我们走
Let's go.

669
00:26:54,710 --> 00:26:57,010
我眼皮也打架呢
Yeah, I can barely keep my eyes open myself.

670
00:26:57,380 --> 00:26:59,590
填写简报真烦人
Filing briefs sucks.

671
00:27:26,550 --> 00:27:27,480
你还真来了
You actually came.

672
00:27:28,570 --> 00:27:30,950
你就是哈维·斯佩克特吧
You must be Harvey Specter.

673
00:27:32,130 --> 00:27:32,940
你是乔吧
"Joe," was it?

674
00:27:33,820 --> 00:27:35,460
你朋友跟你说明白我的条件了吗
Your friend fill you in on the deal that's on the table?

675
00:27:35,870 --> 00:27:37,060
让我直接说重点吧
Let me just get it straight.

676
00:27:37,510 --> 00:27:39,430
你抓到他翻看一些文件
You caught him rifling through some files,

677
00:27:39,610 --> 00:27:40,900
你不去报警
and in lieu of calling the police,

678
00:27:41,090 --> 00:27:42,160
却想让我花钱摆平吗
you want me to pay you off?

679
00:27:42,380 --> 00:27:43,550
我可没这么说
I never said that.

680
00:27:44,240 --> 00:27:45,130
他说的
He did.

681
00:27:46,070 --> 00:27:46,760
真高明
Oh, that's great.

682
00:27:46,940 --> 00:27:49,070
这样的话  如果我告你勒索
This way, if I level a charge of extortion,

683
00:27:49,260 --> 00:27:50,140
也没有证据  对吗
it's hearsay, huh?

684
00:27:50,550 --> 00:27:51,920
在律所工作十年
Ten years working for a law firm,

685
00:27:52,090 --> 00:27:53,710
也能学会一两招  这是好事
you learn a thing or two, which is good,

686
00:27:53,900 --> 00:27:55,650
因为我这工作挣钱可不多
'cause you sure as hell don't make a lot of money doing it.

687
00:27:55,840 --> 00:27:57,590
我倒是觉得你过得还不错
Somehow I think you're getting by fine.

688
00:27:57,760 --> 00:27:59,760
我只想说  你们那个段位的人交手
Just saying, on the level you guys play at,

689
00:27:59,970 --> 00:28:02,300
间谍活动也是常有的事  所以我知道
espionage happens all the time, which is why I know

690
00:28:02,830 --> 00:28:04,670
你会不惜一切代价保护自己的秘密
you'll do anything to protect your secrets.

691
00:28:04,890 --> 00:28:08,390
实际上  家住皇后区  阿斯托里亚
Well actually, Joe Speena, of 2561 Clover Lane,

692
00:28:08,570 --> 00:28:10,140
苜蓿巷2561号的乔·斯皮纳  我们都一样
AsToria, Queens, I think we all would.

693
00:28:10,920 --> 00:28:14,100
比如说你过去六年里  你和妻子合报纳税单
Like those tax returns you filed jointly for the last six years

694
00:28:14,100 --> 00:28:15,990
其实你和她早已经分居了
while no longer living with your wife.

695
00:28:16,190 --> 00:28:18,340
为这事  国税局能毁了你
You know, the IRS can destroy you for that.

696
00:28:18,840 --> 00:28:21,120
你以为你是第一个想勒索我的人吗  乔
You think you're the first person to try to extort me, Joe?

697
00:28:21,320 --> 00:28:22,660
这才是我的段位
'Cause that's the level I play at.

698
00:28:23,330 --> 00:28:25,380
你是个保安
Now...you're a security guard

699
00:28:25,600 --> 00:28:26,950
却甘冒奇险
Who likes to take risks.

700
00:28:27,130 --> 00:28:27,900
这我欣赏
I like that.

701
00:28:28,080 --> 00:28:29,070
所以我们这么办
So here's what we're gonna do.

702
00:28:29,720 --> 00:28:31,440
这里是给小乔伊的少年棒球赛队的
This here's a generous donation

703
00:28:31,610 --> 00:28:33,280
一笔数目可观的捐款
to Joey Junior's little league team.

704
00:28:33,480 --> 00:28:34,920
这钱或许会到他们手上
Now, if it gets to them, it gets to them.

705
00:28:35,130 --> 00:28:36,830
也或许不会
If it doesn't, it doesn't.

706
00:28:37,270 --> 00:28:38,710
不论怎样  下次我们再见面
But the next time we talk,

707
00:28:38,900 --> 00:28:40,480
会是我要你帮忙
it's gonna be me who wants a favor.

708
00:28:46,000 --> 00:28:46,830
长官
Officer.

709
00:28:48,400 --> 00:28:49,840
我还真要还你钱吗
Do I really need to pay you back?

710
00:28:50,180 --> 00:28:51,690
不如你先解释一下
Let's start with an explanation.

711
00:28:52,300 --> 00:28:53,760
你说我得去找证据
You said I needed to find evidence,

712
00:28:53,960 --> 00:28:54,750
我就去找了
So I went to find some.

713
00:28:54,950 --> 00:28:56,670
闯入另一家律所去找吗
By breaking into another law firm?

714
00:28:56,890 --> 00:28:58,680
这真的比贿赂保安还差劲吗
Is that really worse than paying off a security guard?

715
00:28:58,880 --> 00:29:00,390
首先  我们没有贿赂他
Okay, first of all, I didn't pay him off.

716
00:29:00,590 --> 00:29:01,880
第二  如果我不贿赂他
Second of all, if I hadn't paid him off,

717
00:29:02,100 --> 00:29:03,150
你现在就进监狱了
you'd be in jail right now.

718
00:29:04,550 --> 00:29:06,030
你觉得我对斯坦的看法可能是对的
You think I might be right about Stan.

719
00:29:06,240 --> 00:29:07,590
不  我从没说过你错了
No, I never said you were wrong.

720
00:29:07,800 --> 00:29:09,180
我说我们需要证据
I said we needed evidence.

721
00:29:09,790 --> 00:29:11,020
你找到什么了吗
But did you find something?

722
00:29:12,330 --> 00:29:15,300
雷贝克13个月前买了个架上公司
Drybeck bought a shelf company 13 months ago.

723
00:29:15,930 --> 00:29:17,030
什么叫架上公司
What's a shelf company?

724
00:29:17,780 --> 00:29:20,150
是只存在于法律文件上的公司
It's a corporation that exists only on paper,

725
00:29:20,380 --> 00:29:22,550
以便它的所有者藏他们的资产
so its owners can hide their assets.

726
00:29:22,760 --> 00:29:23,880
那不是空壳公司吗
Isn't that a shell company?

727
00:29:24,200 --> 00:29:25,280
不  是家架上公司
No, it's a shelf company.

728
00:29:25,470 --> 00:29:28,100
找个空壳公司  给它开个银行账户
Okay, take a shell company, give it a bank account,

729
00:29:28,290 --> 00:29:29,480
建立信用记录  纳税申报单
credit history, tax returns,

730
00:29:30,380 --> 00:29:33,390
然后将它束之高阁  静静等待多年
and let it season for years on a shelf.

731
00:29:33,590 --> 00:29:35,620
有人买下公司  就更名易主
Someone buys it, sloth their name into it,

732
00:29:36,090 --> 00:29:38,570
买家能拿走一个建立好的公司
and they walk away with an established corporation

733
00:29:38,780 --> 00:29:40,000
而且还有先前的记录
with a preexisting history.

734
00:29:40,580 --> 00:29:41,760
有人来查
Anyone looks any closer,

735
00:29:42,390 --> 00:29:43,570
就关掉公司  卷土重来
they shut it down and do it again.

736
00:29:43,770 --> 00:29:44,710
这不违法吗
That's legal?

737
00:29:44,930 --> 00:29:46,060
架上公司是合法的
Shelf companies are legal.

738
00:29:46,300 --> 00:29:48,570
但我想托莉的架上公司干违法的事了
I'm guessing what Tori's doing with hers isn't.

739
00:29:49,160 --> 00:29:50,500
等等  这公司是叫"阿伯丁"吗
Wait a minute. Is it called "Aberdeen"?

740
00:29:51,410 --> 00:29:52,770
我在一张名单前面看到的
Yeah, I saw it on the top of this list

741
00:29:52,980 --> 00:29:54,980
还有另外的37家管理公司
with 37 other management companies

742
00:29:55,180 --> 00:29:58,330
全都和雷贝克那起不正当解雇官司有关
all related to Drybeck in that wrongful termination suit.

743
00:30:00,330 --> 00:30:01,290
我们回到办公室后
When we get back to the office,

744
00:30:01,500 --> 00:30:02,860
我要你找到法律先例
I want you to find legal precedent

745
00:30:03,050 --> 00:30:04,930
好让我们能传唤那些记录
that will allow us to subpoena the records.

746
00:30:05,120 --> 00:30:05,990
好  就去办
Okay, on it.

747
00:30:06,460 --> 00:30:08,180
我真的得还你钱吗
Do I really have to pay you back?

748
00:30:08,470 --> 00:30:09,440
一分不差
Every penny.

749
00:30:10,100 --> 00:30:10,800
等等
Wait a minute.

750
00:30:11,000 --> 00:30:12,070
信封里有多少钱
How much was in that envelope?

751
00:30:20,510 --> 00:30:21,910
你们在我的桌子前干嘛呢
Hey, what are you all doing at my desk?

752
00:30:22,120 --> 00:30:23,150
伙计  快过来看看
Dude, you got to check this out.

753
00:30:27,570 --> 00:30:29,130
借过  借过
Excuse me. Excuse me.

754
00:30:32,150 --> 00:30:33,000
那是路易吗
Is that Louis?

755
00:30:33,220 --> 00:30:34,080
没错  在大厅里
Uh-huh. In the lobby.

756
00:30:34,270 --> 00:30:36,540
这是监控录像吗  是实时的吗
Is this a security camera? A live feed?

757
00:30:36,630 --> 00:30:37,220
-你们在干嘛  -不是的
- What are you guys doing? - No, no.

758
00:30:37,310 --> 00:30:37,970
这是昨晚的
This is from last night.

759
00:30:38,160 --> 00:30:40,000
保安室的人今早电邮给路易的
The guys in security emailed it up to Louis this morning.

760
00:30:40,600 --> 00:30:42,360
为什么用我的电脑看呢
And why are we watching it on my computer?

761
00:30:42,800 --> 00:30:44,460
我们不敢冒险用我们的电脑看啊
Well, we're not gonna risk watching it on one of ours.

762
00:30:44,860 --> 00:30:46,050
再说大家都知道你的密码
And everyone knows your password.

763
00:30:46,440 --> 00:30:48,020
大家怎么都知道我的密码
How does everybody know my password?

764
00:30:48,220 --> 00:30:49,280
罗斯999
"Ross999."

765
00:30:49,470 --> 00:30:50,580
有多难解开啊
How hard is that to crack?

766
00:30:51,230 --> 00:30:53,460
好吧999增大了...
Okay, "999" increases the odds of--

767
00:30:53,660 --> 00:30:54,310
嘘  好戏来了
Oh, shh! Here it comes.

768
00:30:55,880 --> 00:30:56,690
什么
What?

769
00:31:02,360 --> 00:31:03,080
不
Oh, no.

770
00:31:03,310 --> 00:31:04,560
他跟她说什么了
What did he say to her?

771
00:31:04,810 --> 00:31:06,930
路易貌似要申请限制令
Oh, evidently Louis wants a restraining order

772
00:31:07,100 --> 00:31:08,170
所以想用这个作为凭证
and he needs this asvidence.

773
00:31:09,610 --> 00:31:10,450
怎么了
What?

774
00:31:11,430 --> 00:31:13,370
这...
Uh, um, it--

775
00:31:14,080 --> 00:31:15,450
听我说  不要误会
Okay, listen. Please don't.

776
00:31:16,330 --> 00:31:17,540
我进来时就...
I came in here and it--

777
00:31:18,420 --> 00:31:19,180
听着  我...
Look, I--

778
00:31:20,110 --> 00:31:21,400
你还好吧
Are you okay now?

779
00:31:22,320 --> 00:31:23,140
路易
Louis?

780
00:31:28,630 --> 00:31:31,260
你的留言如果是骗我过来的花招...
If the message you left was another trick to get me down here...

781
00:31:31,440 --> 00:31:32,750
我保证不是耍花招  进来吧
No tricks, I assure you. Come on in.

782
00:31:33,020 --> 00:31:34,330
斯坦  我是杰西卡·皮尔逊
Stan, I'm Jessica Pearson.

783
00:31:34,550 --> 00:31:35,400
我知道你是谁
Oh, yeah. I know who you are.

784
00:31:36,080 --> 00:31:37,720
你说如果我接受遣散和解
You said if I accepted the severance agreement,

785
00:31:37,930 --> 00:31:38,770
就不会闹上法庭了
there wouldn't be a lawsuit.

786
00:31:39,020 --> 00:31:40,070
法庭是要上的
Well, there is one,

787
00:31:41,050 --> 00:31:41,860
但不是要告你
but not against you.

788
00:31:42,500 --> 00:31:43,300
是要跟你并肩作战
With you.

789
00:31:43,850 --> 00:31:45,100
我们知道阿伯丁的事了
We know about Aberdeen.

790
00:31:45,580 --> 00:31:47,200
我们托莉在搞什么名堂
We know what Tori was orchestrating.

791
00:31:47,410 --> 00:31:49,590
有你帮忙  我们能揭发她
And with your help, we can expose her.

792
00:31:53,500 --> 00:31:54,300
我凭什么帮你
Why should I help you?

793
00:31:55,490 --> 00:31:56,750
帮了对你有什么坏处吗
What have you got to lose?

794
00:32:02,820 --> 00:32:03,800
告诉我你要我做什么
Tell me what you need me to do.

795
00:32:12,190 --> 00:32:13,710
他现在又让你找什么了
What does he have you trying to find this time?

796
00:32:14,380 --> 00:32:15,200
你真想知道吗
You really want to know?

797
00:32:19,030 --> 00:32:21,330
我曾看到了一些与我们会计事务所
Uh, I managed to get a look at some files

798
00:32:21,550 --> 00:32:22,770
相关的文件
involving our accounting firm.

799
00:32:23,400 --> 00:32:24,550
我们的会计事务所怎么了
What's up with our accounting firm?

800
00:32:25,340 --> 00:32:26,380
他们在偷我们的钱
They're stealing from us.

801
00:32:28,330 --> 00:32:29,160
你想想你的电话费
You know your phone bill?

802
00:32:29,810 --> 00:32:30,840
有很多附加费用
You have all those surcharges,

803
00:32:31,040 --> 00:32:32,510
你并不知道那些是什么  但你照付不误
you have no idea what they mean, but you pay 'em anyway.

804
00:32:32,760 --> 00:32:33,480
对
Yeah.

805
00:32:33,680 --> 00:32:35,130
雷贝克也在跟我们来这套
Yeah, well, Drybeck's doing the same thing to us,

806
00:32:35,350 --> 00:32:37,780
不过他们的收费完全是欺诈
Except all their charges are a complete scam.

807
00:32:37,970 --> 00:32:39,800
我确信电话费也是欺诈
Pretty sure the phone charges are scams, too.

808
00:32:40,470 --> 00:32:41,470
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.

809
00:32:41,700 --> 00:32:42,740
那你需要什么
So what do you need?

810
00:32:43,780 --> 00:32:46,060
我需要一个合法的理由去拿到那些文件
I need a legal reason to get those files

811
00:32:46,250 --> 00:32:48,680
但不能说我已经看过了那些文件
without saying I saw those files.

812
00:32:49,430 --> 00:32:51,040
你是需要呈上法庭  还是仅仅需要而已
You need them for court or you just need them?

813
00:32:53,490 --> 00:32:54,180
怎么这么问
Why?

814
00:32:54,920 --> 00:32:55,960
你刚说你都看过  是吧
You said you read 'em, right?

815
00:32:56,180 --> 00:32:56,890
是的
Yeah.

816
00:32:57,100 --> 00:32:58,280
那你就已经有了
So then you already have them...

817
00:32:58,990 --> 00:32:59,970
在这里
In here.

818
00:33:01,510 --> 00:33:02,730
你说得对  我已经有了
You're right. I do.

819
00:33:02,940 --> 00:33:04,980
是的  你口授  我记录
Yes, so you dictate, I'll type.

820
00:33:05,800 --> 00:33:06,490
什么
What?

821
00:33:07,230 --> 00:33:08,400
你真愿意这么帮我吗
You'd actually do that for me?

822
00:33:09,020 --> 00:33:10,150
他们偷我们的钱
They're stealing from us.

823
00:33:10,380 --> 00:33:11,710
我也是皮尔逊·哈德曼的人
Person Hardman is my firm too.

824
00:33:13,260 --> 00:33:14,070
开始吧
Come on.

825
00:33:15,690 --> 00:33:16,550
好的
Okay.

826
00:33:17,410 --> 00:33:18,680
关于第三部分的第三方
With the party of the third part,

827
00:33:18,860 --> 00:33:20,890
是指诺顿有限责任公司...
hereto referred to as Norton LLC--

828
00:33:21,090 --> 00:33:23,680
...不受任何可能涉及到的
not to subject to any litigation or any claim

829
00:33:23,680 --> 00:33:26,060
诉讼或索赔所限制...
that might reasonably be anticipated...

830
00:33:26,250 --> 00:33:27,960
...我方承认此项委托不可撤销
We acknowledge that such appointment is irrevocable

831
00:33:27,960 --> 00:33:29,620
且具有效力...
and shall be deemed power...

832
00:33:29,810 --> 00:33:32,510
...合法授权签署此类合同
...lawfully invested with the power to make such contracts

833
00:33:32,570 --> 00:33:37,070
或履行其中适法默示的行为
or to perform acts from which it may be lawfully implied.

834
00:33:38,260 --> 00:33:39,670
就这些  都记下来了吗
That's it. Did we get it?

835
00:33:39,870 --> 00:33:41,850
在保存  等下
Saving and wait for it...

836
00:33:42,510 --> 00:33:43,240
搞定
Done.

837
00:33:50,690 --> 00:33:51,360
怎么
What?

838
00:33:52,390 --> 00:33:54,740
你的脑子太灵光了
Your mind. It's just-- it's amazing.

839
00:33:56,300 --> 00:33:57,080
谢谢
Thanks.

840
00:33:59,530 --> 00:34:00,240
怎么
What?

841
00:34:00,440 --> 00:34:01,960
你的脑子也很灵光
Your mind's amazing too.

842
00:34:02,140 --> 00:34:03,320
谢谢
Oh, thank you.

843
00:34:04,730 --> 00:34:05,410
谢谢
Thank you.

844
00:34:07,220 --> 00:34:08,270
这么晚你给谁打电话
Who you calling this late?

845
00:34:09,730 --> 00:34:10,740
她在熬夜等你吗
She's waiting up for you?

846
00:34:11,170 --> 00:34:12,920
你说得对  太晚了
Yeah, I guess you're right. It's pretty late.

847
00:34:12,920 --> 00:34:14,390
她现在可能已经睡了
She's probably sleeping by now.

848
00:34:14,590 --> 00:34:15,780
我给她发短信好了
I'll just text her.

849
00:34:16,190 --> 00:34:18,950
不管是和律所的新人还是老人谈恋爱
It's tough to have a relationship with the first year

850
00:34:18,950 --> 00:34:20,120
都很不容易
or any year.

851
00:34:20,290 --> 00:34:21,570
咱们生活工作不分家
You just don't have a life.

852
00:34:22,320 --> 00:34:23,250
那你怎么解决的
How'd you make it work?

853
00:34:24,210 --> 00:34:25,050
我也没有好办法
Who said I did?

854
00:34:25,660 --> 00:34:27,480
除非能找到一个和自己一样
It's--it's impossible to have anything long-term

855
00:34:27,680 --> 00:34:29,120
每周工作80小时的人
unless you find someone that has the same

856
00:34:29,120 --> 00:34:31,190
不然感情不可能长久...
80-hour work week and then...

857
00:34:31,920 --> 00:34:34,280
那也没用  因为对方也会很忙
That doesn't work either, because they're busy too.

858
00:34:34,650 --> 00:34:36,100
我不想因为太忙
Yeah, well, I'm not gonna let that be the reason

859
00:34:36,280 --> 00:34:37,280
就和珍妮...
that Jenny and I don't--

860
00:34:50,420 --> 00:34:51,320
你们俩还在这里做什么
What are you two still doing here?

861
00:34:52,140 --> 00:34:53,330
-忙哈维的案子  -没什么
- Uh, it's for Harvey. - Nothing.

862
00:34:54,070 --> 00:34:55,360
-已经做完了  -晚安
- Uh, but we're done. - Good night.

863
00:34:55,560 --> 00:34:56,210
-回头见  -晚安
- Yeah, I'll see you later. - Good night.

864
00:34:56,380 --> 00:34:57,230
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.

865
00:35:02,850 --> 00:35:03,680
这道理你肯定明白
I'm sure you're aware of this,

866
00:35:03,880 --> 00:35:05,990
但我还是要提醒你
But, um, I'm just gonna remind you anyway.

867
00:35:06,720 --> 00:35:09,740
本公司禁止办公室恋情
Um, this office frowns upon relationships in the workplace.

868
00:35:11,750 --> 00:35:12,510
我知道
Yeah.

869
00:35:35,730 --> 00:35:37,210
天啊  真对不起
Oh, god! I'm so sorry.

870
00:35:38,160 --> 00:35:38,850
没关系
That's okay.

871
00:35:41,680 --> 00:35:42,920
昨晚谢谢你
Uh, thank you for last night.

872
00:35:44,660 --> 00:35:45,560
帮我记录
The typing.

873
00:35:45,780 --> 00:35:47,310
不谢
Of cour--right.

874
00:35:47,490 --> 00:35:48,480
-不用客气  -忙了我大忙
- Absolutely. - It was really helpful.

875
00:35:51,400 --> 00:35:52,920
稍等
Um, hold on one second.

876
00:35:53,110 --> 00:35:54,420
抱歉  喂
Sorry. Hello?

877
00:35:55,120 --> 00:35:56,540
我刚才叫你到我办公室来
I said I needed you in my office.

878
00:35:56,730 --> 00:35:57,740
我说了马上到
And I said I was on my way.

879
00:35:57,930 --> 00:35:59,150
省省吧  就是这些文件吗
Save it. Those the files?

880
00:35:59,320 --> 00:36:00,420
是的  给你
Yes, take them, please.

881
00:36:00,680 --> 00:36:02,920
斯坦在我办公室  到会议室等我们
Stan is in my office. Meet us in the conference room.

882
00:36:02,920 --> 00:36:03,880
好的
Okay.

883
00:36:07,810 --> 00:36:08,770
抱歉让你久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.

884
00:36:09,430 --> 00:36:10,200
没关系
That's okay.

885
00:36:10,460 --> 00:36:12,970
我收到了你那封附有其他律所名单的邮件
I got your email with a list of other law firms.

886
00:36:13,200 --> 00:36:14,990
你为了弥补过错而向我推荐新客户
I respect your effort to make amends

887
00:36:15,160 --> 00:36:16,290
我欣赏你的诚意
by referring new clients.

888
00:36:16,550 --> 00:36:17,900
那不是客户推荐名单
hat wasn't a list for client referrals.

889
00:36:18,090 --> 00:36:20,540
那些是你可以考虑聘请的律所
Those are firms you should consider for representation.

890
00:36:20,720 --> 00:36:22,150
我们不再是你的代理律所了  托莉
We're no longer your attorneys, Tori.

891
00:36:23,020 --> 00:36:23,580
什么
What?

892
00:36:23,780 --> 00:36:24,670
我们真的别无选择
We have no choice really.

893
00:36:24,900 --> 00:36:26,490
既然我们准备起诉你
It would be impossible to represent you

894
00:36:26,680 --> 00:36:28,880
就不可能再为你做代理了
when we plan on suing you for every penny you've got.

895
00:36:29,830 --> 00:36:30,930
开玩笑吧
Is this a joke?

896
00:36:31,140 --> 00:36:32,390
阿伯丁咨询公司
Aberdeen Solutions.

897
00:36:32,770 --> 00:36:34,620
成立于2006年6月
Created in June of 2006.

898
00:36:34,800 --> 00:36:36,390
2010年出售给雷贝克
Sold to Drybeck 2010.

899
00:36:36,590 --> 00:36:37,450
两天前解体
Dissolved two days ago.

900
00:36:37,850 --> 00:36:39,950
它的前身是波顿财务公司
Before that, it was Bolton Finances.

901
00:36:40,130 --> 00:36:41,750
再往前追溯  是诺顿服务公司
And before that, it was Norton Services,

902
00:36:41,950 --> 00:36:43,320
利特顿有限责任公司
Littleton LLC.

903
00:36:43,490 --> 00:36:44,200
你从哪里弄到这些的
Where did you get those?

904
00:36:44,370 --> 00:36:45,340
我们知道了你的所作所为  托莉
We know what you did, Tori.

905
00:36:45,530 --> 00:36:47,050
你不可能传召到这些文件
You couldn't have subpoenaed these files.

906
00:36:47,250 --> 00:36:48,320
但我们还是拿到了
And yet we have them.

907
00:36:48,530 --> 00:36:49,860
看看吧  全都在这儿
Take a look. They're all there.

908
00:36:50,050 --> 00:36:52,200
-现在我们有证据  -什么证据
- And now we have proof. - Proof of what?

909
00:36:52,420 --> 00:36:54,720
那些都是合法的公司  用来...
Those are all legitimate corporations used for--

910
00:36:54,930 --> 00:36:56,930
偷钱装进你自己的腰包
Stealing money and lining your own pockets.

911
00:36:57,240 --> 00:36:58,720
你可以不信我的话
But don't take my word for it.

912
00:36:59,140 --> 00:36:59,930
进来吧
Guys?

913
00:37:06,410 --> 00:37:07,370
你好  托莉
Hello, Tori.

914
00:37:07,790 --> 00:37:09,280
我们雇佣斯坦代表我们
Yeah, we hired Stan to do a little

915
00:37:09,280 --> 00:37:10,940
做了点独立咨询
independent consulting on our behalf

916
00:37:10,940 --> 00:37:13,630
他带回了一些很有意思的资料
and he's come up with some very interesting connections.

917
00:37:13,800 --> 00:37:16,340
这工作很容易  我没有学位也能胜任
It was easy, even if I don't really have a degree.

918
00:37:17,330 --> 00:37:19,840
去年假期你邀请我
There was that vacation you invited me on last year...

919
00:37:20,480 --> 00:37:22,090
去了你在巴哈马的新房子
To your new house in the Bahamas.

920
00:37:22,650 --> 00:37:25,510
买房子的钱是你从这家公司偷的
A house you bought with money you stole from this firm.

921
00:37:25,740 --> 00:37:27,210
我的公司
My firm.

922
00:37:28,060 --> 00:37:28,740
杰西卡
Jessica--

923
00:37:28,940 --> 00:37:30,420
你想说什么
"Jessica" what?

924
00:37:30,640 --> 00:37:32,340
这些文件你不能用
You can't use any of this.

925
00:37:32,530 --> 00:37:34,520
我们签有律师及委托人保密协议
We have attorney-client privilege.

926
00:37:34,710 --> 00:37:36,270
与雷贝克会计事务所是有保密协议
With Drybeck Accounting, yes.

927
00:37:36,460 --> 00:37:38,220
但与这些空壳公司  可没有
With the shelf companies? No.

928
00:37:38,400 --> 00:37:39,290
而不幸的是
And unfortunately for you,

929
00:37:39,490 --> 00:37:40,930
你的名字列在空壳公司上
You're listed on the shelf companies.

930
00:37:42,050 --> 00:37:43,200
你偷了我的钱
You stole from me.

931
00:37:44,210 --> 00:37:45,680
要么现在坦白
You either come clean now

932
00:37:45,680 --> 00:37:48,410
要么往后十年  除了探监时间
or the only time you'll see your children in the next decade

933
00:37:48,600 --> 00:37:50,670
你别想见到你的孩子
will be during prison visiting hours.

934
00:37:56,270 --> 00:37:57,560
那我能回去工作了是吗
So I'm gonna get my job back now, right?

935
00:37:58,080 --> 00:37:59,050
没什么问题
I don't see why not.

936
00:37:59,470 --> 00:38:00,750
不  斯坦  你不能回去工作
No, Stan, you're not.

937
00:38:02,290 --> 00:38:02,990
什么
What?

938
00:38:03,190 --> 00:38:05,660
在这次劫难过后  雷贝克就要破产了
Drybeck's going bankrupt after this all shakes out.

939
00:38:05,860 --> 00:38:07,840
就算不破产  他们也不会雇你回去
Even if they don't, they're not gonna hire you back.

940
00:38:08,700 --> 00:38:09,620
为什么
Why?

941
00:38:11,170 --> 00:38:12,800
因为你在简历上造了假
Because you falsified your resume.

942
00:38:16,610 --> 00:38:17,780
那我现在该怎么办
What am I supposed to do now?

943
00:38:18,110 --> 00:38:20,570
我们付你的钱  比你的遣散费还多
Well, we just got you more than your severance package.

944
00:38:20,870 --> 00:38:23,040
我建议你用这笔钱做个过渡
I suggest you use it to tide yourself over

945
00:38:23,700 --> 00:38:25,000
另谋出路去吧
till you figure something out.

946
00:38:37,770 --> 00:38:40,510
斯坦
Stan...Hey.

947
00:38:40,820 --> 00:38:42,290
你最值钱的资产是你的头脑
Your best asset is your mind.

948
00:38:43,150 --> 00:38:44,320
别人拿不走
They can't take that from you.

949
00:38:46,020 --> 00:38:47,040
只是个小错误
One little mistake.

950
00:38:48,040 --> 00:38:51,180
你可以回到学校  拿个正规文凭
You could go back to school, become legitimate.

951
00:38:51,760 --> 00:38:52,710
从头来过
Start over?

952
00:38:58,140 --> 00:38:59,350
早知今日  何必当初
I never should have done it.

953
00:39:22,410 --> 00:39:23,510
跟你说了他们逮不到我
Told you they wouldn't catch me.

954
00:39:24,780 --> 00:39:26,130
你想要什么  哈维
What are you looking for, Harvey?

955
00:39:26,350 --> 00:39:28,140
-要好好奖励你吗  -不用什么大奖
-Positive reinforcement? - Nothing major.

956
00:39:28,550 --> 00:39:30,170
给个诺贝尔奖杯就行
A trophy, Nobel.

957
00:39:30,500 --> 00:39:32,950
在大堂给你塑尊铜像好不好
Would your likeness in bronze in the lobby be okay?

958
00:39:33,030 --> 00:39:34,070
半身像还是全身像
Bust or life-size?

959
00:39:35,890 --> 00:39:37,070
你做了件好事  哈维
You did a good thing, Harvey.

960
00:39:38,180 --> 00:39:39,450
不光是我一个人的功劳
Well, it wasn't just me, you know?

961
00:39:41,120 --> 00:39:42,400
那从现在起
Well, then I guess I should give the kid

962
00:39:42,580 --> 00:39:44,160
我应该相信那孩子了
the benefit of the doubt from now on.

963
00:39:45,670 --> 00:39:46,300
的确应该
You should.

964
00:40:02,840 --> 00:40:03,860
你听说了准会高兴
Well, you'll be happy to know

965
00:40:04,070 --> 00:40:06,570
斯坦不知道他下半辈子该怎么办
That Stan has no idea what he's gonna do with the rest of his life.

966
00:40:06,760 --> 00:40:08,080
那没什么值得高兴的
That doesn't make me happy.

967
00:40:10,370 --> 00:40:12,620
我也不知道自己下半辈子该怎么过了
Well, what if I tell you I have no idea what I'm doing with mine?

968
00:40:16,540 --> 00:40:18,670
要是我被抓住  我们该怎么办  哈维
What the hell are we gonna do when I get caught, Harvey?

969
00:40:19,860 --> 00:40:20,880
你不会被抓住
You're not gonna get caught.

970
00:40:21,080 --> 00:40:21,910
这就是你的回答吗
That's your answer?

971
00:40:25,110 --> 00:40:26,110
还能怎么回答
What else is there?

972
00:40:30,350 --> 00:40:31,130
为什么
Why?

973
00:40:32,610 --> 00:40:33,350
什么
What?

974
00:40:33,560 --> 00:40:35,230
为什么雇我  你为什么要害我
Hire me. Why would you do that to me?

975
00:40:36,530 --> 00:40:38,110
-是为你好  -不  你不是为我好
-You mean for you. - No, I don't.

976
00:40:38,310 --> 00:40:39,010
你说得很清楚
You made it perfectly clear

977
00:40:39,220 --> 00:40:41,600
你做的一切都是为了你自己  为什么
that you only do things for yourself. So why?

978
00:40:41,960 --> 00:40:44,300
你是说我为什么要成为一个律师
You mean the reason why I became a lawyer

979
00:40:44,300 --> 00:40:47,060
你朋友为什么贩毒  还是你为什么要去当枪手
or your friend dealt drugs or you used to cheat?

980
00:40:47,250 --> 00:40:48,060
我当枪手是因为我需要...
I cheated because I needed--

981
00:40:48,260 --> 00:40:50,520
你就没别的法子赚钱了吗  胡扯
You couldn't make money any other way? Bullshit.

982
00:40:51,530 --> 00:40:53,800
常人的生活平淡无奇
Life is this.

983
00:40:54,430 --> 00:40:56,040
而我喜欢高人一等
I like this.

984
00:40:57,350 --> 00:40:58,370
我不是那种人
That's not me.

985
00:40:59,020 --> 00:41:00,700
如果你不是那种人  就不会在这里
Well, if it wasn't me, you wouldn't be here.

986
00:41:00,940 --> 00:41:03,810
所以如果你想结束这种生活  就直接退出好了
So if you want this to stop, all you got to do is tap out.

987
00:41:18,640 --> 00:41:19,560
你好
Hello.

988
00:41:20,060 --> 00:41:20,940
你来找迈克
You're here to see Mike.

989
00:41:21,460 --> 00:41:23,420
我们要庆祝他胜诉了
We're gonna celebrate his victory.

990
00:41:26,900 --> 00:41:28,870
我觉得你来接他下班
You know, I actually think that it's a really,

991
00:41:29,070 --> 00:41:30,820
是个很明智的选择
really good idea that you've come to pick him up.

992
00:41:31,210 --> 00:41:33,550
如果我是你  就会经常过来
In fact, if I were you, i'd do it a little more often.

993
00:41:33,950 --> 00:41:36,340
特别是和瑞秋一起加班的日子
Just all those late nights working with Rachel.

994
00:41:38,180 --> 00:41:39,020
你什么意思
What do you mean?

995
00:41:39,510 --> 00:41:40,260
我的意思是
What do I--

996
00:41:41,230 --> 00:41:42,660
得了吧  你是个聪明的女孩
Well, come on. You're a smart girl.

997
00:41:43,940 --> 00:41:45,360
你知道动物的习性
You understand animal behavior.

998
00:41:46,520 --> 00:41:47,460
你会想明白的
I think you can figure it out.

999
00:41:52,460 --> 00:41:54,000
可以走了吗
Hey. You ready?

1000
00:41:54,230 --> 00:41:55,230
走吧
Yeah.

1001
00:31:31,440 --> 00:31:32,750
我保证不是耍花招  进来吧
No tricks, I assure you. Come on in.

1002
00:31:33,020 --> 00:31:34,330
斯坦  我是杰西卡·皮尔逊
Stan, I'm Jessica Pearson.

1003
00:31:34,550 --> 00:31:35,400
我知道你是谁
Oh, yeah. I know who you are.

1004
00:31:36,080 --> 00:31:37,720
你说如果我接受遣散和解
You said if I accepted the severance agreement,

1005
00:31:37,930 --> 00:31:38,770
就不会闹上法庭了
there wouldn't be a lawsuit.

1006
00:31:39,020 --> 00:31:40,070
法庭是要上的
Well, there is one,

1007
00:31:41,050 --> 00:31:41,860
但不是要告你
but not against you.

1008
00:31:42,500 --> 00:31:43,300
是要跟你并肩作战
With you.

1009
00:31:43,850 --> 00:31:45,100
我们知道阿伯丁的事了
We know about Aberdeen.

1010
00:31:45,580 --> 00:31:47,200
我们托莉在搞什么名堂
We know what Tori was orchestrating.

1011
00:31:47,410 --> 00:31:49,590
有你帮忙  我们能揭发她
And with your help, we can expose her.

1012
00:31:53,500 --> 00:31:54,300
我凭什么帮你
Why should I help you?

1013
00:31:55,490 --> 00:31:56,750
帮了对你有什么坏处吗
What have you got to lose?

1014
00:32:02,820 --> 00:32:03,800
告诉我你要我做什么
Tell me what you need me to do.

1015
00:32:12,190 --> 00:32:13,710
他现在又让你找什么了
What does he have you trying to find this time?

1016
00:32:14,380 --> 00:32:15,200
你真想知道吗
You really want to know?

1017
00:32:19,030 --> 00:32:21,330
我曾看到了一些与我们会计事务所
Uh, I managed to get a look at some files

1018
00:32:21,550 --> 00:32:22,770
相关的文件
involving our accounting firm.

1019
00:32:23,400 --> 00:32:24,550
我们的会计事务所怎么了
What's up with our accounting firm?

1020
00:32:25,340 --> 00:32:26,380
他们在偷我们的钱
They're stealing from us.

1021
00:32:28,330 --> 00:32:29,160
你想想你的电话费
You know your phone bill?

1022
00:32:29,810 --> 00:32:30,840
有很多附加费用
You have all those surcharges,

1023
00:32:31,040 --> 00:32:32,510
你并不知道那些是什么  但你照付不误
you have no idea what they mean, but you pay 'em anyway.

1024
00:32:32,760 --> 00:32:33,480
对
Yeah.

1025
00:32:33,680 --> 00:32:35,130
雷贝克也在跟我们来这套
Yeah, well, Drybeck's doing the same thing to us,

1026
00:32:35,350 --> 00:32:37,780
不过他们的收费完全是欺诈
Except all their charges are a complete scam.

1027
00:32:37,970 --> 00:32:39,800
我确信电话费也是欺诈
Pretty sure the phone charges are scams, too.

1028
00:32:40,470 --> 00:32:41,470
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.

1029
00:32:41,700 --> 00:32:42,740
那你需要什么
So what do you need?

1030
00:32:43,780 --> 00:32:46,060
我需要一个合法的理由去拿到那些

