1
00:00:00,880 --> 00:00:02,570
《诉讼双雄》前情提要

2
00:00:02,720 --> 00:00:04,660
找我们麻烦的不是伍德尔  是...
It's not Woodall coming after us, it's--

3
00:00:04,660 --> 00:00:06,020
肖恩·卡荷尔
Sean Cahill.

4
00:00:06,580 --> 00:00:08,380
欢迎来到崭新的证监会
Welcome to the new S.E.C.

5
00:00:08,380 --> 00:00:10,120
我们针对律所出击
We target law firms.

6
00:00:10,120 --> 00:00:11,180
傅滋曼先生
Mr. Forstman.

7
00:00:11,270 --> 00:00:11,880
不行
No.

8
00:00:11,880 --> 00:00:14,440
你会错过报复哈维·斯佩克特的好机会
You'll miss the opportunity to get back at Harvey Specter.

9
00:00:14,890 --> 00:00:16,330
我投两亿三千万
You've got my 230 mil.

10
00:00:16,330 --> 00:00:17,990
说一旦交易结束
Once the deal closes,

11
00:00:18,570 --> 00:00:19,900
你就会把西德威尔踢出去
you cut Sidwell out.

12
00:00:19,940 --> 00:00:22,210
你以前说"你觉得你走了我还会留吗"
What happened to, "You think I'm staying if you leave"?

13
00:00:22,210 --> 00:00:23,470
对  那是我知道
Yeah, that was before I knew

14
00:00:23,470 --> 00:00:24,550
你要伤害西德威尔之前
you were gonna screw over Sidwell.

15
00:00:24,550 --> 00:00:26,270
傅滋曼可不会做没有回报
Forstman doesn't throw money around

16
00:00:26,270 --> 00:00:27,640
白白撒钱的亏本生意
without getting something in return.

17
00:00:27,640 --> 00:00:29,130
我别无选择了
I have no other choice!

18
00:00:29,130 --> 00:00:31,780
那我们就要这样一直互还人情吗
So we're just gonna go back and forth, trading favors?

19
00:00:31,880 --> 00:00:33,210
你到底做不做我的律师
Are you my lawyer or not?

20
00:00:33,390 --> 00:00:34,310
说真的  瑞秋
Seriously, Rachel,

21
00:00:34,310 --> 00:00:35,650
没有你  我根本做不到
I couldn't have done it without you.

22
00:00:36,940 --> 00:00:38,220
洛根  我该走了
Logan, I should go.

23
00:00:53,600 --> 00:00:54,990
洛根·桑德斯来电

24
00:00:58,890 --> 00:00:59,850
迈克
Mike?

25
00:01:02,110 --> 00:01:02,940
在这儿
Right here.

26
00:01:02,940 --> 00:01:04,730
-你把我闹钟关了吗  -是啊
- Did you turn off my alarm? - I did.

27
00:01:04,730 --> 00:01:05,820
都过九点了
It's after 9:00.

28
00:01:05,820 --> 00:01:07,250
我都睡了...
I have been sleeping for--

29
00:01:07,250 --> 00:01:08,700
快六小时了  我知道
Almost six hours. I know.

30
00:01:08,700 --> 00:01:10,080
可事实是  你需要再睡久点
And the truth is, you need more.

31
00:01:10,080 --> 00:01:11,280
你干嘛这么做
Why would you do that?

32
00:01:11,280 --> 00:01:12,860
瑞秋  你最近一直
Rachel, you've been running back and forth

33
00:01:12,860 --> 00:01:14,810
在学校和公司之间疯了似的奔波
between school and the firm like a maniac.

34
00:01:14,810 --> 00:01:16,860
我都记不得你上次好好睡觉是什么时候了
I don't even remember the last time you got a good night's sleep.

35
00:01:16,860 --> 00:01:17,870
那你也不能那么做
It doesn't give you the right to do that.

36
00:01:17,870 --> 00:01:19,350
而且  哈维会杀了我的
Plus, Harvey's gonna kill me.

37
00:01:19,370 --> 00:01:19,890
他会原谅你的
He'll get over it.

38
00:01:19,890 --> 00:01:21,240
而且我还要写三份报告
And I've got three briefs to write,

39
00:01:21,240 --> 00:01:24,440
一份侵权法论文  明天还有合同法考试
plus a paper for torts and a contracts exam tomorrow.

40
00:01:24,440 --> 00:01:25,880
我根本没有时间睡觉
I don't have the luxury to sleep in.

41
00:01:25,880 --> 00:01:29,150
那你就得让哈维这周放你歇一天
Then you need to ask Harvey for a day off this week.

42
00:01:29,170 --> 00:01:31,620
你工作太累的时候他给过你假期吗
Did he ever give you time off because you were overworked?

43
00:01:33,970 --> 00:01:35,350
-没有  -这不就得了
- No, he didn't. - Exactly.

44
00:01:35,350 --> 00:01:36,740
我可不想搞特殊
I don't want to be any different.

45
00:01:39,730 --> 00:01:42,140
贾米森先生  你将被遣回
Mr. Jamieson, you are hereby remanded

46
00:01:42,140 --> 00:01:45,350
康涅狄格州  丹伯里的联邦监狱
to the federal penitentiary in Danbury, Connecticut.

47
00:01:51,310 --> 00:01:53,430
想上诉打给我
You might want to call me about an appeal.

48
00:01:53,430 --> 00:01:56,130
这个检察官经常违规行事
The prosecutor has a reputation for bending the rules.

49
00:01:57,320 --> 00:02:00,240
你一定是臭名昭著的哈维·斯佩克特吧
You must be the infamous Harvey Specter.

50
00:02:00,260 --> 00:02:02,670
你一定是受了埃里克·伍德尔指示
And you must be the chump Eric Woodall

51
00:02:02,670 --> 00:02:03,790
来针对我的笨蛋
ordered to come after me.

52
00:02:03,930 --> 00:02:05,250
笨蛋是我母亲家的姓氏
Chump's my name on my mother's side.

53
00:02:05,380 --> 00:02:06,370
还是叫我卡荷尔吧
I do prefer Cahill.

54
00:02:06,370 --> 00:02:08,470
你还是别再编造谎言
And I prefer you stop manufacturing bullshit

55
00:02:08,470 --> 00:02:09,880
让我的客户背叛我
to get my clients to turn on me.

56
00:02:09,880 --> 00:02:11,800
抱歉  我从不编造什么
I'm sorry, I'm not in the manufacturing business.

57
00:02:12,130 --> 00:02:13,860
我只是公务员一个
I'm just a humble civil servant.

58
00:02:13,860 --> 00:02:15,190
如果你真如自己声称的那么洁身自好
And if you're as clean as you say you are,

59
00:02:15,190 --> 00:02:16,740
你的客户也说不出什么来
your clients won't have anything to give us.

60
00:02:16,740 --> 00:02:18,660
除非你恐吓他们  让他们编造谎话
Unless you bully them into making things up.

61
00:02:18,660 --> 00:02:20,360
我觉得你把我们的角色弄混了
Oh, see, now I think you've got us confused,

62
00:02:20,360 --> 00:02:21,930
这听起来更像你会做的事
because that sounds like something that you might do.

63
00:02:21,930 --> 00:02:24,360
重点是  肖恩  你有个秘密小计划
The point is, Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst Sean, you hadst

64
00:05:36,970 --> 00:05:41,970
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

65
00:05:41,970 --> 00:05:46,970
翻译：草草  潇湘月影  爱卿遛小鸟  王大可  杳杳君   某羽  Reginamoon

66
00:05:46,970 --> 00:05:51,970
翻译：王小麦   鱼小姐啦   CS漫画家小明   校对：油炸电风扇    潇湘月影

67
00:05:51,970 --> 00:05:56,970
时间轴：阿丹    猫   今    芒果树叶

68
00:05:56,970 --> 00:06:01,970
后期：斯人&加森      精校&总监：某羽

69
00:06:02,820 --> 00:06:04,960
诉 讼 双 雄

70
00:06:02,820 --> 00:06:04,960
第四季   第五集

