1
00:06:09,180 --> 00:06:14,180
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:06:09,180 --> 00:06:14,180
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:06:09,180 --> 00:06:14,180
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:06:09,180 --> 00:06:14,180
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:06:09,180 --> 00:06:14,180
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:06:14,180 --> 00:06:19,180
{\an8}翻译：草草  feilixiaozi  CS漫画家小明  潇湘月影  香茗小焙  Reginamoon

7
00:06:19,180 --> 00:06:24,180
{\an8}翻译：王大可  某羽  小饭  校对：油炸电风扇   潇湘月影

8
00:06:24,180 --> 00:06:29,180
{\an8}时间轴：今    猫

9
00:06:29,180 --> 00:06:34,180
{\an8}后期：斯人&加森      精校&总监：某羽

10
00:06:35,040 --> 00:06:37,180
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

11
00:06:35,040 --> 00:06:37,180
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第十集

12
00:00:01,010 --> 00:00:02,220
{\pos(189,213)}《诉讼双雄》前情提要

13
00:00:02,320 --> 00:00:04,000
希拉·阿曼达·赛斯
Sheila Amanda Sazs

14
00:00:04,000 --> 00:00:05,180
你愿意嫁给我吗
will you marry me?

15
00:00:05,180 --> 00:00:07,140
我愿意嫁给你
Yes, I'll marry you.

16
00:00:07,630 --> 00:00:09,840
等我们有孩子了  全世界就等着看吧
And when we have kids, world, watch out.

17
00:00:09,840 --> 00:00:11,220
路易  我不想要孩子
Louis, I don't want kids.

18
00:00:11,220 --> 00:00:12,920
希拉  我会成为父亲的
Sheila, I'm gonna be a father.

19
00:00:13,080 --> 00:00:15,010
迈克·罗斯不能回来
Mike Ross is not coming back to this firm.

20
00:00:15,010 --> 00:00:16,870
你听到路易的话  他已经把工作给他了
You heard Louis. He already gave him the job.

21
00:00:16,870 --> 00:00:18,760
我想知道你到底为什么回来
I want to know why the hell you came back.

22
00:00:18,760 --> 00:00:20,670
重要的是我会留下来
What matters is that I'm staying

23
00:00:20,800 --> 00:00:22,500
因为我就属于这里
because this is where I belong.

24
00:00:22,500 --> 00:00:24,060
这份文件会表明傅滋曼的付款
This makes it look like Forstman's payment never

25
00:00:24,060 --> 00:00:25,600
从未经过任何离岸账户
went to any offshore accounts

26
00:00:25,600 --> 00:00:26,910
而且跟你毫无关系
and that you never took a piece of it.

27
00:00:26,910 --> 00:00:27,830
这可是伪造
No, that's forgery.

28
00:00:27,830 --> 00:00:30,650
那也比你犯下的罪行要轻
Which is less of a crime than what you did.

29
00:00:30,750 --> 00:00:31,740
我没得选
I had no choice!

30
00:00:31,740 --> 00:00:33,120
去你的没得选
Bullshit, you had no choice!

31
00:00:33,120 --> 00:00:35,870
你可以在任何一个时点上说不
You could've said no at any goddamn point along the way.

32
00:00:35,870 --> 00:00:37,390
有一件事是板上定钉的
One thing is for sure.

33
00:00:37,390 --> 00:00:40,390
当一切结束之后  我会把你炒掉
When all this is over, I'm gonna fire the shit out of you.

34
00:00:40,390 --> 00:00:42,730
如果不是路易  我不可能回来
I wouldn't be back here if it wasn't for Louis.

35
00:00:45,200 --> 00:00:46,570
我来解决
I'll take care of it.

36
00:00:47,450 --> 00:00:48,890
亲爱的哈维和杰西卡
Dear Harvey and Jessica,

37
00:00:48,890 --> 00:00:51,550
我确实为了个人利益  害你们身陷危急
I put all of you in jeopardy for my own personal gain.

38
00:00:51,550 --> 00:00:52,650
立刻生效
Effective immediately,

39
00:00:52,650 --> 00:00:54,820
我  路易·利特
I, Louis Litt,

40
00:00:54,860 --> 00:00:57,180
从皮尔逊-斯佩克特辞职
am resigning from Pearson Specter.

41
00:00:58,000 --> 00:00:59,790
请照看好我的家
Please take care of my home.

42
00:01:22,470 --> 00:01:24,390
-一  二  -等我一下
- One, two. - Give me a second, gimme a sec.

43
00:01:26,530 --> 00:01:27,700
这身衣服不合适
You're not dressed for it.

44
00:01:27,700 --> 00:01:30,130
或许我们可以给你找条短裤  打几回合
Maybe we can get you some trunks, go a few rounds.

45
00:01:30,290 --> 00:01:32,250
我已经练过身手了
I think I've already gone a few rounds.

46
00:01:32,910 --> 00:01:34,180
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.

47
00:01:35,580 --> 00:01:37,490
说吧  要我帮什么
Anything. What can I do for you?

48
00:01:37,490 --> 00:01:39,790
客户  我需要客户
Clients. I need clients.

49
00:01:39,790 --> 00:01:41,830
路易  章程规定
Louis, the by-laws say that--

50
00:01:41,830 --> 00:01:43,710
得了  哈维  你以为我不知道章程吗
Come on, Harvey. You think I don't know what they say?

51
00:01:43,710 --> 00:01:44,870
都是我写的
I wrote the by-laws.

52
00:01:44,870 --> 00:01:46,810
那你是为谁写的呢
Yeah, and who'd you write 'em for, huh?

53
00:01:47,070 --> 00:01:50,390
是杰西卡  她不会为你破例的
Jessica, and she's not gonna make an exception for you.

54
00:01:50,390 --> 00:01:51,270
那她或许会为你破例
Well, maybe she'll make one for you?

55
00:01:51,270 --> 00:01:52,640
不可能的
She's not going to.

56
00:01:52,640 --> 00:01:53,910
哈维  你以为我想来吗
Harvey, do you think I want to be here?

57
00:01:53,910 --> 00:01:56,130
我联系了六家律所面试
I tried to get interviews at six different firms

58
00:01:56,130 --> 00:01:58,310
每一家的答复都一样
and every one of them said the same thing:

59
00:01:58,310 --> 00:02:00,010
现在竞争很激烈
it's a bloodbath out there.

60
00:02:00,010 --> 00:02:01,640
所以如果我不能带走客户
Which means if I can't bring business with me,

61
00:02:01,640 --> 00:02:02,670
还不如搬去西伯利亚
I might as well move to Siberia

62
00:02:02,670 --> 00:02:04,620
因为我在这儿是别想找到工作了
because I'm never gonna find a job in this city.

63
00:02:04,620 --> 00:02:05,570
-路易  -哈维
- Louis... - Harvey.

64
00:02:05,570 --> 00:02:07,300
我没要你给我摘月亮
I'm not askin' for the moon.

65
00:02:07,840 --> 00:02:09,960
只要三家我自己拉来的客户
Just three companies that I brought to the firm myself

66
00:02:09,960 --> 00:02:11,230
三个当时还默默无闻的公司
when they were nothing.

67
00:02:16,210 --> 00:02:17,730
我去跟杰西卡谈谈
Let me talk to Jessica.

68
00:02:17,890 --> 00:02:19,170
谢谢
Thank you.

69
00:02:33,680 --> 00:02:35,390
哈维  你看上去不太忙啊
Harvey, you don't look busy.

70
00:02:35,390 --> 00:02:37,860
要去参加国际证券
Would you like to attend the International Securities

71
00:02:37,860 --> 00:02:39,740
-法规论坛吗  -看情况
- Law Symposium? - That depends.

72
00:02:39,740 --> 00:02:41,620
是在维加斯  迈阿密  还是里约
Is it in Vegas, Miami, or Rio?

73
00:02:41,620 --> 00:02:44,610
-波基普西  -派保罗·波特去吧
- Poughkeepsie. - Send Paul Porter.

74
00:02:45,230 --> 00:02:46,560
有什么事吗
What can I do for you?

75
00:02:47,580 --> 00:02:49,050
我刚刚见了路易
I just saw Louis.

76
00:02:49,530 --> 00:02:52,160
不行  他别想拉走客户
No. He's not getting any clients.

77
00:02:52,160 --> 00:02:53,650
他只想要三个
He just wants three.

78
00:02:53,650 --> 00:02:55,290
放弃这三个对我们没什么损伤
Letting them go won't break us.

79
00:02:55,290 --> 00:02:57,590
的确  但这会开这种坏先例
No, it won't, but it will open the floodgates for 

80
00:02:57,590 --> 00:02:59,750
每个想离开并带走客户的
every partner that ever thought of leaving 

81
00:02:59,750 --> 00:03:01,130
合伙人都会效仿
and taking their clients.

82
00:03:01,130 --> 00:03:02,320
他不是一般的合伙人
He's not every partner

83
00:03:02,320 --> 00:03:04,520
而且他曾为我们拼死卖命过
and he's worked his fingers to the bone for both of us,

84
00:03:04,520 --> 00:03:05,960
现在要求的也并不多
and he's asking for a crumb.

85
00:03:05,960 --> 00:03:08,050
我要是满足他了  接下来
And I give him that crumb, and next thing you know,

86
00:03:08,050 --> 00:03:09,890
就一发不可收拾了
all the cookies in the cabinet are gone.

87
00:03:09,890 --> 00:03:10,860
这未必
You don't know that.

88
00:03:10,860 --> 00:03:13,580
我确定的是你不该在这儿说
I do know that instead of talking about 

89
00:03:13,580 --> 00:03:15,480
要送出路易的客户
giving Louis' clients away,

90
00:03:15,510 --> 00:03:18,020
而是该操心怎么保住自己的客户
you should be working on keeping your own.

91
00:03:18,050 --> 00:03:21,010
杰西卡  我会想办法留下回春制药
Jessica, I'll find a way to keep Versalife,

92
00:03:21,010 --> 00:03:23,000
但那跟路易无关
but that has nothing to do with Louis.

93
00:03:23,000 --> 00:03:24,370
我们欠他的
We owe the man something.

94
00:03:24,370 --> 00:03:26,700
我会给他回报
And I'm giving him something.

95
00:03:26,860 --> 00:03:29,940
如果有人来问我  我一定全力推荐
My phone rings and he gets a glowing recommendation

96
00:03:29,940 --> 00:03:33,540
而不会说他是犯下了重罪才会离开
instead of me saying that he left after committing a felony.

97
00:03:33,540 --> 00:03:35,500
如果他连门都进不去不会有人来要推荐
No one's gonna call if he can't get in the door.

98
00:03:35,500 --> 00:03:37,970
那是他的事  不是我的
That's on him, not on me.

99
00:03:51,110 --> 00:03:53,180
这样真的好吗
Are you sure we should be doing this?

100
00:03:53,530 --> 00:03:54,750
你想要破产部的
You really want those vultures

101
00:03:54,750 --> 00:03:56,420
那些秃鹰来挑拣他的东西吗
in bankruptcy picking through his stuff?

102
00:03:56,420 --> 00:03:59,230
我只是觉得翻他的东西太不好
It just doesn't feel okay going through his things.

103
00:03:59,230 --> 00:04:01,380
瑞秋  你没有他的消息  我也是
Rachel, you haven't heard from him. I haven't heard from him.

104
00:04:01,380 --> 00:04:03,210
如果我们不替他收拾东西  谁来做啊
If we don't pack up his stuff, who will?

105
00:04:03,210 --> 00:04:05,060
看来我们想到一起了
I guess you guys had the same idea I did.

106
00:04:05,060 --> 00:04:06,250
是啊
Yeah.

107
00:04:06,250 --> 00:04:08,070
-那个他都没拿吗  -嗯
- He didn't take that either? - No.

108
00:04:09,280 --> 00:04:10,160
我刚刚清洁过
I just cleaned it.

109
00:04:10,160 --> 00:04:12,940
弄脏了  我不想脏兮兮地拿给他
It was smudged and I didn't want to give it back to him dirty.

110
00:04:12,940 --> 00:04:15,010
他肯定走得很匆忙
He must have been in such a hurry.

111
00:04:15,870 --> 00:04:17,830
他那么匆忙是因为他不好意思
He was in a hurry 'cause he was ashamed.

112
00:04:19,610 --> 00:04:21,730
我只想赶快了结这事
I want to just get this over with.

113
00:04:29,810 --> 00:04:32,480
-杰西卡  你...  -在这儿干什么
- Jessica, what... - Am I doing here?

114
00:04:33,340 --> 00:04:36,400
我是来告诉你  我知道你知道
I'm here to tell you that I know you know the truth

115
00:04:36,400 --> 00:04:38,150
路易辞职的真相
about Louis' resignation.

116
00:04:38,150 --> 00:04:38,730
我不知道
I don't know--

117
00:04:38,730 --> 00:04:41,950
你知道  我想你对此并不高兴
Yes, you do, and I'm guessing you didn't like it.

118
00:04:42,880 --> 00:04:44,100
是的
You're right.

119
00:04:44,100 --> 00:04:45,330
的确
I didn't.

120
00:04:45,330 --> 00:04:48,040
我觉得他不该被解雇
Because I don't think that he deserves to be fired.

121
00:04:48,040 --> 00:04:51,820
有意思  因为我觉得你俩都该被解雇
That's funny, because I think you both deserve to be fired.

122
00:04:51,820 --> 00:04:53,870
-什么...  -你知道他做了什么
- What do you... - You knew what he did,

123
00:04:54,200 --> 00:04:55,810
却什么都没说
and you said nothing.

124
00:04:56,120 --> 00:04:57,850
你是为这个来的啊
So that's why you're here.

125
00:04:58,930 --> 00:04:59,760
解雇我的
To fire me.

126
00:04:59,760 --> 00:05:04,020
不  我是来给你第二次机会的
No. I'm here to give you a second chance.

127
00:05:20,150 --> 00:05:21,410
那些看着不像我的卷宗
Those don't look like my case files.

128
00:05:21,410 --> 00:05:23,660
的确不是  但我不是空手前来
They're not, but I didn't come empty-handed.

129
00:05:23,660 --> 00:05:25,540
-我给你带了点东西  -工作吗
- I got you somethin'. - A job?

130
00:05:25,660 --> 00:05:28,720
宝洁公司法律总顾问
General counsel at Procter & Gamble.

131
00:05:28,720 --> 00:05:31,070
宝洁公司  你逗我呢
Procter & Gamble? What is that, a joke?

132
00:05:31,070 --> 00:05:32,590
他们公司在辛辛那提  
They're in Cincinnati, 

133
00:05:32,590 --> 00:05:34,120
那就是美国的西伯利亚啊
which is like, American for "Siberia."

134
00:05:34,120 --> 00:05:37,160
他们是世界五百强企业第31名
It's American for "Number 31 on the fortune 500,"

135
00:05:37,160 --> 00:05:38,960
而且是重新开始的机会
and it's a chance to make a fresh start.

136
00:05:38,960 --> 00:05:40,540
这是谁的主意
Whose idea was this chance?

137
00:05:40,540 --> 00:05:41,920
女王陛下吗
Her Majesty?

138
00:05:42,210 --> 00:05:43,830
她肯定可开心了
Oh, yeah, I bet she loved that.

139
00:05:43,830 --> 00:05:45,420
让我滚蛋  永远不用再见到我
Ship me off and never see me again.

140
00:05:45,420 --> 00:05:47,660
路易  这是我的主意  你该抓住这机会
Louis, it was my idea, and you should take it.

141
00:05:47,660 --> 00:05:48,990
换你会吗
Well, would you take it?

142
00:05:49,720 --> 00:05:50,870
才不会呢
No way on earth.

143
00:05:50,870 --> 00:05:51,930
你知道为什么吗
You know why?

144
00:05:51,930 --> 00:05:53,910
因为这里是罗马
Because this is Rome,

145
00:05:54,100 --> 00:05:56,490
而你是角斗士  我也是
you're a gladiator, and so am I.

146
00:05:56,490 --> 00:05:57,800
那就做个角斗士
Then be a gladiator.

147
00:05:57,800 --> 00:06:00,780
接受这份工作  再慢慢打回来
Take this job and fight your way back here.

148
00:06:00,780 --> 00:06:04,610
我不用跑去辛辛那提才能打回来
I don't have to go to Cincinnati to fight my way back here.

149
00:06:04,610 --> 00:06:06,720
我能打败杰西卡
I can goddamn fight Jessica.

150
00:06:42,500 --> 00:06:43,770
你来收拾东西吗
You're here to pick up your things?

151
00:06:43,770 --> 00:06:46,210
我是来带走属于我的三个客户的
I'm here to pick the three clients that are mine.

152
00:06:46,430 --> 00:06:49,240
那些客户  和律所的所有客户一样
Those clients, like everyone this firm represents,

153
00:06:49,240 --> 00:06:51,430
都属于我  你对此无能为力
belong to me, and there's nothing you can do about it.

154
00:06:51,430 --> 00:06:53,720
我当然能  因为根据公司规章
Oh yes there is, 'cause pursuant to the by-laws,

155
00:06:53,720 --> 00:06:56,460
任何律师离职你都需要通知客户
you're required to inform clients of any attorney's departure.

156
00:06:56,460 --> 00:06:59,480
如果你在正式辞退我之前没有通知他们
If you fail to do so prior to me giving you formal notice,

157
00:06:59,480 --> 00:07:00,820
他们就任我挑了
they're up for grabs.

158
00:07:00,820 --> 00:07:02,570
公司的规章都是你起草的
Well, you wrote the by-laws.

159
00:07:02,570 --> 00:07:04,030
我就相信你说的是真的
I'll take your word that's what they say.

160
00:07:04,030 --> 00:07:06,410
我懂了  你觉得我撬不走他们吧
Oh, I see. You don't think I can take 'em from you, huh?

161
00:07:06,550 --> 00:07:08,630
把他们介绍来的人是我
Well, I'm the one who brought them in

162
00:07:08,630 --> 00:07:10,340
天不亮就接他们电话的人也是我
and answered their call at 4:00 in the morning,

163
00:07:10,340 --> 00:07:12,900
而你只是坐享分成而已
when all you did was take your cut.

164
00:07:12,900 --> 00:07:13,970
是吗
Is that all I did?

165
00:07:13,970 --> 00:07:15,870
是的  所以我能赢走他们
Yes, and that's why I'm gonna win them,

166
00:07:15,870 --> 00:07:17,020
因为那是我应得的
because I deserve them.

167
00:07:17,020 --> 00:07:19,830
你一直都这么觉得是吗  路易
And that's what it always is with you, Louis, isn't it?

168
00:07:19,830 --> 00:07:20,810
你应得的
What you deserve.

169
00:07:20,810 --> 00:07:22,250
你说对了
You're goddamn right it is,

170
00:07:22,250 --> 00:07:24,030
我为你鞠躬尽瘁
And you have some nerve tellin' me no

171
00:07:24,030 --> 00:07:25,730
你还真有胆拒绝我
after all I've done for you.

172
00:07:25,990 --> 00:07:29,140
你做了违法的事
What you've done is break the law,

173
00:07:29,220 --> 00:07:31,610
而我依旧愿意给你写推荐信
and I'm still willing to give you a good recommendation.

174
00:07:31,610 --> 00:07:35,010
我才不需要你那破推荐信
I don't need your bullshit recommendation.

175
00:07:35,010 --> 00:07:37,150
我要的是客户  要是你不给我
I need clients, and if you're not gonna give 'em to me,

176
00:07:37,150 --> 00:07:38,350
你最好把他们看牢了
you better strap in,

177
00:07:38,350 --> 00:07:39,810
因为我会抢走他们的
because I'm gonna take 'em.

178
00:07:44,790 --> 00:07:45,880
路易
Louis.

179
00:07:45,880 --> 00:07:47,690
你一直没回我电话
You haven't returned any of my phone calls.

180
00:07:47,690 --> 00:07:49,660
过渡期我不想跟任何人联系
I don't like contact during transitional periods.

181
00:07:49,660 --> 00:07:51,270
可你连再见都没说
But you didn't even say goodbye.

182
00:07:51,270 --> 00:07:52,780
有什么好说的  卡特里娜
What is there to say, Katrina?

183
00:07:52,780 --> 00:07:54,030
这个...
Well...

184
00:07:54,920 --> 00:07:56,440
等你整理好了
When you're ready,

185
00:07:56,860 --> 00:07:58,410
我们希望能一起吃顿饭
I would love to take you out for dinner.

186
00:07:58,410 --> 00:08:00,300
这做不到  我们现在是敌人
We can't do that. You're on the other side now.

187
00:08:00,300 --> 00:08:02,060
-这是什么意思  -我告诉杰西卡了
- What are you talking about? - I gave Jessica notice.

188
00:08:02,060 --> 00:08:03,140
我要带走三个客户
I'm going after three clients.

189
00:08:03,140 --> 00:08:03,910
-路易  -别劝了
- Louis-- - No-no-no.

190
00:08:03,910 --> 00:08:05,000
我们注定刀剑相向了
We're gonna go do battle,

191
00:08:05,000 --> 00:08:06,110
我想让你陷入
And I do not want to put you in the position

192
00:08:06,110 --> 00:08:07,420
亲敌的处境当中
to fraternize with the enemy.

193
00:08:07,420 --> 00:08:09,210
你不是敌人  路易
You're not the enemy, Louis.

194
00:08:10,510 --> 00:08:13,520
杰西卡已经让我亲自联系了你的所有旧客户
Jessica had me contact all of your old clients in person.

195
00:08:15,140 --> 00:08:16,210
她让你干了什么
She what?

196
00:08:16,210 --> 00:08:18,790
你不能联系他们了  一切都结束了
You can't approach them. It's over.

197
00:08:19,950 --> 00:08:21,410
我得走了
I have to get going.

198
00:08:22,000 --> 00:08:23,270
路易
Louis!

199
00:08:23,640 --> 00:08:24,830
对不起
I am so sorry.

200
00:08:24,830 --> 00:08:26,980
-我也不想这么做  -别道歉
- I didn't want to do it. - Don't be.

201
00:08:26,980 --> 00:08:29,120
如果总得有人做这件事  我很庆幸是你
If it had to be somebody, I'm glad it was you.

202
00:08:31,030 --> 00:08:32,080
我正处理合并案呢
I'm in the middle of a merger.

203
00:08:32,080 --> 00:08:33,460
什么事这么重要还得让我下楼
What's so important that I had to come down

204
00:08:33,460 --> 00:08:34,280
到你这破办公室来
to your shitty office?

205
00:08:34,280 --> 00:08:35,900
这破办公室原来是你的
This used to be your shitty office.

206
00:08:35,900 --> 00:08:37,790
之后还有六个人用过
And after that, it belonged to six other people,

207
00:08:37,790 --> 00:08:39,230
其中五个已经不在律所了
five of whom are now gone.

208
00:08:39,230 --> 00:08:40,030
你想说什么
What's your point?

209
00:08:40,030 --> 00:08:42,090
眨眼间风云变幻
That things can change in the blink of an eye.

210
00:08:43,520 --> 00:08:45,250
-你想谈路易  -没错
- Louis. - Yes, Louis.

211
00:08:45,250 --> 00:08:47,660
把他的名字从墙上抠掉只用了十秒
Took all of ten seconds to scrape his name off the wall.

212
00:08:47,660 --> 00:08:50,200
你觉得杰西卡抠掉我的名字会用多久
How long do you think it's gonna take Jessica to scrape off mine?

213
00:08:50,200 --> 00:08:51,190
你在找什么  迈克
What are you lookin' for, Mike?

214
00:08:51,190 --> 00:08:53,850
哈维  杰西卡视我为大患
Harvey, Jessica sees me as a huge problem.

215
00:08:53,850 --> 00:08:55,500
解决的方法只有除掉我
The solution is just to get rid of me.

216
00:08:55,500 --> 00:08:56,450
我不想让那种事发生
I don't want that to happen, 

217
00:08:56,450 --> 00:08:58,840
所以得解决个比我自身更大的问题
so I need to solve an even bigger problem.

218
00:08:58,840 --> 00:09:01,150
你想让我给你个大问题
And you want me to give you a bigger problem.

219
00:09:01,150 --> 00:09:02,410
我才刚回来  你得把手上
I just got back. I need you to give me

220
00:09:02,410 --> 00:09:04,410
-最大的案子给我  -好吧
- the biggest problem you've got. - Fine.

221
00:09:04,410 --> 00:09:07,700
斯图灵制药要与辉瑞制药合并
Sterling Pharmaceuticals is merging with Pfizer.

222
00:09:09,100 --> 00:09:11,180
来吧  聪明人  你不是想解决问题吗
Come on, smart guy. You want to solve the problem?

223
00:09:11,180 --> 00:09:12,350
你最好能看出问题在哪
You better be able to identify it.

224
00:09:12,350 --> 00:09:13,790
没什么问题啊  他们合并而已
There is no problem. They merge.

225
00:09:13,790 --> 00:09:16,650
他们总共只占市场份额的26%
They only make up 26% of the market.

226
00:09:16,650 --> 00:09:19,410
没有超过10b-6条款的限制
That's--that's not over the limit for 10b-6.

227
00:09:19,410 --> 00:09:20,670
但是呢
But?

228
00:09:22,110 --> 00:09:23,350
见鬼
Shit.

229
00:09:23,350 --> 00:09:24,860
加上回春制药就超了
Versalife puts us over the limit.

230
00:09:24,860 --> 00:09:25,860
我们得放弃他们了
We have to drop them.

231
00:09:25,860 --> 00:09:28,600
除非我们能想个办法打10b-6的擦边球
Unless we figure out a way around 10b-6.

232
00:09:28,600 --> 00:09:30,580
就像我跟杰西卡保证的那样
Like I told Jessica I would.

233
00:09:31,040 --> 00:09:32,070
你跟她这么说了
You told her that?

234
00:09:32,070 --> 00:09:33,980
哈维  没人做到过这种事
Harvey, no one has ever been able to do that.

235
00:09:33,980 --> 00:09:35,530
要想一鸣惊人
Listen to me. You want to make a splash?

236
00:09:35,530 --> 00:09:37,000
学摩西分开红海吧
Part the Red Sea.

237
00:09:43,200 --> 00:09:45,680
-不是吧  -不是什么
- Oh, no. - "Oh, no," What?

238
00:09:45,680 --> 00:09:46,810
你脸上又是那种表情
You have that look on your face

239
00:09:46,810 --> 00:09:48,810
那种想跟我来一段我不想谈的
like you want me to have some emotional conversation

240
00:09:48,810 --> 00:09:50,560
-感性对话的表情  -别猜了  哈维
- I don't feel like having. - You know what, Harvey?

241
00:09:50,560 --> 00:09:52,320
我只是进来看看你有没有什么需要
I just came in here to see if you needed anything.

242
00:09:52,320 --> 00:09:54,320
-没有  -那好吧
- I don't. - Okay, fine.

243
00:09:55,800 --> 00:09:58,250
我知道路易这些事
Listen, I know that this whole thing with Louis

244
00:09:58,250 --> 00:09:58,970
让你很失落
is upsetting you.

245
00:09:58,970 --> 00:10:00,710
不  让我失落的是你明明说
No. What's upsetting me, is you saying

246
00:10:00,710 --> 00:10:02,120
进来是为了看我有没有需要
you're here to see if I need anything

247
00:10:02,120 --> 00:10:03,730
而你其实是想跟我谈路易的事
when you really want to talk about Louis.

248
00:10:03,730 --> 00:10:05,880
我很担心他  他的处境很不利
I'm worried about him. He's in a really bad place.

249
00:10:05,880 --> 00:10:07,550
你以为我不知道吗  所有我才想帮他
You think I don't know that? That's why I tried to help him.

250
00:10:07,550 --> 00:10:09,440
我把一份工作送到了他面前
I got him a job on a silver platter

251
00:10:09,440 --> 00:10:10,330
可他毫不领情
and he threw it in my face.

252
00:10:10,330 --> 00:10:11,250
他不该拒绝的
And he shouldn't have done that.

253
00:10:11,250 --> 00:10:13,300
说的对  那你还进来干嘛
Yeah. Then why are you here?

254
00:10:13,510 --> 00:10:15,380
因为我觉得我们还能帮他
Because I still think we can help.

255
00:10:19,020 --> 00:10:20,070
-唐娜  -哈维
- Donna-- - Harvey.

256
00:10:20,070 --> 00:10:22,330
你帮他找工作是好事
You did a good thing by getting him that job.

257
00:10:22,330 --> 00:10:24,670
出发点是好的  但搞错了城市
It was the right instinct, but it was the wrong city.

258
00:10:24,670 --> 00:10:26,510
可我没法帮他找到纽约的工作
Yeah, I can't get him anything in New York.

259
00:10:26,510 --> 00:10:28,110
我指的不是纽约
I'm not talking about New York.

260
00:10:28,110 --> 00:10:30,150
那到底是哪儿
Then what the hell are you talking about?

261
00:10:37,730 --> 00:10:39,050
这一轮打得不错
Nice grouping.

262
00:10:40,290 --> 00:10:41,710
你怎么知道我在这儿
How'd you know I'd be here?

263
00:10:42,430 --> 00:10:44,050
因为你高兴的时候会去洗泥巴浴
Because you go mudding when you're happy,

264
00:10:44,050 --> 00:10:45,650
想发泄的时候就会来这儿
and you come here when you're looking to blow off steam.

265
00:10:45,650 --> 00:10:47,810
我是在发泄  唐娜
Well, I am blowing off steam, Donna,

266
00:10:47,810 --> 00:10:49,300
而且我还没发泄完呢
and I'm not finished,

267
00:10:49,300 --> 00:10:50,790
除非你也会射击
so unless you can handle a pistol,

268
00:10:50,790 --> 00:10:53,400
否则你还是别管我了
do me a favor please and just leave me alone.

269
00:11:03,290 --> 00:11:04,190
你是怎么...
Uh, how do you...

270
00:11:04,190 --> 00:11:06,810
康涅狄格州青年手枪射击锦标赛入围选手
Connecticut Junior Pistol Championship finalist.

271
00:11:06,810 --> 00:11:08,010
连续三年
Three years in a row.

272
00:11:08,010 --> 00:11:09,160
哪几年啊
What years?

273
00:11:09,160 --> 00:11:11,600
你敢再问一遍  小心我崩了你
Ask me that again and I will use this on you.

274
00:11:11,600 --> 00:11:12,980
这世上有你不会的事吗
Is there anything that you can't do?

275
00:11:12,980 --> 00:11:14,940
没有
No, there isn't.

276
00:11:14,990 --> 00:11:18,000
包括说服哈维再帮你找份工作
Including talking Harvey into getting you another job.

277
00:11:18,000 --> 00:11:19,630
这次又是哪
So where is it this time?

278
00:11:19,740 --> 00:11:22,190
辛辛那提  明尼阿波利斯
Cincinnati? Minneapolis?

279
00:11:22,230 --> 00:11:23,740
安克雷奇  还是阿拉斯加
Anchorage, Alaska?

280
00:11:23,740 --> 00:11:25,180
波士顿
Boston.

281
00:11:25,880 --> 00:11:26,790
希拉
Sheila.

282
00:11:26,790 --> 00:11:28,140
没错  希拉
Yes, Sheila.

283
00:11:28,140 --> 00:11:29,400
你让哈维这么做的
You got Harvey to do this for me?

284
00:11:29,400 --> 00:11:31,930
我让他答应帮你
I got him to give you his word he will do it,

285
00:11:31,930 --> 00:11:33,490
但你不肯去辛辛那提
but after you turned down Cincinnati,

286
00:11:33,490 --> 00:11:35,690
现在你不点头他是不会去安排的
he's not gonna make the call unless you say you're on board.

287
00:11:35,690 --> 00:11:37,120
-不行  -不行是什么意思
- I can't. - What do you mean, you can't?

288
00:11:37,120 --> 00:11:39,030
唐娜  希拉喜欢强者
Donna, Sheila values strength.

289
00:11:39,030 --> 00:11:40,770
她会觉得我是在最无力的时候
She's gonna see this as me coming to her

290
00:11:40,770 --> 00:11:41,990
跑去找她
at a time of weakness.

291
00:11:41,990 --> 00:11:42,690
路易
Louis,

292
00:11:42,690 --> 00:11:45,710
你去波士顿唯一的目的是和她在一起
you go to Boston with the sole purpose of being with her,

293
00:11:45,710 --> 00:11:48,380
她会觉得那是爱的表现
she's gonna see that as a sign of love.

294
00:11:50,150 --> 00:11:51,630
让他帮我安排吧
Tell him to make the call.

295
00:11:52,870 --> 00:11:55,180
凯尔  我认为你应该问问自己
Okay, Kyle, I think the question you have to ask is,

296
00:11:55,180 --> 00:11:58,020
十年后我会走到哪里
"Where do I see myself in ten years,"

297
00:11:58,020 --> 00:11:59,750
很不幸  答案是
And unfortunately, the answer is,

298
00:11:59,760 --> 00:12:02,140
"跟哈佛毕业生不一样"
"Not as a Harvard graduate."

299
00:12:04,110 --> 00:12:05,360
白痴
Idiot.

300
00:12:06,840 --> 00:12:10,140
路易  你怎么来了
Louis, what are you doing here?

301
00:12:10,150 --> 00:12:11,800
我来赢回你的芳心
I'm here to take you back.

302
00:12:13,580 --> 00:12:15,670
我不明白  我们分开...
I-I don't understand, the way we lef--

303
00:12:15,670 --> 00:12:17,310
我不在乎我们怎么分开的
I don't care how we left it.

304
00:12:18,700 --> 00:12:21,400
我没有一天不在想你
Not a day has gone by that I haven't thought of you,

305
00:12:22,670 --> 00:12:24,710
我再也忍受不了相思之苦
and I can't hold it back anymore.

306
00:12:26,290 --> 00:12:27,900
希拉  我爱你
Sheila, I love you,

307
00:12:28,670 --> 00:12:31,310
我想跟你在一起
and I want us to be together.

308
00:12:32,640 --> 00:12:36,160
路易  太好了  但是...
Louis, this is wonderful, but it's--it's--

309
00:12:36,160 --> 00:12:38,040
只是一下子有点惊讶
It's just a lot to take in.

310
00:12:38,750 --> 00:12:41,540
不敢相信你真的愿意做承诺了
To believe that you're really ready to commit.

311
00:12:41,540 --> 00:12:42,720
这个怎么样
Well, how's this for ready?

312
00:12:42,720 --> 00:12:44,620
-我要来波士顿工作  -什么
- I'm taking a job in Boston. - What?

313
00:12:44,620 --> 00:12:46,390
我从皮尔逊-斯佩克特辞职了
I quit Pearson Specter.

314
00:12:46,710 --> 00:12:48,320
天啊
Oh, my god.

315
00:12:49,630 --> 00:12:51,370
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.

316
00:12:51,390 --> 00:12:52,580
你这都是为了我吗
You did all that for me?

317
00:12:52,580 --> 00:12:53,770
是啊
Yes.

318
00:12:53,770 --> 00:12:55,080
不过  我...
Well, I--

319
00:12:55,890 --> 00:12:58,640
-你怎么了  -我来波士顿工作是为了你
- Well, what? - I got a job in Boston for you.

320
00:13:00,360 --> 00:13:01,630
路易  你做这个决定
Louis, did you make that decision

321
00:13:01,630 --> 00:13:03,520
是在辞职以前还是辞职以后
before or after you quit your old job?

322
00:13:03,520 --> 00:13:05,040
有区别吗
What difference does it make?

323
00:13:05,120 --> 00:13:07,110
区别大了
It makes a huge difference.

324
00:13:07,110 --> 00:13:09,320
你都六个月没联系我了  然后...
You don't call for six months, and then...

325
00:13:09,870 --> 00:13:11,150
一天你醒来  辞了职
One day you wake up, quit your job,

326
00:13:11,150 --> 00:13:13,790
突然之间就要我填补你生活的空白吗
and suddenly I'm supposed to fill the hole in your life?

327
00:13:13,790 --> 00:13:15,190
不不不  不是这样的
No-no-no-no-no, it's not like that.

328
00:13:15,190 --> 00:13:17,100
-好  那是怎么回事  -你知道
- Okay, then what is it? - I mean, do you know

329
00:13:17,100 --> 00:13:19,570
不给你打电话对我来说有多难吗
how hard it was for me to not call you?

330
00:13:19,570 --> 00:13:22,030
-我努力想向前看  -那怎么不继续了
- I was tryin' to move on. - Then why didn't you move on?

331
00:13:22,030 --> 00:13:24,640
因为我意识到我不需要纽约
Because I realized that I don't need New York.

332
00:13:24,640 --> 00:13:26,030
我需要的是你
I need you.

333
00:13:27,810 --> 00:13:30,440
路易  异地是咱俩之间最微不足道的问题
Louis, geography was the least of our problems.

334
00:13:30,440 --> 00:13:31,780
我知道
No, I know.

335
00:13:31,780 --> 00:13:34,220
我想让你知道  我能接受
And--and I want you to know that I've come around on that.

336
00:13:34,220 --> 00:13:36,550
孩子的问题你不会"接受"
You don't "Come around" on children.

337
00:13:36,600 --> 00:13:39,030
我不想要孩子  也不会改变主意
I don't want them, and I'm not going to change my mind.

338
00:13:39,030 --> 00:13:40,810
不用你改  因为我改主意了
You don't have to, because I've changed mine.

339
00:13:40,810 --> 00:13:42,880
好吧  我相信你是这么认为的
Okay, and I believe that you believe that, it's--

340
00:13:42,880 --> 00:13:43,790
那如果你...
Well, then if you b--

341
00:13:43,790 --> 00:13:45,230
我只是觉得你不知道我...
I'm just sensing that you don't know where I'm--

342
00:13:45,230 --> 00:13:46,950
路易  我问你是不是辞职在先
Louis, when I asked if you'd quit first,

343
00:13:46,950 --> 00:13:48,830
是因为如果...
I was asking because if--

344
00:13:48,970 --> 00:13:50,850
如果我相信你真的准备好
If I believed that you were really ready

345
00:13:50,850 --> 00:13:52,340
不要孩子
to give up children, 

346
00:13:52,510 --> 00:13:55,160
我会跑进你的臂弯永远不放手
I would run into your arms and never let go,

347
00:13:56,120 --> 00:13:58,710
但如果你这么做是因为一时落魄
but if you're doing this because you're down and out--

348
00:13:58,710 --> 00:13:59,540
是这样的
But that's just it.

349
00:13:59,540 --> 00:14:01,560
你知道吗  几周前
Do you understand that I was going to change

350
00:14:01,560 --> 00:14:04,710
我本准备为你改变整个工作安排
my entire work schedule weeks ago for you?

351
00:14:04,730 --> 00:14:08,020
-早在这一切之前  -你本准备
- Before all this. - You were going to.

352
00:14:09,350 --> 00:14:11,080
-但你没有  -希拉  拜托
- But you didn't. - Sheila, please.

353
00:14:11,080 --> 00:14:12,290
你要明白我...
You have to understand where I'm--

354
00:14:12,290 --> 00:14:14,240
我很高兴见到你  路易
It was good to see you, Louis.

355
00:14:14,880 --> 00:14:16,190
请走吧
Please go.

356
00:14:32,600 --> 00:14:33,750
你看起来很沮丧
I see frustration.

357
00:14:33,750 --> 00:14:35,370
我被联邦商务委员会的
You see me getting my ass kicked 

358
00:14:35,370 --> 00:14:37,480
10b-6条例搞得焦头烂额
by FTC Rule 10b-6.

359
00:14:37,480 --> 00:14:38,080
然后呢
And?

360
00:14:38,080 --> 00:14:39,710
哈维要我汇报进度  我一点进度都没有
Harvey needs an update and I don't have shit.

361
00:14:39,710 --> 00:14:41,360
如果你是哈维  他是杰西卡
And if you were Harvey and he was Jessica,

362
00:14:41,360 --> 00:14:43,110
你会说一切尽在掌握
you'd say you're all over it.

363
00:14:43,400 --> 00:14:44,470
这好办
I can make that happen.

364
00:14:44,470 --> 00:14:45,180
-一切尽在掌握  -很好
- I'm all over it. - Good.

365
00:14:45,180 --> 00:14:47,300
唐娜  送瓶尊尼获加蓝牌威士忌
Donna, send a bottle of Johnnie Walker Blue

366
00:14:47,300 --> 00:14:48,100
给乔纳森·帕默
to Jonathan Palmer,

367
00:14:48,100 --> 00:14:50,060
再给他搞几张白袜队下场比赛的门票
and get him tickets to the next Sox game,

368
00:14:50,060 --> 00:14:51,980
搞清楚他老婆的生日
and then find out when his wife's birthday is,

369
00:14:51,980 --> 00:14:54,000
他孩子的生日  他的狗的生日
His kid's birthday, his dog's birthday.

370
00:14:54,000 --> 00:14:56,040
-我该怎么  -我不管你怎么做到
- How am I supposed to-- - I don't care how you do it.

371
00:14:56,040 --> 00:14:56,960
自己想办法
Figure it the hell out.

372
00:14:56,960 --> 00:14:58,180
哈维  只是要向他表达感谢
Harvey, this is a thank you to him.

373
00:14:58,180 --> 00:14:59,020
你为什么要冲我发火
Why are you so mad at me?

374
00:14:59,020 --> 00:15:01,070
这不是感谢而是道歉
It's not a thank you, it's an apology

375
00:15:01,070 --> 00:15:03,620
因为你说服我请他给路易一份工作
for you talking me into getting him to give Louis a job.

376
00:15:03,620 --> 00:15:05,450
-他做了什么  -他没去面试
- What did he-- - He didn't show up to the interview,

377
00:15:05,450 --> 00:15:07,040
还有回春制药的问题怎么样了
And what's happening with our Versalife problem?

378
00:15:07,040 --> 00:15:07,720
一切尽在掌握
I'm all over it.

379
00:15:07,720 --> 00:15:10,210
"尽在掌握"说明你什么都没有
Yeah, "all over it" means you don't have dick.

380
00:15:10,210 --> 00:15:12,540
我下次看见你的时候  拿出点成果
Next time I see you, have something.

381
00:15:15,070 --> 00:15:17,240
乔纳森·帕默在波士顿
Jonathan Palmer's in Boston.

382
00:15:17,490 --> 00:15:18,850
哈维帮路易在那里找工作
Harvey got Louis a job there

383
00:15:18,850 --> 00:15:19,960
是因为希拉  对吗
because of Sheila, didn't he?

384
00:15:19,960 --> 00:15:22,400
-是的  -唐娜  如果他没去面试
- Yes. - Donna, if he didn't show up for the interview,

385
00:15:22,400 --> 00:15:24,000
说明他和希拉没有和好
it means it didn't work with Sheila.

386
00:15:24,000 --> 00:15:25,260
糟了
Shit.

387
00:15:25,940 --> 00:15:27,710
他现在一定伤心欲绝了
He's gonna be devastated.

388
00:15:29,500 --> 00:15:30,860
你把他的东西拿给他了吗
You bring him his box of stuff yet?

389
00:15:30,860 --> 00:15:33,320
还没  我马上去
No, but I'm going to right now.

390
00:15:33,730 --> 00:15:35,050
-让我去吧  -听我说
- Let me do it. - Listen to me.

391
00:15:35,050 --> 00:15:37,000
哈维因为你没成果而正冲你发火
Harvey's pissed at you because you don't have anything

392
00:15:37,000 --> 00:15:37,950
而路易现在需要的是我
and Louis needs me.

393
00:15:37,950 --> 00:15:39,380
唐娜  我能在这里完全是因为
Donna, I am here because that man

394
00:15:39,380 --> 00:15:40,980
他把我的利益放在了他自己之前
put my well-being before his own.

395
00:15:40,980 --> 00:15:43,250
他为了我才放弃了去找希拉
He gave up going after Sheila for me.

396
00:15:43,250 --> 00:15:45,550
我猜这很有可能就是他们没和好的原因
For all I know, that's why it didn't work out for him up there,

397
00:15:45,550 --> 00:15:46,800
而我...
and it's...

398
00:15:47,550 --> 00:15:51,210
现在最起码应该去安慰他
the least I can do, is comfort him when he's down.

399
00:15:53,360 --> 00:15:54,640
去吧
Go.

400
00:16:00,690 --> 00:16:02,090
请进  请进
Come in, come in.

401
00:16:02,090 --> 00:16:03,470
你来干什么
What are you doin' here?

402
00:16:03,470 --> 00:16:05,960
这些东西在你桌子上放了好多天了
Stuff has been sitting on your desk for days.

403
00:16:05,960 --> 00:16:08,140
我想给你拿过来
I wanted you to have it.

404
00:16:08,660 --> 00:16:11,820
好的  我的新办公室会需要它们
Okay. I'll need it for my new office.

405
00:16:12,390 --> 00:16:13,730
你找到工作了吗
You got a job?

406
00:16:14,240 --> 00:16:16,760
还没有  不过我会的
Not yet, but I will.

407
00:16:19,070 --> 00:16:20,740
白帽协会会员
Order of the Coif.

408
00:16:19,070 --> 00:16:20,740
{\an8}美国属于该协会的法学院前10%的毕业生可获此荣誉

409
00:16:20,940 --> 00:16:23,790
看看这个以优等成绩毕业的人是谁啊
Yeah, look who graduated Magna Cum Laude.

410
00:16:23,790 --> 00:16:26,490
实际上是最优等  好像也没帮上我什么
Summa, actually, for all the good it'll do me.

411
00:16:26,780 --> 00:16:29,710
我猜这把钥匙也一定有什么典故  对吗
I know there's got to be a story behind this key. Yeah?

412
00:16:29,710 --> 00:16:31,330
是你第一个案子纪念还是
From one of your first cases or...

413
00:16:31,330 --> 00:16:32,320
迈克  拜托了
Mike, do me a favor, please.

414
00:16:32,320 --> 00:16:33,800
-别这样  好吗  -别什么样
- Just stop it, will you? - Stop what?

415
00:16:33,800 --> 00:16:36,130
别再为了在这里多呆一会
Stop asking questions that you already know the answers to

416
00:16:36,130 --> 00:16:36,960
而问这些你早就知道答案的问题
just to stay here longer.

417
00:16:36,960 --> 00:16:38,280
-路易  我没有  -你没有在干什么
- Louis, I'm not-- - You're not what?

418
00:16:38,280 --> 00:16:39,450
试探我吗  你本来就是
Examining me? Yes, you are.

419
00:16:39,450 --> 00:16:41,810
你在一边假装聊天一边偷偷环视房间
You're just making small talk while you look around the room

420
00:16:41,810 --> 00:16:43,870
看附近有没有什么我可能拿来自杀的东西
to see if there are any sharp objects in the vicinity.

421
00:16:43,870 --> 00:16:45,080
我不是因为这个来的
That is not why I came here.

422
00:16:45,080 --> 00:16:47,400
你也不是来给我送东西的
Well, it wasn't to deliver a box of my shit.

423
00:16:48,700 --> 00:16:51,360
我走投无路的时候  是你救了我
Look, when I was drowning, you threw me a lifeline, okay?

424
00:16:51,360 --> 00:16:53,380
你这样说很贴心
Okay, well, that's nice of you to say,

425
00:16:53,380 --> 00:16:55,710
我也很感谢你把我的东西拿过来
and I appreciate you bringing over my things,

426
00:16:55,710 --> 00:16:57,690
但这些可救不了我
but they're not exactly a lifeline.

427
00:16:57,690 --> 00:16:59,200
我听说波士顿的事了
I heard about Boston.

428
00:16:59,760 --> 00:17:01,020
你都听说了什么
What'd you hear?

429
00:17:01,480 --> 00:17:04,110
听说哈维给你找了份工作而你却没有去
That Harvey got you a job and you didn't even show up.

430
00:17:04,110 --> 00:17:05,680
我此生的至爱都已经把我的心伤透了
Well, why would I when the love of my life

431
00:17:05,680 --> 00:17:07,270
我还去干什么
rips out my heart and then stomps on it?

432
00:17:07,270 --> 00:17:08,550
路易  我只是想帮你
Louis, I'm just trying to help.

433
00:17:08,550 --> 00:17:09,930
你帮不了
Well, you can't!

434
00:17:11,920 --> 00:17:13,850
我得不到希拉
I don't have Sheila.

435
00:17:14,320 --> 00:17:16,180
我没有工作
I don't have a job.

436
00:17:17,580 --> 00:17:20,820
现在我只想一个人待着
And right now I'd just prefer to be alone.

437
00:17:34,480 --> 00:17:35,780
不行
No.

438
00:17:37,120 --> 00:17:39,600
我不管他怎么说
Well, I don't care what he says.

439
00:17:39,600 --> 00:17:42,240
15%的垃圾依旧是垃圾
15% of bullshit is still bullshit.

440
00:17:43,120 --> 00:17:44,380
混蛋
Dick.

441
00:17:44,760 --> 00:17:45,870
我能为你做什么  迈克
What can I do for you, Mike?

442
00:17:45,870 --> 00:17:48,220
看得出来你很忙  先生  我就直说了
I can see you're busy, sir, so I'll just jump right to it and--

443
00:17:48,220 --> 00:17:49,550
等等
Hold it right there.

444
00:17:49,550 --> 00:17:52,590
如果你是来请我同意你向瑞秋求婚的
If this is your asking me for Rachel's hand in marriage,

445
00:17:52,590 --> 00:17:54,440
用这种方式可不行
you know, you're goin' about it the wrong way.

446
00:17:56,290 --> 00:17:57,820
先生  如果我要那样做
Sir, I think if I were gonna do that,

447
00:17:57,820 --> 00:17:58,910
我想我会想到
I'd have the foresight to ask your wife

448
00:17:58,910 --> 00:18:01,080
先去想您的妻子打听该怎样来问您
how to approach you first.

449
00:18:01,290 --> 00:18:02,620
回答的不错
Good answer.

450
00:18:03,940 --> 00:18:05,590
我实际上是为了路易·利特来的
I'm actually here about Louis Litt.

451
00:18:05,590 --> 00:18:06,760
对了  我听说他辞职了
Yeah, I heard he resigned.

452
00:18:06,760 --> 00:18:09,130
是的  他现在在找工作
He did, and he's looking for a job.

453
00:18:09,660 --> 00:18:11,770
他这样的人应该什么样的工作都能找到吧
A fellow like that should have his pick.

454
00:18:11,780 --> 00:18:12,980
合伙人协议
Well, the partnership agreement 

455
00:18:12,980 --> 00:18:14,890
使他无法带走客户
prohibits him from taking clients.

456
00:18:14,890 --> 00:18:17,070
够倒霉的
Ooh, shit. Yeah.

457
00:18:17,070 --> 00:18:18,990
杰西卡可不是吃干饭的  对吧
Ah, Jessica doesn't play around, does she?

458
00:18:18,990 --> 00:18:20,350
她连他长子都扣下当人质了吧
She took his firstborn too?

459
00:18:20,350 --> 00:18:22,370
我知道现在生意不好做
Look, I know it's bad out there, but--

460
00:18:22,370 --> 00:18:24,090
不好做  简直是像世界末日
Bad? It's the apocalypse.

461
00:18:24,090 --> 00:18:25,280
我可不是开慈善机构的
And I'm not runnin' a soup kitchen.

462
00:18:25,280 --> 00:18:27,180
如果一个合伙人不能给我带来客户
If a partner can't bring me clients...

463
00:18:28,640 --> 00:18:29,430
这是什么
What's that?

464
00:18:29,430 --> 00:18:32,220
这是路易十五年来的收入单
These are Louis' billables for the last 15 years.

465
00:18:35,620 --> 00:18:38,370
-这家伙有空睡觉吗  -他不只能挣钱
- This guy ever sleep? - And he doesn't just bill.

466
00:18:38,370 --> 00:18:40,310
他还负责训练初级律师  他还发表著作
He trains the associates, he publishes.

467
00:18:40,310 --> 00:18:42,870
他会把命搭上来为你工作
He will give his life to you.

468
00:18:43,200 --> 00:18:44,410
而你希望我雇用他
And you want me to do this

469
00:18:44,410 --> 00:18:45,320
是因为你和我女儿在一起
because you're with my daughter?

470
00:18:45,320 --> 00:18:47,180
是因为我从没有求过您什么
I want you to do this because I've never asked you for a thing,

471
00:18:47,180 --> 00:18:49,010
而我第一次求您
and the first time I am,

472
00:18:49,010 --> 00:18:50,990
是为了帮助别人
it's a favor for someone else.

473
00:18:50,990 --> 00:18:52,940
和您女儿在一起的是这样一个人
That's the kind of man that your daughter is with.

474
00:18:52,940 --> 00:18:55,280
所以还是因为你和我女儿在一起
So it's because you're with my daughter?

475
00:18:55,530 --> 00:18:56,970
随便您怎么想
You're gonna see it how you're gonna see it,

476
00:18:56,970 --> 00:18:58,950
真正的问题是
but the real question is:

477
00:18:58,950 --> 00:19:01,170
关于路易·利特你打算怎么办
what are you gonna do about Louis Litt?

478
00:19:04,090 --> 00:19:05,460
我可以见他
I'll meet with him.

479
00:19:07,930 --> 00:19:09,360
但不能保证什么
But there's no guarantee.

480
00:19:09,630 --> 00:19:11,180
我只要求这一点
Well, that's all I can ask.

481
00:19:13,380 --> 00:19:16,230
你转告我女儿记得给她爸爸打电话
You tell my daughter to give her old man a call sometime.

482
00:19:16,680 --> 00:19:18,050
好的  先生
Yes, sir.

483
00:19:23,380 --> 00:19:24,430
你看起来心情不错啊
You look happy.

484
00:19:24,430 --> 00:19:27,310
我是很高兴  因为今天我做了件好事
I am happy, because today I did a good thing.

485
00:19:27,310 --> 00:19:30,130
你准备同意把卧室漆成知更鸟蛋蓝色了吗
You're going to let me paint the bedroom Robin's egg blue?

486
00:19:30,130 --> 00:19:31,340
我说我做了件好事
I said I did a good thing.

487
00:19:31,340 --> 00:19:34,170
又没说我做了件荒唐事
I didn't say I did a ridiculous thing.

488
00:19:35,350 --> 00:19:37,930
我帮路易在纽约弄到了个工作面试的机会
I got Louis a job interview in New York.

489
00:19:38,140 --> 00:19:39,740
-什么  -是的
- What? - Mm-hmm.

490
00:19:39,790 --> 00:19:41,450
-太棒了  -是啊
- That's amazing! - Yeah.

491
00:19:41,450 --> 00:19:43,090
我爱你
Oh, I love you.

492
00:19:43,460 --> 00:19:44,890
我要给你倒杯酒庆祝一下
I'm gonna fix you a drink to celebrate.

493
00:19:44,890 --> 00:19:46,780
你还应该为你自己倒一杯
Well, you should fix one for yourself too,

494
00:19:46,780 --> 00:19:49,090
因为要不是因为你  我做不成这事儿
because I couldn't have done it without you.

495
00:19:49,810 --> 00:19:50,570
什么意思
What do you mean?

496
00:19:50,570 --> 00:19:52,530
那个面试机会是你爸爸给的
I mean the interview's with your dad.

497
00:19:53,710 --> 00:19:54,540
怎么
What?

498
00:19:54,540 --> 00:19:57,660
我为了路易去找你爸爸了
I went to your dad for Louis.

499
00:20:00,210 --> 00:20:01,490
怎么了
What?

500
00:20:03,650 --> 00:20:05,340
这真是太好了
It's really sweet.

501
00:20:05,340 --> 00:20:06,730
但是...
But...

502
00:20:08,070 --> 00:20:08,760
简单来说吧
Let's just say

503
00:20:08,760 --> 00:20:11,190
我没让我爸爸帮我支付法学院学费
there's a reason that I didn't go to my dad 

504
00:20:11,190 --> 00:20:12,200
是有原因的
to pay for law school.

505
00:20:12,200 --> 00:20:12,780
我还以为就像你说的
I thought you said

506
00:20:12,780 --> 00:20:14,720
是因为你想自力更生呢
it was because you wanted to do it yourself.

507
00:20:14,720 --> 00:20:17,360
是这样的  但是其他人
It is, but other people don't have a problem

508
00:20:17,360 --> 00:20:18,450
去找父母求助不会有问题
going to their parents

509
00:20:18,450 --> 00:20:22,650
因为他们不用提心吊胆等其他麻烦
because they don't have to wait for the other shoe to drop.

510
00:20:22,750 --> 00:20:24,140
你这是什么意思
What are you talking about?

511
00:20:24,140 --> 00:20:25,980
他不会平白无故给人恩惠的
He's not gonna give something for nothing.

512
00:20:25,980 --> 00:20:26,940
所以你的意思是  这件事之后
So you mean after this,

513
00:20:26,940 --> 00:20:28,110
他会向我索要回报吗
he's gonna want something from me?

514
00:20:28,110 --> 00:20:29,210
我不知道
I don't know,

515
00:20:29,210 --> 00:20:31,810
但他一定会向某个人索要回报的
but he's gonna want something from someone.

516
00:20:33,410 --> 00:20:36,700
假如这能帮路易重新开始  我还真不介意
If it gets louis a fresh start, I really don't care.

517
00:20:46,420 --> 00:20:47,670
天啊
Oh man.

518
00:20:47,670 --> 00:20:49,240
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.

519
00:20:49,240 --> 00:20:50,300
-你在哄我呢吧  -没有
- You got to be kiddin' me. - No.

520
00:20:50,300 --> 00:20:51,480
你也去那儿吗
You went there too?

521
00:20:51,480 --> 00:20:52,930
过去的五年里  每周二都去
Every Tuesday for the last five years.

522
00:20:52,930 --> 00:20:54,670
我是周三去
Oh. Wednesday.

523
00:20:54,960 --> 00:20:56,490
奶酪鸡[菜名]日
Chicken parm day.

524
00:20:57,370 --> 00:20:58,510
对我而言就像圣诞节一样
More like christmas to me.

525
00:20:58,510 --> 00:21:00,270
-我很相信这一点  -路易
- Oh, I believe it. - Oh, Louis.

526
00:21:00,270 --> 00:21:01,210
和你聊天很愉快
This has been a pleasure,

527
00:21:01,210 --> 00:21:04,440
但我们是时候说说重点了
but it's time that we got down to the crux of the matter.

528
00:21:04,440 --> 00:21:05,710
你想知道我为什么辞职了
You want to know why I resigned.

529
00:21:05,710 --> 00:21:07,210
我确实打过电话给杰西卡
Well, I did call Jessica,

530
00:21:07,210 --> 00:21:09,230
然后她向我大力推荐你
and she gave you a glowing recommendation,

531
00:21:09,230 --> 00:21:11,090
但是我们都知道那是屁话
and we both know that's bullshit.

532
00:21:11,620 --> 00:21:12,530
你想知道真相
You want to know the truth.

533
00:21:12,530 --> 00:21:13,770
我说过和真相有什么关系吗
Did I say anything about the truth?

534
00:21:13,770 --> 00:21:16,460
我只是想让你知道  我明白那些都是屁话
I'm just makin' sure you know I know that it's bullshit.

535
00:21:16,460 --> 00:21:18,850
但就我而言  我才不在乎你为什么辞职
But my truth is, I don't care why you left.

536
00:21:18,850 --> 00:21:21,170
我唯一在乎的是  你能带来什么
All I care about is what you're gonna take.

537
00:21:21,260 --> 00:21:22,260
什么
What?

538
00:21:22,260 --> 00:21:24,200
你只要带来一个客户
You take one client,

539
00:21:24,200 --> 00:21:25,770
我不在乎客户大小
I don't give a shit how big it is,

540
00:21:25,770 --> 00:21:27,690
我立刻让你当高级合伙人
and I'll make you a senior partner on the spot.

541
00:21:27,690 --> 00:21:30,440
等等  迈克·罗斯说了
Wait a second. Mike Ross said

542
00:21:30,440 --> 00:21:32,650
你不要求我带生意来啊
that I was not required to bring business.

543
00:21:32,650 --> 00:21:34,210
这和生意无关
This isn't about business.

544
00:21:34,210 --> 00:21:35,850
和胆量有关
This is about balls.

545
00:21:35,940 --> 00:21:37,220
我不需要另一个业界精英
I don't need another grinder,

546
00:21:37,220 --> 00:21:39,000
我需要一个能攻城略地的律师
I need a lawyer who can kick a door in,

547
00:21:39,000 --> 00:21:41,230
我说的这个城  就是皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所
and the door in question is Pearson Specter's.

548
00:21:41,230 --> 00:21:43,420
你想看看我能不能打破自己的合伙契约是吧
You want to see if I can break my partnership agreement?

549
00:21:43,420 --> 00:21:44,660
真让你说对了
You're damn right I do,

550
00:21:44,660 --> 00:21:46,100
因为假如你连这个都做不到
Because if you can't do that,

551
00:21:46,100 --> 00:21:48,790
那你还算什么厉害人物
then what the hell good are you?

552
00:21:50,590 --> 00:21:52,220
你和杰西卡没什么不同
You're no different than Jessica.

553
00:21:52,580 --> 00:21:54,420
我把这句话当成是赞美了
I'll take that as a compliment.

554
00:21:54,690 --> 00:21:55,960
现在  恕我失陪
Well, if you'll excuse me,

555
00:21:55,960 --> 00:21:58,290
西尔维娅会送你出去的
Sylvia will validate you on the way out.

556
00:21:58,290 --> 00:21:59,310
好的  但是
Yeah, well,

557
00:21:59,310 --> 00:22:01,260
罗伯特  这是纽约  我会拦的士的
Robert, this is New York. I take a cab.

558
00:22:01,260 --> 00:22:03,270
我这是在婉转地说"给我滚出去"
See, that's my way of saying "Get the hell out."

559
00:22:13,150 --> 00:22:14,410
"一会儿"是多久
Well, how long is a little while?

560
00:22:15,190 --> 00:22:16,490
-你知道...  -路易
- Do you have any-- - Louis!

561
00:22:17,340 --> 00:22:17,880
失陪
Excuse me.

562
00:22:19,630 --> 00:22:20,490
卡特里娜  你来这儿干什么
Katrina, what are you doing here?

563
00:22:20,490 --> 00:22:21,410
你知道我来这儿干什么的
You know what I'm doing here.

564
00:22:21,410 --> 00:22:22,580
他们已经不是你的客户了
This isn't your client anymore.

565
00:22:22,580 --> 00:22:24,490
你被禁止和他们联系
You're prohibited from contacting them.

566
00:22:24,490 --> 00:22:26,690
-我不是来见...  -纽宝客投资公司吗
- I-I'm not here to see-- - Neubacher Capital?

567
00:22:26,690 --> 00:22:28,090
你就是来见他们的
Yes, you are.

568
00:22:28,370 --> 00:22:30,040
就好像你接下来还要去见卡佛科技
Just like you're going to go see Carver Tech

569
00:22:30,040 --> 00:22:31,840
和布莱克斯隆-西蒙斯公司一样
and Blackthorne Simons.

570
00:22:32,990 --> 00:22:33,940
你怎么知道
How do you know that?

571
00:22:33,940 --> 00:22:34,930
因为他们给我打电话了
Because they called me.

572
00:22:34,930 --> 00:22:35,730
他们说了什么
What are they saying?

573
00:22:35,730 --> 00:22:37,070
他们说了什么不重要
Doesn't matter what they're saying.

574
00:22:37,070 --> 00:22:38,730
明摆着你就是想把他们偷走
It's plain as day you're trying to poach them.

575
00:22:38,730 --> 00:22:40,120
-杰西卡知道这件事了吗  -还没
- Does Jessica know? - Not yet.

576
00:22:40,120 --> 00:22:41,780
但假如你继续这样做  她绝对会发现的
But if you keep doing this, she's gonna find out.

577
00:22:41,780 --> 00:22:42,700
是啊  让她来告我啊
Yeah, well, let her sue me,

578
00:22:42,700 --> 00:22:43,970
因为我真的别无选择了
'cause I don't have any other choice.

579
00:22:43,970 --> 00:22:44,890
你这话什么意思
What are you talking about?

580
00:22:44,890 --> 00:22:46,550
罗伯特·赞恩许诺我当高级合伙人
Robert Zane offered me senior partner

581
00:22:46,550 --> 00:22:48,180
只要我能毁了合伙契约
if I can break the partnership agreement.

582
00:22:48,180 --> 00:22:50,560
那可是纽约的一家大律所啊
That is a major law firm in New York.

583
00:22:50,560 --> 00:22:52,410
不会有比这更好的机会了
I'm not gonna get a better chance than that.

584
00:22:52,410 --> 00:22:53,130
路易...
Louis--

585
00:22:53,130 --> 00:22:54,750
假如有必要的话你尽管告诉杰西卡吧
Look, tell Jessica if you have to.

586
00:22:54,750 --> 00:22:56,950
我不想让你陷入麻烦  明白吗
I don't want to get you in trouble, okay?

587
00:22:57,180 --> 00:22:58,660
但我刚刚丢了我的工作
But I just lost my job.

588
00:23:00,970 --> 00:23:03,150
而且我还第二次失去了我爱的女人
And I just lost the woman I love for the second time,

589
00:23:03,150 --> 00:23:04,520
一切都在一周之内发生
all in one week.

590
00:23:04,870 --> 00:23:07,860
现在我有这个机会能咸鱼翻身
Now I have this chance to turn my life around...

591
00:23:08,480 --> 00:23:10,460
只用一个客户就好
with this one client.

592
00:23:12,420 --> 00:23:13,460
我志在必得
I'm gonna take it.

593
00:23:15,940 --> 00:23:16,790
路易
Louis.

594
00:23:22,220 --> 00:23:24,760
你想要一个客户  我会给你一个的
You want one client, I'll give you one client.

595
00:23:25,540 --> 00:23:27,290
什么  等等  不行...
What? Wait, no--

596
00:23:27,290 --> 00:23:28,550
你同意接纳我的时候
When you agreed to take me on,

597
00:23:28,550 --> 00:23:30,770
我发过誓说我会忠于你的
I swore that I would be loyal to you,

598
00:23:31,170 --> 00:23:34,080
可如果现在我不忠  我就没有忠诚可言
and if I'm not loyal now, then I never was.

599
00:23:34,080 --> 00:23:36,660
卡特里娜  如果你这么干被杰西卡发现
Katrina, if you do this and Jessica figures it out,

600
00:23:36,660 --> 00:23:38,280
她会炒了你
she will fire you,

601
00:23:38,280 --> 00:23:40,290
而我会良心不安
and I cannot live with that.

602
00:23:40,290 --> 00:23:42,100
可如果你能得到那份工作
That won't matter if you get the job

603
00:23:42,100 --> 00:23:43,690
再把我挖过去  就不要紧了
and you take me with you.

604
00:23:45,870 --> 00:23:47,070
告诉我是哪家公司
Give me the goddamn name.

605
00:23:51,450 --> 00:23:52,390
怎么了
What?

606
00:23:53,180 --> 00:23:54,330
我要告诉你点事
I'm gonna tell you something,

607
00:23:54,330 --> 00:23:56,230
但希望你不要有过激反应
and I don't want you to overreact.

608
00:23:56,230 --> 00:23:58,430
看你这表情  我不会做出任何承诺的
From the look on your face, I'm not makin' any promises.

609
00:23:58,430 --> 00:23:59,810
我刚收到了路易的邮件
I just got an email from Louis.

610
00:23:59,810 --> 00:24:01,120
他想拿下回春制药
He's going after Versalife.

611
00:24:01,850 --> 00:24:03,590
-给我联系雷  -你要干嘛
- Get me Ray. - What are you gonna do?

612
00:24:03,590 --> 00:24:04,770
联系雷
Get me ray!

613
00:24:04,770 --> 00:24:06,800
哈维  那只是一封通知邮件
Harvey, it was just a notification email.

614
00:24:06,800 --> 00:24:09,170
-你连他在哪都不知道  -我知道他在哪
- You don't even know where he is! - Yes, I do.

615
00:24:09,170 --> 00:24:10,010
你说什么
What are you talking about?

616
00:24:10,010 --> 00:24:13,040
依照规定  他必须通知我们
That notification is required by the bylaws.

617
00:24:13,040 --> 00:24:14,400
他肯定是最后一秒才发的
He's doing it at the last second.

618
00:24:14,400 --> 00:24:17,350
我向你保证他现在正走进回春制药的门
I guarantee you he's walking in Versalife's door right now.

619
00:24:21,880 --> 00:24:23,560
你以为你在干什么
Hell do you think you're doing?

620
00:24:25,130 --> 00:24:26,280
不是"在干什么"而是"干了什么"
Not doing, did.

621
00:24:26,280 --> 00:24:27,070
我刚签下了回春制药
I just signed Versalife.

622
00:24:27,070 --> 00:24:29,360
-你没权利...  -拜托  我当然有权利
- You have no right. - Please, I have every right.

623
00:24:29,360 --> 00:24:30,190
因为我辞职时
Because when I quit,

624
00:24:30,190 --> 00:24:31,700
杰西卡只通知了我的客户
Jessica only notified my clients,

625
00:24:31,700 --> 00:24:33,090
却没通知你的  因为她想
not yours, because she didn't think

626
00:24:33,090 --> 00:24:34,770
我没胆量动你的客户
I had enough balls to go after you head-on.

627
00:24:34,770 --> 00:24:35,790
不是她这么想  而是我
That wasn't her, that was me,

628
00:24:35,790 --> 00:24:37,710
因为我想你还没堕落到这种地步
because I didn't think you would stoop this low.

629
00:24:37,710 --> 00:24:40,110
太糟糕了  你暴露了弱点  现在为时已晚
Oh, too bad. You exposed your flank, now you're too late.

630
00:24:40,110 --> 00:24:42,640
是啊  我好害怕啊
Yeah, and you can see the fear in my eyes.

631
00:24:42,640 --> 00:24:43,970
借过
Excuse me.

632
00:24:45,290 --> 00:24:46,350
我告诉你了  为时已晚
I told you, you're too late.

633
00:24:46,350 --> 00:24:48,160
我要告诉他们  那个失业的小丑
To tell them an unemployed clown

634
00:24:48,160 --> 00:24:49,970
说的都是屁话
just sold them a pile of bullshit?

635
00:24:49,970 --> 00:24:52,550
是指你不得不放弃他们这个客户的屁话吗
You mean the bullshit that you have to drop them as a client?

636
00:24:54,100 --> 00:24:55,010
瑞辉并购案
The Pfizer merger.

637
00:24:55,400 --> 00:24:57,150
联邦贸易委员会第10b-6号条例
FTC rule 10b-6.

638
00:24:57,150 --> 00:24:59,400
你对他们有所隐瞒  他们很不开心
They were not pleased that you kept them in the dark.

639
00:24:59,400 --> 00:25:01,420
-你这个混蛋  -现在谁才是小丑
- You are a son of a bitch. - Who's the clown now?

640
00:25:01,420 --> 00:25:02,840
你才混蛋
You're a son of a bitch.

641
00:25:02,840 --> 00:25:04,210
我只是想要一个
I'm only taking one client

642
00:25:04,210 --> 00:25:05,600
你迟早得放弃掉的客户而已
that you're gonna have to drop anyway.

643
00:25:05,600 --> 00:25:07,190
你至少可以和气点吧
The least you could do is be a gentleman about it.

644
00:25:07,190 --> 00:25:08,950
和气点  我给你弄到两份工作
A gentleman? I got you two jobs!

645
00:25:08,950 --> 00:25:10,830
两份在西伯利亚的工作
Two jobs in Siberia!

646
00:25:12,110 --> 00:25:13,040
而且是处于怜悯
Out of pity.

647
00:25:13,380 --> 00:25:15,760
我帮你是出于同情
I got you those jobs out of compassion,

648
00:25:15,760 --> 00:25:17,390
就像我一开始就向杰西卡争取
just like when I fought for Jessica

649
00:25:17,390 --> 00:25:19,190
不要解雇你一样
to not fire you in the first place.

650
00:25:19,190 --> 00:25:20,910
但等我把回春制药夺回来
But when I take Versalife back,

651
00:25:20,910 --> 00:25:23,180
我再也不会同情你
it's gonna be without any feeling for you at all.

652
00:25:32,340 --> 00:25:32,990
出什么事了
What happened?

653
00:25:32,990 --> 00:25:35,250
我失去了他们  但我会夺回来的
I lost them, but I'm gonna get 'em back.

654
00:25:35,250 --> 00:25:38,270
我想知道的是  路易怎么知道
What I want to know is how the hell did Louis find out

655
00:25:38,270 --> 00:25:39,670
我们不得不放弃这个客户的
that we had to drop them?

656
00:25:39,670 --> 00:25:40,280
我也不知道
I don't know.

657
00:25:40,280 --> 00:25:41,690
人们就是知道
People know shit.

658
00:25:41,690 --> 00:25:42,710
人们不可能知道
People don't know shit.

659
00:25:43,240 --> 00:25:44,910
有人说出去  人们才会知道
People get told shit.

660
00:25:44,910 --> 00:25:47,310
杰西卡  我是想帮他一把
Jessica, I know I wanted to throw him a bone,

661
00:25:47,310 --> 00:25:48,810
但我不会告诉他这种事
but I did not tell him.

662
00:25:48,810 --> 00:25:50,430
我没怀疑你
I wasn't talkin' about you.

663
00:25:50,910 --> 00:25:52,560
我说的是迈克·罗斯
I was talking about Mike Ross.

664
00:25:52,560 --> 00:25:53,770
那是胡说  迈克才不会...
Bullshit, Mike didn't tell--

665
00:25:53,770 --> 00:25:55,550
你没有让他插手回春制药的案子吗
Tell me you didn't have him working on Versalife.

666
00:25:55,550 --> 00:25:57,170
-那也不证明...  -我就知道
- That doesn't mean-- - I knew it.

667
00:25:57,330 --> 00:25:58,800
他插手了回春制药的案子
He was working on Versalife.

668
00:25:59,400 --> 00:26:01,530
路易帮他回到了这里
He owes Louis for bringing him back here.

669
00:26:01,530 --> 00:26:03,280
这就是他的动机和机会
That is motive and opportunity.

670
00:26:03,280 --> 00:26:05,710
反正一有机会你就想要他走人
You just want him gone by any means necessary.

671
00:26:05,710 --> 00:26:09,240
没错  我觉得我已经表达得很清楚了
Oh, I think I have been more than clear about that.

672
00:26:09,240 --> 00:26:10,390
怀疑其他人去吧
Yeah, well, try another theory,

673
00:26:10,390 --> 00:26:12,110
因为迈克绝不会做那种事
because Mike would never do this.

674
00:26:12,110 --> 00:26:13,710
很多事
Oh, there are a lot of things

675
00:26:13,710 --> 00:26:15,560
你都会觉得迈克·罗斯不会做
you never thought mike ross would do.

676
00:26:16,640 --> 00:26:18,710
卖掉一个老人[沃尔特·吉利斯]的公司
Sell out an old man's company.

677
00:26:19,390 --> 00:26:21,390
跟有钱人[傅滋曼]串通一气
Get in bed with a billionaire.

678
00:26:21,390 --> 00:26:24,310
把自己的老板踢出局
Cut his boss out of a deal.

679
00:26:25,060 --> 00:26:28,110
-杰西卡  -人是会变的  哈维
- Jessica-- - People change, Harvey.

680
00:26:28,630 --> 00:26:29,760
而更有甚者
And to top it all off,

681
00:26:29,760 --> 00:26:32,210
路易是把回春制药带给了罗伯特·赞恩
Louis is taking Versalife to Robert Zane.

682
00:26:33,100 --> 00:26:35,060
迈克·罗斯未来的岳父
Mike Ross' future father-in-law.

683
00:26:36,100 --> 00:26:37,700
你怎么不想想这个呢
Why don't you think about that?

684
00:26:49,460 --> 00:26:52,410
迈克  我想知道你对回春制药都做过什么
Mike, I need to know what you have on Versalife.

685
00:27:00,670 --> 00:27:02,510
-确实是我  -什么确实是你
- It was me. - What was you?

686
00:27:02,510 --> 00:27:04,100
路易看准他们确实是我的错
Louis going after them is my fault.

687
00:27:04,100 --> 00:27:05,760
-你干了什么  -我去找了罗伯特·赞恩
- What did you-- - I went to Robert Zane

688
00:27:05,760 --> 00:27:07,480
要他给路易一个职位
and I asked him to give Louis a job.

689
00:27:07,480 --> 00:27:08,530
就这些吗
That's it?

690
00:27:08,960 --> 00:27:10,730
关于回春制药  你什么都没跟他说吗
You didn't tell him about Versalife?

691
00:27:10,730 --> 00:27:13,060
当然没有  你觉得我会那么干吗
Of course not, wh-- you think I would do that?

692
00:27:13,060 --> 00:27:14,260
别在意我怎么想
Never mind what I think.

693
00:27:14,260 --> 00:27:15,940
你去找了我们最大的竞争对手
You went to one of our biggest competitors

694
00:27:15,940 --> 00:27:17,830
把他跟绝望的路易撮合到一起
and put 'em together with a desperate Louis.

695
00:27:17,830 --> 00:27:19,870
我那么做是因为路易确实很绝望  好吗
I did it because Louis was desperate, all right?

696
00:27:19,870 --> 00:27:21,440
前几天我去给路易送他的东西
I went to see him the other day to bring him his stuff,

697
00:27:21,440 --> 00:27:22,410
-那只是...  -前些天
- it was just-- - The other day?

698
00:27:22,410 --> 00:27:25,600
你是说你应该努力帮我们
You're telling me when you were supposed to be helping us

699
00:27:25,600 --> 00:27:26,760
保住客户的时候
keep our client,

700
00:27:26,760 --> 00:27:29,000
却忙着把他们送了给路易
you were busy giving them to Louis on a silver platter?

701
00:27:29,000 --> 00:27:31,540
本来是的  但我也想出了办法夺回他们
I was, but I also figured out how to get them back.

702
00:27:31,540 --> 00:27:33,270
-那之后你怎么没说  -因为我想努力想出
- Why didn't you tell me then? - 'Cause I was trying to think

703
00:27:33,270 --> 00:27:34,270
一个更好的办法
of a better option.

704
00:27:34,270 --> 00:27:35,620
已经有的办法有什么不好
What the hell's wrong with this option?

705
00:27:35,620 --> 00:27:37,650
刚才的办法牵扯到沃尔特·吉利斯
It involves going to Walter Gillis.

706
00:27:47,940 --> 00:27:49,910
看看是谁来了
Well, look who decided to drop by.

707
00:27:49,910 --> 00:27:51,700
那个害我丢了公司的家伙
The man who lost me my company

708
00:27:51,700 --> 00:27:53,980
还有他那个把公司拆散的搭档
and his partner who tore it to shreds.

709
00:27:53,980 --> 00:27:55,870
沃尔特  我明白你的感受
Walter, I understand how you must feel.

710
00:27:55,870 --> 00:27:57,330
那你们还来这里干什么
So, why are you here?

711
00:27:57,330 --> 00:27:59,020
因为我们为你准备了一个提议
Because we have a proposition for you.

712
00:27:59,020 --> 00:28:01,160
提议里包括道歉吗
Does it involve an apology?

713
00:28:01,160 --> 00:28:02,420
它本身就是道歉
It is an apology.

714
00:28:10,170 --> 00:28:11,870
你想让我把回春制药买下来
You want me to buy Versalife?

715
00:28:11,870 --> 00:28:14,220
我们想让你把回春制药的一个部门买下来
We want you to buy a division of Versalife.

716
00:28:14,220 --> 00:28:15,980
生产那种药物的部门
The division that makes that drug.

717
00:28:15,980 --> 00:28:18,460
他们致力于研发抗瘾药物很多年了
They've been working on anti-addiction meds for years.

718
00:28:18,460 --> 00:28:20,730
看看那些结果  这个有效
Look at the results. This one works.

719
00:28:20,730 --> 00:28:22,940
但那是个赔钱货  而且要花费数年
But it's a money-loser and it's gonna take years.

720
00:28:22,940 --> 00:28:24,780
他们没有那样的财力  和耐心
They don't have the capital, the patience,

721
00:28:24,780 --> 00:28:26,360
-或者说意愿  -但你有
- or the will. - But you do.

722
00:28:26,360 --> 00:28:29,020
让我猜猜  你们俩来这里
And let me guess, you two are here out of the goodness

723
00:28:29,020 --> 00:28:31,160
-是出于善心  -你想听真话吗
- of your hearts. - You want the truth?

724
00:28:31,160 --> 00:28:33,980
不管对他有没有好处  他都会来
He'd be here whether this was for his own good or not.

725
00:28:33,980 --> 00:28:36,490
但我来  是因为这可以帮我跳出泥潭
For me, I'm here because it gets me out of a jam.

726
00:28:36,490 --> 00:28:38,800
所以你也可以继续跟我们对着干
So you can stick it to us if you want to,

727
00:28:39,220 --> 00:28:40,400
但如果你那样做了
but if you do that...

728
00:28:41,390 --> 00:28:43,440
你会失去拯救其他很多跟菲利普
You're gonna miss the chance to save a lot of other people

729
00:28:43,440 --> 00:28:44,480
一样的人的机会
just like Phillip.

730
00:28:45,290 --> 00:28:47,000
不要再跟我谈菲利普
Don't ever talk to me about Phillip again.

731
00:28:47,350 --> 00:28:48,600
-沃尔特  -不行
- Walter-- - No.

732
00:28:48,600 --> 00:28:52,180
这一切就是这样开始的  你利用我的儿子
This is how all this started, with you using my son.

733
00:28:52,180 --> 00:28:54,740
不  我才是利用你儿子的人
No, I'm the one who used your son.

734
00:28:55,000 --> 00:28:57,640
我利用他控制你的公司
I used him to get control of your company,

735
00:28:57,640 --> 00:28:59,760
但迈克自从遇到你  所做的每一件事
but everything Mike did from the second he met you

736
00:28:59,760 --> 00:29:01,310
都是为了拯救你的公司
was to save your company,

737
00:29:01,310 --> 00:29:03,420
因为谈到关心他人的时候
because when it comes to caring about people,

738
00:29:03,790 --> 00:29:05,120
他比我强太多
he's twice the man that I am,

739
00:29:05,120 --> 00:29:06,930
顺便一提  他从来没有放弃过你
and by the way, he never gave up on you,

740
00:29:06,930 --> 00:29:08,590
也从来没有出卖过你
and he never sold you out.

741
00:29:08,590 --> 00:29:09,610
胡说
Bullshit.

742
00:29:09,950 --> 00:29:10,880
你说得对  没错
You're right, it is.

743
00:29:10,880 --> 00:29:11,880
迈克  别说了
Mike, no.

744
00:29:14,090 --> 00:29:15,890
真相是  我给了你承诺
The truth is, is that I gave you my word.

745
00:29:15,890 --> 00:29:17,470
我告诉你我永远不会出卖你
I told you I would never sell you out

746
00:29:17,470 --> 00:29:20,030
可我和一个我不该信任的人联手
and then I got into bed with someone that I never should have trusted

747
00:29:20,030 --> 00:29:22,290
-害你丢了公司  -是的
- and I lost you your company. - Yes, you did.

748
00:29:22,290 --> 00:29:23,650
那个公司是你的家
And that company was your family.

749
00:29:23,650 --> 00:29:26,820
他给你生存的目标  但你还有钱
It gave you purpose, but you still have money,

750
00:29:26,820 --> 00:29:28,520
这也是一个目标
and this is a purpose.

751
00:29:28,520 --> 00:29:31,020
沃尔特  如果你不想这么做  我理解
Walter, if you don't want to do this, I get it.

752
00:29:31,800 --> 00:29:33,620
但我需要你明白
But I need you to understand that the only reason

753
00:29:33,620 --> 00:29:36,190
我一开始就想找你的唯一原因
I even thought to come to you in the first place

754
00:29:37,520 --> 00:29:39,360
是因为我的余生都会后悔
is that I'm gonna regret what I did to you

755
00:29:39,360 --> 00:29:40,880
我对你所做的那些事
for the rest of my life.

756
00:29:49,440 --> 00:29:50,950
-我能进来吗  -当然
- Can I come in? - Of course.

757
00:29:53,670 --> 00:29:56,110
我希望你不要生我的气
I hope you're not furious with me.

758
00:29:56,940 --> 00:29:57,690
我没有生气
I'm not mad.

759
00:29:59,440 --> 00:30:00,110
你没有吗
You're not?

760
00:30:00,900 --> 00:30:01,580
没有
No.

761
00:30:02,660 --> 00:30:03,450
那就好
Well, good.

762
00:30:05,150 --> 00:30:06,990
我想  谢谢你
I wanted to... thank you

763
00:30:06,990 --> 00:30:08,740
为我安排与罗伯特·赞恩的会面
for setting up that meeting with Robert Zane.

764
00:30:09,060 --> 00:30:10,710
我只希望你明白如果我有得选
I just hope you understand that if I had a choice,

765
00:30:10,710 --> 00:30:12,030
我绝不会去找回春制药
I never would have gone after Versalife,

766
00:30:12,030 --> 00:30:13,280
但我没得选
but I had no choice.

767
00:30:13,280 --> 00:30:14,530
路易  我们把它抢回来了
Louis, we took them back.

768
00:30:16,210 --> 00:30:17,000
什么
What?

769
00:30:18,390 --> 00:30:19,580
但你必须放弃他们
But you had to drop them.

770
00:30:19,580 --> 00:30:20,480
不用了
Not anymore.

771
00:30:22,000 --> 00:30:24,590
我们说服他们卖掉了试验药物部门
We convinced them to sell their trial drug division.

772
00:30:24,780 --> 00:30:27,540
当然了  你帮他们摆脱了赔钱的大包袱
Of course. You drop a drain on their earnings,

773
00:30:27,850 --> 00:30:29,250
股价会飞上天的
stock price goes right through the roof.

774
00:30:29,250 --> 00:30:31,280
而市场份额也会降至临界值以下
And their market share falls below the threshold.

775
00:30:31,280 --> 00:30:32,480
但是谁会买它呢
But who the hell would buy it?

776
00:30:32,480 --> 00:30:33,510
沃尔特·吉利斯
Walter Gillis.

777
00:30:43,710 --> 00:30:45,340
当然了  沃尔特·吉利斯
Of course, Walter Gillis.

778
00:30:45,340 --> 00:30:46,810
-路易  听我说  -迈克
- Louis, listen-- - Mike.

779
00:30:47,150 --> 00:30:48,140
你赢了
You won.

780
00:30:49,230 --> 00:30:50,600
你是个出色的律师
You're a brilliant lawyer.

781
00:30:51,130 --> 00:30:52,830
你才是出色的律师
You are a brilliant lawyer.

782
00:30:52,830 --> 00:30:55,180
是啊  我是个不会再有工作的出色律师
Yeah, I'm a brilliant lawyer who's never gonna work again.

783
00:30:55,180 --> 00:30:56,340
别这么说
Hey, stop.

784
00:30:56,340 --> 00:30:57,530
不是这样的
That is not true.

785
00:30:59,260 --> 00:31:01,010
看看  看看你所拥有的一切
Look--look--look at everything that you have.

786
00:31:01,010 --> 00:31:03,380
哈佛法学院的文凭  最优成绩毕业
A Harvard law diploma, summa cum laude,

787
00:31:03,380 --> 00:31:04,330
白帽协会会员
order of the coif.

788
00:31:04,330 --> 00:31:06,850
那些都是最高法院法官才有的荣誉
Those are the credentials of a Supreme Court justice.

789
00:31:06,850 --> 00:31:09,180
那些加两块钱能在地铁里给我找个位置
Nah, that and 2 bucks will get me a seat on the subway,

790
00:31:09,640 --> 00:31:12,650
但还是谢谢你尊重我
but thank you for having the decency

791
00:31:12,650 --> 00:31:13,720
亲自来告诉我
to tell me in person.

792
00:31:14,740 --> 00:31:15,580
路易  别这样
Louis, come on.

793
00:31:15,580 --> 00:31:16,660
让我  让我
Let me--let me--

794
00:31:16,660 --> 00:31:17,920
让我再待一会
Let me stick around for a while.

795
00:31:17,920 --> 00:31:19,500
我们喝两杯
We'll have--we'll have a couple of drinks.

796
00:31:19,500 --> 00:31:21,270
你可以给我讲讲那个钥匙的故事
You--you can tell me the story about that key.

797
00:31:23,930 --> 00:31:25,280
迈克  我知道你在干什么
Mike, I know what you're tryin' to do.

798
00:31:26,270 --> 00:31:27,440
现在不是时候
Now's not the time.

799
00:31:28,760 --> 00:31:29,710
请走吧
Please go.

800
00:31:51,220 --> 00:31:51,950
进来
Come in.

801
00:31:55,720 --> 00:31:56,990
你不是路易·利特
You're not Louis Litt.

802
00:31:57,150 --> 00:31:59,820
我不是  但如果你在等他
No, I'm not. But if you're expecting him to show up,

803
00:31:59,820 --> 00:32:01,020
那恐怕要等很久了
it's gonna be a long wait.

804
00:32:01,020 --> 00:32:02,630
你是来抢他位子的吗
You here to take his spot?

805
00:32:02,630 --> 00:32:05,270
我立刻给你高级合伙人的位置
I'll give you senior partner right now.

806
00:32:05,270 --> 00:32:07,810
我是来告诉你  你不会得到回春制药了
I'm here to tell you you're not getting versalife.

807
00:32:08,630 --> 00:32:10,130
对不起  我不知道那是什么
I'm sorry, I don't know who that is.

808
00:32:10,130 --> 00:32:12,320
就是那家你想从我那里偷走的公司
It's the company you tried to poach from me.

809
00:32:12,320 --> 00:32:14,770
-你看起来不开心  -我没有不开心
- You seem upset. - I'm not upset.

810
00:32:15,070 --> 00:32:16,920
我只想提醒你  你曾经告诉我
I just wanted to remind you you once told me

811
00:32:16,920 --> 00:32:19,650
我利用你的女儿对付你是个混蛋
I was a piece of shit for using your daughter against you,

812
00:32:19,650 --> 00:32:21,800
但现在你转过头利用路易对付我
but now you turn around and use Louis against me?

813
00:32:22,000 --> 00:32:24,130
-不  那不一样  -对我来说一样
- No, that's not the same. - It is to me.

814
00:32:24,400 --> 00:32:26,960
我虽然在对付他  但他依旧是我的家人
I may fight with him, but he's still my family.

815
00:32:27,260 --> 00:32:29,560
-那他为什么离开  -这是我和路易之间的事
- Then why did he leave? - That's between me and louis.

816
00:32:29,910 --> 00:32:31,610
我是想要回春制药
I wanted Versalife,

817
00:32:31,610 --> 00:32:33,950
但那也不值得来炫耀
but it's not worth gloating over.

818
00:32:34,310 --> 00:32:35,930
你到底为什么来这儿
So why are you really here, Harvey?

819
00:32:35,930 --> 00:32:37,850
我来请求你无论如何雇下路易
I'm here to ask you to take Louis anyway.

820
00:32:37,850 --> 00:32:39,390
我为什么要雇他
And why would I do that?

821
00:32:39,390 --> 00:32:40,830
因为你是个聪明人
'Cause you're a smart man.

822
00:32:40,830 --> 00:32:42,540
你雇下他  我就欠你份情
If you do it, I'll owe you one.

823
00:32:44,430 --> 00:32:46,150
我不需要你欠我情
I don't need you owin' me one.

824
00:32:46,520 --> 00:32:48,450
你不如先考虑一夜
Why don't you take the night to think about it?

825
00:32:48,450 --> 00:32:49,820
要说我学到的事情  有一件
'Cause if there's one thing I've learned,

826
00:32:49,820 --> 00:32:52,240
人情永远不嫌多
you can never have too many favors in the bank.

827
00:33:02,120 --> 00:33:03,110
你想见我
You wanted to see me?

828
00:33:03,570 --> 00:33:05,170
我听说了回春制药的事
I heard about Versalife.

829
00:33:05,430 --> 00:33:06,330
做得好
Good work.

830
00:33:08,320 --> 00:33:09,520
不是你做的
It wasn't you.

831
00:33:09,520 --> 00:33:11,270
对  不是
No, it wasn't.

832
00:33:11,270 --> 00:33:12,970
你知道我以为是你
You know I thought it was you.

833
00:33:14,000 --> 00:33:15,010
哈维没跟我说
Harvey didn't tell me,

834
00:33:15,010 --> 00:33:17,540
但我也没有太过天真无知
but I didn't just fall off the turnip truck.

835
00:33:17,540 --> 00:33:19,160
对  是没有
No, you didn't.

836
00:33:20,880 --> 00:33:21,640
怎么了
What?

837
00:33:21,640 --> 00:33:25,750
每次我觉得留用你没好处时
Every damn time I think there's no upside to having you,

838
00:33:25,990 --> 00:33:27,450
你就会做点事让我觉得
you do some shit to make me think

839
00:33:27,450 --> 00:33:29,520
有你在还是挺好的
it's actually nice to have you around.

840
00:33:30,420 --> 00:33:31,730
那我们没事了
So, we're good?

841
00:33:32,050 --> 00:33:35,010
你今晚再贡献几个工时  就没事了
We're good after you bill a few more hours tonight.

842
00:33:36,080 --> 00:33:37,660
那得再等等
Well, that's gonna have to wait until later,

843
00:33:37,660 --> 00:33:40,170
我现在必须得出去庆祝一下
because I am definitely going out to celebrate.

844
00:33:40,880 --> 00:33:42,090
你应得的
You've earned it.

845
00:33:42,610 --> 00:33:43,550
杰西卡
Jessica.

846
00:33:46,870 --> 00:33:49,140
她做了哈维愿意为你做的事
She did what Harvey would have done for you.

847
00:34:03,100 --> 00:34:04,910
-杰西卡  -卡特里娜
- Jessica. - Katrina.

848
00:34:05,380 --> 00:34:06,860
你找我是为...
Is this about the--

849
00:34:06,860 --> 00:34:08,330
我可以解雇你
I can either fire you...

850
00:34:09,580 --> 00:34:11,000
或者你可以自己辞职
or you can resign.

851
00:34:11,350 --> 00:34:12,590
你自己选吧
The choice is yours.

852
00:34:14,570 --> 00:34:15,550
你知道了
You know?

853
00:34:15,550 --> 00:34:16,670
我知道了
I know.

854
00:34:17,970 --> 00:34:19,750
那你为什么这么和善
Then why are you being so nice about it?

855
00:34:20,900 --> 00:34:22,650
因为让你离开就够了
Because letting you go is enough.

856
00:34:23,340 --> 00:34:25,770
你也不想与我为敌
And you also don't want to antagonize me,

857
00:34:26,220 --> 00:34:28,050
因为我要去为罗伯特·赞恩工作了
since I'll be working for Robert Zane.

858
00:34:28,600 --> 00:34:29,790
你还没听说吗
You haven't heard?

859
00:34:31,560 --> 00:34:33,410
我们把回春制药抢回来了
We got Versalife back.

860
00:34:35,060 --> 00:34:36,670
路易不会去赞恩那里
Louis won't be going to Zane,

861
00:34:37,210 --> 00:34:38,410
你也不会了
and neither will you.

862
00:34:42,430 --> 00:34:43,660
祝你好运
I wish you luck.

863
00:34:45,620 --> 00:34:47,320
我会明早会把辞职信
You'll have my letter of resignation on your desk

864
00:34:47,320 --> 00:34:48,320
放在你桌上
in the morning.

865
00:35:24,780 --> 00:35:26,000
你怎么这么长时间才出来
What took you so long?

866
00:35:26,000 --> 00:35:27,560
你是什么  卫生间监控器吗
What are you, the bathroom monitor?

867
00:35:27,560 --> 00:35:29,980
如果我是  会说你一小时已经去三次了
Well, if I were, I'd say you'd gone three times in an hour.

868
00:35:29,980 --> 00:35:31,900
对  而这是咱们第三杯酒
Yes, and this is our third drink.

869
00:35:32,570 --> 00:35:34,710
你知道他们有治那病的药  对吧
You know they have medicine for that, right?

870
00:35:34,870 --> 00:35:35,860
你是说我老了
You saying I'm old?

871
00:35:35,860 --> 00:35:37,080
对  我也是说
Yes, but I'm also saying

872
00:35:37,080 --> 00:35:38,510
我知道你不是去卫生间
I know you haven't been goin' to the bathroom.

873
00:35:38,510 --> 00:35:40,090
好吧  你想知道真相吗
All right, you want the truth?

874
00:35:40,090 --> 00:35:41,370
我在给唐娜打电话
I've been calling Donna.

875
00:35:41,370 --> 00:35:43,150
天呐  太好了
Oh my god, that is so great.

876
00:35:43,150 --> 00:35:45,350
你俩终于决定更进一步了
You guys finally decided to take the plunge.

877
00:35:45,350 --> 00:35:47,770
我想知道罗伯特·赞恩回我电话没有
I wanted to know if Robert Zane called me back.

878
00:35:47,770 --> 00:35:48,780
给你回电话做什么
Called you back about what?

879
00:35:48,780 --> 00:35:50,600
我要他无论如何雇下路易
I asked him to hire Louis anyway.

880
00:35:50,600 --> 00:35:52,350
-你开玩笑吧  -没有
- You're kidding. - I'm not.

881
00:35:52,350 --> 00:35:54,900
我还跟他说  他雇了我就欠他份情
I even told him if he did I'd owe him one.

882
00:35:54,900 --> 00:35:56,750
怎么了
What?

883
00:35:56,750 --> 00:35:58,210
我只是在想你上周什么时候
Oh, I'm just tryin' to figure out at what point

884
00:35:58,210 --> 00:36:00,960
决定变成娘炮的
in the last week you decided to become a pussy.

885
00:36:00,960 --> 00:36:04,110
为人做好事就是变娘炮吗
Oh, so doing something nice for someone makes you a pussy?

886
00:36:04,110 --> 00:36:05,640
-我没那么说  -你说了
- I didn't say that exactly. - Yes, you did.

887
00:36:05,640 --> 00:36:07,330
咱们来数数你为别人
Let's just go through some of the nice things

888
00:36:07,330 --> 00:36:08,080
做过的好事吧
you've done for people. 

889
00:36:08,080 --> 00:36:08,830
好吧  哈维
Okay, you know what, Harvey?

890
00:36:08,830 --> 00:36:09,830
我有罪
Guilty as charged.

891
00:36:09,830 --> 00:36:11,970
我是好人  如果这样就是娘炮
I am nice, and if that makes me a pussy, 

892
00:36:11,970 --> 00:36:12,510
那就是吧
then so be it.

893
00:36:13,150 --> 00:36:15,670
那就结案了  你是个好娘炮
Then it's settled: you're a nice pussy.

894
00:36:15,670 --> 00:36:18,110
女士  能给我朋友来本《时尚》吗
Miss, can I get a Cosmo here for my friend?

895
00:36:17,110 --> 00:36:19,110
{\an8}《时尚》  女性杂志

896
00:36:18,110 --> 00:36:19,720
再点杯酒吧
Go ahead, order another drink.

897
00:36:19,720 --> 00:36:20,960
但是小心点  再过五分钟
Just be careful, 'cause you're gonna

898
00:36:20,960 --> 00:36:22,400
你又要去卫生间了
be in the bathroom in another five minutes.

899
00:36:22,400 --> 00:36:24,000
你又要说前列腺的事了吗
You going back to the prostate again?

900
00:36:24,000 --> 00:36:26,270
怎么  你就没说过老笑话吗
What, like you've never repeated jokes before?

901
00:36:26,270 --> 00:36:28,740
-我完全不知道  -我在说什么
- I have no idea what-- - What I'm talking about?

902
00:36:28,740 --> 00:36:30,010
我想想啊  "你看
Let's see uh, "You see,

903
00:36:30,010 --> 00:36:31,780
"真有意思  因为什么什么"
that's funny, because blah-blah-blah,"

904
00:36:31,780 --> 00:36:34,010
或者"我说什么  是什么什么"
or "By blah-blah-blah, I mean blah-blah-blah."

905
00:36:34,010 --> 00:36:36,010
-好了  我明白了  -我才刚开始
- Okay, I get it. - Oh, I'm just getting started.

906
00:36:36,010 --> 00:36:36,990
我能说一晚上呢
I could do this all night. 

907
00:36:36,990 --> 00:36:37,960
你猜怎么
Hey, you know what?

908
00:36:37,960 --> 00:36:39,250
我现在真得去卫生间了
Now I have to go to the bathroom.

909
00:36:39,250 --> 00:36:41,580
去吧  慢慢来  不急
Go for it. Take your time, no rush.

910
00:36:41,580 --> 00:36:43,630
疼的话  记得打电话找人
If it hurts, call someone.

911
00:36:57,340 --> 00:36:59,610
路易  你在这儿做什么
Louis, what are you doing here?

912
00:36:59,610 --> 00:37:00,960
我在等哈维
I'm waiting for Harvey.

913
00:37:02,090 --> 00:37:03,310
哈维不在
Harvey's not here.

914
00:37:05,570 --> 00:37:06,710
那就你吧
Then you'll have to do.

915
00:37:07,210 --> 00:37:08,780
听我说  路易
Look, Louis,

916
00:37:08,780 --> 00:37:11,160
我知道你最近经历了很多
I know you've been through a lot,

917
00:37:11,160 --> 00:37:12,240
但哈维会...
but Harvey's gonna--

918
00:37:12,240 --> 00:37:14,500
我根本不关心哈维会做什么
I don't give a shit what Harvey's gonna do.

919
00:37:14,500 --> 00:37:16,020
你吓着我了
Okay, you're scaring me.

920
00:37:26,130 --> 00:37:27,830
你知道奥斯卡是什么样吗
You know what an oscar looks like?

921
00:37:28,660 --> 00:37:31,380
-什么  -奥斯卡奖杯  光头男
- What? - Academy award. Bald guy.

922
00:37:31,770 --> 00:37:33,420
我们当然都知道它是什么样
I mean, of course we all know what it looks like,

923
00:37:33,420 --> 00:37:35,410
特别是你  你是演员
but especially you, you're an actress.

924
00:37:35,410 --> 00:37:37,370
那是你们圈子里最高的荣誉
It's the highest honor in your field.

925
00:37:38,060 --> 00:37:39,490
你当然不需要人告诉你它是什么
I mean, of course you don't need to be told what it is.

926
00:37:39,490 --> 00:37:40,810
你在说什么
What are you talking about? 

927
00:37:40,820 --> 00:37:43,160
哈佛法学院的最高荣誉
The highest academic honor in Harvard Law

928
00:37:43,160 --> 00:37:45,220
是白帽协会
is the order of the coif.

929
00:37:46,650 --> 00:37:47,930
白帽协会没有奖杯
You don't get a trophy.

930
00:37:49,330 --> 00:37:50,920
只颁三样东西
You get three things.

931
00:37:51,550 --> 00:37:54,620
一卷羊皮纸证书  可以挂在墙上
You get a parchment to hang on your wall,

932
00:37:55,030 --> 00:37:56,640
一块在毕业典礼上戴的奖牌
a medal to wear at graduation,

933
00:37:58,070 --> 00:37:59,030
还有这个
and this.

934
00:38:00,550 --> 00:38:04,620
这把钥匙上没写"白帽协会"
Now, this key doesn't say "Order of the coif."

935
00:38:05,290 --> 00:38:06,560
什么也没写
It doesn't say anything.

936
00:38:06,940 --> 00:38:08,270
只是个象征
It's just a symbol.

937
00:38:08,760 --> 00:38:10,100
那跟哈维有什么关系
What does that have to do with Harvey?

938
00:38:10,100 --> 00:38:11,630
是没关系  但跟迈克有关系
It doesn't. It has to do with Mike.

939
00:38:11,630 --> 00:38:13,450
知道吗  路易  今天已经够漫长了  能...
You know what, Louis? It's been a long day, can--

940
00:38:13,450 --> 00:38:14,840
还得再长点
It's about to get longer.

941
00:38:17,800 --> 00:38:19,710
你看  迈克问我这玩意儿
See, Mike asked me about this.

942
00:38:21,320 --> 00:38:22,930
我还以为他...
And I thought he was--

943
00:38:25,070 --> 00:38:29,340
我以为他是想让我忘掉我的烦恼
I thought he was trying to get my mind off of my problems,

944
00:38:29,340 --> 00:38:30,770
但他又问了
but then he did it again.

945
00:38:31,710 --> 00:38:33,370
这让我想到
And it got me to thinking:

946
00:38:34,180 --> 00:38:36,820
迈克以极优成绩毕业
Mike graduated magna cum laude.

947
00:38:38,700 --> 00:38:41,060
他是白帽协会的会员
He's in order of the coif.

948
00:38:43,550 --> 00:38:45,200
但他没有认出这个
But he didn't recognize this.

949
00:38:45,610 --> 00:38:47,120
他只是忘了一把愚蠢的钥匙
So he forgot a stupid key.

950
00:38:47,920 --> 00:38:49,620
迈克·罗斯过目不忘
Mike Ross doesn't forget anything.

951
00:38:50,680 --> 00:38:52,970
他认不出这钥匙的原因
See, the reason he didn't recognize this

952
00:38:53,530 --> 00:38:56,950
是因为他根本没有得到过  因为...
was because he never got one, because...

953
00:38:58,520 --> 00:39:00,120
他没上过哈佛
he didn't go to Harvard.

954
00:39:02,310 --> 00:39:04,070
路易  我们以前就讨论过这个了
Louis, we've been down this road before.

955
00:39:04,070 --> 00:39:05,510
哈佛资料库里有迈克
Mike is in the Harvard database.

956
00:39:05,510 --> 00:39:07,100
但年鉴里没有
But he's not in the yearbook,

957
00:39:07,100 --> 00:39:08,570
并且根据他的信用报告
and according to his credit report,

958
00:39:08,570 --> 00:39:11,210
他读法学院期间的地址在纽约
his address during his law school years was in New York.

959
00:39:11,740 --> 00:39:14,430
他甚至每月第一天亲自去交房租
He even paid rent the first of the month in person.

960
00:39:15,040 --> 00:39:17,090
-我相信一定有...  -坐下
- Well, I'm sure there's an-- - Sit down!

961
00:39:18,460 --> 00:39:21,690
去年  你告诉我别跟希拉说迈克的档案
Last year, you told me not to tell Sheila about Mike's file.

962
00:39:22,140 --> 00:39:25,140
你表现出在乎我的样子
You acted like you cared about me.

963
00:39:25,140 --> 00:39:27,960
但其实根本不在乎
You didn't give a shit about me.

964
00:39:28,440 --> 00:39:29,980
你只在乎自己
You cared about you!

965
00:39:30,400 --> 00:39:31,450
-和哈维  -不是的
- And Harvey! - No.

966
00:39:31,450 --> 00:39:32,420
-还有迈克  -不是
- And Mike! - No.

967
00:39:32,420 --> 00:39:34,380
-还有杰西卡  -路易  不是这样的
- And Jessica! - Louis, that's not true!

968
00:39:34,380 --> 00:39:36,410
那现在就给希拉打电话
Well, let's call Sheila right now.

969
00:39:36,780 --> 00:39:38,850
号码我都记得
I know all of the numbers by heart.

970
00:39:38,850 --> 00:39:41,060
她可能对我没兴趣了
I mean, she may not be interested in me anymore,

971
00:39:41,060 --> 00:39:43,680
但她肯定会对谎称上过哈佛的
but she will definitely be interested in a fraud claiming

972
00:39:43,680 --> 00:39:45,050
骗子有兴趣
that he went to Harvard.

973
00:39:53,540 --> 00:39:54,520
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

974
00:39:57,510 --> 00:39:58,680
你很抱歉吗
You're sorry?

975
00:40:02,810 --> 00:40:06,580
你从迈克·罗斯来的第一天就开始骗我
You've been lying to me since the day Mike Ross arrived.

976
00:40:09,170 --> 00:40:12,500
我知道哈维和杰西从未真正接受我
I knew Harvey and Jessica never really accepted me,

977
00:40:12,500 --> 00:40:14,070
但我以为你不一样
but I thought you were different.

978
00:40:14,880 --> 00:40:16,540
我当你是我朋友
I thought you were my friend.

979
00:40:16,850 --> 00:40:19,970
-我是你朋友啊  路易  -不  你不是
- I am your friend, Louis. - No, you're not.

980
00:40:22,400 --> 00:40:24,320
你再也不准对我说那样的话
And don't you ever say that to me again.

981
00:40:27,210 --> 00:40:28,240
你要去哪里
Where are you going?

982
00:40:30,870 --> 00:40:32,510
去见你朋友杰西卡
To see your friend Jessica.

983
00:40:40,150 --> 00:40:41,540
路易知道了
Louis knows.

984
00:40:49,520 --> 00:40:50,430
路易
Louis.

985
00:40:51,120 --> 00:40:52,460
我知道你是个坚守规则的人
I know you're a stickler for the rules,

986
00:40:52,460 --> 00:40:54,870
所以我来还我的身份卡
so I figured I'd just come by to return my I.D.

987
00:40:54,870 --> 00:40:56,250
你想要个解释
You want an explanation.

988
00:40:56,250 --> 00:40:58,040
我想看到你这个罪犯铐着手铐
I want to see you perp walked through the bullpen

989
00:40:58,040 --> 00:41:01,050
上面盖着你那漂亮的小外套  走过候审室
with your pretty little jacket draped over your handcuffs.

990
00:41:01,890 --> 00:41:03,910
但在那之前  我需要个解释
But until then, yeah, I'll take an explanation.

991
00:41:05,500 --> 00:41:09,200
我搞清迈克·罗斯的真实情况时
When I found out the truth about Mike Ross,

992
00:41:09,500 --> 00:41:10,980
木已成舟
it had already been done.

993
00:41:11,800 --> 00:41:12,750
哈维干的吗
By Harvey?

994
00:41:14,530 --> 00:41:17,960
就在他取代我成为资深合伙人之后吗
Right after he made senior partner over me?

995
00:41:17,960 --> 00:41:20,350
他就是在那时雇的那个骗子吗
That's when he hired the fraud?

996
00:41:20,350 --> 00:41:21,350
是在那个时候吗
That's the correct timeline, right?

997
00:41:21,350 --> 00:41:22,010
对
Yes.

998
00:41:22,880 --> 00:41:24,350
但你非但没有告发他
So instead of turning him in,

999
00:41:24,350 --> 00:41:26,470
-还帮他掩盖了过去  -路易
- you cover it up. - Louis--

1000
00:41:26,470 --> 00:41:28,890
而当我犯了事
And the one time that I do something...

1001
00:41:30,160 --> 00:41:31,550
你根本没有帮我掩盖
you don't cover it up at all.

1002
00:41:33,110 --> 00:41:34,510
而是把我送入虎口
You throw me to the wolves.

1003
00:41:34,510 --> 00:41:36,660
我帮你虎口脱险
I saved you from the wolves.

1004
00:41:36,660 --> 00:41:39,310
之后我卑躬屈膝
Then I ask you for the smallest gesture,

1005
00:41:39,600 --> 00:41:41,830
请求你允许我有尊严地继续我的事业
just to allow my career to continue with dignity,

1006
00:41:41,830 --> 00:41:46,360
你却一丝同情都不给
and you couldn't muster the tiniest shred of compassion.

1007
00:41:49,090 --> 00:41:50,290
你想让我说什么
What do you want me to say?

1008
00:41:50,290 --> 00:41:52,480
我想让你告诉我你是个骗子
I want you to tell me you're a liar!

1009
00:41:54,920 --> 00:41:56,320
是个伪君子
And a hypocrite!

1010
00:42:02,380 --> 00:42:04,330
我想让你道歉
I want you to say you're sorry.

1011
00:42:10,070 --> 00:42:11,230
我是个骗子
I am a liar.

1012
00:42:15,870 --> 00:42:19,500
也是个伪君子
And I am a hypocrite.

1013
00:42:22,140 --> 00:42:24,600
但我不会道歉
But I will not say I'm sorry,

1014
00:42:25,430 --> 00:42:29,720
因为我做的这一切是为了保护律所
because I did what I did to protect this firm.

1015
00:42:29,720 --> 00:42:32,340
看来船长就要和船一起沉没了
Well, looks like the captain's about to go down with her ship.

1016
00:42:32,340 --> 00:42:33,330
胡说
Bullshit.

1017
00:42:34,370 --> 00:42:35,700
你是有目的的
You want something.

1018
00:42:35,940 --> 00:42:37,600
我告诉过你  我想看到你
Oh, I told you. I want to see you in--

1019
00:42:37,600 --> 00:42:39,130
戴着手铐吗
In handcuffs?

1020
00:42:39,540 --> 00:42:40,400
如果真是那样
If that were true,

1021
00:42:40,410 --> 00:42:42,570
来这儿的应该是警察而不是你
the police would be here instead of you.

1022
00:42:43,570 --> 00:42:48,520
不是的  你想在向我提出
No, you wanted to see me squirm

1023
00:42:49,030 --> 00:42:51,800
真正的诉求前  看到我局促不安
before asking me for what you really want.

1024
00:42:55,260 --> 00:42:57,530
我不会满足你的
I'm not gonna give you the satisfaction.

1025
00:42:58,420 --> 00:43:00,570
你还是直接说吧
So you might as well spit it out.

1026
00:43:02,460 --> 00:43:04,960
你曾经问过我想要什么  我告诉了你
You asked me what I wanted once before and I told you.

1027
00:43:04,960 --> 00:43:06,780
那时你说我不可能得到
And then you tole me I couldn't have it.

1028
00:43:09,530 --> 00:43:10,870
但我现在可以了
But now I can. 

1029
00:43:13,900 --> 00:43:15,100
皮尔逊
Pearson.

1030
00:43:17,270 --> 00:43:18,620
斯佩克特
Specter

1031
00:43:21,940 --> 00:43:23,450
利特
Litt.

