1
00:00:00,040 --> 00:00:01,590
《訴訟雙雄》前情提要

2
00:00:01,700 --> 00:00:03,430
這很明顯就是賄賂
I'm looking at a bribe, plain as day.

3
00:00:03,430 --> 00:00:05,150
事實就是這樣
That's exactly what it is.

4
00:00:05,150 --> 00:00:07,690
托尼·揚諾普洛斯不知如何拿到了那盤錄像
Tony Gianopolous got a hold of that video somehow.

5
00:00:07,690 --> 00:00:09,200
我覺得他在試圖控制你們的公司
I think he's trying to take over the company.

6
00:00:09,200 --> 00:00:11,490
你個狗娘養的  是你把錄像泄露出去的
You son of a bitch. You leaked it.

7
00:00:11,490 --> 00:00:13,510
艾娃·海辛頓就是海辛頓石油
Ava hessington is Hessington Oil.

8
00:00:13,510 --> 00:00:15,090
-不會太久了  -你說什么
- Not for long. - Excuse me?

9
00:00:15,090 --> 00:00:17,500
-這由我決定  -我恐怕不是你能決定的
- This is my call. - I'm afraid it isn't.

10
00:00:17,500 --> 00:00:19,510
你希望艾娃主動退出管理層
You'd like her to remove herself from management?

11
00:00:19,510 --> 00:00:21,890
我不會眼睜睜地看著這場官司打輸
I'm not going to stand for losing this takeover.

12
00:00:21,890 --> 00:00:24,630
那就別光看不做  但是艾娃絕不能離開
Then don't. But Ava isn't going anywhere.

13
00:00:24,820 --> 00:00:26,970
我剛剛被自己公司投票表決踢出來了
I just got voted out of my own company.

14
00:00:26,970 --> 00:00:29,110
我堅信這么做沒錯  即使有下次我還會這么做
I stand by my decision, and I'd do it again.

15
00:00:29,110 --> 00:00:30,800
我知道這件事和達比有關
Don't tell me it doesn't have to do with Darby.

16
00:00:30,800 --> 00:00:33,670
是你在一開始給了他51%的股份
You're the one who gave him the 51% in the first place.

17
00:00:33,680 --> 00:00:35,670
你受不了一輩子當二把手
You can't stand being number two.

18
00:00:38,840 --> 00:00:40,110
拜托告訴我
Please tell me you're calling me

19
00:00:40,110 --> 00:00:41,350
你打給我是因為被綁架了
because you've been kidnapped.

20
00:00:41,490 --> 00:00:42,950
失蹤的又不是我
I'm not the one who disappeared.

21
00:00:43,130 --> 00:00:44,570
跟你說了我有件事要辦
I told you I had a thing.

22
00:00:44,790 --> 00:00:47,140
一點說的  現在差一刻兩點了
At 1:00. It's 1:45.

23
00:00:47,140 --> 00:00:49,050
這是午休時間  哈維
And it's called a lunch hour, Harvey.

24
00:00:49,050 --> 00:00:51,950
有整整一小時  這是我的牙應得的
60 whole minutes, which my teeth deserve.

25
00:00:51,950 --> 00:00:53,390
你午餐這點時間還能去看牙醫
You fit the dentist in at lunch?

26
00:00:53,390 --> 00:00:54,860
他可以快得驚人
He can be surprisingly quick,

27
00:00:54,860 --> 00:00:56,100
同時又非常深入
yet remarkably thorough.

28
00:00:56,100 --> 00:00:58,510
唐娜  阿特金斯法官已經準備
Donna, Judge Atkins is ready to hear

29
00:00:58,520 --> 00:01:01,660
聽我的即決審判動議了  但前提是
my motion for summary judgment, which she won't do

30
00:01:01,660 --> 00:01:03,240
十分鐘后我的手頭要有
if there aren't two copies of that motion

31
00:01:03,240 --> 00:01:04,780
兩份動議書
in my hands in ten minutes.

32
00:01:04,780 --> 00:01:06,200
好吧  告訴你怎么辦
All right, here's what you're gonna do.

33
00:01:06,660 --> 00:01:08,440
在我的電腦上按下"打印"鍵
Go to my computer and press "print".

34
00:01:08,450 --> 00:01:09,940
把動議書從打印機里取出來
Pick the motions up off the printer,

35
00:01:09,950 --> 00:01:12,080
然后走到角落里  把東西都扔進垃圾桶
then walk over to the corner, throw everything in the trash,

36
00:01:12,080 --> 00:01:13,380
因為這會兒你桌上
because there's already two copies

37
00:01:13,380 --> 00:01:15,290
已經躺著兩份動議書了
on your desk at this very moment.

38
00:01:15,290 --> 00:01:17,870
垃圾桶原來在角落里啊
So the trash can's in the corner then?

39
00:01:18,010 --> 00:01:19,050
再見
Bye.

40
00:01:24,380 --> 00:01:25,970
你只有一件"事”[亦有高潮之意]
You had "a thing"?

41
00:01:25,970 --> 00:01:29,570
其實有兩件
Well... Two things.

42
00:01:30,420 --> 00:01:31,600
但誰會去數呢
But who's counting?

43
00:01:34,700 --> 00:01:36,000
他要干什么
What did he want anyway?

44
00:01:37,080 --> 00:01:39,630
不是說好了午餐時間不討論工作嗎
I thought we agreed not to talk about work at lunch.

45
00:01:39,880 --> 00:01:40,500
是說好了
Yeah, we did,

46
00:01:40,500 --> 00:01:43,130
但我們也說好午餐時間該吃午餐的
but we also agreed to have lunch at lunch.

47
00:01:44,200 --> 00:01:46,570
你說得對
Yeah, you're right.

48
00:01:47,050 --> 00:01:50,670
只是我習慣了眼觀四路
It's just that, uh, I've always made it my business

49
00:01:51,040 --> 00:01:53,110
耳聽八方
knowing about things.

50
00:01:54,250 --> 00:01:55,490
你做得挺好
And you're good at your business.

51
00:01:55,490 --> 00:01:57,140
是挺好
Business is good.

52
00:01:57,140 --> 00:01:59,710
性致高昂啊
Some might say booming.

53
00:02:01,760 --> 00:02:03,500
我們只剩十五分鐘了
Listen, we've only got 15 minutes left,

54
00:02:03,500 --> 00:02:06,540
看來我得爭取快得驚人了
so I'll endeavor to be surprisingly quick.

55
00:02:06,540 --> 00:02:09,250
只要你保持非常深入就行
As long as you continue to be remarkably thorough.

56
00:02:14,830 --> 00:02:16,780
法官大人  您說過要是除了賄賂錄像
Your honor, you said you would dismiss this case

57
00:02:16,780 --> 00:02:18,210
他拿不出別的證據
if he couldn't produce evidence

58
00:02:18,210 --> 00:02:20,320
就不會受理這案子  而他的確拿不出
beyond the bribery tape. Well, he couldn't.

59
00:02:20,320 --> 00:02:22,250
我們找到了五名目擊者
We found five witnesses that tied the man

60
00:02:22,250 --> 00:02:24,540
能證明錄像上艾娃·海辛頓賄賂的人就是兇手
that Ava Hessington bribed on that tape to the murders.

61
00:02:24,550 --> 00:02:26,440
而這些目擊者都不愿出庭作證
And those witnesses refused to come forward.

62
00:02:26,440 --> 00:02:27,320
要是我們不能當堂對質
If we can't confront them,

63
00:02:27,320 --> 00:02:28,650
那他們的口供法庭就不能采納
then their statements are inadmissible.

64
00:02:28,650 --> 00:02:30,000
他們不愿出庭作證
Just because they won't come forward

65
00:02:30,000 --> 00:02:30,990
不代表他們不存在
doesn't mean they don't exist.

66
00:02:30,990 --> 00:02:33,110
他說得對  他們的口供法庭也許不能采納
He's right, their statements may be inadmissible,

67
00:02:33,110 --> 00:02:35,070
但我不能無視有這些口供的存在
but I can't ignore the fact that they were made.

68
00:02:35,140 --> 00:02:38,580
既然如此  那我們要求快速庭審
Well, in that case, we move for an expedited trial.

69
00:02:39,220 --> 00:02:41,560
十秒之前  他還要求不予受理
Ten seconds ago, he was moving for a dismissal.

70
00:02:41,560 --> 00:02:42,870
就是那十秒
And in the ten seconds since,

71
00:02:42,870 --> 00:02:45,960
我委托人的公眾形象更不堪了
public opinion of my client has gone down even further.

72
00:02:45,960 --> 00:02:47,500
她是個殺人兇手  還能不堪到哪去
She's a murderer. How much lower can it go?

73
00:02:47,530 --> 00:02:48,510
你告訴我啊
Well, you tell me.

74
00:02:48,510 --> 00:02:50,250
是你把證據泄露給托尼·揚諾普洛斯的
You leaked evidence to Tony Gianopolous

75
00:02:50,250 --> 00:02:52,040
害她丟了自己的公司
that lost her her company.

76
00:02:52,040 --> 00:02:53,280
你也許會泄露給任何人
You might leak it to anyone.

77
00:02:53,280 --> 00:02:54,870
法官大人  我們早就已經談過這些了
Your honor, we've been down this road before.

78
00:02:54,870 --> 00:02:56,620
這就是一派胡言
It's called bullshit highway.

79
00:02:56,620 --> 00:02:59,270
冗長的庭審只會使艾娃·海辛頓
All dragging this out does is delay Ava Hessington

80
00:02:59,270 --> 00:03:00,770
洗清罪名的機會白白流失
the opportunity to vindicate herself.

81
00:03:00,770 --> 00:03:03,900
但這也會大大減少我準備的時間
It also conveniently gives me less time to build my case.

82
00:03:03,910 --> 00:03:06,170
但你剛還在爭辯這案子證據十足可以庭審啊
But the case you just argued was solid enough to go to trial.

83
00:03:06,170 --> 00:03:08,580
你現在讓你的小跟班代你說話了嗎
You're letting your mini-me make your arguments for you now?

84
00:03:08,580 --> 00:03:09,480
你還讓你的小胡子...
Are you letting your moustache--

85
00:03:09,480 --> 00:03:10,420
夠了
Enough.

86
00:03:10,420 --> 00:03:12,580
下下周一開庭
The trial starts a week from Monday.

87
00:03:12,580 --> 00:03:13,510
出去
Get out.

88
00:03:13,610 --> 00:03:15,710
你還沒跟哈維說史蒂芬的事嗎
You still haven't told Harvey about Stephen?

89
00:03:15,710 --> 00:03:18,070
我本想告訴他的  但他當時心情不好
I went to tell him, but he was in a bad mood,

90
00:03:18,070 --> 00:03:19,430
不知怎的我就跟他說
and then somehow I ended up telling him

91
00:03:19,430 --> 00:03:21,020
我幫史蒂芬印了幾份文件
that I made some copies for Stephen,

92
00:03:21,020 --> 00:03:22,350
他便勃然大怒
and he got really pissed.

93
00:03:23,060 --> 00:03:25,220
要是知道我和史蒂芬的事不知會怎樣呢
What's he gonna do when he finds out about this?

94
00:03:25,220 --> 00:03:27,470
我記得你們倆不是從沒...
But I thought you said that you two had never--

95
00:03:28,290 --> 00:03:29,080
那又如何
So?

96
00:03:29,080 --> 00:03:30,480
我懂他為什么不想你幫別人干活
So I get why he doesn't want to share you here.

97
00:03:30,480 --> 00:03:31,550
在律所你就是他的一切
You're his everything here.

98
00:03:31,550 --> 00:03:32,790
但你和史蒂芬的事和工作無關
But what you're doing with Stephen isn't here,

99
00:03:32,790 --> 00:03:34,930
是你的私事  完全兩碼事
it's there. Two completely different things.

100
00:03:35,420 --> 00:03:37,240
那你為什么非讓我告訴他
Then why did you tell me I had to tell him?

101
00:03:37,240 --> 00:03:38,710
為了讓他知道你的私事和他的公事
To let him know that your there and his here

102
00:03:38,710 --> 00:03:40,050
可以共存于此
can coexist in the same place.

103
00:03:41,030 --> 00:03:42,650
我還是比較喜歡談論你和邁克的事
I liked it better when we talked about you and Mike.

104
00:03:42,650 --> 00:03:43,620
那廢話
I'm sure you did.

105
00:03:43,880 --> 00:03:46,290
那你們是否準備繼續...
So are you two going to keep--

106
00:03:46,290 --> 00:03:48,870
當然  這是我長久以來
Yes, it is some of the best damn...

107
00:03:48,870 --> 00:03:51,340
做的最爽的瑜伽了
yoga I've had in a long time.

108
00:03:51,340 --> 00:03:52,760
他遲早會發現的
Well, sooner or later, he's gonna find out,

109
00:03:52,760 --> 00:03:54,650
因為你臉上全寫著呢
because it is all over your face.

110
00:03:54,650 --> 00:03:55,650
拜托  你是女人
Oh, please, you're a woman.

111
00:03:55,660 --> 00:03:57,140
男人才不會注意到
Men are oblivious.

112
00:03:58,340 --> 00:03:59,510
你有點不同
There's something different about you.

113
00:04:00,170 --> 00:04:01,210
是什么呢
What is it?

114
00:04:01,620 --> 00:04:03,450
對啊  快告訴這位男士你有什么不同
Yes, please tell the man what it is.

115
00:04:04,400 --> 00:04:05,270
沒有  路易
Nothing, Louis.

116
00:04:05,270 --> 00:04:06,820
我就是  練了點瑜伽
I'm just-- been doing some yoga.

117
00:04:06,820 --> 00:04:08,540
不  不是這原因
No, that's not it.

118
00:04:08,890 --> 00:04:10,040
你整個人散發著光彩
You're practically glowing.

119
00:04:10,280 --> 00:04:11,260
告訴我你的秘訣
Tell me your secret.

120
00:04:12,370 --> 00:04:14,580
我覺得這應該不適合你做
I-I don't think that it's your cup of tea.

121
00:04:14,580 --> 00:04:15,860
為了這種光彩我什么都做
For that glow, I'd tea.

122
00:04:16,740 --> 00:04:18,540
這是我的小秘密  路易
I'm gonna have to keep this to myself, Louis.

123
00:04:18,540 --> 00:04:19,670
好吧  向我保證
Okay, well, promise me

124
00:04:19,670 --> 00:04:20,950
你要堅持繼續做下去
you'll keep doing whatever it is you're doing.

125
00:04:20,960 --> 00:04:21,520
她可以的
I think she can do that.

126
00:04:21,520 --> 00:04:23,730
不  唐娜我說真的  早午晚都要堅持
No, I'm serious, Donna. Morning, noon, and night.

127
00:04:23,850 --> 00:04:25,220
有必要的話一天五次
Five times a day if necessary.

128
00:04:25,250 --> 00:04:26,330
我會盡力的
I will do my best.

129
00:04:31,350 --> 00:04:34,030
-我們已經盡力了  -盡力
- Well, we did our best. - Our best?

130
00:04:35,240 --> 00:04:37,120
等等  你從沒計劃
Wait a minute, you never expected

131
00:04:37,120 --> 00:04:38,790
讓這案子被駁回吧
this case to get dismissed.

132
00:04:38,810 --> 00:04:40,100
那我還要求干什么
Then why would I ask for it?

133
00:04:40,180 --> 00:04:42,800
因為她拒絕駁回的請求后  更有可能
Because she was more likely to grant an expedited trial

134
00:04:42,810 --> 00:04:44,480
同意加速庭審
after saying no to a dismissal.

135
00:04:44,510 --> 00:04:47,060
所以現在卡梅隆可棘手了
And now, Cameron's got a shity case to try

136
00:04:47,450 --> 00:04:48,270
沒有證據
with no evidence

137
00:04:48,270 --> 00:04:50,390
而時間也只剩不到兩周了
and less than two weeks to get any more.

138
00:04:50,390 --> 00:04:51,380
等等
Wait a second.

139
00:04:52,710 --> 00:04:54,600
要是他們現在在找的不止是新證據
What if they didn't just have to scramble for new evidence?

140
00:04:54,600 --> 00:04:56,570
而是個新律師呢
What if they had to scramble for a whole new lawyer?

141
00:04:56,730 --> 00:04:58,580
這個案子只剩兩周時間了
Any lawyer who got assigned this case

142
00:04:58,580 --> 00:05:00,670
任何分配到的律師都會放棄的
with only two weeks to go would drop the whole thing.

143
00:05:00,670 --> 00:05:02,080
除非這個律師和你有私人恩怨
Unless they had a personal beef with you,

144
00:05:02,080 --> 00:05:03,830
-但是根本沒有  -只有一個方法
- which they wouldn't. - There's only one way

145
00:05:03,830 --> 00:05:05,320
讓卡梅隆放棄這個案子
to get Cameron thrown off this case.

146
00:05:05,320 --> 00:05:06,950
證明他和揚諾普洛斯勾結
Prove he colluded with Gianopolous.

147
00:05:06,950 --> 00:05:10,770
把一派胡言變成一派...事實
Turn bullshit highway into... fact highway.

148
00:05:11,040 --> 00:05:12,250
一派事實
Fact highway?

149
00:05:12,250 --> 00:05:13,430
對  你理解了就行
Yeah, you know, it's right next to

150
00:05:13,430 --> 00:05:15,290
就不要再討論這個用詞問題了
"I don't want to talk about this anymore" lane.

151
00:05:15,440 --> 00:05:17,730
但我們得好好討論下如何證明他們互相勾結
We're gonna have to talk about how to prove they colluded

152
00:05:17,730 --> 00:05:20,020
因為這個機會能讓我們永遠地
because we have a chance to get rid of this murder charge

153
00:05:20,020 --> 00:05:21,180
擺脫謀殺指控
once and for all.

154
00:05:21,950 --> 00:05:25,490
人人影視
YYeTs.com

155
00:05:21,950 --> 00:05:25,490
原創翻譯  中文字幕

156
00:05:21,950 --> 00:05:25,490
■

157
00:05:21,950 --> 00:05:25,490
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com

158
00:05:25,460 --> 00:05:29,400
翻譯：愛卿遛小鳥    圈圈    妄想的絨布熊    小小

159
00:05:29,460 --> 00:05:35,400
翻譯：Reginamoon    宅女之后    士也瓜    阿囧

160
00:05:35,460 --> 00:05:39,400
校對：油炸電風扇     士也瓜

161
00:05:39,460 --> 00:05:44,400
時間軸：sinagujia     憑陵新月

162
00:05:44,460 --> 00:05:49,460
后期：愛卿遛小鳥     總監：swears

163
00:05:47,900 --> 00:05:49,770
《訴訟雙雄》
第二季第四集

164
00:05:57,140 --> 00:05:58,160
卡特里娜說你找我
Katrina said you wanted to see me?

165
00:05:58,160 --> 00:05:59,980
西蒙  進來  我有個問題
Hey, Simon, come on in. I have a question for you.

166
00:06:01,290 --> 00:06:02,420
過來  你看看這個
Come on, you need to see this.

167
00:06:02,430 --> 00:06:03,920
你看  真是太搞笑了
Look at this. This is so funny.

168
00:06:04,090 --> 00:06:05,160
你這是跟我開玩笑嗎
Is that some sort of joke?

169
00:06:05,160 --> 00:06:06,380
開頭一堆廢話
Nominal in the first paragraph,

170
00:06:06,380 --> 00:06:07,920
左側分頁
pagination on the left-hand side,

171
00:06:08,060 --> 00:06:09,670
還有滿頁滑稽的
times new roman's stupid little feet

172
00:06:09,670 --> 00:06:11,060
新羅馬字體
walking all across the page.

173
00:06:11,130 --> 00:06:12,180
那個詞是怎么回事
And what's that word?

174
00:06:13,500 --> 00:06:14,530
-"應該"嗎  -對
- "Shall"? - Mm.

175
00:06:15,980 --> 00:06:19,070
在我們公司  我們指導  建議  命令
At this firm, we instruct, we advise, we order,

176
00:06:19,070 --> 00:06:21,190
必須  但是我們從不"應該"
we must, but we do not "Shall."

177
00:06:21,200 --> 00:06:23,460
-那其實不是  -我們為什么必須"必須"
- That's not really a-- - Why must we "Must"?

178
00:06:23,850 --> 00:06:25,270
因為我們進擊  從不躲避
Because we thrust, we don't parry.

179
00:06:25,650 --> 00:06:26,630
回去重寫
Rewrite this.

180
00:06:27,350 --> 00:06:28,190
不行
I can't.

181
00:06:31,200 --> 00:06:31,960
你說什么
Excuse me?

182
00:06:31,960 --> 00:06:33,140
奈斯比特先生明確指示我們...
Mr. Nesbitt has clearly instructed us--

183
00:06:33,140 --> 00:06:35,790
等等  等等  這是奈杰爾叫你做的
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. This was Nigel's doing?

184
00:06:35,930 --> 00:06:37,310
根據他最近一次的備忘錄
Per his most recent memo.

185
00:06:37,310 --> 00:06:39,150
他通過備忘錄跟你交流嗎
He's communicating with you through memos?

186
00:06:39,180 --> 00:06:41,310
你孤身一人在善變的法律海洋中漂流
You've been left adrift on lady law's fickle ocean

187
00:06:41,310 --> 00:06:42,700
沒有舵手也沒有船長嗎
with no rudder, no captain?

188
00:06:43,410 --> 00:06:44,420
他自從接管了這個項目
He hasn't been in the office

189
00:06:44,420 --> 00:06:45,910
就沒進過辦公室
since he took over the program,

190
00:06:45,910 --> 00:06:46,950
如果你想問的是這個
if that's what you're asking.

191
00:06:46,960 --> 00:06:47,960
不  我想我的問題
No, I think I was perfectly clear

192
00:06:47,960 --> 00:06:49,080
表達得很清楚了  西蒙
in what I was asking, Simon.

193
00:06:50,150 --> 00:06:51,210
我應該作出回應嗎
Am I supposed to respond to that?

194
00:06:51,210 --> 00:06:52,680
對  回答就是馬上回自己的辦公桌
Yeah, by going back to your desk right now

195
00:06:52,680 --> 00:06:53,620
然后正確地重做一遍  
and doing it correctly.

196
00:06:53,620 --> 00:06:53,850
但是
But--

197
00:06:53,850 --> 00:06:55,040
西蒙  違背奈杰爾的備忘錄
Simon, a memo from Nigel

198
00:06:55,040 --> 00:06:56,120
不會讓你屁股開花
is not gonna stick its boot in your ass.

199
00:06:56,120 --> 00:06:57,430
但違背我  你就等著吧  出去
A memo from me will. Get out.

200
00:07:07,660 --> 00:07:09,700
不是說過嗎  在辦公室不行
I told you, not at the office.

201
00:07:09,700 --> 00:07:11,490
你是說我不能在辦公室見哈維嗎
You mean I can't see Harvey at the office?

202
00:07:11,500 --> 00:07:12,610
因為我是來見他的
'Cause that's what I'm here to do.

203
00:07:14,430 --> 00:07:15,420
-怎么了  -明知故問
- What? - You know what.

204
00:07:15,420 --> 00:07:16,410
你還沒告訴他
You haven't told him yet.

205
00:07:16,410 --> 00:07:17,800
跟他又沒什么關系
It's none of his business.

206
00:07:17,860 --> 00:07:21,030
我和他在這是公事  而我和你的私事在那兒
He and I are here, and you and I are...there.

207
00:07:21,030 --> 00:07:21,850
我多希望現在我們在那兒
I wish we were there.

208
00:07:21,850 --> 00:07:23,340
剛才說過  不能在這里這樣
I just told you, not here.

209
00:07:23,340 --> 00:07:24,810
唐娜  你那兒有事嗎
Donna, what's going on out there?

210
00:07:24,810 --> 00:07:26,610
他應該是指這邊吧
I think he means out here.

211
00:07:26,850 --> 00:07:27,940
有人找你
You have a walk-in.

212
00:07:31,270 --> 00:07:32,280
你來干什么
What are you doing here?

213
00:07:32,280 --> 00:07:33,580
干我一直干的事
What I've always been doing here,

214
00:07:33,590 --> 00:07:35,230
代表愛德華·達比的意愿
representing Edward Darby's wishes.

215
00:07:35,870 --> 00:07:37,300
我沒能幫艾娃保住公司
I lost Ava her company.

216
00:07:37,300 --> 00:07:39,760
這樣我跟愛德華的協議就無效了吧
I assume my deal with Edward is dead.

217
00:07:39,940 --> 00:07:42,000
愛德華可不這么想
Well, Edward doesn't see it like that.

218
00:07:42,800 --> 00:07:43,610
你可能是失敗了
You may have failed,

219
00:07:43,610 --> 00:07:45,740
但杰西卡是捅了自己人一刀
but Jessica took a shot at her own team.

220
00:07:45,770 --> 00:07:47,480
這樣做的后果是什么
And the consequences of that are what?

221
00:07:47,480 --> 00:07:48,890
只要你贏下謀殺案的庭審
Deal stays in place

222
00:07:49,130 --> 00:07:50,830
協議依然有效
as long as you win her murder trial.

223
00:07:51,010 --> 00:07:53,580
要是我的計劃是將庭審扼殺在搖籃呢
What if my plan is to not even have a murder trial?

224
00:07:53,590 --> 00:07:55,400
只要你不是通過讓艾娃認罪
Well, as long as you don't accomplish that

225
00:07:55,410 --> 00:07:57,190
來達到這一目標
by having Ava plead guilty,

226
00:07:58,080 --> 00:07:59,770
那你就是下一個執行合伙人
you'll be the next managing partner.

227
00:07:59,770 --> 00:08:02,400
很好  因為我將證明卡梅隆·丹尼斯
Good, because I'm going to accomplish it

228
00:08:02,420 --> 00:08:04,490
和托尼·揚諾普洛斯相互勾結
by getting Cameron Dennis thrown off this case

229
00:08:04,490 --> 00:08:06,480
從而逼他撤訴
for colluding with Tony Gianopolous.

230
00:08:06,490 --> 00:08:08,250
你又將如何證明呢
And how are you going to accomplish that?

231
00:08:08,250 --> 00:08:10,260
靠起訴托尼·揚諾普洛斯
By suing Tony Gianopolous.

232
00:08:10,260 --> 00:08:11,100
起訴他什么
For what?

233
00:08:11,250 --> 00:08:13,660
因為這個  或者這個
For this... or this...

234
00:08:13,680 --> 00:08:15,960
或者再加上這個
And/or that.

235
00:08:28,890 --> 00:08:30,640
很不錯
Yeah, that's good.

236
00:08:30,640 --> 00:08:31,930
-當然  -是啊
- It is. - Yeah.

237
00:08:32,390 --> 00:08:34,700
-但我可以做得更好  -不可能
- But I can do better. - No way.

238
00:08:35,560 --> 00:08:37,360
賭五千  我可以
$5,000 says I can.

239
00:08:38,230 --> 00:08:39,910
我賭一萬  你不行
$10,000 says you can't.

240
00:08:41,520 --> 00:08:42,440
很好
Excellent.

241
00:08:43,010 --> 00:08:43,960
你想怎么做
What's your idea?

242
00:08:44,690 --> 00:08:46,350
這需要你帶上我一起
Well, it requires you to take me with you

243
00:08:46,350 --> 00:08:48,240
-去見揚諾普洛斯先生  -邁克
- to see Mr. Gianopolous. - Mike?

244
00:08:48,240 --> 00:08:49,820
-在  -這個案子你不用參加了
- Yeah. - You're off the case.

245
00:08:50,850 --> 00:08:52,870
什么  你要讓他代替我的位子嗎
What? You're gonna let him get away with that?

246
00:08:52,870 --> 00:08:53,990
我也沒辦法  剛跟他打了賭
I have to. I just took a bet.

247
00:08:53,990 --> 00:08:55,100
打賭這種事又不能反悔
There's no going back on a bet.

248
00:08:55,100 --> 00:08:56,940
那要是我跟他打賭我的主意更好呢
Okay, what if I bet him that my idea's better?

249
00:08:56,940 --> 00:08:57,740
那我能來嗎
Then can I come?

250
00:08:57,740 --> 00:08:59,360
你會押上一萬美金嗎
You gonna pony up $10,000?

251
00:09:01,180 --> 00:09:03,640
祝你們好運  希望能成功
Best of luck, guys. Hope it works out.

252
00:09:05,820 --> 00:09:06,860
也就是說你退出那個案子了
So you're off the case?

253
00:09:06,860 --> 00:09:08,770
對  歸功于史蒂芬·亨特利啊
Yeah, thanks to Stephen Huntley.

254
00:09:08,870 --> 00:09:10,910
他最近還真是職場情場都得意啊
Well, doesn't he have his hand in a lot of cookie jars?

255
00:09:12,010 --> 00:09:13,720
-什么意思  -沒什么
- What does that mean? - Nothing.

256
00:09:14,360 --> 00:09:16,590
等等  "沒什么"一定說明有什么
Wait a second, "Nothing" never means nothing.

257
00:09:16,590 --> 00:09:18,070
有時確實是指有事
Sometimes it means something.

258
00:09:18,070 --> 00:09:19,910
你想讓我逼你說出來嗎
Ah, do you want me to force it out of you?

259
00:09:19,910 --> 00:09:22,320
我不知道該不該說
I may or may not need plausible deniability.

260
00:09:22,320 --> 00:09:24,090
-瑞秋  -唐娜跟史蒂芬上床了
- Rachel. - Donna slept with Stephen.

261
00:09:25,650 --> 00:09:27,320
我勒個去
Holy shit.

262
00:09:27,320 --> 00:09:29,320
不能讓她知道你知道了
You cannot let her know that you know.

263
00:09:29,320 --> 00:09:30,660
-哈維知道嗎  -還不知道
- Does Harvey know? - No, not yet.

264
00:09:30,660 --> 00:09:31,960
你決不準告訴他
Don't you dare tell him.

265
00:09:31,960 --> 00:09:33,710
當然  好像我會旁敲側擊暗示他一樣
Yeah, like I'm gonna touch that with a 10-foot pole.

266
00:09:33,710 --> 00:09:35,640
但是她不跟他說  他一定會在意的
But he's gonna care that she didn't tell him.

267
00:09:36,930 --> 00:09:40,070
那你要怎么重回那件案子呢
So how are you gonna get back on that case?

268
00:09:41,450 --> 00:09:43,150
我有別的案子了
Um, I got a different case.

269
00:09:43,910 --> 00:09:44,840
格雷姆·斯丹頓
Graham Stenton.

270
00:09:45,290 --> 00:09:48,460
那個挪用了我們客戶三千萬的會計
The accountant who embezzled $30 million from our client?

271
00:09:48,460 --> 00:09:49,100
就是他
Yep.

272
00:09:49,280 --> 00:09:51,870
而我們要多的就是把錢追回來  悄悄的
And our job is to get the money back, quietly.

273
00:09:51,870 --> 00:09:53,050
是為皮爾遜-達比做這件事
Our job as in Pearson Darby?

274
00:09:53,050 --> 00:09:54,290
是為我倆做這件事
Our job as in you and me.

275
00:09:55,050 --> 00:09:56,950
我下午要去采訪他的助理
I'm interviewing his associate this afternoon,

276
00:09:57,370 --> 00:09:58,420
我需要你的幫助
and I need your help.

277
00:09:59,920 --> 00:10:02,400
你想讓我當你的邁克  而你當哈維
You want me to be the Mike to your Harvey.

278
00:10:04,740 --> 00:10:06,510
我的確想讓你當邁克  我當哈維
I do want you to be the Mike to my Harvey.

279
00:10:06,510 --> 00:10:07,850
這基本不可能
Yeah, well, it's not really a thing.

280
00:10:07,850 --> 00:10:08,790
這可說不定
It can be.

281
00:10:10,970 --> 00:10:12,240
一半問題得由我來提問
I get to ask half the questions.

282
00:10:12,240 --> 00:10:14,840
哈維才不會把一半的問題給邁克來提問呢
Oh, Harvey doesn't let Mike ask half the questions.

283
00:10:14,840 --> 00:10:16,120
好吧  三分之一
Fine, 1/3.

284
00:10:16,250 --> 00:10:17,690
哈維才不會和邁克討價還價
Harvey doesn't negotiate with Mike.

285
00:10:17,700 --> 00:10:19,550
邁克可不會和哈維上床
Mike doesn't have sex with Harvey.

286
00:10:21,990 --> 00:10:24,030
我瞧著三分之一的問題挺合理的
1/3 of the questions seems reasonable to me.

287
00:10:34,710 --> 00:10:37,560
你走路能輕點嗎
Could you possibly keep your thwacking to yourself?

288
00:10:38,750 --> 00:10:39,880
這可是私人俱樂部
This is a private club.

289
00:10:39,920 --> 00:10:41,390
它在倫敦有家姐妹店
With a sister club in London.

290
00:10:42,630 --> 00:10:43,980
怪不得有泥浴特權
Courtesy mudding privileges.

291
00:10:44,010 --> 00:10:46,300
而且沒錯  這是土耳其貨 
And, yes, it's Turkish.

292
00:10:46,300 --> 00:10:48,920
外來泥顯而易見是違反俱樂部規定的
Outside mud is a clear violation of club policy.

293
00:10:48,920 --> 00:10:49,960
這里是有規定的  奈杰爾
There are rules, Nigel.

294
00:10:49,960 --> 00:10:51,510
同樣  也有規定
Just as there are rules

295
00:10:51,510 --> 00:10:53,250
禁止干涉我的律師們
forbidding interference with my associates.

296
00:10:53,430 --> 00:10:57,530
是啊是啊  你根本不在乎他們
Yeah, well, you don't give a rat's ass about them.

297
00:10:57,630 --> 00:10:58,780
你怎么敢這么說
How dare you?

298
00:10:58,790 --> 00:11:00,820
讓我告訴你一些你可能不知道的事
You know, let me tell you something you may not know.

299
00:11:01,130 --> 00:11:04,070
律師們  他們就像細沙
Associates, they're like grains of sand.

300
00:11:04,300 --> 00:11:05,690
他們需要壓力和熱量
They need pressure and heat

301
00:11:05,690 --> 00:11:07,250
奇胡利  玻璃藝術大師

302
00:11:05,690 --> 00:11:07,570
才能被塑造成奇胡利的玻璃藝術品
to shape them into Chihuly glass.

303
00:11:07,600 --> 00:11:10,540
遠程備忘錄對他們屁用都沒有
Memos from a distant land don't shape shit into shit.

304
00:11:10,540 --> 00:11:11,480
荒唐
Nonsense.

305
00:11:11,740 --> 00:11:14,340
我四歲幼齡就上了寄宿學校
I attended boarding school from the tender age of four,

306
00:11:14,340 --> 00:11:17,300
那段時間我每周都會收到我父親給的備忘
during which time I received weekly memos from my father.

307
00:11:17,300 --> 00:11:18,460
是啊是啊  然后看看你現在成啥樣了
Yeah, and look how you turned out.

308
00:11:18,460 --> 00:11:21,480
以最好成績從劍橋和哈佛畢業
Graduating summa cum laude from both Cambridge and Harvard

309
00:11:21,480 --> 00:11:22,730
可真算是失敗啊
is quite the failure.

310
00:11:22,900 --> 00:11:26,430
你父母選擇讓你在家上學  果然更厲害
Your parents' choice to "Homeschool", much better.

311
00:11:26,430 --> 00:11:27,690
好吧  這是我十歲以前的事
Okay, that was only till I was ten,

312
00:11:27,690 --> 00:11:29,440
并且我媽媽辦的科學博覽會可是個傳奇
and my mother's science fair was legendary.

313
00:11:29,560 --> 00:11:32,860
你一定對無需競爭就能獲得頭獎深感自豪
You must be so proud of your uncontested blue ribbons.

314
00:11:33,280 --> 00:11:34,190
你知道嗎
Okay, you know what,

315
00:11:35,550 --> 00:11:36,870
我不會讓你粉碎
I'm not gonna let you shatter

316
00:11:36,870 --> 00:11:38,750
我花了幾年制作的玻璃
the glass that I spent years blowing.

317
00:11:38,750 --> 00:11:40,620
而我也不會讓像你這種人
And I'm certainly not gonna let the likes of you

318
00:11:40,620 --> 00:11:42,350
來告訴我能擊敗哪些人
tell me who I can and cannot blow.

319
00:11:47,160 --> 00:11:48,160
他不會來的
He's not gonna come.

320
00:11:48,270 --> 00:11:49,170
他會
He will.

321
00:11:49,230 --> 00:11:50,560
你給他的助理施壓了
You pushed his assistant?

322
00:11:51,070 --> 00:11:51,980
我是用了我的魅力
I charmed her.

323
00:11:52,130 --> 00:11:52,980
你沒有
You didn't.

324
00:11:53,460 --> 00:11:55,590
他說得對  你沒有
He's right, you didn't.

325
00:11:56,230 --> 00:11:57,470
她被激怒了
She was irritated.

326
00:11:59,090 --> 00:12:00,220
但是我很好奇
But I was curious.

327
00:12:00,740 --> 00:12:01,620
一樣管用
Works for me.

328
00:12:01,740 --> 00:12:03,820
你知道他們是怎么談論好奇心的嗎
You know what they say about curiosity.

329
00:12:08,460 --> 00:12:09,330
我明白了
I get it.

330
00:12:10,000 --> 00:12:12,180
我追著海辛頓石油  你們就追著我
I come after Hessington Oil, you come after me.

331
00:12:12,600 --> 00:12:14,450
放馬過來吧  男孩兒們
Well, bring it on, boys.

332
00:12:14,450 --> 00:12:15,320
我有一堆律師
I got a team of lawyers

333
00:12:15,320 --> 00:12:16,810
急著要上崗賺你們的午飯錢呢
just itching to take your lunch money.

334
00:12:16,820 --> 00:12:19,310
不幸的是  你不能用他們了
Well, unfortunately, you're not gonna be able to use them.

335
00:12:19,480 --> 00:12:20,780
他不打算這里起訴你了
He's not gonna sue you here.

336
00:12:20,990 --> 00:12:22,660
而他會在倫敦起訴你
He's gonna sue you in London,

337
00:12:22,780 --> 00:12:24,430
在那里你有無數的資產
where you have countless holdings.

338
00:12:24,640 --> 00:12:27,100
在那里舉證不是原告的責任
Where the burden of proof isn't on the plaintiff.

339
00:12:27,100 --> 00:12:28,400
而是被告的
It's on the defendant.

340
00:12:28,400 --> 00:12:30,830
所以不是我們要證明你有罪
So instead of us having to prove you're guilty,

341
00:12:30,930 --> 00:12:32,300
而是你要證明你無罪
you'll have to prove you're innocent.

342
00:12:32,610 --> 00:12:33,850
看起來可不像是無罪的
Doesn't look very innocent.

343
00:12:33,880 --> 00:12:35,520
所以你們以為我會因為可能輸掉一些小錢
So you guys think I'm gonna run scared

344
00:12:35,520 --> 00:12:37,230
就害怕地逃跑么
at the prospect of losing a little money.

345
00:12:38,500 --> 00:12:39,720
我是一個企業狙擊手
I'm a corporate raider.

346
00:12:41,080 --> 00:12:43,130
這是五萬元的債券
This is a $50,000 bond.

347
00:12:45,600 --> 00:12:49,220
你看  我參與這件事可不是為了錢
You see, I'm not in this business for the money.

348
00:12:49,910 --> 00:12:51,610
錢只是用來記分的
Money's just about keeping score.

349
00:12:52,600 --> 00:12:54,160
我參與這件事是為了贏
I'm in this business to win.

350
00:12:54,380 --> 00:12:55,660
有這么件事  托尼
Well, here's the thing, Tony.

351
00:12:55,660 --> 00:12:57,320
這場庭審會持續有一段時間
This trial's gonna take a while.

352
00:12:57,420 --> 00:12:58,970
你會不斷地被去聽證
You'll be going to hearing after hearing,

353
00:12:58,970 --> 00:13:00,510
錄一份又一份的口供
deposition after deposition.

354
00:13:00,510 --> 00:13:02,560
你就完全不能享受你的生意了
You won't be able to enjoy your business at all.

355
00:13:02,560 --> 00:13:04,590
所以即使你贏了  也算輸了
So even if you win, you lose.

356
00:13:05,230 --> 00:13:06,120
或者
Or?

357
00:13:06,190 --> 00:13:08,380
我可以撤訴
Well, I... I could withdraw the suit.

358
00:13:08,590 --> 00:13:10,520
你只需要承認
And all that'll cost you

359
00:13:10,520 --> 00:13:14,050
你和卡梅倫·丹尼斯勾結
is the truth, that you colluded with Cameron Dennis.

360
00:13:14,050 --> 00:13:15,850
但是我并沒有勾結任何人
Ah, but I didn't collude shit.

361
00:13:15,860 --> 00:13:16,900
不  你有
Yes, you did,

362
00:13:17,120 --> 00:13:20,050
你讓他把艾娃·海辛頓的視頻泄露給你
When you let him leak you that video of Ava Hessington,

363
00:13:20,060 --> 00:13:22,550
然后再利用這個視頻來搶海辛頓石油
then tried to use it to take over Hessington Oil.

364
00:13:31,840 --> 00:13:33,460
好了  到我們慶祝的時候了
All right, it's time we celebrate

365
00:13:33,460 --> 00:13:34,080
慶祝什么
Celebrate what?

366
00:13:34,670 --> 00:13:36,230
我們作為情侶辦的第一個案子
Our first case as a couple.

367
00:13:36,230 --> 00:13:37,530
我們應該去那家你喜歡的法國餐廳
We should go to that French place you like,

368
00:13:37,530 --> 00:13:38,380
點一瓶酒
get a bottle of wine,

369
00:13:38,380 --> 00:13:40,090
和一堆我不知道怎么讀的東西
a couple of things that I don't know how to pronounce,

370
00:13:40,090 --> 00:13:42,520
然后回我家  慶祝
and then go back to my place and celebrate.

371
00:13:42,520 --> 00:13:43,870
最經流行這樣稱呼那事兒嗎
That's what we're calling it these days?

372
00:13:43,880 --> 00:13:45,680
"勝利性愛"聽起來沒那么浪漫
Well, "victory sex" seemed less romantic.

373
00:13:45,680 --> 00:13:47,490
-我今晚不行  -為什么
- Well, I can't tonight. - Why not?

374
00:13:47,490 --> 00:13:48,760
我和父母約了一起吃晚餐
I have dinner with my parents.

375
00:13:49,330 --> 00:13:50,420
也許我能和你一起去
Maybe I could come with you.

376
00:13:51,030 --> 00:13:52,720
是啊  我
Um...yeah, I--

377
00:13:52,720 --> 00:13:53,920
除非你不想我去
Unless you don't want me there.

378
00:13:55,330 --> 00:13:56,440
等等
Wait a minute.

379
00:13:56,620 --> 00:13:57,520
你不想我去
You don't want me there.

380
00:13:58,230 --> 00:13:59,030
我當然想了
Of course I do.

381
00:13:59,210 --> 00:14:00,540
你看起來不像是想的樣子
You don't look like you do.

382
00:14:00,540 --> 00:14:01,700
是因為我是白人嗎
Is it because I'm white?

383
00:14:01,700 --> 00:14:02,640
這一點也不好笑
That's not funny.

384
00:14:02,640 --> 00:14:03,460
這句話通常很好笑
Empirically it is.

385
00:14:03,460 --> 00:14:04,120
不  不是因為這原因
No, it's not,

386
00:14:04,120 --> 00:14:05,140
而且你表現得像是這不是什么大事
and you're acting like it's nothing.

387
00:14:05,140 --> 00:14:07,300
瑞秋  拜托  我知道這是件大事
Rachel, come on, look, I know it's something,

388
00:14:07,300 --> 00:14:08,800
但是你表現得太小題大做了
But you're acting like it's everything.

389
00:14:08,810 --> 00:14:09,800
這本來就不是"小題"
It is everything.

390
00:14:11,050 --> 00:14:11,830
等等
Wait a second.

391
00:14:11,830 --> 00:14:12,340
你是不想我今晚見他們
Do you not want me

392
00:14:12,340 --> 00:14:13,850
還是根本都不想我見他們
to meet them tonight or at all?

393
00:14:15,450 --> 00:14:17,460
我不想讓他們發現你的秘密
I don't want them to find out your secret.

394
00:14:18,220 --> 00:14:19,680
他們不會發現的
They're not gonna find out.

395
00:14:19,680 --> 00:14:20,370
你怎么知道
How do you know that?

396
00:14:20,370 --> 00:14:21,750
因為從來沒人發現
Because no one finds out.

397
00:14:21,830 --> 00:14:23,530
你  唐娜  杰西卡
You, Donna, Jessica,

398
00:14:23,530 --> 00:14:24,820
都是別人告訴你們的
you were all told.

399
00:14:24,820 --> 00:14:27,020
另外  我見過你爸爸  他沒發現
Besides, I met your dad. He didn't figure it out.

400
00:14:27,020 --> 00:14:27,780
他上次見你的時候
He met you as someone

401
00:14:27,780 --> 00:14:30,120
認為你只是路人甲  邁克
that he wouldn't give a second thought to, Mike.

402
00:14:30,120 --> 00:14:32,110
而對我的男朋友  他會把你放在
As my boyfriend, he is going to put you

403
00:14:32,110 --> 00:14:33,330
放在顯微鏡下好好觀察一番的
under the microscope.

404
00:14:33,340 --> 00:14:34,960
-我肯定能通過  -那我呢
- I can pass inspection. - Well, what about me?

405
00:14:34,960 --> 00:14:36,950
因為也許你已經習慣欺騙全世界了
Because you might be experienced at lying to the world,

406
00:14:36,950 --> 00:14:37,900
但我沒有
But I'm not.

407
00:14:38,550 --> 00:14:41,020
而且這次不是對全世界  是對我的家人
And it's not the world, it's my family.

408
00:14:41,020 --> 00:14:43,060
好吧  瑞秋  我們倆早已相互表白
Okay, Rachel, you and I have told each other

409
00:14:43,070 --> 00:14:44,270
我愛你  你也愛我  是吧
that we love each other, right?

410
00:14:45,370 --> 00:14:46,590
我們當時是認真的吧
Did we mean that or not?

411
00:14:47,360 --> 00:14:49,460
如果是的話  總有一天
If we did, then at some point,

412
00:14:49,460 --> 00:14:51,350
我會去見你的父母
I am gonna have to meet your parents.

413
00:14:52,750 --> 00:14:54,660
會談二十分鐘后開始  我們得走了
Interview's in 20 minutes. We should go.

414
00:15:02,250 --> 00:15:03,150
不用客氣
Make yourself at home.

415
00:15:03,150 --> 00:15:04,610
我想和你在這談談
I wanted to talk to you in here.

416
00:15:06,990 --> 00:15:09,020
-是有關你的...  -不是
- Is this about your-- - No, no.

417
00:15:09,120 --> 00:15:10,670
你都不知道我要說什么
You don't even know what I was gonna say.

418
00:15:16,490 --> 00:15:17,690
揚諾普洛斯的案子怎樣
How'd it go with Gianopolous?

419
00:15:18,180 --> 00:15:19,650
他不是輕易被嚇倒的人
Well, he's not a pushover,

420
00:15:19,650 --> 00:15:21,510
但我覺得我們有個不錯的計劃
but I think we have a good plan.

421
00:15:21,510 --> 00:15:23,470
-一切順利嗎  -順利
- So it went well? - Yeah, it went well.

422
00:15:23,470 --> 00:15:24,310
你什么時候開始...
And since when are you--

423
00:15:24,310 --> 00:15:25,570
我和史蒂芬睡過了
I'm sleeping with Stephen.

424
00:15:27,330 --> 00:15:28,270
預料之中
I can see that.

425
00:15:29,980 --> 00:15:30,970
在你的預料之中
You can see that?

426
00:15:30,970 --> 00:15:33,030
你只想說這個嗎
That's all you have to say?

427
00:15:33,610 --> 00:15:34,890
那還想讓我多說點嗎
Do you want me to say more?

428
00:15:35,000 --> 00:15:36,730
那就看你要說什么了
It depends on what you would say.

429
00:15:38,180 --> 00:15:39,370
我想說"什么時候的事"
I'd say, "When?"

430
00:15:39,440 --> 00:15:40,290
三天前
Three days ago.

431
00:15:41,330 --> 00:15:42,600
你之前怎么不告訴我
Why didn't you tell me before?

432
00:15:42,730 --> 00:15:44,410
我本來要告訴你的
I was going to, but you got so upset

433
00:15:44,410 --> 00:15:45,800
但你覺得我在為他工作  就不高興了
when you thought I was working for him.

434
00:15:46,010 --> 00:15:47,330
因為你是要為我工作的
Because you work for me.

435
00:15:48,170 --> 00:15:50,050
事實上我也沒有為他工作
Well, I'm not working for him.

436
00:15:50,050 --> 00:15:50,970
很好
Good.

437
00:15:53,690 --> 00:15:54,610
這么說你沒不高興
So you're not upset.

438
00:15:55,650 --> 00:15:56,610
沒有
No.

439
00:15:56,980 --> 00:15:59,060
你和他之間  是你的私事
What you're doing with him is personal.

440
00:15:59,070 --> 00:16:00,670
-那這就不是了嗎  -唐娜
- And this isn't? - Donna,

441
00:16:00,830 --> 00:16:02,920
-我真不想小題大做  -我也不想
- I don't wanna make this a thing. - I don't either.

442
00:16:02,920 --> 00:16:04,820
我只想確保這不會被小題大做
I just want to make sure that it doesn't become a thing.

443
00:16:04,880 --> 00:16:07,710
只要你的工作不受影響  就不會
It won't as long as you don't let that affect this.

444
00:16:07,710 --> 00:16:08,560
好
Okay.

445
00:16:11,170 --> 00:16:12,920
克拉克女士  你和格雷姆·斯丹頓很熟嗎
Miss Clark, do you know Graham Stenton well?

446
00:16:13,060 --> 00:16:14,500
我們一起工作了一段時間
We've worked together for a while.

447
00:16:14,680 --> 00:16:16,270
是你為他的賬戶處理賬目
And you handle the books for his accounts,

448
00:16:16,270 --> 00:16:17,040
對吧
is that right?

449
00:16:17,150 --> 00:16:18,100
是的  沒錯
Yes, that's right.

450
00:16:18,500 --> 00:16:20,480
我們只想了解你是什么時候知道
We just need to know when exactly you became aware

451
00:16:20,480 --> 00:16:22,570
斯丹頓先生在對賬目作假的
that Mr. Stenton was manipulating the numbers.

452
00:16:24,390 --> 00:16:25,590
我不相信他做過
I don't believe he was.

453
00:16:28,020 --> 00:16:29,310
但審計師可不這么認為
Well, the auditors disagree.

454
00:16:29,310 --> 00:16:30,500
那我也不同意他們的看法
Well, I disagree with them.

455
00:16:30,500 --> 00:16:31,460
格雷姆是個好人
Graham's a good person.

456
00:16:31,550 --> 00:16:33,760
伯尼·麥道夫的朋友當然都是一個口徑的
I'm sure Bernie Madoff's friends all said the same thing.

457
00:16:33,760 --> 00:16:34,920
這么說不公平
That isn't fair.

458
00:16:34,930 --> 00:16:36,220
而且格雷姆也不是唯一一個
And Graham isn't the only person

459
00:16:36,230 --> 00:16:37,770
有權限進入那些賬號的人
who had access to those accounts.

460
00:16:37,770 --> 00:16:39,590
奧克斯納德先生  狄皮托先生
Mr. Oxnard, Mr. Dipetro,

461
00:16:40,010 --> 00:16:42,720
以及一些控制室的人也可以
several individuals from the controller's office.

462
00:16:42,720 --> 00:16:44,290
我只想問你一個問題
I just have one question for you.

463
00:16:44,430 --> 00:16:46,060
你和他睡了多久了
How long have you been sleeping with him?

464
00:16:47,870 --> 00:16:48,740
什么
What?

465
00:16:48,840 --> 00:16:51,630
每當你提到他的時候  你都會微笑
You smiled when you started talking about him.

466
00:16:52,300 --> 00:16:53,360
你叫他"格雷姆"
You called him "Graham."

467
00:16:53,360 --> 00:16:56,600
而你把其他人稱為"先生"或"人"
You've referred to everyone else as "Mister" or "Individual."

468
00:16:56,600 --> 00:16:59,090
還有當我的同事問你和他睡了多久時
And when my colleague asked you about sleeping with him,

469
00:16:59,860 --> 00:17:01,980
你看起來并沒有很抵觸  而是慌張
you didn't seem offended, you seemed caught.

470
00:17:01,980 --> 00:17:03,200
那也和這件事沒關系啊
I had nothing to do with this.

471
00:17:03,200 --> 00:17:04,320
但你還是知道些什么內幕吧
That doesn't mean you don't know anything.

472
00:17:04,320 --> 00:17:05,550
克拉克女士
Look, Miss Clark,

473
00:17:05,550 --> 00:17:07,060
我們想私底下解決這件事情
we're trying to make this go away quietly,

474
00:17:07,180 --> 00:17:08,030
但如果做不到的話
but if we can't,

475
00:17:08,030 --> 00:17:09,260
我們也就只能大張旗鼓了
we're gonna make it go away loudly,

476
00:17:09,260 --> 00:17:11,140
這就意味著我們得法庭上見了
which means putting you on the stand.

477
00:17:11,140 --> 00:17:13,450
貝絲  你無法引據第五修正案
Beth, you won't be able to take the Fifth

478
00:17:13,450 --> 00:17:15,270
因為你不是在為自己作證
because you won't be testifying against yourself.

479
00:17:15,270 --> 00:17:16,380
而且如果你在法庭上撒謊
And if you lie on the stand,

480
00:17:16,380 --> 00:17:17,120
那可是作偽證
that's perjury.

481
00:17:17,120 --> 00:17:19,260
如果你真想保護他
Look, if you really want to protect him,

482
00:17:19,450 --> 00:17:21,740
那就要讓他現在把錢還給我們
just get him to give us the money back now,

483
00:17:22,240 --> 00:17:24,730
現在還可以低調處理這件事情
while we can still take care of this quietly.

484
00:17:28,610 --> 00:17:29,640
我做不到
I can't.

485
00:17:29,900 --> 00:17:31,240
那就到此為止  我要去找地方檢察官
That's it, I'm calling the D.A.

486
00:17:31,240 --> 00:17:32,560
我覺得我們得給她點時間考慮
I think we should give her some time to think about it.

487
00:17:32,560 --> 00:17:33,030
我不覺得
I don't think so.

488
00:17:33,030 --> 00:17:34,200
邁克  這不是個簡單的決定
Mike, it's a hard decision.

489
00:17:38,640 --> 00:17:40,600
好吧  她明天就得給答復
Fine. She has until tomorrow.

490
00:17:53,380 --> 00:17:55,840
-什么事  -沒什么  
- Oh, what's going on? - Nothing.

491
00:17:55,910 --> 00:17:56,800
西蒙
Simon.

492
00:17:58,350 --> 00:17:59,780
奈斯比特先生給了我們每人一個禮物
Mr. Nesbitt gave us all gifts.

493
00:18:01,500 --> 00:18:02,610
禮物很搞笑嗎
And they're funny?

494
00:18:03,760 --> 00:18:05,190
我想應該是吧
I think they're meant to be.

495
00:18:05,920 --> 00:18:07,770
你懂的  他有交流障礙
Well, you know, he has trouble connecting,

496
00:18:09,240 --> 00:18:10,030
但他其實很努力在克服了
but he's making an effort.

497
00:18:10,030 --> 00:18:11,340
也許他把我的話放心上了
Maybe he took my words to heart.

498
00:18:16,080 --> 00:18:17,100
你和他說了什么
What'd you say to him?

499
00:18:18,310 --> 00:18:20,060
路易·利特
去你的

500
00:18:20,950 --> 00:18:23,380
效果還不錯啊
Turned out quite well.

501
00:18:24,720 --> 00:18:27,030
-你越線了  -我才沒有
- You crossed a line. - I did no such thing.

502
00:18:27,130 --> 00:18:28,770
你挑起了私人爭斗  而且搞得眾所周知
You took a private feud, and you made it public.

503
00:18:28,880 --> 00:18:30,990
在企圖危害我的權威之后
After you tried to undermine my authority.

504
00:18:30,990 --> 00:18:32,140
因為你根本就不知道自己在干什么
Because you don't know what you're doing.

505
00:18:32,220 --> 00:18:34,240
我是有意將他們從你身邊奪走
I knew what I was doing when I took them from you

506
00:18:34,240 --> 00:18:35,610
就像從校園男生手中奪去餅干一樣  
like biscuits from a schoolboy.

507
00:18:35,610 --> 00:18:36,760
你行啊  混球
All right, you son of a bitch.

508
00:18:36,760 --> 00:18:38,880
你最好小心點了  因為我就要...
You better get yourself ready, 'cause I'm about to kick--

509
00:18:40,530 --> 00:18:42,750
我知道這是違反公司規定的
I know it's generally against regulations,

510
00:18:42,760 --> 00:18:44,550
但她的保姆病了  而且...
but her nanny fell ill, and--

511
00:18:44,550 --> 00:18:45,580
不不不  別說了
No, no, no, no. Say no more.

512
00:18:46,400 --> 00:18:47,830
父愛入山  無人可擋
A father's love knows no rule.

513
00:18:47,980 --> 00:18:49,280
我都不知道原來你也喜歡貓
I didn't know you were a cat man.

514
00:18:49,300 --> 00:18:50,630
我有腦子嗎
Do I have brains in my head?

515
00:18:50,730 --> 00:18:51,960
我有心嗎
Do I have a heart in my chest?

516
00:18:51,960 --> 00:18:53,130
這只漂亮的小生命是...
Who is this stunning creature?

517
00:18:53,130 --> 00:18:54,890
她叫"米卡度"[日本天皇]
Her moniker is "Mikado."

518
00:18:55,600 --> 00:18:56,740
那這是意味著她喜歡...
So does that mean she enjoys--

519
00:18:56,740 --> 00:18:59,190
是的  每次出游  我都得保證她
Yes, whenever we travel, I make sure she has

520
00:18:59,190 --> 00:19:01,440
有吉爾伯特和薩利文陪伴
some Gilbert and Sullivan playing in her sherpa.

521
00:19:00,000 --> 00:19:04,000
同名輕歌劇《日本天皇》
劇作:威廉·吉爾伯特
曲作:阿瑟·薩利文

522
00:19:01,440 --> 00:19:03,390
小心點  她不太喜歡...
Uh, do be careful, she doesn't normally like--

523
00:19:06,210 --> 00:19:07,210
天吶
My God.

524
00:19:07,300 --> 00:19:08,790
怎么了
What?

525
00:19:08,830 --> 00:19:09,760
她是喜歡被撓左邊嗎
Does she prefer the left side?

526
00:19:10,060 --> 00:19:12,270
除了我以外  她不太喜歡別人碰她
She doesn't normally let anyone touch her except me.

527
00:19:12,620 --> 00:19:15,050
對付這種貓科動物  我自有妙招
I happen to have a way with those of the feline persuasion.

528
00:19:17,080 --> 00:19:17,830
你有奶油嗎
Do you have any cream?

529
00:19:19,880 --> 00:19:22,600
杰西卡·皮爾遜
執行合伙人

530
00:19:25,860 --> 00:19:26,830
你要見我嗎
You wanted to see me?

531
00:19:29,310 --> 00:19:31,330
是的  我剛好有些空閑時間
Yes. I had some free time.

532
00:19:31,700 --> 00:19:33,740
奧克伍德食品公司取消了十點的會
Oakwood Foods canceled our 10:00 a.m. meeting,

533
00:19:33,740 --> 00:19:35,570
奧姆尼股份公司中午的會
as did Omni Holdings at noon

534
00:19:35,570 --> 00:19:38,100
鄧巴證券下午四點的會談也都取消了
and Dunbar Securities at 4:00.

535
00:19:38,100 --> 00:19:40,370
看來你的交際能力還得多下功夫啊
Sounds like you need to work on your people skills.

536
00:19:40,870 --> 00:19:42,750
是你得多為你的交際能力下功夫
You need to work on your people skills.

537
00:19:43,140 --> 00:19:45,470
那些會議被取消是因為我們被解約了
Those meetings were canceled because we just got fired.

538
00:19:46,120 --> 00:19:47,420
那為何又怪在我頭上
And why is that my fault?

539
00:19:47,470 --> 00:19:49,460
他們不是我的客戶  我都沒見過他們
They're not my clients. I've never even met them.

540
00:19:49,460 --> 00:19:50,860
的確  不過顯然
No, but evidently,

541
00:19:51,170 --> 00:19:53,120
你見過他們的新老板
you have met their new owner,

542
00:19:54,170 --> 00:19:56,270
托尼·揚諾普洛斯收購了他們
Tony Gianopolous, who bought them

543
00:19:56,270 --> 00:19:58,160
只為了開除我們
for the sole purpose of firing us.

544
00:19:58,610 --> 00:19:59,480
真好啊
Good.

545
00:19:59,480 --> 00:20:01,360
我惹到他了  證明管用了
I pissed him off. That means it's working.

546
00:20:01,560 --> 00:20:03,410
這是你的計劃啊
Oh, you mean that plan of yours

547
00:20:03,410 --> 00:20:04,680
你都沒想過要告訴我吧
you didn't think to tell me about.

548
00:20:04,680 --> 00:20:06,440
我想過啊  不過轉念一想
Oh, I thought about it, and then I thought

549
00:20:06,440 --> 00:20:08,270
你肯定會背著我搞破壞
you'd just go behind my back and undo it.

550
00:20:08,270 --> 00:20:11,450
所以你背著我去找史蒂芬·亨特利
So you went behind my back and went to Stephen Huntley.

551
00:20:11,450 --> 00:20:13,140
我跟你說過  我信任他
I told you, I trust him.

552
00:20:13,140 --> 00:20:15,240
既然你這么喜歡
Well, you're the one

553
00:20:15,240 --> 00:20:17,500
把達比的名字掛在嘴邊
who likes to throw Darby's name around.

554
00:20:17,500 --> 00:20:20,560
不如你跟史蒂芬打電話給他
So why don't you and Stephen call him

555
00:20:20,560 --> 00:20:21,470
順便告訴他
and let him know

556
00:20:21,470 --> 00:20:25,080
你瞬間害我們失去的客戶
that you single-handedly lost us more business in a day

557
00:20:25,080 --> 00:20:26,750
比你一個月接的客戶還多
than you've ever gotten in a month.

558
00:20:26,750 --> 00:20:28,900
用我電話打  別客氣
And feel free to use my phone.

559
00:20:28,900 --> 00:20:30,460
既然我下午都沒事干了
Since you freed up my afternoon,

560
00:20:30,460 --> 00:20:32,390
我就休息了
I'm taking the rest of the day off.

561
00:20:33,720 --> 00:20:35,330
你看到她的表情了嗎
Did you see the look on her face?

562
00:20:35,330 --> 00:20:38,690
開玩笑  是我們安給她的
Are you kidding? We put that look on her face.

563
00:20:38,690 --> 00:20:40,950
紅臉  白臉
Good cop, bad cop.

564
00:20:40,950 --> 00:20:42,880
邁克  哈維
Mike, Harvey.

565
00:20:42,880 --> 00:20:44,080
還真有這么一回事啊
So I guess it is a thing.

566
00:20:44,080 --> 00:20:46,120
這周末就能把錢拿回來
So we should have the money back by this weekend,

567
00:20:46,120 --> 00:20:47,630
那時再慶祝吧
and then, we can celebrate.

568
00:20:47,630 --> 00:20:49,850
不如我們今晚就慶祝...
I was thinking that we could celebrate tonight...

569
00:20:50,670 --> 00:20:52,480
在我跟父母吃完飯之后
after dinner with my parents.

570
00:20:53,890 --> 00:20:55,310
要我一起去嗎
Do you want me to come?

571
00:20:55,900 --> 00:20:58,420
你看貝絲那張臉
That look on Beth's face,

572
00:20:58,960 --> 00:21:01,210
不僅表示他倆睡過了
it didn't just say that they slept together.

573
00:21:01,780 --> 00:21:03,060
她愛他
She loves him.

574
00:21:03,340 --> 00:21:06,800
我說過我愛你  我是真心的
I told you I love you, and I meant it.

575
00:21:08,020 --> 00:21:10,660
這件事我不會瞞著我家人
That's not something I want to hide from my family.

576
00:21:15,670 --> 00:21:17,810
我還做了計劃  所以我能
I actually made plans, so I'm not gonna be able to--

577
00:21:17,810 --> 00:21:18,750
不好笑嗎
Bad joke?

578
00:21:18,750 --> 00:21:19,680
-不  時機不對  -時機不對
- No, terrible timing. - Bad timing.

579
00:21:19,680 --> 00:21:21,310
那好吧 
Okay. I guessed.

580
00:21:27,590 --> 00:21:29,540
我需要你幫忙對付揚諾普洛斯
I need your help with Gianopolous.

581
00:21:29,540 --> 00:21:31,720
放松  如果他還想
Relax, if he's making another run

582
00:21:31,720 --> 00:21:33,410
對付海辛頓石油  這是不可能的
at Hessington Oil, that's not gonna happen.

583
00:21:33,410 --> 00:21:34,510
你怎么知道
Well, how can you know that?

584
00:21:34,510 --> 00:21:35,970
因為公司重組沒多久
Because you just restructured,

585
00:21:35,970 --> 00:21:37,880
至少半年內都不能
and he can't force another takeover vote

586
00:21:37,880 --> 00:21:39,030
進行收購投票
for at least six months.

587
00:21:39,030 --> 00:21:41,520
那為什么他要讓公司股價大跌
Then why is he driving my stock into the ground?

588
00:21:41,520 --> 00:21:44,240
-什么  -他一整天都在拋售
- What? - He's been dumping it all day.

589
00:21:45,080 --> 00:21:46,520
我會處理的
I'll take care of it.

590
00:21:47,270 --> 00:21:48,850
你做了什么
What did you do?

591
00:21:49,880 --> 00:21:51,670
我們跟他杠上了
We picked a fight with him.

592
00:21:51,820 --> 00:21:53,880
我們才跟他大戰了一回
We've just finished a fight with him

593
00:21:53,890 --> 00:21:55,950
結果是我失去了公司的控制權
that ended with me losing control of my company,

594
00:21:55,950 --> 00:21:58,120
你到底為什么又要去惹他呢
so why in god's name would you pick another?

595
00:21:58,120 --> 00:22:00,840
為了徹底給你洗脫殺人罪名
To get you out of these murder charges once and for all,

596
00:22:00,840 --> 00:22:02,240
在那之后
and after I do,

597
00:22:02,240 --> 00:22:04,820
我們會想辦法讓你重掌公司大權
we'll figure out a way to get you back in charge.

598
00:22:04,830 --> 00:22:06,880
你最好說到做到
You see that you do,

599
00:22:07,140 --> 00:22:09,350
因為我寧可在監獄老死
because I would rather rot in a cell

600
00:22:09,350 --> 00:22:11,950
也不能讓那人掌控我的公司
than let that man take over my company.

601
00:22:17,790 --> 00:22:20,250
所以我說  她產期提前又不是我的錯
So I tell this, it's not my fault that she may be early.

602
00:22:20,250 --> 00:22:22,180
當時我正忙著結案陳詞呢
I'm in the middle my of closing arguments.

603
00:22:22,180 --> 00:22:24,470
然后我說  如果孩子出生時他不在 
And I tell him that if he's not with me when she arrives,

604
00:22:24,470 --> 00:22:25,800
他的下一個案子
the next case he'll trail

605
00:22:25,800 --> 00:22:26,590
就是自己的謀殺案
is his own murder.

606
00:22:26,590 --> 00:22:27,600
之后我走進來
Then I walk in the room,

607
00:22:27,600 --> 00:22:29,520
她才知道其實我就在外邊
and she sees that I was right outside the door the whole time.

608
00:22:29,520 --> 00:22:30,520
我一點也不驚喜啊
I was not amused.

609
00:22:30,520 --> 00:22:31,610
沒有驚喜嗎
You weren't amused?

610
00:22:31,610 --> 00:22:33,260
你過了一個星期才生
You actually didn't go into labor for another week.

611
00:22:33,260 --> 00:22:34,750
我輸了案子
I lost that case.

612
00:22:34,960 --> 00:22:36,450
羅伯特  你吃了夠多土豆的了
Robert, you've had enough potatoes.

613
00:22:36,450 --> 00:22:38,320
她逼著我吃那狗屁健康餐
She's trying to make me eat that foodie bullshit.

614
00:22:38,320 --> 00:22:40,140
真的嗎
Oh, I find that hard to believe.

615
00:22:40,140 --> 00:22:41,260
今早給我做了冰沙
Made me a smoothie this morning,

616
00:22:41,270 --> 00:22:42,780
我好開心啊  結果發現是綠色的
I got all excited. It was green.

617
00:22:42,790 --> 00:22:44,170
健康飲食就這個顏色
That's what healthy looks like.

618
00:22:44,170 --> 00:22:45,010
謝謝  瑞秋
Thank you, Rachel.

619
00:22:45,020 --> 00:22:46,320
-你不孤單  -什么意思
- You're not alone. - What was that?

620
00:22:46,320 --> 00:22:47,960
我和你爸可是同一戰壕里的
I'm bonding with your father here.

621
00:22:47,960 --> 00:22:49,360
-說到這  -羅伯特
- Speaking of which-- - Robert.

622
00:22:49,360 --> 00:22:51,430
怎么了  你都不知道我要說什么
What? You don't even know what I'm gonna say.

623
00:22:51,430 --> 00:22:53,080
我知道你接下來要說的六件事
I know the next six things you're gonna say,

624
00:22:53,080 --> 00:22:54,850
你不能說  因為我跟你說過
and you're not gonna say them, because I told you,

625
00:22:54,850 --> 00:22:57,270
瑞秋不想你拷問這位可憐的年輕人
Rachel doesn't want you grilling this poor young man.

626
00:22:57,270 --> 00:22:58,030
-什么啊  -媽
- What? - Mom.

627
00:22:58,030 --> 00:22:59,430
你是不會手下留情的吧
You're not taking it easy on me, are you?

628
00:22:59,430 --> 00:23:01,040
-差不多吧  -你讓我管好他啊
- A little. - You told me to rein him in.

629
00:23:01,040 --> 00:23:02,110
我也讓你別告訴他啊
I also told you not to tell him.

630
00:23:02,110 --> 00:23:03,580
我們家不這樣做的
That's not how we do things in this family.

631
00:23:03,580 --> 00:23:04,870
我不會瞞著你爸爸
I'm not keeping things from your father.

632
00:23:04,880 --> 00:23:06,550
你沒告訴我  你把車刮花了啊
You kept it from me when you scratched the car.

633
00:23:06,560 --> 00:23:08,040
羅伯特  吃你的土豆去
Robert, eat your potatoes.

634
00:23:08,740 --> 00:23:09,490
什么這么好笑
What's so funny?

635
00:23:09,490 --> 00:23:11,070
土豆問題她不再堅持了
She's not consistent with the potatoes.

636
00:23:11,070 --> 00:23:12,520
她沒哪件事會堅持到底的
She's not consistent with anything.

637
00:23:12,520 --> 00:23:14,970
好吧  那你別吃土豆了
Okay, you're not getting any potatoes.

638
00:23:15,130 --> 00:23:16,140
又什么這么好笑
Now what's so funny?

639
00:23:16,140 --> 00:23:18,330
我知道她是遺傳的誰了
I see where she gets it from.

640
00:23:18,780 --> 00:23:19,860
遺傳什么
Gets what?

641
00:23:20,820 --> 00:23:22,830
還是閉嘴吃你的土豆吧
You better shut up and eat your potatoes.

642
00:23:28,730 --> 00:23:31,360
她真說了她寧愿在監獄老死嗎
She actually said she'd prefer to rot in a cell?

643
00:23:32,130 --> 00:23:33,840
你得滿足她這個愿望啊
Well, you've gotta give her credit for that.

644
00:23:33,840 --> 00:23:35,670
是啊  而且她這樣說有道理
You do, and she's right.

645
00:23:36,420 --> 00:23:38,140
這說不過去啊
It's not making any sense.

646
00:23:38,390 --> 00:23:40,890
如果他不想收購  為什么他要拋售股份呢
If he's not making a run, why is he dumping her shares?

647
00:23:40,890 --> 00:23:43,960
-他在做出反應  -他反應過激了
- He's reacting. - He's overreacting.

648
00:23:44,320 --> 00:23:45,500
他或許有閑錢可以燒
He may have money to burn,

649
00:23:45,500 --> 00:23:48,310
但這可不是幾萬的事  可是幾千萬
but this isn't tens of thousands, it's tens of millions.

650
00:23:48,310 --> 00:23:50,040
完全不合情理
It's completely out of proportion.

651
00:23:50,040 --> 00:23:51,170
也不是
Not exactly.

652
00:23:51,170 --> 00:23:52,580
什么意思
What are you talking about?

653
00:23:53,020 --> 00:23:54,900
我傳審了他女兒
I subpoenaed his daughter.

654
00:23:56,120 --> 00:23:57,230
什么
You what?

655
00:23:57,360 --> 00:24:00,230
他害我們丟失客戶  我要回擊
He fired our client, so I struck back.

656
00:24:00,230 --> 00:24:02,320
你也不事前跟我商量
And you didn't think to run that by me?

657
00:24:02,320 --> 00:24:04,110
不  我覺得你不會反對
No, I didn't think you'd say no.

658
00:24:04,110 --> 00:24:06,420
我會反對  因為我不是白癡
I'd say no because I'm not an idiot.

659
00:24:06,840 --> 00:24:07,520
白癡
Idiot?

660
00:24:07,530 --> 00:24:08,940
我們需要他的幫助
We need this man to help us.

661
00:24:08,940 --> 00:24:10,580
你把他變成我們永遠的敵人
You just made him a permanent enemy.

662
00:24:10,580 --> 00:24:12,540
只有我嗎  我們是一起合作的
Me? We did this together.

663
00:24:12,540 --> 00:24:14,810
-別怪到我頭上  -是你在怪我
- Don't put this on me. - You're putting it on me.

664
00:24:14,810 --> 00:24:16,210
因為這是你干的
Because you goddamn did it!

665
00:24:16,220 --> 00:24:18,140
不管我說什么  你都會去找他的茬
You were going to go after him no matter what I said.

666
00:24:18,140 --> 00:24:19,470
我只打擊他的生意
I attacked his business.

667
00:24:19,470 --> 00:24:21,210
你對他的家人動手
You went after his family.

668
00:24:21,210 --> 00:24:23,570
別說你沒做過同樣的事
Don't tell me you've never done the same thing,

669
00:24:23,570 --> 00:24:25,180
現在只不過換成了是我做而已
and what's the difference between me doing it,

670
00:24:25,180 --> 00:24:26,770
和你做有什么
other than the fact that--

671
00:24:30,160 --> 00:24:31,200
我明白了
I see.

672
00:24:32,430 --> 00:24:35,270
這和我私下攻擊揚諾普洛斯無關
This isn't about me getting personal with Gianopolous.

673
00:24:36,170 --> 00:24:39,410
而是因為我私下與唐娜有關系
This is about me getting personal with Donna.

674
00:24:41,110 --> 00:24:43,440
我現在就裝作沒聽到你說這句話
I'm gonna pretend you didn't just say that.

675
00:24:43,970 --> 00:24:45,470
因為她全都聽得到嗎
Is that because she's listening?

676
00:24:45,470 --> 00:24:47,320
她聽不聽得到我壓根不在乎
I don't give a shit if she hears it or not.

677
00:24:47,320 --> 00:24:49,410
對揚諾普洛斯你越界了
You crossed a line with Gianopolous,

678
00:24:49,410 --> 00:24:51,610
而你剛才對我又越界了
and you just crossed another one with me.

679
00:24:52,030 --> 00:24:54,700
你從一開始就對我有意見
You know, you've had it in for me from the start.

680
00:24:54,700 --> 00:24:56,900
你和唐娜好上不過才三天
And you've only been with Donna for three days,

681
00:24:56,900 --> 00:24:58,450
你應該知道是跟什么有關
that should tell you something.

682
00:24:58,450 --> 00:25:00,330
你給我聽清楚了
Let me spell it out for you, okay?

683
00:25:00,330 --> 00:25:02,800
不準背著我做我的案子
You don't work my case without me,

684
00:25:02,800 --> 00:25:05,200
既然你對這句話理解有困難
and since you seem to be having trouble understanding that,

685
00:25:05,200 --> 00:25:06,580
你完全不準碰我的案子
you don't work my case at all.

686
00:25:06,580 --> 00:25:08,210
現在給我滾出我的辦公室
Now get out of my office.

687
00:25:22,170 --> 00:25:23,710
邁克爾
So, Michael,

688
00:25:23,710 --> 00:25:24,900
邁克
Mike.

689
00:25:25,110 --> 00:25:26,940
現在輪到你教我該怎么叫你了嗎
So now you're gonna tell me what to call you?

690
00:25:27,690 --> 00:25:29,690
不  只是大家通常都這么叫我
No, I-I--it's-- people usually call me--

691
00:25:29,690 --> 00:25:31,040
和你開個玩笑而已
I'm just messing with you.

692
00:25:33,750 --> 00:25:34,980
你來自哪兒
So where are you from?

693
00:25:35,380 --> 00:25:37,000
我在布魯克林長大
I grew up in Brooklyn.

694
00:25:37,750 --> 00:25:39,030
有兄弟姐妹嗎
Brothers, sisters?

695
00:25:39,030 --> 00:25:40,190
我是獨生子
Only child.

696
00:25:40,800 --> 00:25:42,200
父母還在那兒嗎
Parents still there?

697
00:25:42,450 --> 00:25:44,000
我還小的時候他們就去世了
They both died when I was a kid.

698
00:25:44,000 --> 00:25:45,990
換成你開我玩笑了
Nah, you're messing with me.

699
00:25:53,980 --> 00:25:56,600
我剛才向一個孤兒打聽他已故的雙親
I just asked an orphan about his dead parents

700
00:25:56,600 --> 00:25:58,720
還開了個玩笑  是不是
and made a joke about it, didn't I?

701
00:26:00,610 --> 00:26:02,130
他喜歡蘋果還是藍莓
Does he like apple or blueberry?

702
00:26:02,130 --> 00:26:03,400
媽小點聲  我想聽他們在說點什么
Mom, shh, I'm trying to hear what they're saying.

703
00:26:03,400 --> 00:26:06,360
放松  瑞秋  他能應付你父親
Rachel, relax, he can handle your father.

704
00:26:06,370 --> 00:26:07,470
你怎么知道
How do you know?

705
00:26:07,470 --> 00:26:09,400
如果他應付不了你就不會帶他來了
Because you wouldn't have brought him here if he couldn't.

706
00:26:09,400 --> 00:26:11,740
話說回來  你害怕他們說什么
Besides, what are you so afraid they're gonna say?

707
00:26:13,100 --> 00:26:14,690
你說得對  沒什么
You're right. Nothing.

708
00:26:15,820 --> 00:26:19,030
寶貝  怎么了
Honey, what is it?

709
00:26:22,410 --> 00:26:23,890
你不必告訴我
You don't have to tell me.

710
00:26:25,690 --> 00:26:27,160
只要告訴我
But just tell me this,

711
00:26:28,340 --> 00:26:29,550
你愛他嗎
do you love him?

712
00:26:33,410 --> 00:26:36,130
只要他沒殺過人  沒什么解決不了的
As long as he hasn't killed someone, it'll all work out.

713
00:26:38,930 --> 00:26:40,150
過來
Come on.

714
00:26:47,550 --> 00:26:49,390
你不是說要休息一天嗎
I thought you were taking the day off.

715
00:26:49,390 --> 00:26:51,070
我指白天休息  現在是晚上
That was the day, this is the night,

716
00:26:51,070 --> 00:26:52,900
我的名字還刻在墻上呢
and my name is still on the door.

717
00:26:53,280 --> 00:26:54,420
確實是
It is.

718
00:26:57,710 --> 00:26:58,880
你想要什么  哈維
What do you want, Harvey?

719
00:26:58,880 --> 00:26:59,960
你是對的
You were right.

720
00:26:59,960 --> 00:27:01,840
我們最近的分歧可不少
We've had a lot of disagreements lately.

721
00:27:01,840 --> 00:27:03,180
你是指哪個
Which one are you referring to?

722
00:27:03,180 --> 00:27:05,710
我現在不確定史蒂芬·亨特利的判斷
I'm not entirely sure Stephen Huntley's judgment

723
00:27:05,710 --> 00:27:07,360
是否要比你的好
is better than yours.

724
00:27:07,460 --> 00:27:09,080
他背著我擅作主張
He went behind my back.

725
00:27:09,780 --> 00:27:11,280
背著別人擅作主張
Going behind someone's back

726
00:27:11,280 --> 00:27:13,460
不像是會讓你不爽的事情
doesn't seem like something you have a problem with.

727
00:27:13,460 --> 00:27:17,170
或許是吧  但他不正當地攻擊揚諾普洛斯
Maybe, but he hit Gianopolous below the belt,

728
00:27:17,170 --> 00:27:18,490
現在我們有麻煩了
and now we have a problem.

729
00:27:18,490 --> 00:27:20,010
"我們"有麻煩了
We have a problem?

730
00:27:20,660 --> 00:27:22,730
你剛才不還說墻上刻著你的名字
You said your name was still on the door.

731
00:27:22,810 --> 00:27:24,480
我是來尋求幫助的
I'm coming to you for help.

732
00:27:29,200 --> 00:27:30,430
出了什么問題
What's our problem?

733
00:27:31,290 --> 00:27:33,550
他在拋售海辛頓石油的股票
He's dumping Hessington Oil shares

734
00:27:33,550 --> 00:27:35,760
只為把她逼上絕路
just to drive her into the ground.

735
00:27:43,680 --> 00:27:45,450
如果我們能合作
Well, if we can come together,

736
00:27:46,650 --> 00:27:48,270
或許他們也可以
maybe they can come together.

737
00:27:48,270 --> 00:27:49,350
我聽著
I'm listening.

738
00:27:49,350 --> 00:27:53,320
托尼·揚諾普洛斯想要擁有海辛頓石油
Tony Gianopolous wants to own Hessington Oil.

739
00:27:55,010 --> 00:27:56,790
艾娃想要掌控海辛頓石油
Ava wants to control it.

740
00:27:56,850 --> 00:27:58,940
她把她的股份賣給他
She sells him her shares,

741
00:27:59,740 --> 00:28:01,300
他把投票權給她
he gives her the voting rights.

742
00:28:01,300 --> 00:28:03,520
他再放棄卡梅隆·丹尼斯
And he gives up Cameron Dennis.

743
00:28:03,520 --> 00:28:05,970
他們各取所需  也成全我們
They get what they want, and so do we.

744
00:28:07,360 --> 00:28:09,120
你覺得他會不會同意
You think he'll still go for it?

745
00:28:09,700 --> 00:28:11,910
他知道我們會去找他的  因為他勝券在握
He'll know we're coming to him because he won.

746
00:28:12,480 --> 00:28:14,020
他不是問題
He won't be the problem.

747
00:28:14,280 --> 00:28:15,780
艾娃說她寧愿爛在牢內
Ava said she'd rather rot

748
00:28:15,780 --> 00:28:17,660
也不愿看他收購她的公司
than see him take over her company.

749
00:28:18,630 --> 00:28:20,180
艾娃這邊我來搞定
I'll take care of Ava.

750
00:28:20,520 --> 00:28:23,600
你們兩個看上去相處得不錯
Look, it seems like you two get along,

751
00:28:24,380 --> 00:28:25,940
我也挺喜歡你的
And I like you.

752
00:28:26,640 --> 00:28:28,500
那我就不和你繞彎子了
So I'm gonna ask you this straight.

753
00:28:29,770 --> 00:28:31,840
她費盡心思想要成為律師
She's worked her ass off to become a lawyer.

754
00:28:31,840 --> 00:28:32,920
我知道
I know.

755
00:28:32,970 --> 00:28:34,970
我不希望會有什么阻礙她
Well, I don't want anything to stand in her way.

756
00:28:34,970 --> 00:28:36,300
我絕不會阻礙她的
I would never do that.

757
00:28:36,300 --> 00:28:39,230
那等她進斯坦福了你打算怎么辦
So what happens when she gets into Stanford?

758
00:28:42,190 --> 00:28:43,980
你還不知道她申請那兒了吧
You didn't know she applied there.

759
00:28:47,510 --> 00:28:49,740
看來你們該好好談談了
Looks like you two have something to talk about.

760
00:28:57,770 --> 00:28:59,290
今天早上怎么這么安靜
You're very quite this morning.

761
00:28:59,290 --> 00:28:59,860
只是有點累
Just tired.

762
00:28:59,860 --> 00:29:02,170
還累呢  昨天吃完飯你就直接回家了啊
Still? I mean, you went home right after dinner last night.

763
00:29:02,170 --> 00:29:03,890
失眠了
Yeah, trouble sleeping.

764
00:29:04,770 --> 00:29:06,000
出什么問題了
Is something wrong?

765
00:29:07,290 --> 00:29:09,150
你他媽的以為自己是誰啊
Hey, who the hell do you think you are?

766
00:29:09,150 --> 00:29:10,990
斯丹頓先生  我猜你明白我們的意思了
Mr. Stenton, I guess you got our message.

767
00:29:10,990 --> 00:29:13,220
收到了  現在我也有話要給你
Oh, I did, and now I've got one for you.

768
00:29:13,220 --> 00:29:15,660
貝絲和我今早結婚了
Beth and I got married this morning.

769
00:29:16,040 --> 00:29:17,880
你為了保護自己而娶她
You married a woman to protect yourself?

770
00:29:17,890 --> 00:29:19,290
我娶她是因為我愛她
I married her because I love her.

771
00:29:19,300 --> 00:29:20,850
但你這么做是為了讓你和她
But you did it to make any conversation

772
00:29:20,850 --> 00:29:22,280
之間所有的對話都被保密
that the two of you had privileged.

773
00:29:22,280 --> 00:29:23,600
你這個威脅她的律師還真敢說
Says the lawyer who threatened her.

774
00:29:23,600 --> 00:29:27,180
現在就算上了法庭  她也不會作證
Well, now you take this to trial, she won't testify.

775
00:29:27,390 --> 00:29:29,310
太可惜了  配偶特權
Well, it's too bad spousal privilege

776
00:29:29,310 --> 00:29:30,750
才不會適用于這種狗屁婚姻
doesn't apply to bullshit marriages.

777
00:29:30,750 --> 00:29:32,290
是嗎  那你就試試看啊
Yeah, good luck arguing that.

778
00:29:32,290 --> 00:29:34,730
我們給了你們一次還掉錢
We offered the two of you a chance to give back the money

779
00:29:34,730 --> 00:29:36,750
抽身離開的機會  但是如果我們證明你
and walk away, but after we prove you did this--

780
00:29:36,750 --> 00:29:38,280
你什么都證明不了
Oh, you can't prove I did a thing.

781
00:29:38,280 --> 00:29:41,070
現在  你也不能強迫她來幫你證明什么了
And now, you can't force her to prove it for you either.

782
00:29:49,960 --> 00:29:51,580
昨晚你沒回我電話
You never returned my call last night.

783
00:29:51,580 --> 00:29:53,130
昨晚和前天晚上
Well, what could be different about last night

784
00:29:53,130 --> 00:29:55,320
有什么區別呢
than the night before? Hmm?

785
00:29:56,350 --> 00:29:57,670
也許區別在于昨晚你去找了哈維
Maybe the fact that you went to Harvey

786
00:29:57,670 --> 00:29:59,890
當著他的面把我拿出來說事兒
and you threw me in his face.

787
00:30:00,560 --> 00:30:03,120
我只是實話實話
Um, I was just telling it how it was.

788
00:30:03,690 --> 00:30:05,160
他本來就對我們不滿了
He's already got it in for us anyway.

789
00:30:05,160 --> 00:30:07,610
那也是我和他的事  不關你事
Well, that's my business with him, not yours.

790
00:30:09,170 --> 00:30:11,350
你說得對  我很抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.

791
00:30:11,420 --> 00:30:14,570
我沒想讓你和哈維之間難堪
I never wanted to make things awkward for you and Harvey.

792
00:30:15,600 --> 00:30:17,810
你是讓我和你之間難堪了
You made things awkward for you and me.

793
00:30:19,450 --> 00:30:21,260
-唐娜  -我喜歡你  史蒂芬
- Donna-- - I like you, Stephen,

794
00:30:21,260 --> 00:30:23,170
我也很享受我們的短期協議
And I have enjoyed our short-term arrangement,

795
00:30:23,180 --> 00:30:25,100
但我不喜歡問題復雜化
but I don't enjoy complications.

796
00:30:25,140 --> 00:30:27,730
我也一樣  但看來眼前就有一個問題
I don't either, but it seems we have one.

797
00:30:28,640 --> 00:30:31,980
你對我的影響超出了我的預期
Now, I'm affected by you more than I thought,

798
00:30:32,690 --> 00:30:36,470
我想延長我們的協議
and I'm finding I'd like to extend our term.

799
00:30:38,850 --> 00:30:40,680
我會考慮的
I'll take your offer under advisement.

800
00:30:51,790 --> 00:30:54,470
我絕不把我的股份出售給那個人
I am not selling my shares to that man.

801
00:30:55,380 --> 00:30:56,920
我跟你不太熟  艾娃
I don't know you that well, Ava,

802
00:30:56,920 --> 00:30:58,480
我也不打算套近乎
and I won't pretend that I do,

803
00:30:58,500 --> 00:31:00,290
但我們的確有個共同之處
but we do have something in common.

804
00:31:00,420 --> 00:31:01,470
是什么
What is that?

805
00:31:01,610 --> 00:31:03,060
我選擇跟愛德華·達比合并
I merged with Edward Darby

806
00:31:03,060 --> 00:31:05,060
來挽救我的事務所
to save my firm from being hijacked

807
00:31:05,060 --> 00:31:06,900
免遭我前合伙人的劫持
by my piece of shit ex-partner.

808
00:31:06,900 --> 00:31:09,200
這算哪門子共同之處
And what exactly does that give us in common?

809
00:31:09,200 --> 00:31:11,720
我能理解你的心情  寧愿暴死街頭
I know what it's like to prefer rotting in the ground

810
00:31:11,720 --> 00:31:14,900
也不愿敵人奪走屬于我的一切
than letting my enemy take what's mine.

811
00:31:16,070 --> 00:31:17,490
我說的是"死在牢里"
I said, "Rotting in a cell."

812
00:31:17,490 --> 00:31:19,330
我又沒被指控謀殺
I wasn't up on murder charges.

813
00:31:19,330 --> 00:31:20,530
這么說你寧愿去死
And you'd rather have died?

814
00:31:20,530 --> 00:31:23,240
我這是比喻  我知道你也是
I was speaking metaphorically, as I'm sure you were.

815
00:31:23,240 --> 00:31:24,370
是嗎
Was I?

816
00:31:24,830 --> 00:31:27,260
你在牢里可沒法經營公司
You won't be able to run your company from a cell.

817
00:31:27,980 --> 00:31:29,370
我想說的是
My point is,

818
00:31:29,870 --> 00:31:31,470
我也不想合并
I didn't want to merge,

819
00:31:31,470 --> 00:31:34,540
但為了保住自己的公司  我不得不合并
but I did what I had to do to keep my company mine.

820
00:31:34,670 --> 00:31:36,880
那結果又怎樣呢
And how is that working out for you?

821
00:31:36,950 --> 00:31:38,610
有利有弊
It has its ups and downs,

822
00:31:39,540 --> 00:31:41,980
但我如今能站在你面前
but I wouldn't be standing here in front of you

823
00:31:41,990 --> 00:31:43,590
全得益于此
if I hadn't done it.

824
00:31:43,680 --> 00:31:46,370
這也沒多少說服力
Not exactly a ringing endorsement.

825
00:31:46,370 --> 00:31:47,470
艾娃...
Ava...

826
00:31:48,380 --> 00:31:51,630
聽我的  擺脫謀殺的指控
Do this. Get free of your murder charges.

827
00:31:52,450 --> 00:31:54,690
之后再不會有人覺得
Nobody is saying we can't try

828
00:31:54,690 --> 00:31:56,880
我們對你也回天乏術
to get you out of this deal later.

829
00:31:58,780 --> 00:31:59,730
我不管付出多少代價
I don't care what it takes,

830
00:31:59,740 --> 00:32:00,800
反正我不能輸給他
I'm not losing to that guy.

831
00:32:00,800 --> 00:32:02,850
我們得從配偶特權上想辦法
We need to find a way around spousal privilege.

832
00:32:02,850 --> 00:32:03,880
我覺得不好辦
I don't see how we can.

833
00:32:03,880 --> 00:32:05,510
該死的法律  不好意思
Stupid goddamn law. Excuse me.

834
00:32:05,510 --> 00:32:07,690
也沒那么該死
It's not entirely stupid.

835
00:32:07,980 --> 00:32:09,660
你現在也向著他了
Oh, what, so now, you're on his side?

836
00:32:09,660 --> 00:32:11,540
不是  特權自有其存在的意義
No, privilege exists for a reason.

837
00:32:11,540 --> 00:32:12,270
你也不想擔心
You don't want to have to worry about

838
00:32:12,280 --> 00:32:13,500
不敢信任你的家人
what you trust your partner with.

839
00:32:13,500 --> 00:32:14,630
那也得建立在
That's assuming your partner

840
00:32:14,640 --> 00:32:15,830
家人也信任你的基礎上
even trusts you in the first place.

841
00:32:15,830 --> 00:32:16,660
這話什么意思
What is that even supposed to mean?

842
00:32:16,660 --> 00:32:19,030
你打算何時才告訴我你申請了斯坦福大學
It means, when were you gonna tell me you applied to Stanford?

843
00:32:30,260 --> 00:32:32,360
這就是為什么昨晚以后
Okay, so that's why you've barely

844
00:32:32,360 --> 00:32:34,820
你幾乎都沒怎么和我說話的原因吧
said three words to me since last night.

845
00:32:34,820 --> 00:32:35,730
我爸告訴你的
My dad told you.

846
00:32:35,730 --> 00:32:38,040
他沒告訴我  他問我怎么看這事
No, no, he didn't tell me, he asked me how I felt about it

847
00:32:38,040 --> 00:32:39,350
他以為我知道
because he assumed I knew,

848
00:32:39,350 --> 00:32:40,980
就像我知道 你在東海岸申請的
like I know about all the east coast schools

849
00:32:39,920 --> 00:32:42,080
紐約位于東海岸  斯坦福大學位于西海岸

850
00:32:40,980 --> 00:32:42,170
-所有學校那樣  -邁克 
- that you applied to. - Mike...

851
00:32:42,170 --> 00:32:43,370
一開始你不想讓我見父母
First you didn't want me to meet your parents,

852
00:32:43,370 --> 00:32:44,070
現在又這樣
and now this?

853
00:32:44,070 --> 00:32:45,920
可我后來還是帶你見我父母了
Yeah, and I changed my mind about you meeting my parents,

854
00:32:45,920 --> 00:32:48,220
現在我開始后悔了
which I'm now beginning to regret.

855
00:32:48,230 --> 00:32:50,140
為什么  因為我發現你有事瞞著我
Oh, why, because I found out you hid something from me?

856
00:32:50,140 --> 00:32:51,650
你也曾對我有過隱瞞
Like you never hid anything from me.

857
00:32:51,650 --> 00:32:53,590
我之前有所隱瞞  所以我們有了嫌隙
I hid something from you, it kept us apart.

858
00:32:53,590 --> 00:32:56,230
而我對你和盤托出以后我們就和好了
What brought us together was me telling you everything.

859
00:32:56,230 --> 00:32:57,940
-我準備告訴你的  -什么時候
- I was going to tell you. - When?

860
00:32:59,580 --> 00:33:02,410
我離開之前  周五
Before I went, on Friday.

861
00:33:06,020 --> 00:33:07,320
你真要去
You're going there?

862
00:33:08,300 --> 00:33:09,570
我要去面試  我很抱歉
I got an interview. I'm sorry.

863
00:33:09,570 --> 00:33:10,620
我不知道怎么跟你開口  邁克
I just didn't know how to tell you, Mike

864
00:33:10,620 --> 00:33:11,470
我也不知道  這個怎么樣
I don't know, how about,

865
00:33:11,470 --> 00:33:13,710
"邁克  我要去三千英里外上法學院啦"
"Hey, Mike,I might go to law school 3,000 miles away"?

866
00:33:13,710 --> 00:33:14,850
我都不確定我會不會被錄取
I don't even know if I'm gonna get in,

867
00:33:14,850 --> 00:33:16,960
所以我現在不想談這個
which is exactly why I didn't want to have this conversation.

868
00:33:16,960 --> 00:33:18,700
才不是  你不想談是因為你可能會被錄取
No, you didn't want to have it because you might go there

869
00:33:18,700 --> 00:33:20,510
而且你不敢承認
and you're too afraid to say it.

870
00:33:22,700 --> 00:33:25,910
那好  我就是想去
Okay. I might want to go there.

871
00:33:26,900 --> 00:33:28,240
我承認了
I've said it.

872
00:33:41,500 --> 00:33:42,640
進來吧
You may enter.

873
00:33:43,280 --> 00:33:46,760
我可能有麻煩了
I'm afraid I've got a bit of a sticky wicket.

874
00:33:47,700 --> 00:33:48,950
聽起來不妙
That sounds uncomfortable.

875
00:33:48,950 --> 00:33:50,780
香港辦公室方面緊急召我
The Hong Kong office urgently requires me

876
00:33:50,780 --> 00:33:51,780
過去幾周時間
for a few weeks.

877
00:33:51,780 --> 00:33:53,510
通常我會帶上米卡度  不過...
Normally, I'd bring Mikado, but...

878
00:33:53,510 --> 00:33:55,140
等等  你是要我...
Whoa, wait, are you asking me to...

879
00:33:55,140 --> 00:33:56,580
我來不及完成她的手續
I can't get her papers in time.

880
00:33:56,590 --> 00:33:58,460
她會被海關隔離檢疫
She'd be facing quarantine.

881
00:33:58,460 --> 00:33:59,910
她哪受得了啊
She'd sooner die.

882
00:33:59,930 --> 00:34:01,700
你真懂她
You already understand her so well.

883
00:34:01,700 --> 00:34:03,710
那必須  可你這請求不小啊...
I do, yet a request of this magnitude...

884
00:34:03,710 --> 00:34:07,230
你說得對  我有點過分了
No, you're probably right, it's too much to ask.

885
00:34:07,230 --> 00:34:10,540
那里肯定會有貓咪專屬的奢華酒店
I'm sure there is a suitable luxury feline hotel.

886
00:34:11,040 --> 00:34:13,560
別逗了  你我都知道不會有
Don't play games, okay? We both know there isn't.

887
00:34:13,560 --> 00:34:15,980
-那你答應了  -沒有  才怪  貓咪呢
- So you'll do it? - N...yes, can I have her?

888
00:34:18,150 --> 00:34:18,830
你有空嗎
Do you have a minute?

889
00:34:18,830 --> 00:34:20,500
我現在沒心情說我們的事
I don't really feel like talking about us right now.

890
00:34:20,500 --> 00:34:21,400
不是我們的事
It's not about that.

891
00:34:21,400 --> 00:34:23,490
我們的交談讓我想到個點子
Our discussion gave me an idea.

892
00:34:23,920 --> 00:34:25,180
我們的交談
Our discussion?

893
00:34:25,180 --> 00:34:27,370
我們不爭怎么命名吵架行嗎
Can we please not fight about what to call our fight?

894
00:34:27,370 --> 00:34:28,230
你有什么點子
What's the idea?

895
00:34:28,230 --> 00:34:30,070
我們不扮紅臉白臉了
We don't do good cop, bad cop anymore.

896
00:34:30,070 --> 00:34:31,790
我們都唱白臉
We do bad cop, bad cop.

897
00:34:32,160 --> 00:34:33,700
以我現在的心情
The way I'm feeling right now,

898
00:34:33,710 --> 00:34:35,250
可以唱白臉
yeah, I can do bad cop.

899
00:34:38,180 --> 00:34:39,440
什么風把你吹來了
Since when do you come out here?

900
00:34:39,440 --> 00:34:41,440
這有阿齊亞戈干酪
Since they added asiago cheese.

901
00:34:41,940 --> 00:34:44,690
干得不錯  你可以選擇獎勵
Your reward of choice for a job well done.

902
00:34:44,690 --> 00:34:45,950
你還記得那故事
You remember that story?

903
00:34:45,950 --> 00:34:48,330
這是你給我講的第一個故事  怎么能忘
First story you ever told me. You think I'd forget?

904
00:34:48,330 --> 00:34:50,100
故事主旨可不是這個
That wasn't the point of the story.

905
00:34:50,300 --> 00:34:51,750
我猜你說服艾娃了
I assume you got Ava to agree.

906
00:34:51,750 --> 00:34:53,000
沒錯
Yes, I did.

907
00:34:53,000 --> 00:34:55,200
給你買個阿齊亞戈貝果慶祝一下嗎
Should I be buying you an asiago bagel?

908
00:34:55,590 --> 00:34:56,860
我要罌粟籽的
Poppy seed.

909
00:34:57,110 --> 00:34:58,710
你有消息要透露
The "Good news, bad news" bagel.

910
00:34:58,720 --> 00:35:00,160
揚諾普洛斯接受交易
Gianopolous agreed to the deal.

911
00:35:00,170 --> 00:35:01,520
他不用卡梅隆·丹尼斯了
He gave up Cameron Dennis.

912
00:35:01,520 --> 00:35:02,690
壞消息是什么
What's the bad news?

913
00:35:02,690 --> 00:35:04,070
卡梅隆留了一手
Cameron protected himself.

914
00:35:04,070 --> 00:35:06,800
他沒跟揚諾普洛斯明確說過錄像帶的事
He never explicitly told Gianopolous about the tape

915
00:35:06,800 --> 00:35:08,850
也沒給他看過
and never actually showed him the tape.

916
00:35:09,650 --> 00:35:11,120
那好消息呢
So what's the good news?

917
00:35:11,120 --> 00:35:13,340
雖然他沒說過錄像帶的存在
He never explicitly said anything,

918
00:35:13,340 --> 00:35:15,890
但他把錄像帶留在
but he left Gianopolous alone

919
00:35:15,890 --> 00:35:17,850
只有揚諾普洛斯一個人的房間里了
in the room with that tape.

920
00:35:29,620 --> 00:35:30,700
睡太晚了嗎
Late night?

921
00:35:31,370 --> 00:35:32,830
壓根沒睡
No sleep at all.

922
00:35:33,280 --> 00:35:34,540
潰瘍
The ulcer?

923
00:35:34,640 --> 00:35:36,120
奈杰爾的貓折騰的
No, Nigel's cat.

924
00:35:36,550 --> 00:35:37,870
你在奈杰爾家過夜了
You slept at Nigel's?

925
00:35:37,950 --> 00:35:40,850
沒有  他出差了  我替他照顧貓
No, he's out of town. I'm cat-sitting.

926
00:35:41,350 --> 00:35:42,230
米卡度只喝
Mikado won't drink her cream

927
00:35:42,230 --> 00:35:44,290
5.5攝氏度的奶糊
unless it's precisely 5.5 degrees celsius,

928
00:35:44,290 --> 00:35:46,460
她看都不看布魯諾收藏的折紙工藝品
she turned her nose up at Bruno's origami collection,

929
00:35:46,460 --> 00:35:47,740
而且必須把貓砂盆面向倫敦方向
and she won't use her litter box unless

930
00:35:47,740 --> 00:35:49,040
她才肯方便
it's facing london.

931
00:35:50,880 --> 00:35:52,200
太討厭了
Hate that damn thing.

932
00:35:52,740 --> 00:35:54,560
但你每分每秒都好愛她  對吧
You're loving every second with her, aren't you?

933
00:35:54,560 --> 00:35:56,440
整整八萬六千四百秒
All 86,400 of them.

934
00:35:57,500 --> 00:36:01,310
另外  你今天沒有那種光彩了 唐娜 
By the way, you don't have that glow today, Donna.

935
00:36:01,340 --> 00:36:02,470
你瑜伽不練了嗎
You stop yoga?

936
00:36:02,940 --> 00:36:04,560
我休息了幾天
I took a couple nights off.

937
00:36:04,560 --> 00:36:05,770
這是哈維的原因嗎
Is this because of Harvey?

938
00:36:05,770 --> 00:36:07,180
因為我不管他說什么
Cause I don't care what he says, Donna,

939
00:36:07,180 --> 00:36:09,080
你千萬不能因工作失了這份光彩
you can't let work get in the way of that glow.

940
00:36:09,680 --> 00:36:11,370
你說的有道理  路易
You know what, Louis, you're right.

941
00:36:12,160 --> 00:36:14,550
我今晚會預約一趟加長時間的瑜伽訓練
I'm gonna schedule an extra long session tonight.

942
00:36:14,550 --> 00:36:15,760
我能一起去嗎
Ooh, can I come?

943
00:36:25,080 --> 00:36:26,810
哈維  你來這干什么
Harvey, what are you doing here?

944
00:36:27,110 --> 00:36:28,750
我來告訴你你輸了
I'm here to tell you that you lost.

945
00:36:28,760 --> 00:36:30,760
我可沒輸  也許我時間不多了
I didn't lose. I may not have much time,

946
00:36:30,760 --> 00:36:32,680
-但我手上還有  -那錄像嗎
- But I still got... - That tape?

947
00:36:33,740 --> 00:36:36,490
那你可錯了  除非你想和
Not anymore, unless you want to dispute

948
00:36:36,490 --> 00:36:38,580
托尼·揚諾普洛斯的白紙黑字爭辯
Tony Gianopolous' sworn statement

949
00:36:38,580 --> 00:36:40,130
他作證是你把錄像單獨留給他的
that you left him alone with it.

950
00:36:50,270 --> 00:36:51,460
我能推翻他
I can fight this.

951
00:36:51,460 --> 00:36:52,650
我對證據鏈還是略知一二的
Chain of custody is something

952
00:36:52,660 --> 00:36:54,590
這還得多謝你
I know a little bit about, thanks to you.

953
00:36:54,590 --> 00:36:56,000
錄像已經沒用了  你也該走人了
That tape is gone, and so are you.

954
00:36:56,000 --> 00:36:56,840
我哪兒也不去
I'm not going anywhere.

955
00:36:56,840 --> 00:36:58,800
承認吧  卡梅隆  我打敗了你
Admit it, Cameron, I beat you.

956
00:36:59,250 --> 00:37:01,750
別讓自己難堪了  趕緊撤訴
Save yourself the embarrassment, and cancel this trial.

957
00:37:01,940 --> 00:37:03,720
如果你真以為我會這樣做
If you think I would ever do that,

958
00:37:03,720 --> 00:37:05,930
那你從我這兒學到的比我想象中還少
I taught you even less than I thought.

959
00:37:06,300 --> 00:37:07,690
這案子原本勢均力敵  
This case was 50/50.

960
00:37:07,690 --> 00:37:09,220
現在只不過你占了優勢而已
All you did was make it 80/20.

961
00:37:09,220 --> 00:37:10,480
絕對優勢
99 to 1.

962
00:37:10,480 --> 00:37:12,850
我可不管你占多少優勢
It could be a million to one for all I care.

963
00:37:12,870 --> 00:37:16,530
只要我還沒有倒下  這就不會結束
We're in the ring, I'm still standing, and this isn't done.

964
00:37:16,530 --> 00:37:20,290
趕快給我消失吧  我還有要準備上法庭
Now get out of my face. I got a trial to prepare for.

965
00:37:28,320 --> 00:37:28,840
你們要干什么  
What do you want?

966
00:37:28,840 --> 00:37:31,580
這是對格雷姆·斯丹頓的起訴書
This is a request for charges to be filed against Graham Stenton

967
00:37:31,580 --> 00:37:33,140
控告他挪用三千萬美金
for stealing $30 million.

968
00:37:33,140 --> 00:37:35,360
此罪可判處十五年監禁
The penalty for which is 15 years in a federal prison.

969
00:37:35,360 --> 00:37:36,140
你們若有證據
If you had proof of that,

970
00:37:36,140 --> 00:37:37,760
你們根本不會來找我
you wouldn't have come after me in the first place.

971
00:37:37,770 --> 00:37:39,430
我們有證據表明你對此有所知
We have proof that you knew something was wrong

972
00:37:39,430 --> 00:37:40,940
卻沒有告知你的上司
and you didn't notify your employer.

973
00:37:40,940 --> 00:37:42,390
所以我們也帶來了對你的提請起訴書
Which is why this is a request for charges

974
00:37:42,390 --> 00:37:45,090
指控你在得知犯罪事實后成為了同謀
to be filed against you as an accessory after the fact.

975
00:37:45,090 --> 00:37:48,130
而這項罪行可判處五年監禁
The penalty for which is five years in a federal prison.

976
00:37:48,140 --> 00:37:51,330
但只要你作證指控他  就能免于牢獄
But you can avoid that by testifying against him.

977
00:37:51,670 --> 00:37:53,840
即使我愿意  我也不能
Even if I was willing to, I can't.

978
00:37:53,950 --> 00:37:55,920
我們結婚了  他不會讓我作證的
We're married. He'd stop me from testifying.

979
00:37:55,920 --> 00:37:57,780
在紐約是如此  在康涅狄格州就不然了
In New York, not in Connecticut.

980
00:37:57,780 --> 00:37:59,780
所以訴訟會在那兒進行
Which is where the charges will be filed.

981
00:37:59,940 --> 00:38:01,970
你們是在勸我背叛我心愛的人
You're asking me to turn against the man I love.

982
00:38:01,970 --> 00:38:03,460
那就去監獄并相信著他吧
Then go to jail and trust him.

983
00:38:03,460 --> 00:38:05,820
我猜你出來之后  他不會在那兒守候你
I'm guessing he's not gonna be there when you get out.

984
00:38:06,090 --> 00:38:09,110
貝絲  即使他等你
Beth, even if he waits for you,

985
00:38:09,110 --> 00:38:12,080
這也是他干的  害怕怕他被捉到的恐懼
he did this, and the fear of him getting caught

986
00:38:12,080 --> 00:38:13,360
會籠罩在你們共同度過的
is going to cast a shadow over every moment

987
00:38:13,360 --> 00:38:15,910
每一分每一秒
of the rest of your life together.

988
00:38:18,240 --> 00:38:20,520
他也許沒法感受到  但我知道你可以
He may not be able to see that, but I know you can.

989
00:38:30,020 --> 00:38:31,630
我會把錢還給你們的
I'll get you the money back.

990
00:38:38,900 --> 00:38:39,930
你做什么呢
What are you doing?

991
00:38:40,220 --> 00:38:41,560
留個言而已
Just leaving a note.

992
00:38:42,180 --> 00:38:45,030
順便恭喜你了
By the way, congratulations.

993
00:38:45,790 --> 00:38:47,320
我聽說你將錄像除出證物之外了
I hear you got the tape thrown out

994
00:38:47,320 --> 00:38:49,780
艾娃也被重新任命為執行總裁
and Ava reinstated as the CEO.

995
00:38:49,790 --> 00:38:52,160
-完全不用你插手  -我知道
- In spite of you. - yeah, I know.

996
00:38:52,620 --> 00:38:55,200
你尋求了杰西卡的幫助
You went to Jessica for help.

997
00:38:55,230 --> 00:38:57,640
-你對此有問題嗎  -沒有
- You have a problem with that? - No.

998
00:38:58,130 --> 00:38:59,470
我只是覺得這很諷刺
I just think it's ironic that

999
00:38:59,470 --> 00:39:00,810
她根本沒意識到
she doesn't realize

1000
00:39:00,810 --> 00:39:02,990
她竟幫了你掘她自己的墳墓
she just helped you dig her own grave.

1001
00:39:10,900 --> 00:39:11,960
是我
It's me.

1002
00:39:17,690 --> 00:39:19,660
錢匯到賬了
Money got wired into the account.

1003
00:39:19,820 --> 00:39:21,230
恭喜
Congratulations.

1004
00:39:21,950 --> 00:39:23,100
要不是你臨場發揮
I don't think she would've caved

1005
00:39:23,100 --> 00:39:24,310
突然唱紅臉
If you hadn't broken script

1006
00:39:24,310 --> 00:39:26,500
她是不會妥協的
and gone all good cop on me.

1007
00:39:29,050 --> 00:39:30,510
-對不起  -對不起
- Look, I'm sorry.  - I'm sorry.

1008
00:39:30,840 --> 00:39:32,520
-瑞秋  -不  邁克
- Rachel-- - No, Mike.

1009
00:39:33,050 --> 00:39:34,750
我們吵架  因為我犯了個錯
We're in a fight because I made the mistake

1010
00:39:34,750 --> 00:39:36,030
沒有告訴你
of not telling you that

1011
00:39:36,030 --> 00:39:37,830
我考慮去斯坦福
I was considering going to Stanford,

1012
00:39:37,830 --> 00:39:39,040
但我們吵架的真正原因
but we're really in a fight

1013
00:39:39,050 --> 00:39:41,580
是因為我真的打算去斯坦福了
because I'm considering going to Stanford.

1014
00:39:42,440 --> 00:39:43,890
你對貝絲說的話
What you said to Beth,

1015
00:39:43,890 --> 00:39:45,670
實際上是對我說的嗎
was that really about me?

1016
00:39:45,670 --> 00:39:47,220
因為你說
Because you said

1017
00:39:47,230 --> 00:39:48,800
害怕他被抓的恐懼
the fear of him getting caught

1018
00:39:48,800 --> 00:39:50,960
會籠罩在你們共同度過的
was gonna cast a shadow over every minute

1019
00:39:50,960 --> 00:39:52,140
每一分每一秒
of the rest of their life together.

1020
00:39:52,210 --> 00:39:55,110
如果你這是在問我
If you're asking if it's occurred to me

1021
00:39:55,110 --> 00:39:58,920
去斯坦福對我來說會不會是個嶄新的開始
that going to Stanford could be a fresh start...

1022
00:40:01,170 --> 00:40:02,010
沒錯
Yeah.

1023
00:40:02,010 --> 00:40:03,780
這有可能  但事實是
It has, but the truth is

1024
00:40:03,780 --> 00:40:05,980
我不知道我能不能進耶魯或哥倫比亞大學
I may or may not get into Yale or Columbia,

1025
00:40:05,990 --> 00:40:08,480
但你告訴過我
and you were the one that told me

1026
00:40:08,480 --> 00:40:10,720
我不能就這樣止步不前  滿于現狀
that it'd be stupid if I didn't just cover my bases,

1027
00:40:10,720 --> 00:40:12,200
所以我得過去
so I just need to go

1028
00:40:12,200 --> 00:40:15,170
看看到底我能不能錄取
and see if I even get in or not.

1029
00:40:15,170 --> 00:40:16,410
我懂
I get it.

1030
00:40:17,490 --> 00:40:18,390
我都能理解
I get all of it.

1031
00:40:18,390 --> 00:40:21,000
但我不得不想如果你被錄取了該怎么辦
I just can't stop thinking about what will happen if you do.

1032
00:40:25,670 --> 00:40:26,680
你最終自己決定
You came to the decision

1033
00:40:26,680 --> 00:40:29,320
和我分享你的秘密
to let me in on your secret on your own,

1034
00:40:30,010 --> 00:40:32,690
我只是需要你給我
and I just need you to give me the freedom

1035
00:40:33,780 --> 00:40:36,010
做出自己的選擇的自由
to come to this decision on my own.

1036
00:40:39,460 --> 00:40:41,640
我不感情用事
I'm not one for sentimental gestures,

1037
00:40:42,620 --> 00:40:44,580
但我想起哈德曼回來的時候
but I was thinking about when Hardman came back

1038
00:40:44,580 --> 00:40:46,280
你我都陷入那場混亂
and you and I got into it.

1039
00:40:48,040 --> 00:40:49,930
你幫我奪回了我的茶具[亦有控制權之意]
you got me my tea set back.

1040
00:40:50,310 --> 00:40:52,180
你就為了這個來謝我嗎
You here to thank me for that?

1041
00:40:52,600 --> 00:40:54,880
我自有我感謝的方式
I'm here with a gesture of my own.

1042
00:40:55,800 --> 00:40:59,880
皮爾森-達比-斯佩克特律所
哈維·斯佩克特

1043
00:41:02,040 --> 00:41:03,580
這可不是套茶具
This isn't a tea set.

1044
00:41:03,990 --> 00:41:05,800
明天你名字就將掛在墻上
It's going up on the wall tomorrow.

1045
00:41:07,410 --> 00:41:09,140
我之前就向你要過
I asked for that a while ago.

1046
00:41:09,140 --> 00:41:10,450
你說我還沒準備好
You said I wasn't ready.

1047
00:41:10,460 --> 00:41:12,630
我還說過我不會隨意
I also said I wasn't just going to slap

1048
00:41:12,630 --> 00:41:15,110
將別人的名字掛在我的旁邊
someone else's name up there next to mine,

1049
00:41:15,830 --> 00:41:16,950
但我做了
but I did.

1050
00:41:16,950 --> 00:41:18,500
而你現在后悔了
And now you regret it.

1051
00:41:21,140 --> 00:41:22,950
你又開始下棋了
And you're playing chess again.

1052
00:41:24,150 --> 00:41:25,200
什么意思
What does that mean?

1053
00:41:25,200 --> 00:41:27,720
意思是  我想知道你這是感謝我
It means, I want to know if this is a gesture

1054
00:41:27,720 --> 00:41:29,310
還是一步棋
or if it's a move.

1055
00:41:31,500 --> 00:41:35,150
我這是用我的方法告訴你
What it is, is my way of showing you

1056
00:41:35,690 --> 00:41:38,480
達比對待我  就像我過去對待你
that Darby's treating me the same way I treated you,

1057
00:41:39,270 --> 00:41:41,190
我現在了解了你當時的感受
and I understand how you felt.

1058
00:41:42,620 --> 00:41:43,850
你不喜歡這種感受
You don't like it,

1059
00:41:45,340 --> 00:41:47,990
所以這是你拉我到你一邊的手段
and this is your way of getting me on your side.

1060
00:41:50,070 --> 00:41:51,900
哈維  我無法讓你相信我
Harvey, I can't make you believe me,

1061
00:41:53,190 --> 00:41:55,030
但我不想讓你站我這邊
but I don't want you on my side.

1062
00:41:55,920 --> 00:41:57,910
我是希望我們在同一邊
I want us to be on the same side.

1063
00:42:09,330 --> 00:42:13,250
皮爾森-達比-斯佩克特律所
哈維·斯佩克特
資深合伙人

