1
00:04:52,550 --> 00:04:56,550
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:04:52,550 --> 00:04:56,550
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:04:52,550 --> 00:04:56,550
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:04:52,550 --> 00:04:56,550
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:04:52,550 --> 00:04:56,550
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:04:56,550 --> 00:05:01,550
{\an8}翻译：草草  猫咪赐我速死  CS漫画家小明  杳杳君

7
00:05:01,550 --> 00:05:06,550
{\an8}翻译：香茗小焙  Reginamoon   校对：油炸电风扇    王小麦

8
00:05:06,550 --> 00:05:11,550
{\an8}时间轴：阿丹    猫   今    芒果树叶

9
00:05:11,550 --> 00:05:16,550
{\an8}后期：斯人&加森      精校总监：某羽

10
00:05:18,410 --> 00:05:20,590
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

11
00:05:18,410 --> 00:05:20,590
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第七集

12
00:00:02,570 --> 00:00:05,280
我希望你一字一句的检查你的工作
I want you to go back over your work with a fine-tooth comb,

13
00:00:05,280 --> 00:00:06,710
我们不会出事的
We're as protected as we can be.

14
00:00:06,710 --> 00:00:08,450
我要求任何一个合伙人复查工作
Every partner at this firm

15
00:00:08,450 --> 00:00:10,110
他们就必须去复查
goes over their work if I say so.

16
00:00:10,110 --> 00:00:12,470
我跟他们可不一样
I'm not every goddamn partner.

17
00:00:12,550 --> 00:00:13,940
我跟傅滋曼达成笔交易
I made a deal with Forstman.

18
00:00:14,020 --> 00:00:16,250
这肯定是你整个有趣的生命中
this has got to be the most genius thing

19
00:00:16,250 --> 00:00:19,950
做的最聪明的一件事
you have ever done in your entire, wonderful, life.

20
00:00:20,200 --> 00:00:22,020
傅滋曼坚持要我
Forstman's insisting that I run the money

21
00:00:22,020 --> 00:00:23,490
通过瑞士和开曼群岛管理资金
through Switzerland and the Caymans.

22
00:00:23,490 --> 00:00:24,670
路易  那是违法的
Louis, that's illegal.

23
00:00:24,670 --> 00:00:26,410
你没看见哈维发现
You didn't see the look on Harvey's face

24
00:00:26,410 --> 00:00:28,750
是我拯救了一切时的表情
when he found out that I was the one who saved the day,

25
00:00:28,750 --> 00:00:30,130
而我不想看到
and I am not gonna see 

26
00:00:30,130 --> 00:00:32,380
他发现我没成功时的表情
the look on his face when he finds out that I didn't.

27
00:00:32,380 --> 00:00:33,940
多少钱都不足以
There isn't enough money in the world for me

28
00:00:33,940 --> 00:00:35,690
-让我重新信任你了  -听我说
- to ever trust you again. - Listen to me.

29
00:00:35,690 --> 00:00:37,230
-我...  -不  你听我说
- I'm-- - No, you listen to me!

30
00:00:37,640 --> 00:00:38,770
你被解雇了
You're fired.

31
00:00:42,560 --> 00:00:43,420
我不能这样
I can't.

32
00:00:43,420 --> 00:00:44,510
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel. Rachel.

33
00:00:44,610 --> 00:00:46,560
-这是什么  -工作邀请
- What the hell is this? - A job offer.

34
00:00:47,410 --> 00:00:49,320
我要去告诉迈克
I am going to tell Mike what happened.

35
00:00:49,410 --> 00:00:50,160
你这么做
If you do this,

36
00:00:50,160 --> 00:00:52,170
是在拿你俩的生活冒险
you will be risking your whole life with Mike.

37
00:00:52,200 --> 00:00:54,300
不告诉他也很危险
I am risking it if I don't.

38
00:01:26,090 --> 00:01:27,080
我知道了
I heard.

39
00:01:28,180 --> 00:01:28,980
怎么知道的
How?

40
00:01:29,670 --> 00:01:30,500
艾米
Amy.

41
00:01:31,380 --> 00:01:32,020
她为什么要
Why would she--

42
00:01:32,020 --> 00:01:33,380
你就不用自己说了
So that you wouldn't have to.

43
00:01:33,760 --> 00:01:34,430
喝吧
Here.

44
00:01:35,550 --> 00:01:36,490
该死
Shit.

45
00:01:37,920 --> 00:01:39,970
我都没想她会怎么样
I didn't even think about what would happen to her.

46
00:01:40,010 --> 00:01:41,170
迈克  你现在不用去考虑别人
Mike, you don't have to think about anyone 

47
00:01:41,170 --> 00:01:42,420
考虑你自己就行了
except for you right now.

48
00:01:43,040 --> 00:01:44,440
我不想考虑我的事
I don't want to think about me.

49
00:01:44,440 --> 00:01:46,930
我让所有人失望了  包括你
All I've done is let everyone down, including you.

50
00:01:47,450 --> 00:01:48,950
你没有让我失望
You have not let me down.

51
00:01:50,080 --> 00:01:51,660
你都不知道我做了什么
You don't even know what I've done.

52
00:01:55,490 --> 00:01:58,740
不管是什么  都不会...
Whatever it is, it can't be as bad as--

53
00:01:58,740 --> 00:01:59,780
像我想的那么糟吗
As I think?

54
00:02:04,570 --> 00:02:06,040
瑞秋  我丢了工作
Rachel, I lost my job.

55
00:02:07,050 --> 00:02:08,100
我输了收购战
I lost the takeover.

56
00:02:08,100 --> 00:02:09,810
我丢了沃尔特·吉利斯的公司
I lost Walter Gillis his company.

57
00:02:09,810 --> 00:02:11,450
我跟人达成协议
I cut a deal to sell out the man

58
00:02:11,450 --> 00:02:13,080
出卖当初给了我机会的人
who gave me a chance in the first place.

59
00:02:13,080 --> 00:02:14,070
而且
And to top it all off,

60
00:02:14,070 --> 00:02:16,730
那个逼我这么做的人  说我是他的人
the guy who made me do that called me his guy

61
00:02:16,730 --> 00:02:18,240
还说要给我份工作
and then offered me a job.

62
00:02:18,240 --> 00:02:19,580
我算什么啊
So what does that make me?

63
00:02:20,850 --> 00:02:22,680
普通人
It makes you a human being.

64
00:02:34,180 --> 00:02:35,490
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.

65
00:02:36,130 --> 00:02:37,260
我也是
I don't either.

66
00:02:37,940 --> 00:02:39,960
我们今晚什么都不用做
But we don't have to do anything tonight.

67
00:02:41,900 --> 00:02:43,340
路易  你得冷静下来
Louis, you need to calm down.

68
00:02:43,340 --> 00:02:44,350
我犯了法
I broke the law.

69
00:02:44,350 --> 00:02:46,090
小点声
Please keep your voice down.

70
00:02:46,090 --> 00:02:47,740
何必  让人人都来指责我吧
Why? Let any man judge me.

71
00:02:47,740 --> 00:02:48,980
《圣经》如是说
So says the good book.

72
00:02:48,980 --> 00:02:49,980
-才不是呢  -告诉你
- No, it doesn't. - You know what?

73
00:02:49,980 --> 00:02:51,540
《圣经》怎么写的我还是知道的
I think I know what the goddamn good book says.

74
00:02:51,540 --> 00:02:52,400
听我说
Listen to me.

75
00:02:53,030 --> 00:02:55,310
-你也是不得已 -是吗
- You did what you had to do. - Oh, really?

76
00:02:55,370 --> 00:02:57,100
你刚刚发现的时候可不是这么说的
Well, that's not what you said when you found out.

77
00:02:57,100 --> 00:02:58,310
你说"路易  那是违法的"
You said, "Louis, that's illegal."

78
00:02:58,310 --> 00:03:00,120
当时我想劝你别那么做
Because I was trying to get you not to go through with it.

79
00:03:00,120 --> 00:03:02,130
但你做了决定  我能理解你
But you made a decision. I understand why.

80
00:03:02,130 --> 00:03:03,500
既然做都做了
And now that it's done,

81
00:03:03,720 --> 00:03:06,440
我不希望你这么自责下去
I'm not going to let you beat yourself up about it.

82
00:03:06,670 --> 00:03:08,030
你或许是这样  但等哈维和杰西卡发现
Yeah, well, you may not, but what do you think Harvey

83
00:03:08,030 --> 00:03:09,520
你觉得他们会怎么说
and Jessica are going to do when they find out?

84
00:03:09,520 --> 00:03:12,430
路易  你一次又一次地拯救了大家
Louis, you have been a hero again and again.

85
00:03:12,820 --> 00:03:14,810
如果这一次他们终于承认你是英雄
And if the one time they actually treat you like one

86
00:03:14,810 --> 00:03:16,410
而你为了达到这个效果做了点过分的事
you crossed a little line to get there,

87
00:03:16,410 --> 00:03:17,880
不代表你就是恶人
that doesn't make you horrible.

88
00:03:18,200 --> 00:03:19,340
你只是像哈维
It makes you Harvey.

89
00:03:19,650 --> 00:03:20,990
你说得太对了
You know what? You're absolutely right.

90
00:03:21,390 --> 00:03:22,320
从现在起
And as of this second,

91
00:03:22,320 --> 00:03:24,110
我就要有英雄该有的样子
I'm going to start acting like the hero that I am.

92
00:03:24,820 --> 00:03:25,780
二货
Hey, jerk-off.

93
00:03:25,970 --> 00:03:27,590
我得给谁吹箫才能再上点干果啊
Who do I have to blow to get some more nuts?

94
00:03:33,200 --> 00:03:35,110
原来他早就知道农作物报告的事
It turned out he knew all about the crop reports.

95
00:03:35,110 --> 00:03:35,970
你知道我怎么干的吗
You know what I did?

96
00:03:35,970 --> 00:03:38,210
我用六起邮件欺诈告倒了他
I nailed him on six counts of mail fraud.

97
00:03:39,630 --> 00:03:41,690
你跟他们讲你把头埋在埃里克·伍德尔屁股里
Did you tell them the one about how you got your head

98
00:03:41,690 --> 00:03:43,400
那个笑话了吗
stuck up Eric Woodall's ass?

99
00:03:45,330 --> 00:03:46,580
失陪一下
Excuse me for a second.

100
00:03:49,510 --> 00:03:50,910
你来干什么
What the hell are you doing here?

101
00:03:51,120 --> 00:03:53,760
你觉得只有你能安排人盯梢吗
You think you're the only person who can have someone followed?

102
00:03:53,760 --> 00:03:54,830
你没有权力
You have no right.

103
00:03:54,830 --> 00:03:56,150
我当然有权了
Oh, I have every right.

104
00:03:56,150 --> 00:03:57,580
但我不需要雇任何人
I just didn't need to hire someone

105
00:03:57,580 --> 00:04:00,830
因为你每晚都来这个破地方
'cause it turns out you come to the same shithole every night,

106
00:04:00,830 --> 00:04:03,510
跟同一拨人  讲同样的故事
telling the same stories to the same people

107
00:04:03,510 --> 00:04:05,470
因为你根本没别处可去
because you have no place else to go.

108
00:04:06,140 --> 00:04:08,760
如果你觉得你可以引诱我打你
If you're thinking you can bait me into taking a swing at you,

109
00:04:08,760 --> 00:04:09,560
或许是想对了
you might be right.

110
00:04:09,560 --> 00:04:11,140
你还是对付这个吧
Why don't you take a swing at this?

111
00:04:11,360 --> 00:04:12,980
还想贿赂我啦
Oh, you're trying to bribe me now.

112
00:04:13,310 --> 00:04:15,630
这封信里列出了
That's a certified letter outlining everything

113
00:04:15,630 --> 00:04:17,930
你开始针对我之后发生的每件事
that's happened since you started targeting me,

114
00:04:17,930 --> 00:04:19,710
你每个无理取闹的举动
every bullshit move you've made.

115
00:04:19,710 --> 00:04:21,920
不是无理取闹  这是正在进行中的调查
It's not bullshit. It's an ongoing investigation.

116
00:04:21,920 --> 00:04:23,330
结果什么都没查到
And it's turned up bullshit,

117
00:04:23,330 --> 00:04:25,570
我给霍普金斯法官列出了所有事
which I've outlined for Judge Hopkins.

118
00:04:25,570 --> 00:04:28,670
从针对我的客户到找人跟踪我
Everything from targeting my clients to having me followed.

119
00:04:28,670 --> 00:04:31,670
你有十天时间对我所列事项进行辩解
So now you have ten days to dispute my accounting of events,

120
00:04:31,670 --> 00:04:34,000
完事之后  我再也不想见到你
and when they're done, I expect to never see you again.

121
00:04:34,740 --> 00:04:36,030
你不够了解我
You don't know me that well.

122
00:04:36,220 --> 00:04:38,850
肖恩  你什么时候想放下你的徽章
Sean, any time you want to put the badge down

123
00:04:38,850 --> 00:04:40,600
像男人一样  跟我一对一
and fight me man-to-man,

124
00:04:41,190 --> 00:04:42,510
你知道该去哪找我
you know where to find me.

125
00:05:29,370 --> 00:05:31,130
工作找得如何了
How's the job hunting going?

126
00:05:32,480 --> 00:05:33,720
你想干什么  傅滋曼
What do you want, Forstman?

127
00:05:33,820 --> 00:05:37,410
不需要我的钱了  就叫得这么生硬了
Oh, now that you don't want my money, it's Forstman?

128
00:05:37,550 --> 00:05:38,550
连先生都不说了
No mister?

129
00:05:39,420 --> 00:05:41,280
那个去咖啡店里找我
What happened to the obsequious little shit

130
00:05:41,280 --> 00:05:43,760
向我伸手要钱的阿谀奉承的小混蛋哪去了
who approached me in a coffee shop with his hand out?

131
00:05:43,850 --> 00:05:45,600
他意识到你根本不配得到尊敬
He realized that you don't deserve any respect.

132
00:05:45,600 --> 00:05:46,850
我不需要你的尊敬
I don't need your respect.

133
00:05:47,030 --> 00:05:48,480
我需要你答复是否接受我给你的工作
I need an answer on my job offer.

134
00:05:48,850 --> 00:05:50,180
我不是都说清楚了吗
Thought I was pretty clear.

135
00:05:50,450 --> 00:05:51,790
你嘴上是那么说
Your mouth said one thing.

136
00:05:52,860 --> 00:05:54,610
看看你眼睛怎么想吧
Let's see what your eyes have to say.

137
00:06:00,970 --> 00:06:02,030
一百万美金
A million dollars.

138
00:06:02,500 --> 00:06:04,920
-你在拿我寻开心吗  -是你的签约奖金
- Is this a joke? - It's your signing bonus.

139
00:06:05,480 --> 00:06:07,400
现在愿意来给我工作了吗
Are you ready to come work for me now?

140
00:06:08,310 --> 00:06:10,890
我不是阿谀奉承的小混蛋吗
Thought I was an obsequious little shit.

141
00:06:11,250 --> 00:06:13,770
你是啊  我像你这年纪的时候也是这样
You are, but so was I when I was your age,

142
00:06:13,770 --> 00:06:15,160
看我如今的成就
and look what happened to me.

143
00:06:16,970 --> 00:06:19,460
一千万也无所谓  查尔斯
You could make it ten million, Charles.

144
00:06:20,010 --> 00:06:20,720
我不要你的钱
I don't want your money.

145
00:06:20,720 --> 00:06:22,010
我不会给你一千万的
I'm not gonna make it ten million.

146
00:06:22,910 --> 00:06:24,060
就是一百万
The offer is one,

147
00:06:24,060 --> 00:06:25,410
不会改的
and that's where it's standing.

148
00:06:26,150 --> 00:06:27,390
给你一天考虑
You have a day.

149
00:06:27,820 --> 00:06:29,630
如果你不接受我的提议
If you decide not to take my offer,

150
00:06:30,160 --> 00:06:31,920
我就会知道你不仅混蛋
I will know you're not only an asshole.

151
00:06:32,410 --> 00:06:33,420
还很傻
You're a fool.

152
00:06:34,680 --> 00:06:35,570
走吧
Let's go.

153
00:06:45,760 --> 00:06:46,570
杰西卡
Jessica.

154
00:06:46,970 --> 00:06:48,630
何事大驾光临啊  找我什么事
To what do I owe the honor? What can I do for you?

155
00:06:48,630 --> 00:06:50,270
路易  我来找你
Louis, I am coming to you

156
00:06:50,430 --> 00:06:52,580
不是要你为我做什么
because the question isn't what you can do for me,

157
00:06:52,580 --> 00:06:54,180
而是要问我能为你做什么
but what can I do for you?

158
00:06:54,790 --> 00:06:56,260
哈维和我对你
Harvey and I were very impressed

159
00:06:56,260 --> 00:06:57,720
应付查尔斯·傅滋曼的手段很钦佩
by what you did with Charles Forstman.

160
00:06:58,060 --> 00:06:59,810
你知道这有多厉害让我很高兴
I'm impressed that you understand how impressive it was.

161
00:06:59,810 --> 00:07:03,840
因为我们想不出该怎么表示感激
And since we couldn't figure out how best to show our gratitude,

162
00:07:04,370 --> 00:07:06,550
我就干脆来问你想要什么
I'm here to ask you what you would like.

163
00:07:06,740 --> 00:07:07,520
抱歉
I'm sorry.

164
00:07:10,250 --> 00:07:12,050
-你要给我  -一份奖励
- You want to give me... - A reward.

165
00:07:12,050 --> 00:07:13,700
-随便什么都行吗  -你开口便是
- Anything I want? - All you have to do is ask--

166
00:07:13,700 --> 00:07:14,620
冠名合伙人
Pearson, Specter, Litt.

167
00:07:15,780 --> 00:07:17,140
-什么  -我说得很清楚了
- Excuse me? - I think I was clear.

168
00:07:17,140 --> 00:07:18,550
我要做冠名合伙人  排第三也行
I want my name on the door. It can go third.

169
00:07:18,600 --> 00:07:21,080
路易  冠名合伙人可不是我随手就能给你的
Louis, named partner isn't something I can just hand out.

170
00:07:21,240 --> 00:07:22,390
但你说是我挽救了大局啊
But you just said I saved the day.

171
00:07:22,390 --> 00:07:24,880
那是你自己的话
You just said you saved the day.

172
00:07:24,880 --> 00:07:26,930
我说我们想表示感激
I said we wanted to show our gratitude.

173
00:07:26,930 --> 00:07:28,420
告诉我我可以随便选择奖励
By telling me I get to choose whatever I want,

174
00:07:28,420 --> 00:07:29,980
但就是不能选我最想要的
except for the one thing I really want.

175
00:07:29,980 --> 00:07:31,390
或许我该说得更明白些
Maybe I should have been more clear.

176
00:07:31,400 --> 00:07:32,170
是啊
Maybe you should have.

177
00:07:32,170 --> 00:07:33,870
你可也是律师啊
I mean, you're a goddamn lawyer, after all.

178
00:07:35,580 --> 00:07:36,370
路易
Louis,

179
00:07:36,910 --> 00:07:39,810
那我说明白
then let me be clear right now.

180
00:07:41,200 --> 00:07:43,610
我要给你一个机会
I am giving you an opportunity

181
00:07:43,800 --> 00:07:47,610
优雅地接受你应得的感激
to accept a well-deserved thank-you with grace.

182
00:07:48,210 --> 00:07:49,410
你可以接受
You can either take it,

183
00:07:49,970 --> 00:07:52,140
也可以把它变成责罚
or you can turn it into a personal snub

184
00:07:52,400 --> 00:07:54,640
毁掉你刚刚赢得的
and ruin all the goodwill 

185
00:07:54,640 --> 00:07:57,710
我和哈维的好感
that you've just earned with me and Harvey.

186
00:07:59,720 --> 00:08:00,940
选择权在你
The choice is yours.

187
00:08:04,740 --> 00:08:06,450
-我能回头答复你吗  -抱歉  什么
- Can I get back to you on that? - I'm sorry. What?

188
00:08:06,450 --> 00:08:07,540
我能回头答复你吗
Can I get back to you on that?

189
00:08:08,810 --> 00:08:10,710
这正是我所希望的  路易
That's all I can hope for you, Louis.

190
00:08:16,620 --> 00:08:18,910
我只是来给你过一遍这周
So I just wanted to run through your schedule

191
00:08:18,910 --> 00:08:19,940
你接下来几天的日程
for the rest of the week.

192
00:08:19,940 --> 00:08:20,820
好
Go ahead.

193
00:08:20,920 --> 00:08:22,940
你今天四点要见埃利斯
You've got Ellis at 4:00 today,

194
00:08:23,080 --> 00:08:24,830
明天十点见麦肯尼
Mckinney at 10:00 tomorrow,

195
00:08:24,830 --> 00:08:26,030
两点见张伯伦
Chamberlain at 2:00,

196
00:08:26,030 --> 00:08:29,270
你去找迈克的时间我该安排在几点
and when should I pencil you in to go see Mike?

197
00:08:29,510 --> 00:08:31,780
-见他干嘛  -朋友间的会面
- See him for what? - To be a friend.

198
00:08:31,780 --> 00:08:33,330
唐娜  对他来说
Donna, as far as he's concerned,

199
00:08:33,330 --> 00:08:35,040
我为赢收购案出卖了他
I sold him out to win the takeover.

200
00:08:35,040 --> 00:08:37,100
我现在是他最不想见到的人
I am the last person he wants to see right now.

201
00:08:37,100 --> 00:08:38,350
我完全同意
And I would agree with all that,

202
00:08:38,350 --> 00:08:40,280
但是迈克被解雇了
except for the fact that Mike got fired.

203
00:08:41,020 --> 00:08:41,770
什么
What?

204
00:08:43,050 --> 00:08:44,350
-什么时候  -昨晚
- When? - Last night.

205
00:08:44,490 --> 00:08:45,380
而且我本不该告诉你的
And I wasn't gonna tell you

206
00:08:45,380 --> 00:08:46,940
因为他应该自己告诉你
because you should be hearing it from him,

207
00:08:46,940 --> 00:08:47,830
但男人都是白痴
but men are idiots,

208
00:08:47,830 --> 00:08:49,350
他们宁愿一个人凄凄惨惨
and they would rather be alone and miserable

209
00:08:49,350 --> 00:08:50,970
也不愿被人说
than ever run the risk of being accused

210
00:08:50,970 --> 00:08:52,130
需要别人
of needing someone.

211
00:08:52,130 --> 00:08:53,360
他有瑞秋
He has Rachel.

212
00:08:53,450 --> 00:08:54,700
迈克相信无论发生什么
Who is the one person Mike believes

213
00:08:54,700 --> 00:08:56,210
瑞秋都会站在他这边
will stand by him no matter what,

214
00:08:56,480 --> 00:08:58,600
所以不论她怎样说他没有一败涂地
which makes her the one person he won't believe

215
00:08:58,600 --> 00:09:00,810
他都当做那是安慰而已
when she says he didn't completely fail.

216
00:09:01,680 --> 00:09:03,510
和埃利斯的会面有多重要
How important is the meeting with Ellis?

217
00:09:03,690 --> 00:09:04,670
他说是急事
He says it's urgent.

218
00:09:05,150 --> 00:09:06,380
告诉他重约时间
Tell him I have to reschedule.

219
00:09:11,730 --> 00:09:13,960
奇怪  我已经叫他重约了
That's weird. I already did.

220
00:09:21,900 --> 00:09:23,050
瑞秋还是唐娜
Rachel or Donna?

221
00:09:23,640 --> 00:09:25,170
谁叫你来看我的
Who told you to check up on me?

222
00:09:25,170 --> 00:09:26,600
你就不想是我自己来的吗
You don't think I'd do that on my own?

223
00:09:26,600 --> 00:09:27,880
不  不会
No, I don't.

224
00:09:27,960 --> 00:09:29,050
我本来不会来
Well, I wouldn't have

225
00:09:29,050 --> 00:09:30,290
因为我想你不需要
because I didn't think you'd need it.

226
00:09:30,290 --> 00:09:31,910
然后我得知你被炒了
Then I found out you got fired.

227
00:09:33,720 --> 00:09:34,650
那又如何
So what?

228
00:09:34,960 --> 00:09:37,150
每天都有人失业
People lose their jobs every single day.

229
00:09:37,150 --> 00:09:38,690
是啊  但不会是你这样的人
Yeah, not people like you.

230
00:09:39,110 --> 00:09:40,440
肯定出什么事了
Something's going on.

231
00:09:40,640 --> 00:09:41,560
你为什么被炒
Why'd you get fired?

232
00:09:41,560 --> 00:09:42,680
你是说除了我挑起一场
You mean other than the fact

233
00:09:42,680 --> 00:09:44,200
我赢不了的战争吗
that I picked a fight I couldn't win?

234
00:09:44,270 --> 00:09:45,720
我不关心结果
I don't care how it turned out.

235
00:09:45,720 --> 00:09:48,260
你第一次出场  就打满了十五回合
You went 15 rounds on your first shot.

236
00:09:48,260 --> 00:09:50,810
乔纳森·西德威尔没理由让你走
No way Jonathan Sidwell lets you go after that.

237
00:09:54,820 --> 00:09:56,440
是傅滋曼  对吗
It was Forstman, wasn't it?

238
00:09:56,620 --> 00:09:59,050
只有我同意让不给西德威尔分成
I only got his money if I agreed to cut Sidwell

239
00:09:59,050 --> 00:09:59,920
他才会给我钱
out of the deal.

240
00:10:01,070 --> 00:10:02,650
而西德威尔发现了
And Sidwell found out.

241
00:10:03,270 --> 00:10:04,330
不只是发现
He didn't just find out.

242
00:10:04,330 --> 00:10:05,490
傅滋曼告诉他的
Forstman told him.

243
00:10:06,130 --> 00:10:07,330
那个婊子养的
That son of a bitch.

244
00:10:07,330 --> 00:10:08,430
是啊  还有呢
Yeah, there's more.

245
00:10:08,810 --> 00:10:10,540
那个婊子养的要给我份工作
That son of a bitch has offered me a job.

246
00:10:10,790 --> 00:10:13,170
迈克  你不能接受  你知道的
Mike, you can't do it, and you know it.

247
00:10:13,260 --> 00:10:14,480
我有的选吗
What choice do I have?

248
00:10:15,360 --> 00:10:17,110
我只做了几分钟的投资银行家
I was an investment banker for ten minutes,

249
00:10:17,110 --> 00:10:19,140
还把我唯一接手的案子搞砸了
and I blew the only deal I'm ever gonna get near.

250
00:10:19,340 --> 00:10:21,790
听起来的确像是傅滋曼劝人
Well, that sounds exactly like the kind of bullshit

251
00:10:21,790 --> 00:10:24,300
乖乖听他指挥时会说的屁话
Forstman tells people to wrap them around his finger.

252
00:10:24,300 --> 00:10:26,000
-但不代表那不是事实  -确是事实
- Doesn't mean it's not true. - Yes, it does.

253
00:10:26,000 --> 00:10:28,250
不等到明天  我就能给你安排五个面试
I could get you five interviews before tomorrow.

254
00:10:28,300 --> 00:10:29,480
你打算怎么做到
And how are you going to do that?

255
00:10:29,480 --> 00:10:31,320
打五个电话而已
By making five goddamn phone calls.

256
00:10:31,320 --> 00:10:33,030
他们回复的时候你要怎么说呢
And what are you gonna say when they answer?

257
00:10:34,040 --> 00:10:34,630
你要告诉他们
You gonna tell them

258
00:10:34,630 --> 00:10:36,580
我是个曾为你工作的哈佛法学毕业生吗
I was a Harvard-educated lawyer working for you?

259
00:10:36,580 --> 00:10:37,370
因为如果你这么做
Because you do that,

260
00:10:37,370 --> 00:10:39,130
我还是回去做个骗子好了
I might as well go back to being a fraud.

261
00:10:42,250 --> 00:10:44,270
如果我能让杰西卡让你回来呢
What if I can get Jessica to take you back?

262
00:10:47,600 --> 00:10:49,490
你不如让我父母复活
What if you could bring my parents back to life?

263
00:10:49,490 --> 00:10:50,450
因为这两件事
Because both those things

264
00:10:50,450 --> 00:10:52,130
发生的概率是一样的
have about the same chance of happening.

265
00:10:52,130 --> 00:10:53,130
迈克  我是想帮你  
Mike, I'm trying to help you. 

266
00:10:53,130 --> 00:10:54,260
我非常感谢
And I appreciate that.

267
00:10:54,260 --> 00:10:56,130
但我只有两个推荐人  哈维
But I only have two references, Harvey,

268
00:10:56,130 --> 00:10:57,980
一个不得不为我撒谎的你
you, who has to lie for me,

269
00:10:57,980 --> 00:10:59,420
和一个想杀了我的乔纳森
and Jonathan, who wants to kill me.

270
00:10:59,420 --> 00:11:00,890
-迈克  -哈维  够了
- Mike. - Harvey, it's enough.

271
00:11:02,840 --> 00:11:04,110
虽然你非常想帮我
As much as you want to help me,

272
00:11:04,110 --> 00:11:06,390
但你根本不知道
you have no idea what it is

273
00:11:06,390 --> 00:11:09,610
一个骗子要重新开始意味着什么
to have been a fraud and have to start all over.

274
00:11:10,210 --> 00:11:10,960
我不知道
I don't.

275
00:11:12,900 --> 00:11:14,190
但有人知道
But someone else does.

276
00:11:26,570 --> 00:11:29,860
这不是7611053号员工吗
If it isn't employee number 7611053.

277
00:11:29,860 --> 00:11:31,410
你还记得
You still remember that.

278
00:11:31,410 --> 00:11:32,340
我简历作了假
I lied on my resume.

279
00:11:32,340 --> 00:11:34,050
我的数字天赋可不是假的
I never lied about having a head for numbers.

280
00:11:35,360 --> 00:11:37,680
你发生了那样的事  我还没说过抱歉
I never said how sorry I was for what happened to you.

281
00:11:39,330 --> 00:11:40,660
不用觉得抱歉  迈克
You don't need to be sorry, Mike.

282
00:11:40,660 --> 00:11:42,020
实际上  我应该感谢你
The truth is, I should be thanking you.

283
00:11:43,180 --> 00:11:43,750
什么
What?

284
00:11:44,270 --> 00:11:45,210
你知道我现在做什么工作吗
You know what I do now?

285
00:11:46,110 --> 00:11:48,610
给《梦幻棒球》做统计分析
Statistical analysis for Fantasy Baseball.

286
00:11:49,910 --> 00:11:51,670
太棒了
That's awesome.

287
00:11:51,670 --> 00:11:52,560
好的还在后面呢
You don't know the half of it.

288
00:11:52,560 --> 00:11:54,150
我从前那份好工作
My old, better job,

289
00:11:54,720 --> 00:11:57,290
我坐在办公室里  咀嚼着枯燥的数字
I sat in my office, crunched my numbers,

290
00:11:57,620 --> 00:11:58,720
赚很多钱
made a lot more money,

291
00:11:59,060 --> 00:12:01,500
同楼层的人几乎一个不认识
barely knew the name of one person on my floor.

292
00:12:01,500 --> 00:12:04,090
现在  我的同事都是最好的朋友
Now my best friends are people I work with.

293
00:12:07,860 --> 00:12:10,660
你约我有什么事
Well, why'd you call me?

294
00:12:11,070 --> 00:12:12,280
上次我见到你的时候
The last time I saw you,

295
00:12:12,280 --> 00:12:13,790
你完全不知道以后
you had no idea what you were gonna do

296
00:12:13,790 --> 00:12:14,970
你要做什么
with the rest of your life.

297
00:12:16,800 --> 00:12:18,480
你不得不一切重新开始
You had to completely start over,

298
00:12:20,210 --> 00:12:21,710
而现在看来你做到了
and it looks like you did.

299
00:12:21,710 --> 00:12:24,010
-我想  -想知道我怎么做到的
- I guess I-- - Want to know how.

300
00:12:26,430 --> 00:12:27,610
从"开始"开始
Start by starting.

301
00:12:28,630 --> 00:12:29,580
那是什么意思
What does that mean?

302
00:12:29,580 --> 00:12:30,580
就是  整整六个月
It means, for six months,

303
00:12:30,580 --> 00:12:32,650
我陷入了无限的自怨自艾中
I threw myself a giant pity party,

304
00:12:33,390 --> 00:12:34,290
想我到底要怎样
wondered how the hell

305
00:12:34,290 --> 00:12:36,480
从这困境中走出来
I was gonna get out of the mess I was in.

306
00:12:37,660 --> 00:12:39,300
然后一天我对自己说  够了
And then one day I said, "Enough's enough."

307
00:12:40,010 --> 00:12:42,220
我不再疑问
And instead of asking questions,

308
00:12:42,220 --> 00:12:43,600
开始寻求答案
I started looking for answers.

309
00:12:45,040 --> 00:12:46,730
然后你的答案是梦幻棒球
And you found Fantasy Baseball.

310
00:12:46,730 --> 00:12:48,720
不  我发现你赚多少钱
No, I found out that how much money you make

311
00:12:48,720 --> 00:12:50,930
并不是最重要的
is not the most important thing in the world.

312
00:12:52,330 --> 00:12:55,360
每天与你相处的人  才最重要
Who you spend it with, every day, is.

313
00:12:59,860 --> 00:13:01,300
谢谢  斯坦  谢谢你
Thanks, Stan. I appreciate it.

314
00:13:01,300 --> 00:13:03,120
迈克
Whoa, Mike.

315
00:13:03,120 --> 00:13:05,630
你到底为什么要重新开始
Why exactly is it you need to start over?

316
00:13:06,640 --> 00:13:09,140
说来话长
That's a long story.

317
00:13:09,140 --> 00:13:10,300
我有的是时间
I have time.

318
00:13:11,460 --> 00:13:12,630
改天吧  斯坦
Another day, Stan.

319
00:13:16,170 --> 00:13:17,590
-你要见我  -是的
- You wanted to see me? - Yes.

320
00:13:17,590 --> 00:13:18,710
把你明晚空出来
Clear your schedule tonight.

321
00:13:18,710 --> 00:13:19,860
已经空了  怎么
Done. Why?

322
00:13:20,280 --> 00:13:21,860
杰西卡为奖励我的英雄行为
Jessica offered me anything I want

323
00:13:21,860 --> 00:13:23,290
会给我任何我想要的
as a reward for my heroism,

324
00:13:23,290 --> 00:13:24,870
我们要讨论一下要什么
and we're gonna figure out what that is.

325
00:13:24,870 --> 00:13:26,640
还要讨论什么  冠名合伙人啊
What's to figure out? Named partner.

326
00:13:26,640 --> 00:13:29,180
不是  除了那个什么都行
No, not that. Anything but that.

327
00:13:29,180 --> 00:13:30,520
除了那个  是什么意思
What do you mean, "Anything but that?"

328
00:13:30,520 --> 00:13:32,020
我们只要那个
There isn't anything but that.

329
00:13:32,020 --> 00:13:33,310
你以为我没提出来吗
Oh, you think I didn't ask for it?

330
00:13:33,310 --> 00:13:34,430
那句话从我嘴里溜得
The words were out of my mouth

331
00:13:34,430 --> 00:13:35,850
比十三岁的以斯帖还快
faster than Esther when she was 13.

332
00:13:34,710 --> 00:13:35,710
{\an8}以斯帖  《圣经》中在危急中未经准许面见国王救得全族的王后

333
00:13:35,850 --> 00:13:37,470
路易  我不关心你的骚货姐姐
Louis, I don't care about your slutty sister.

334
00:13:37,470 --> 00:13:38,750
冠名合伙人是你应得的
You deserve named partner.

335
00:13:38,750 --> 00:13:39,990
我不在乎你关不关心
And I don't care that you don't care

336
00:13:39,990 --> 00:13:41,120
因为这不可能发生
because it's not gonna happen.

337
00:13:41,940 --> 00:13:44,510
现在  我们有个机会往上走
Now, we were given a chance to take the high road,

338
00:13:44,960 --> 00:13:46,410
我们就要往上走
and that's exactly what we're gonna do.

339
00:13:48,430 --> 00:13:49,820
如果说我会被你吸引
If I were ever going to be attracted to you,

340
00:13:49,820 --> 00:13:50,700
那一定就是此刻
now would be the time.

341
00:13:51,800 --> 00:13:54,340
那我另外准备一份配得起英雄的需求清单
Instead I'll prepare a list of demands befitting a hero.

342
00:13:54,340 --> 00:13:55,040
好
Good.

343
00:13:55,440 --> 00:13:56,850
还有别再提被我吸引这件事儿了
And don't ever talk about being attracted to me again.

344
00:13:56,850 --> 00:13:57,970
感觉怪怪的
It weirds me out.

345
00:14:05,330 --> 00:14:06,390
不行
The answer's no.

346
00:14:06,390 --> 00:14:07,870
你连我是为什么来的都不知道
You don't even know what I'm here for.

347
00:14:07,870 --> 00:14:09,300
我知道你不是为什么来的
I know what you're not here for.

348
00:14:09,300 --> 00:14:11,340
你不是来告诉我  经过一夜的灵魂灵魂之后
To tell me after a long night of soul-searching,

349
00:14:11,340 --> 00:14:13,990
你决定把吉利斯工业的全部控制权给我
you've decided to give me full control of Gillis Industries.

350
00:14:13,990 --> 00:14:15,070
你说的没错  我的确没打算
You're right. I'm not.

351
00:14:15,070 --> 00:14:17,490
但我来是为了给你这个的全部控制权
But I am here to give you full control of this.

352
00:14:24,830 --> 00:14:26,600
这可不是公开信息
This isn't public information.

353
00:14:26,600 --> 00:14:28,130
24小时之后就是了
It will be in 24 hours.

354
00:14:28,310 --> 00:14:29,770
因此现在给你是合法的
So it's legal to give it to you.

355
00:14:29,770 --> 00:14:31,230
而这个给了我24小时的优势
And it gives me a 24-hour edge

356
00:14:31,230 --> 00:14:33,090
假如我决定就这个信息做出行动的话
if I decide to act on this information.

357
00:14:33,090 --> 00:14:34,960
而从文件中可以看出
Which, as you can see from that filing,

358
00:14:34,960 --> 00:14:37,360
根据这个信息行动  获利是非常可观的
would be a very profitable thing to do.

359
00:14:37,360 --> 00:14:39,600
而我只需雇佣你的律所来报答你吗
And all I have to do in return is use your law firm?

360
00:14:39,600 --> 00:14:41,540
我才不在乎你雇佣哪家律所
I don't care what law firm you use.

361
00:14:41,540 --> 00:14:42,750
我只想你让迈克·罗斯
I just want you to have Mike Ross

362
00:14:42,750 --> 00:14:43,870
来负责这个交易
run point on the deal.

363
00:14:43,870 --> 00:14:45,100
那我们又回到原点了
Then we're back where we started,

364
00:14:45,100 --> 00:14:46,430
你给我滚出我的办公室
and you can get the hell out of my office.

365
00:14:46,430 --> 00:14:48,220
乔纳森  我知道他做了什么
Jonathan, I know what he did,

366
00:14:48,670 --> 00:14:50,320
但他觉得自己别无选择
but he thought he had no choice.

367
00:14:51,830 --> 00:14:54,200
当一个人觉得自己别无选择时
When a person thinks he has no choice

368
00:14:54,200 --> 00:14:56,020
你就可以看清他的真品行了
is when you see his true character.

369
00:14:56,020 --> 00:14:57,360
你现在也是觉得自己别无选择
You think you have no choice

370
00:14:57,360 --> 00:14:59,500
而不是觉得自己在泄愤
other than to be vindictive right now.

371
00:14:59,500 --> 00:15:01,370
这不是泄愤  这是常识
This isn't vindictive. It's common sense.

372
00:15:01,370 --> 00:15:02,460
而且就我家乡的习俗
And where I come from,

373
00:15:02,460 --> 00:15:04,600
我们不会给狐狸再进鸡舍的机会
you don't give the fox another run at the henhouse.

374
00:15:04,600 --> 00:15:06,560
要不是他把你从托尼·扬诺普洛斯的压迫下
You wouldn't have even had a shot at the henhouse

375
00:15:06,560 --> 00:15:09,390
解救出来  你连进鸡舍的机会都没有
If it wasn't for him getting you out from under Tony Gianopolous.

376
00:15:09,390 --> 00:15:11,560
但我给了他在投行界的第一个机会
And I repaid him for that by giving him his first shot

377
00:15:11,560 --> 00:15:12,700
已经报答他了
at investment banking.

378
00:15:12,700 --> 00:15:13,720
就我家乡的习俗
And where I come from,

379
00:15:13,720 --> 00:15:15,640
真正报答一个人的方法
the way you really repay someone

380
00:15:15,640 --> 00:15:17,810
是再给他们该死的一次机会
is by giving them a second goddamn shot.

381
00:15:17,810 --> 00:15:19,920
那你就滚回你家乡去吧
Then go the hell back to where you came from.

382
00:15:21,540 --> 00:15:23,920
还有  假如你真觉得他这么好
And, hey, if you think he's so great,

383
00:15:25,590 --> 00:15:27,090
带他一起回老家去
take him back there with you.

384
00:15:36,640 --> 00:15:39,100
-路易  有时间吗  -没有
- Louis, you have a minute? - Not really.

385
00:15:39,100 --> 00:15:41,170
我正在进行非常重要的礼物挑选呢
I'm in the middle of some very important gift-choosing.

386
00:15:41,780 --> 00:15:42,440
什么
What?

387
00:15:42,440 --> 00:15:43,720
可不是嘛  你当然想知道是怎么回事了
Yeah, wouldn't you like to know?

388
00:15:43,720 --> 00:15:44,920
但你永远也不会知道
But you never will

389
00:15:44,920 --> 00:15:46,530
因为只有当一个人补救了
because a person only gets gifts

390
00:15:46,530 --> 00:15:48,600
杰夫·马龙犯的错误  他才能获得礼物
when they fix the mistakes that Jeff Malone's made.

391
00:15:48,600 --> 00:15:50,660
路易  实际上我就是为这件事来的
Actually, Louis, that's why I'm here.

392
00:15:51,190 --> 00:15:53,510
我想谢谢你找出了
I wanted to thank you for catching that error

393
00:15:53,510 --> 00:15:54,910
韦克斯勒股票上的错误
on the Wexler stock.

394
00:15:55,450 --> 00:15:56,560
你想要谢谢我
You want to thank me?

395
00:15:56,560 --> 00:15:58,540
没错  路易  我是想
Yes, Louis, I do.

396
00:15:58,540 --> 00:16:00,260
我知道你不信任我
Look, I know you don't trust me,

397
00:16:00,260 --> 00:16:02,600
但是你帮我们度过难关
but you got us out of a jam,

398
00:16:02,600 --> 00:16:04,690
而我是来感谢你的  单独来感谢
and I'm here to thank you, man-to-man.

399
00:16:05,160 --> 00:16:05,980
放屁
Bullshit.

400
00:16:05,980 --> 00:16:06,950
你是来亲我屁股的[拍马屁之意]
You're here to kiss my ass

401
00:16:06,950 --> 00:16:07,770
因为你发现
because you found out that 

402
00:16:07,770 --> 00:16:09,250
现在我的地位比你高了
I'm now above you in the pecking order.

403
00:16:09,250 --> 00:16:11,050
路易  我不在乎什么地位高低
Louis, I don't care about the pecking order,

404
00:16:11,050 --> 00:16:13,940
我唯一看到的是你是帮了哈维
and all I found out is that you fixed this thing for Harvey,

405
00:16:13,940 --> 00:16:16,110
而我来感谢你
and I am here to thank you.

406
00:16:16,110 --> 00:16:17,750
我说的不是哈维那儿的地位  你知道的
I'm not talking about Harvey, and you know it.

407
00:16:17,750 --> 00:16:19,590
-不  路易  -别和我装蒜
- No, Louis. - Don't play dumb with me.

408
00:16:19,590 --> 00:16:21,200
我是在说杰西卡·皮尔逊
I'm talking about Jessica Pearson,

409
00:16:21,200 --> 00:16:23,080
那个你真的在亲她屁股的女人
the woman whose ass you've really been kissing,

410
00:16:23,080 --> 00:16:25,130
同样也是亲自来找我
the very same woman who came to me

411
00:16:25,130 --> 00:16:27,880
检查你的工作的女人
and asked me to check your work.

412
00:16:28,340 --> 00:16:30,220
是的  没错
Yeah, uh-huh.

413
00:16:31,200 --> 00:16:32,180
现在  请离开吧
Now, if you'll excuse me,

414
00:16:32,180 --> 00:16:34,350
我有些利皮扎马[名贵马种]得选选
I have some Lipizzaner stallions to look at.

415
00:16:45,090 --> 00:16:47,140
你让路易·利特来检查我的工作
You had Louis Litt check my work?

416
00:16:47,510 --> 00:16:49,170
我还在想我们什么时候会谈到这个呢
I was wondering when we might get into this.

417
00:16:49,170 --> 00:16:51,170
不用再想了  现在就谈
Well, the wondering is over because it's now.

418
00:16:51,170 --> 00:16:52,890
你在做这种事之前
And if you were going to do something like that,

419
00:16:52,890 --> 00:16:54,550
应该先和我商量商量
you should have discussed it with me first

420
00:16:54,550 --> 00:16:56,020
不该背着我做
before going behind my back.

421
00:16:56,020 --> 00:16:57,400
我和你商量过了啊
I did discuss it with you,

422
00:16:57,400 --> 00:16:59,890
你就站在那儿  说你的工作做得很完美
and you stood right there and said your work was perfect

423
00:16:59,890 --> 00:17:01,060
叫我应该信任你
and I should trust you.

424
00:17:01,060 --> 00:17:02,290
看见没  这就是问题所在
You see, that's the problem right there.

425
00:17:02,290 --> 00:17:03,520
你不信任我
You don't trust me.

426
00:17:03,940 --> 00:17:06,660
而你如今就在用我的错误打我的脸
And now you're just rubbing my mistake in my face.

427
00:17:06,980 --> 00:17:09,320
我要是为了打你脸
If the goal was to rub it in your face,

428
00:17:09,320 --> 00:17:10,350
我早就打了
I would have done that already,

429
00:17:10,350 --> 00:17:12,110
我们也就不会有这个谈话了
and we wouldn't be having this conversation.

430
00:17:12,110 --> 00:17:13,000
如果是那样  也许我们应该
In that case, maybe we should

431
00:17:13,000 --> 00:17:16,060
在一段时间内保持交流的专业性
keep our conversations on a professional level for a while.

432
00:17:16,060 --> 00:17:17,710
你才是那个想两者兼得的人
You're the one who wanted to do both.

433
00:17:17,710 --> 00:17:19,300
那也许是我做错了
And maybe I was wrong.

434
00:17:20,110 --> 00:17:21,700
我从没说过我不信任你
I never said I didn't trust you.

435
00:17:23,210 --> 00:17:25,860
我是说我不信任你在韦克斯勒上的工作
I said I didn't trust your work on Wexler.

436
00:17:25,860 --> 00:17:28,380
这就是我俩的不同之处  杰西卡
That's the difference between us, Jessica.

437
00:17:29,080 --> 00:17:31,070
当我说  "信任我"时
You see, when I say, "Trust me,"

438
00:17:31,480 --> 00:17:33,970
我的意思是  信任为你工作的这个男人
I mean trust the man who works for you

439
00:17:33,970 --> 00:17:35,520
也是和你在一起的这个男人
and the man that's with you.

440
00:17:46,220 --> 00:17:47,330
你想见我
You wanted to see me?

441
00:17:48,230 --> 00:17:49,500
你看起来心情不太好啊
You don't seem in a good mood.

442
00:17:49,500 --> 00:17:50,500
的确不好
I'm not.

443
00:17:51,150 --> 00:17:52,330
我们可以晚点再谈
We can talk about it later.

444
00:17:52,330 --> 00:17:53,680
我大老远走过来
I walked all the way down here.

445
00:17:54,030 --> 00:17:54,930
现在就可以谈
We can talk about it now.

446
00:17:55,260 --> 00:17:57,960
我只是想问问你和路易谈得怎样
I was just gonna ask how Louis' talk went.

447
00:17:58,370 --> 00:17:59,390
骗鬼
Bullshit.

448
00:17:59,390 --> 00:18:01,900
这可不值得千里迢迢把我叫过来
That is not an "I have to come talk to you" conversation.

449
00:18:09,020 --> 00:18:10,440
我想把迈克带回来
I want to bring Mike back.

450
00:18:12,560 --> 00:18:14,790
这个话题我永远也不想谈
That is not a conversation I ever want to have.

451
00:18:14,790 --> 00:18:15,500
杰西卡...
Jessica--

452
00:18:15,500 --> 00:18:17,560
哈维  他走的那天
Harvey, I haven't slept better

453
00:18:17,560 --> 00:18:18,990
我睡得最安心
since his last night,

454
00:18:18,990 --> 00:18:21,010
并且之后每晚也一直很安心
except for every night since,

455
00:18:21,010 --> 00:18:22,530
我不要重新提心吊胆
and I'm not going back.

456
00:18:22,530 --> 00:18:24,630
还有如果你真的想知道的话
In case you really were wondering,

457
00:18:24,630 --> 00:18:26,750
路易像个混蛋一样对待我们的感谢
Louis took his thank-you like a dick.

458
00:18:27,480 --> 00:18:29,200
如果没别的事  我要回家了
And if that's all, I'm going home.

459
00:18:46,610 --> 00:18:48,330
你在做饭吗
Are you cooking?

460
00:18:48,690 --> 00:18:49,900
我只做了一个菜
I make one thing,

461
00:18:49,900 --> 00:18:51,730
但我把它做得很完美
and I make it awesome.

462
00:18:52,550 --> 00:18:55,740
迈克  每个男人都觉得自己的意面酱...
Mike, every single guy thinks that his spaghetti sau--

463
00:18:59,790 --> 00:19:02,150
天呐  太棒了
Oh, my god. That's amazing.

464
00:19:02,150 --> 00:19:05,330
不是每个男人都是自己的奶奶养大的
Not every single guy was raised by his grandmother.

465
00:19:06,950 --> 00:19:09,110
现在你快点坐好  老老实实的
Now you sit down, shut up,

466
00:19:09,110 --> 00:19:11,200
然后和我讲讲你今天过得怎样
and tell me about your day.

467
00:19:12,560 --> 00:19:14,370
什么让你心情这么好
What got you in such a good mood?

468
00:19:14,370 --> 00:19:15,610
你知道的  没什么
Oh, you know, nothing.

469
00:19:15,610 --> 00:19:16,470
就是花了一下午
Just spent the afternoon

470
00:19:16,470 --> 00:19:18,610
思考出了我想要什么样的人生
figuring out what I'm gonna do with my life.

471
00:19:18,610 --> 00:19:20,260
听起来还真是个有意义的下午
Well, that sounds like quite the afternoon.

472
00:19:20,260 --> 00:19:21,870
你思考出什么了
What did you figure out?

473
00:19:25,450 --> 00:19:26,830
我思考出了我不想
Well, I figured out I don't want

474
00:19:26,830 --> 00:19:28,450
接受傅滋曼的工作
to take the job with Forstman,

475
00:19:28,450 --> 00:19:32,690
而我也不想在投行干了
and I don't want to be an investment banker.

476
00:19:32,690 --> 00:19:34,350
那你想干什么
So what do you want to be?

477
00:19:35,480 --> 00:19:36,360
我不知道
I don't know.

478
00:19:39,020 --> 00:19:40,340
但我知道我想和你在一起
But I know I want to be with you.

479
00:19:41,830 --> 00:19:43,860
-这话是什么意思  -我想重新开始
- What are you saying? - I want to start over.

480
00:19:45,590 --> 00:19:46,890
我不明白
I don't understand.

481
00:19:46,890 --> 00:19:47,830
瑞秋  当我遇见你时
Rachel, when I met you,

482
00:19:47,830 --> 00:19:49,220
我一无所有
I had nothing in my life

483
00:19:49,220 --> 00:19:50,920
除了当骗子所获得的一些东西
except what came from being a fraud.

484
00:19:52,350 --> 00:19:55,050
而如今除了你之外  我也一无所有
And now I have nothing in it except being with you,

485
00:19:55,050 --> 00:19:56,250
而且就算可以
and I wouldn't go back

486
00:19:56,250 --> 00:19:57,550
我也不会回头  因为...
even if I could because...

487
00:19:57,550 --> 00:20:00,010
-迈克...  -我不在乎我以什么为生
- Mike-- - I don't care what I do for a living.

488
00:20:01,640 --> 00:20:02,770
我是说  我会想出办法的
I mean, I'll figure it out,

489
00:20:02,770 --> 00:20:05,340
但只要拥有你
but as long as I have you,

490
00:20:05,510 --> 00:20:06,810
我就拥有了全世界
I have everything.

491
00:20:09,260 --> 00:20:10,020
瑞秋
Rachel?

492
00:20:11,740 --> 00:20:13,660
怎么回事...我不是想惹你哭啊
What-- I didn't mean to make you cry.

493
00:20:13,660 --> 00:20:15,400
我是想让你开心点
I meant to make you feel better.

494
00:20:15,400 --> 00:20:17,330
不会有事的
Hey, hey, everything's going to be okay.

495
00:20:17,330 --> 00:20:20,310
-不  有事  -瑞秋  怎么了
- No, it's not. - Rachel, what's wrong?

496
00:20:20,310 --> 00:20:21,660
抱歉  稍等一下
I'm sorry. I just need a minute.

497
00:20:21,660 --> 00:20:23,050
-瑞秋  -稍等一下
- Rachel. - I just need a minute.

498
00:20:23,050 --> 00:20:24,960
我在这  跟我说说
Hey. Hey, hey, hey. I'm right here. You can tell me.

499
00:20:24,960 --> 00:20:26,790
-怎么回事  -我不能说
- What's going on? - I can't.

500
00:20:26,790 --> 00:20:28,810
瑞秋  别哭  你能说
Rachel, stop. Yes you can.

501
00:20:28,810 --> 00:20:30,160
不  你不懂...
No, you don't--

502
00:20:30,160 --> 00:20:32,120
-我配不上你  -你胡说些什么啊
- I don't deserve you. - What are you talking about?

503
00:20:32,120 --> 00:20:33,860
-瑞秋  -洛根跟我接吻了
- Rachel, hey-- - Logan and I kissed.

504
00:20:35,830 --> 00:20:36,600
什么
What?

505
00:20:38,190 --> 00:20:39,830
我们本来在谈话
We were just talking,

506
00:20:39,830 --> 00:20:41,300
然后他
and then he--

507
00:20:42,100 --> 00:20:42,770
他怎么了
He what?

508
00:20:43,150 --> 00:20:44,470
迈克  求你了
Mike, please.

509
00:20:45,100 --> 00:20:46,220
我非常抱歉
I am so sorry.

510
00:20:46,630 --> 00:20:47,570
迈克  不  求你了
Mike, no, please.

511
00:20:50,380 --> 00:20:52,800
求你了  那毫无意义
Please, it didn't mean anything.

512
00:20:53,270 --> 00:20:53,910
等等  求你了
Wait. Please.

513
00:20:56,030 --> 00:20:56,980
我
I'm...

514
00:21:15,340 --> 00:21:16,730
输了之后就是这种反应吗
This is how you handle losing?

515
00:21:16,730 --> 00:21:18,630
我来不是为了吉利斯工业的事
I'm not here about Gillis Industries.

516
00:21:18,780 --> 00:21:19,510
你要揍我吗
Ooh, you gonna fight me?

517
00:21:19,510 --> 00:21:21,310
你离瑞秋远点
You stay the hell away from Rachel.

518
00:21:22,660 --> 00:21:23,640
那取决于她
Well, that's up to her.

519
00:21:24,710 --> 00:21:25,770
如果她又来找我
But if she does come back here,

520
00:21:25,770 --> 00:21:27,270
绝对不会是让我离她远点
it won't be to tell me to stay away.

521
00:21:54,670 --> 00:21:56,080
我不知道她怎么跟你说的
I don't know what she told you.

522
00:21:59,060 --> 00:22:01,050
但我们吻了很久
But she let it go on a long time.

523
00:22:05,860 --> 00:22:06,980
她不只是喜欢那个吻
And she didn't just like it.

524
00:22:06,980 --> 00:22:08,520
她简直不能自拔
She loved it.

525
00:22:15,030 --> 00:22:16,090
你跟他说了
You told him.

526
00:22:17,470 --> 00:22:19,230
我都不知道他去哪了
I don't even know where he is.

527
00:22:19,760 --> 00:22:21,140
他去哈维家了
He's at Harvey's.

528
00:22:21,960 --> 00:22:23,060
你怎么知道
How do you know?

529
00:22:23,790 --> 00:22:24,850
你去了哪
Where did you go?

530
00:22:32,370 --> 00:22:33,470
傅滋曼干的
Forstman?

531
00:22:34,090 --> 00:22:35,160
洛根
Logan.

532
00:22:35,390 --> 00:22:36,460
因为吉利斯的事
Gillis.

533
00:22:38,030 --> 00:22:39,090
瑞秋
Rachel.

534
00:22:39,660 --> 00:22:40,900
进来吧
Get the hell in here.

535
00:22:42,780 --> 00:22:44,680
我真不该告诉他
I never should have told him.

536
00:22:45,800 --> 00:22:47,870
瑞秋  现在想那些也没用
Rachel, there's no use thinking that.

537
00:22:51,240 --> 00:22:52,810
他要是不肯原谅我怎么办
What if he doesn't forgive me?

538
00:22:52,820 --> 00:22:54,050
你怎么知道他不肯
You don't know that he won't.

539
00:22:54,050 --> 00:22:55,350
你怎么知道他肯
You don't know that he will.

540
00:22:56,100 --> 00:22:57,240
而且是你说的
And you're the one that said,

541
00:22:57,240 --> 00:22:59,370
"这么做等于是投下了颗炸弹"
"This will bore a hole in his head."

542
00:22:59,370 --> 00:23:00,980
是你说  你需要相信他
And you're the one who said you had to find a way

543
00:23:00,980 --> 00:23:02,800
能承受你说出实情
to trust him with the truth.

544
00:23:03,800 --> 00:23:04,870
他夺门而出  我不能
He walked out. I can't just--

545
00:23:04,870 --> 00:23:05,980
今晚住在这儿
Stay here tonight?

546
00:23:05,980 --> 00:23:07,100
当然可以
Of course you can.

547
00:23:09,890 --> 00:23:11,230
我不想回去
I'm not going back there.

548
00:23:11,230 --> 00:23:12,490
我没说你必须回去
I'm not saying you have to.

549
00:23:12,490 --> 00:23:14,720
我是说你要冷静下来
I'm saying you need to calm down.

550
00:23:14,720 --> 00:23:16,210
如果有人对你说了那样的事
Would you calm down after someone

551
00:23:16,210 --> 00:23:17,680
你能冷静下来吗
stuck it in your face like that?

552
00:23:17,680 --> 00:23:20,470
如果那人只想让我心烦意乱  我会冷静下来的
I would if I knew he was just trying to get in my head.

553
00:23:21,030 --> 00:23:22,700
你怎么知道他说的不是真的
How the hell do you know that's all it is?

554
00:23:22,700 --> 00:23:25,070
因为那王八蛋以前也这么对付过你
Because that piece of shit did it to you before,

555
00:23:25,070 --> 00:23:26,730
我没有阻止他因为我是他的律师
and I let him because I'm his lawyer,

556
00:23:26,730 --> 00:23:28,350
但我不会让他再这么干了
but I'm not gonna let him do it to you now.

557
00:23:28,350 --> 00:23:29,650
但是他已经让我心烦意乱了
Yeah, well, he got in my head.

558
00:23:29,650 --> 00:23:31,960
他让我胡思乱想  我没办法停下来
He put the image in there, and now I can't get it out.

559
00:23:31,960 --> 00:23:33,850
-迈克  -听着  我得知道是不是真的
- Mike-- - Look, I need to know if it's true.

560
00:23:33,850 --> 00:23:35,400
你知道了又有什么好处
And what good is gonna come of that?

561
00:23:38,640 --> 00:23:40,080
我就是要知道
I just need to know.

562
00:23:42,030 --> 00:23:43,810
那只有一个办法才能知道
Then there's only one way to find out.

563
00:23:44,170 --> 00:23:45,900
不过不是今晚
But you're not gonna find out tonight.

564
00:23:47,550 --> 00:23:48,580
来
Here.

565
00:24:05,920 --> 00:24:07,010
迈克
Mike.

566
00:24:07,310 --> 00:24:09,060
天啊  我好担心
Oh, my God, I was so worry-

567
00:24:12,620 --> 00:24:14,620
天啊  你的脸  怎么回事
Oh, my God, your face. What happened?

568
00:24:14,960 --> 00:24:16,240
你知道怎么回事
You know what happened.

569
00:24:17,910 --> 00:24:19,290
你去找洛根了
You went to see Logan.

570
00:24:20,260 --> 00:24:21,960
我要你如实告诉我  你和他之间
I want you to tell me exactly what happened

571
00:24:21,960 --> 00:24:23,090
到底发生了什么
between you and him.

572
00:24:25,400 --> 00:24:27,240
好  我们现在就回家吧
Okay, why don't we just go home right now.

573
00:24:27,240 --> 00:24:28,900
我们可以在家谈
And we can talk about all of it there?

574
00:24:28,900 --> 00:24:30,660
就在这里说
You're gonna tell me what happened right here.

575
00:24:31,090 --> 00:24:32,190
迈克  我
Mike, I--

576
00:24:32,610 --> 00:24:34,200
我不知道还能不能相信你
I need to know that I can trust you,

577
00:24:34,200 --> 00:24:35,900
因为你说那并不意味着什么
because you said that it didn't mean anything,

578
00:24:35,900 --> 00:24:37,290
-但他说  -迈克  求你了
- but he said-- - Mike, please.

579
00:24:37,290 --> 00:24:38,970
那到底意味着什么吗
Did it mean something or not?

580
00:24:40,280 --> 00:24:42,340
在当时确实有些许意味  但是现在
It meant something when it happened, but now--

581
00:24:42,340 --> 00:24:44,480
听我说
Okay, look. Okay.

582
00:24:44,700 --> 00:24:45,870
我犯了个大错
I made a huge mistake,

583
00:24:45,870 --> 00:24:46,970
你刚刚说你是否能相信我
But you just asked if you could trust me--

584
00:24:46,970 --> 00:24:48,040
相信你
Trust you?

585
00:24:48,920 --> 00:24:50,640
你瞒了我整整一周
You didn't tell me about this for a week,

586
00:24:50,640 --> 00:24:52,670
而当你终于坦白时  你还撒了谎
and then when you finally did, you lied.

587
00:24:52,670 --> 00:24:53,490
我没撒谎
I didn't lie.

588
00:24:53,490 --> 00:24:55,220
我还没来得及说出事情原委  你就夺门而出了
You walked out before I could tell you the whole story.

589
00:24:55,220 --> 00:24:56,070
原委
The whole story?

590
00:24:56,070 --> 00:24:57,970
你根本没打算告诉我原委
There's no way you were going to tell me that whole story.

591
00:24:57,970 --> 00:25:01,030
-迈克  求你了  -他说你简直不能自拔
- Mike, please. - He said that you loved it!

592
00:25:08,320 --> 00:25:09,510
我昨天说  只要有你
And when I said that it didn't matter

593
00:25:09,510 --> 00:25:11,650
下一步做什么都无关紧要
what I'd do next because I have you?

594
00:25:14,170 --> 00:25:15,220
我错了
I was wrong.

595
00:25:16,250 --> 00:25:17,280
因为我们完了
Because we're done.

596
00:25:31,230 --> 00:25:33,030
好忙啊
Ooh, it's busy.

597
00:25:33,030 --> 00:25:36,000
听着瑞秋  等你忙完这个  能不能
Okay, listen, Rachel. When you are done can you just--

598
00:25:36,010 --> 00:25:37,340
我去  你没事吧
Holy shit, are you?

599
00:25:37,350 --> 00:25:38,910
不  我有事
No, I'm not.

600
00:25:39,300 --> 00:25:41,480
如果哈维欺负你了  我会...
So help me, if Harvey mistreated you, I will--

601
00:25:41,480 --> 00:25:43,960
不是哈维  路易  是迈克
It wasn't Harvey, Louis. It's Mike.

602
00:25:43,960 --> 00:25:45,580
那个遭雷劈的  他在哪
That son of a bitch. Where is he?

603
00:25:45,580 --> 00:25:48,140
-我非要...  -不怪他  怪我
- Because I'll-- - It wasn't him. It was me.

604
00:25:50,600 --> 00:25:51,600
瑞秋
Rachel.

605
00:25:51,600 --> 00:25:55,040
听着  我知道他曾在希拉的事上伤害过你
Look, I know that he hurt you with Sheila,

606
00:25:55,040 --> 00:25:56,430
但是我爱他
But I love him,

607
00:25:57,750 --> 00:25:58,630
而我却失去了他
and I lost him.

608
00:25:58,640 --> 00:26:00,210
我现在不知所措了
And I don't really know what to do.

609
00:26:00,210 --> 00:26:02,560
听我说
Oh, come on, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,

610
00:26:02,560 --> 00:26:04,470
听我说  好吗
Listen to me right now, okay?

611
00:26:05,700 --> 00:26:07,480
不管我对迈克有什么看法
Whatever I may think of Mike,

612
00:26:07,480 --> 00:26:09,320
我知道他爱你
I have no doubt that he loves you.

613
00:26:10,360 --> 00:26:13,610
只要两个人相爱
And when two people love each other,

614
00:26:13,610 --> 00:26:16,080
就没有什么克服不了的
no problem is insurmountable.

615
00:26:17,500 --> 00:26:18,790
都是胡说
That's bullshit.

616
00:26:20,370 --> 00:26:22,320
你更应该明白这是胡说
And you of all people know it.

617
00:26:22,730 --> 00:26:23,790
什么
What?

618
00:26:24,000 --> 00:26:25,640
你和希拉也很相爱
You and Sheila loved each other,

619
00:26:25,640 --> 00:26:27,910
可是即使你们俩
and you still broke up,

620
00:26:27,910 --> 00:26:31,780
都没有做错什么  你们还是分手了
even though neither of you had done anything wrong.

621
00:26:32,730 --> 00:26:34,900
-那不一样  -你有没有在听
- That's different. - Did you hear me?

622
00:26:35,840 --> 00:26:37,620
是我错了
I did something wrong.

623
00:26:38,200 --> 00:26:40,120
现在他不再相信我了
And now he doesn't trust me,

624
00:26:40,120 --> 00:26:44,260
我也没法让他相信或者原谅我
and I can't make him trust me or forgive me.

625
00:26:44,480 --> 00:26:47,580
所以我有多爱他都不重要了  好吗
So it doesn't matter how much I love him, okay?

626
00:26:47,580 --> 00:26:48,670
因为...
Because...

627
00:26:49,180 --> 00:26:50,770
好了  听着
Okay, all right, listen.

628
00:26:50,770 --> 00:26:53,490
瑞秋  你的生活还在继续
Rachel, you have so much going for you.

629
00:26:53,490 --> 00:26:54,990
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.

630
00:26:56,930 --> 00:26:58,780
失去了那个我愿意共度此生的人
And what good is any of it

631
00:26:58,860 --> 00:27:01,620
有没有事又有什么意义
if I don't have the one person I want to share it with?

632
00:27:14,890 --> 00:27:16,220
洛根  你来这干嘛
Logan, what are you doing here?

633
00:27:16,220 --> 00:27:19,990
你要我别告诉迈克  可你自己却说了
You told Mike after you explicitly told me not to.

634
00:27:20,570 --> 00:27:23,150
我不需要跟你解释什么
I don't have to explain myself to you.

635
00:27:24,100 --> 00:27:26,710
-真的  -这我真没想..
- Really? - I didn't mean for it--

636
00:27:26,710 --> 00:27:28,460
你想或者不想什么都不重要
It doesn't matter what you did or didn't mean to happen.

637
00:27:28,460 --> 00:27:29,510
发生就是发生了
It happened,

638
00:27:29,670 --> 00:27:31,110
我也知道为什么会发生
and I know why it did.

639
00:27:31,820 --> 00:27:33,940
-你在说什  -你告诉他
- What are you talk-- - You told him because

640
00:27:35,690 --> 00:27:37,260
是因为内心深处  你想跟我在一起
deep down inside, you want to be with me,

641
00:27:37,260 --> 00:27:38,730
你知道告诉他之后就能跟我在一起了
and you knew this would make it happen.

642
00:27:38,730 --> 00:27:39,930
胡说八道
That is bullshit.

643
00:27:39,930 --> 00:27:40,940
真的吗
Really?

644
00:27:40,940 --> 00:27:43,480
那可是我跟艾莉森坦白的时候
Because that is exactly what you said to me

645
00:27:43,480 --> 00:27:45,050
你跟我说的原话
when I told Allison about us.

646
00:27:45,050 --> 00:27:47,380
-那跟这没关系  -瑞秋
- That has nothing to do with this. - Rachel.

647
00:27:47,380 --> 00:27:48,880
既然你来的目的是
And since you obviously came here

648
00:27:48,880 --> 00:27:50,390
想知道我们俩现在的关系
to find out where it is we stand,

649
00:27:50,390 --> 00:27:51,660
让我告诉你
Let me tell you.

650
00:27:52,380 --> 00:27:53,680
没有我们可言
There is no us.

651
00:27:53,930 --> 00:27:55,660
永远都不会有
There will never be an us.

652
00:27:56,180 --> 00:27:58,920
无论我和迈克之间发生了什么
And no matter what happens between me and Mike,

653
00:27:59,760 --> 00:28:00,920
这是我和你
this is the last time

654
00:28:00,930 --> 00:28:03,600
最后一次对话
that you and I are ever gonna have a conversation again.

655
00:28:03,900 --> 00:28:05,820
-你是我的律师  -不再是了  洛根
- You're my lawyer. - Not anymore, Logan.

656
00:28:05,820 --> 00:28:07,960
所以无论你是不是真的来和哈维会面的
So whatever real or fake meeting you have with Harvey,

657
00:28:07,960 --> 00:28:09,270
你现在可以去了
You can go to it now,

658
00:28:09,270 --> 00:28:10,470
但我是不会参加的
but I won't be in it

659
00:28:11,030 --> 00:28:13,100
以后的所有会面也是一样
or any other meeting you have here in the future

660
00:28:13,100 --> 00:28:14,370
因为我们结束了
because we're done.

661
00:28:23,180 --> 00:28:25,070
路易  你来得正好
Louis, glad you're here.

662
00:28:25,140 --> 00:28:27,060
我刚和查尔斯·傅滋曼通过电话
I just got off the phone with Charles Forstman.

663
00:28:27,060 --> 00:28:29,920
他想再确认一下合同的细节
He wants to cross the "t"s, dot the "i"s,

664
00:28:29,930 --> 00:28:31,700
完成交易  我也是这么想的
and be done with this deal, and so do I.

665
00:28:31,710 --> 00:28:32,970
相信我  杰西卡  没人比我更想
Oh, believe me, Jessica. Nobody wants to be done 

666
00:28:32,970 --> 00:28:34,160
早点跟他结束
with that man more than me.

667
00:28:34,160 --> 00:28:36,340
我一个小时后就去找他
I'm actually heading over there in an hour,

668
00:28:36,350 --> 00:28:37,810
但在此之前  我想告诉你
but before I do, I just wanted to tell you

669
00:28:37,810 --> 00:28:41,330
我终于想好要什么奖励了
that I finally figured out what I want as my reward.

670
00:28:42,090 --> 00:28:43,160
是什么呢
And what is that?

671
00:28:45,330 --> 00:28:46,900
我想修改我的合同
I want to amend my contract

672
00:28:46,900 --> 00:28:49,510
允许我在需要的时候远程办公
to allow for telecommuting whenever I deem appropriate

673
00:28:49,510 --> 00:28:53,090
以及每年多一个月的假期供我安排
and a month's more vacation every year to be used at my discretion.

674
00:28:54,360 --> 00:28:55,140
还有什么吗
Anything else?

675
00:28:55,140 --> 00:28:56,130
这些条款要写进合同
I want it in writing,

676
00:28:56,130 --> 00:28:57,500
以及在此期间
and I want my partnership protected

677
00:28:57,510 --> 00:28:59,630
保障我的合伙人关系
for as long as this situation persists.

678
00:29:01,030 --> 00:29:02,090
好的
Okay.

679
00:29:02,320 --> 00:29:03,500
在我同意这些要求之前
Before I give you what you're asking--

680
00:29:03,500 --> 00:29:05,280
杰西卡  你说过我可以提任何要求
Jessica, you said I could have whatever I want.

681
00:29:05,280 --> 00:29:06,490
你别想说服我放弃
You're not gonna talk me out of this.

682
00:29:06,490 --> 00:29:08,210
我没想说服你放弃任何东西
I'm not trying to talk you out of anything.

683
00:29:08,210 --> 00:29:10,290
我只是想说
I just want to say that the fact

684
00:29:10,290 --> 00:29:12,420
你现在不能成为冠名合伙人
that name partner isn't happening now

685
00:29:12,590 --> 00:29:14,530
不代表以后不会
doesn't mean it never will,

686
00:29:14,800 --> 00:29:18,400
我不想你因为失去信念而认输
and I'd hate to see you throw in the towel because you've lost faith.

687
00:29:19,310 --> 00:29:20,960
我现在只想
Yeah, well, the only thing I'm throwing

688
00:29:20,960 --> 00:29:23,800
赢得希拉的心
is my hat in the ring for Sheila's heart.

689
00:29:24,220 --> 00:29:25,540
我不明白
I don't understand.

690
00:29:25,890 --> 00:29:26,910
我爱她
I love her.

691
00:29:28,790 --> 00:29:30,140
我很想她
And I miss her.

692
00:29:32,020 --> 00:29:34,910
我想要赢回她的心
And I want to try to win her back,

693
00:29:34,910 --> 00:29:38,720
我需要这些条件的帮助
and I need these things to make that happen.

694
00:29:41,290 --> 00:29:42,530
没问题
Then you have them.

695
00:29:50,210 --> 00:29:52,020
-瑞秋  你还好吗  -我不知道
- Rachel, are you okay? - I don't know.

696
00:29:52,310 --> 00:29:53,570
-你要去哪儿  -我不知道
- Where are you going? - I don't know.

697
00:29:53,570 --> 00:29:55,170
我就是没法儿呆在这儿  我也不能回家
I just can't be here, and I can't be at home.

698
00:29:55,170 --> 00:29:56,360
我无处可去
I can't be anywhere.

699
00:29:57,330 --> 00:29:58,400
去见他
Go see him.

700
00:29:58,920 --> 00:30:00,700
我不知道他在哪儿
I don't even know where he is.

701
00:30:03,250 --> 00:30:04,350
不  你知道的
Yes, you do.

702
00:30:04,350 --> 00:30:05,550
我见过他了
I did see him.

703
00:30:05,550 --> 00:30:08,150
他来过  事情变得一团糟
He came here, and everything went to shit.

704
00:30:08,150 --> 00:30:10,730
我想要解释  但他不肯听
And I tried to explain, and he wouldn't listen.

705
00:30:11,850 --> 00:30:13,380
他说我们之间结束了
And then he said we're just done.

706
00:30:13,900 --> 00:30:16,070
-瑞秋  -抱歉  唐娜
- Rachel. - I'm sorry, Donna.

707
00:30:27,720 --> 00:30:29,220
如果是迈克的事  我很忙
If it's about Mike, I'm busy.

708
00:30:29,220 --> 00:30:31,570
哈维  我知道你对不忠的心结
Harvey, I know about your issues with infidelity,

709
00:30:31,570 --> 00:30:32,360
但是
but--

710
00:30:32,360 --> 00:30:33,890
唐娜  别说了
Donna, stop right there.

711
00:30:33,890 --> 00:30:35,370
不  我要说
No, I'm not gonna stop

712
00:30:35,370 --> 00:30:37,550
你需要和迈克谈谈瑞秋的事
because you need to go talk to Mike about Rachel.

713
00:30:37,560 --> 00:30:40,840
-需要  -是的  需要
- Need. - Yes, need.

714
00:30:41,290 --> 00:30:43,650
你听清楚了  我只说一遍
Listen to me because I'm only gonna say this once.

715
00:30:43,650 --> 00:30:45,660
她做了什么是他们之间的事
What she did is between the two of them,

716
00:30:45,660 --> 00:30:47,290
我不想以任何方式
and I'm not gonna get in the middle of it

717
00:30:47,290 --> 00:30:49,790
掺和进去  即使我介入了
one way or another, but if I did,

718
00:30:49,940 --> 00:30:52,570
也肯定不会帮她说话
it sure as shit wouldn't be to defend her.

719
00:30:53,820 --> 00:30:55,300
哈维  你对感情的无知
Harvey, your lack of emotional awareness

720
00:30:55,300 --> 00:30:56,460
总能让我很震惊
never ceases to amaze me.

721
00:30:56,460 --> 00:30:57,560
你说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?

722
00:30:57,560 --> 00:30:59,860
我不是让你为了瑞秋这么做
I'm not asking you to do this for Rachel.

723
00:30:59,890 --> 00:31:01,750
是为了迈克
I'm asking you to do this for Mike.

724
00:31:01,900 --> 00:31:03,590
我说过了  我很忙
Like I said, I'm busy.

725
00:31:11,210 --> 00:31:12,250
我能进来吗
May I?

726
00:31:12,800 --> 00:31:14,600
你什么时候需要得到允许了
Since when do you need permission?

727
00:31:14,820 --> 00:31:16,540
进门  不需要
To come in, I don't.

728
00:31:16,540 --> 00:31:18,330
可不是吗
No, you don't.

729
00:31:18,330 --> 00:31:21,740
等你能接受了我再来
And I'll come back when you're in a more receptive mood.

730
00:31:23,620 --> 00:31:25,770
我要接受什么呢
What exactly am I being receptive to?

731
00:31:30,900 --> 00:31:32,530
你
You are 

732
00:31:33,080 --> 00:31:35,970
并不只是这间律所的一个合伙人
not just any partner in this firm.

733
00:31:37,230 --> 00:31:38,940
你还是我的情侣
You are the man I am involved with,

734
00:31:38,940 --> 00:31:43,770
从现在开始我会考虑这一点的
and I need to take that into consideration from now on.

735
00:31:44,020 --> 00:31:46,210
你听着像是为了控制损失
You sound like you're saying that as damage control.

736
00:31:46,210 --> 00:31:48,440
我是出于真心才这么说的
I'm saying it because I mean it.

737
00:31:48,440 --> 00:31:49,370
那为什么你听上去
Then why does it still sound 

738
00:31:49,370 --> 00:31:51,380
还是像在和员工讲话
like you're talking to your employee?

739
00:31:52,710 --> 00:31:55,040
因为对我来说
Because it's hard for me

740
00:31:55,930 --> 00:31:57,530
要说出我不希望
to say that I don't want to lose you

741
00:31:57,530 --> 00:31:59,790
因为工作上的蠢事失去你很困难
over some stupid work bullshit.

742
00:32:03,410 --> 00:32:05,260
这才是我要的
Now, that's what I'm talkin' about.

743
00:32:08,900 --> 00:32:10,670
所以你就是想为难我
So you just wanted to make it hard for me.

744
00:32:10,680 --> 00:32:12,670
我只是想听你说出口
I just wanted to hear you say it.

745
00:32:13,160 --> 00:32:15,250
为不为难是你的事
It being hard for you is on you.

746
00:32:17,370 --> 00:32:18,710
那我们之间没问题了吧
So we're good.

747
00:32:19,370 --> 00:32:21,250
是的  没问题了
Oh, yeah. We're good.

748
00:32:22,830 --> 00:32:23,870
好吧
All right.

749
00:32:25,290 --> 00:32:26,740
杰西卡  还有件事
Jessica, one more thing.

750
00:32:27,120 --> 00:32:30,370
如果你不想因为工作上的蠢事失去我
If you don't want to lose me over some stupid work bullshit,

751
00:32:31,540 --> 00:32:34,270
就请不要做这种蠢事
then please don't do stupid work bullshit.

752
00:32:39,030 --> 00:32:40,480
你被开除了
You're fired.

753
00:32:46,750 --> 00:32:48,010
基本条件
"Simple term condition,"

754
00:32:48,020 --> 00:32:49,780
巴拉巴拉  巴拉巴拉
Blah-blah, blah-blah.

755
00:32:52,460 --> 00:32:53,390
是啊  都写在那儿了
Yeah, it's all there.

756
00:32:53,390 --> 00:32:55,820
你只要在箭头处签字就可以了
You just need to sign by the arrows.

757
00:32:57,790 --> 00:32:59,700
再跟我过一遍
Walk me through this one more time.

758
00:33:00,810 --> 00:33:02,110
合同上说桑德斯集团
It says Sanders International

759
00:33:02,110 --> 00:33:04,910
同意支付你上述金额
agrees to pay you the aforementioned amount.

760
00:33:05,110 --> 00:33:06,740
通过瑞士账户还是开曼群岛账户
Through a Swiss account or the Caymans?

761
00:33:06,740 --> 00:33:08,190
按你的要求  都有
Both, per your instructions.

762
00:33:08,190 --> 00:33:09,200
我们能结束了吗
Now are we done?

763
00:33:10,270 --> 00:33:13,530
你为了替我避税下了不少功夫
You went to a lot of trouble to shelter some money for me.

764
00:33:14,360 --> 00:33:15,970
因为你强迫我这么做的
Because you forced me to.

765
00:33:16,270 --> 00:33:17,920
不禁使我担心
Which got me to wondering.

766
00:33:19,150 --> 00:33:21,150
怎么能保证你离开这里后
what's to keep you from walking out of here,

767
00:33:21,150 --> 00:33:22,770
不会良心发现
growing a conscience,

768
00:33:22,770 --> 00:33:25,260
告诉别人我们之间的小秘密呢
and telling someone about our little arrangement?

769
00:33:25,260 --> 00:33:27,160
因为如果我这么做  自己也脱不了责任
Because if I do, I'll be admitting to my own guilt,

770
00:33:27,160 --> 00:33:28,350
你清楚得很
which you damn well know.

771
00:33:28,350 --> 00:33:32,760
没错  但你具体有什么责任呢
Right, but what exactly are you guilty of?

772
00:33:34,490 --> 00:33:35,320
这是什么
What is this?

773
00:33:35,320 --> 00:33:38,520
这是你完成这笔交易的酬金
That's your fee for putting this deal together.

774
00:33:39,770 --> 00:33:40,930
我不想要酬金
I don't want a fee.

775
00:33:40,930 --> 00:33:42,940
这正是你得收下的原因
That's exactly why you're gonna take it.

776
00:33:44,070 --> 00:33:44,700
你这个混蛋
Son of a bitch.

777
00:33:44,700 --> 00:33:46,450
你让我来不是为了让你签字
You didn't bring me here for you to sign on the arrows.

778
00:33:46,450 --> 00:33:48,550
而是为了让我签字
You brought me here for me to sign on the arrows.

779
00:33:48,660 --> 00:33:49,910
没错
Yep.

780
00:33:49,910 --> 00:33:51,580
我不关心钱进了你的账户后
And I don't give a shit what you do with the money

781
00:33:51,580 --> 00:33:52,730
你会怎么用
after it goes into your account,

782
00:33:52,730 --> 00:33:54,210
钱进去了就行
But it's going in there.

783
00:33:54,440 --> 00:33:55,550
我不会签字的
I won't.

784
00:33:55,550 --> 00:33:56,870
随你便
It's up to you.

785
00:33:56,960 --> 00:33:58,920
你可以选择完成这笔交易
Now you can either close this deal

786
00:33:59,470 --> 00:34:00,890
或者再次在日记本里
or go back to writing in your diary

787
00:34:00,890 --> 00:34:03,570
写下哈维·斯佩克特觉得你是个废物
about what a loser Harvey Specter thinks you are.

788
00:34:07,100 --> 00:34:08,540
签字吧  伙计
Sign it, pal.

789
00:34:53,790 --> 00:34:55,220
迈克  你在这里干嘛
Mike, what are you doing here?

790
00:34:55,530 --> 00:34:56,990
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?

791
00:34:57,750 --> 00:35:00,510
算了  无所谓
You know what? Doesn't matter.

792
00:35:01,380 --> 00:35:02,750
我来接受工作邀请的
I'm here to take a job.

793
00:35:02,750 --> 00:35:04,090
等等  什么
Wait. What?

794
00:35:04,370 --> 00:35:06,010
不  你不能这么做
No, you can't do that.

795
00:35:06,770 --> 00:35:09,100
-跟你有什么关系  -迈克  听我说
- What do you care? - Mike, listen to me.

796
00:35:09,890 --> 00:35:11,750
我知道我因为希拉的事生你气
I know I'm mad at you about Sheila,

797
00:35:12,760 --> 00:35:14,200
但我现在不在乎了
but I don't care about that right now.

798
00:35:14,200 --> 00:35:16,270
你不能和那个人一起工作
You cannot take a job with that man.

799
00:35:16,360 --> 00:35:18,620
我没有其他选择  路易
I don't have any other options, Louis.

800
00:35:18,680 --> 00:35:19,750
而我落到这步田地
And I'm in this position

801
00:35:19,750 --> 00:35:21,210
就是因为你给了那个人一笔反收购支付金
because you paid that man greenmail

802
00:35:21,210 --> 00:35:22,770
让他放弃和我的交易
to walk away from my deal in the first place.

803
00:35:22,770 --> 00:35:24,160
相信我  我希望我没那么做
Believe me, I wish I hadn't.

804
00:35:24,160 --> 00:35:25,880
那又是什么意思
What the hell is that supposed to mean?

805
00:35:25,880 --> 00:35:27,950
-迈克  -算了
- Mike-- - You know what?

806
00:35:28,000 --> 00:35:30,470
无所谓了了  都无所谓了
Doesn't matter. None of it matters.

807
00:35:30,470 --> 00:35:32,280
这是因为瑞秋  对吗
This is about Rachel, isn't it?

808
00:35:33,480 --> 00:35:34,980
她告诉我她伤了你的心
She told me she hurt you.

809
00:35:36,020 --> 00:35:38,080
相信我  我能理解
Believe me, I understand,

810
00:35:38,080 --> 00:35:40,190
但是你不能因为那件事就这么做
but you cannot do this because of that.

811
00:35:40,190 --> 00:35:41,370
这是一份工作  路易  好吗
This is a job, Louis, all right?

812
00:35:41,370 --> 00:35:43,350
-我又不是要去抢银行  -这不是工作
- I'm not robbing a bank. - it's not a job!

813
00:35:43,350 --> 00:35:44,790
这是一个决定
It's a decision,

814
00:35:44,790 --> 00:35:46,390
而我不会让你做这个决定的
and I'm not gonna let you make it.

815
00:35:46,390 --> 00:35:47,430
是吗
Yeah?

816
00:35:47,430 --> 00:35:49,120
你又能做什么
What are you gonna do about it?

817
00:35:49,910 --> 00:35:51,350
任何我需要做的
Anything I have to.

818
00:35:59,500 --> 00:36:00,420
你想见我
You want to see me?

819
00:36:00,420 --> 00:36:02,030
我以为是你想见我
I thought you wanted to see me.

820
00:36:02,150 --> 00:36:03,760
是我想见你们两个
I wanted to see you both.

821
00:36:04,430 --> 00:36:05,480
路易
Louis.

822
00:36:05,480 --> 00:36:07,850
这是关于你为了希拉所提的条件吗
Is this about implementing your request with Sheila?

823
00:36:07,850 --> 00:36:09,660
这是关于收回我为了希拉所提的条件
It's about retracting my request with Sheila.

824
00:36:09,660 --> 00:36:10,830
发生了什么事  我以为
What happened? I thought--

825
00:36:10,830 --> 00:36:12,210
什么事也没发生
Nothing happened.

826
00:36:12,270 --> 00:36:14,500
我重新雇佣了迈克·罗斯
I hired Mike Ross back at the firm.

827
00:36:15,080 --> 00:36:16,050
什么
What?

828
00:36:16,050 --> 00:36:17,290
如果希拉和我命中注定该在一起
If Sheila and I are meant to be,

829
00:36:17,290 --> 00:36:18,290
我们会在一起的
we'll make that work,

830
00:36:18,290 --> 00:36:20,570
但是迈克正要做一件
but Mike was gonna do something

831
00:36:20,570 --> 00:36:23,090
我不能让他做的事情
that I could not let him do.

832
00:36:23,090 --> 00:36:26,150
所以我把我的奖励用在了他身上
So I'm using my reward on him.

833
00:36:26,180 --> 00:36:28,130
-好的  路易  -这个选择非常高尚
- Okay, Lewis, I-- - It's a great choice.

834
00:36:28,130 --> 00:36:29,530
我为你感到自豪
I'm proud of you.

835
00:36:29,820 --> 00:36:31,930
请让我和杰西卡单独谈几句
Why don't you give me a minute with Jessica

836
00:36:32,220 --> 00:36:33,740
看看能不能给他找间办公室
and see if we can't get him an office?

837
00:36:33,740 --> 00:36:35,640
谢谢  哈维  谢谢你们
Thank you, Harvey. Thank you both.

838
00:36:37,740 --> 00:36:39,010
就这些了吗
Is that it?

839
00:36:39,340 --> 00:36:40,940
我还是希望能在犹太历新年的时候放假
I'd still like to be able to take Rosh Hashanah off,

840
00:36:40,940 --> 00:36:42,230
如果可以的话
if that's okay.

841
00:36:43,340 --> 00:36:45,120
我想这可以安排
I think we can work something out.

842
00:36:48,820 --> 00:36:50,070
-不行  -杰西卡
- No way. - Jessica.

843
00:36:50,070 --> 00:36:52,030
迈克·罗斯不能回来
Mike Ross is not coming back to this firm.

844
00:36:52,030 --> 00:36:53,670
你听到路易的话  他已经把工作给他了
You heard Louis. He already gave him the job.

845
00:36:53,670 --> 00:36:55,290
他还可以收回来
He can un-give him the job.

846
00:36:55,350 --> 00:36:56,740
已经太晚了  你心里明白
It's too late for that, and you know it.

847
00:36:56,740 --> 00:36:59,330
你突然跳出来说这个选择非常高尚
Well, it damn sure didn't help when you jumped on in there

848
00:36:59,330 --> 00:37:00,550
显然没有帮上忙
and told him it was a great choice.

849
00:37:00,550 --> 00:37:01,590
这本来就是个高尚的选择
It was a great choice,

850
00:37:01,590 --> 00:37:03,930
如果我没有跳出来而是让你说了你想说的
and if I hadn't jumped in and let you speak your mind,

851
00:37:03,930 --> 00:37:05,280
你知道他会听到什么吗
you know what he would have heard?

852
00:37:05,280 --> 00:37:06,770
他会听出迈克·罗斯有问题
Something's wrong with Mike Ross.

853
00:37:06,770 --> 00:37:07,750
你不知道会是那样的
You don't know that.

854
00:37:07,750 --> 00:37:08,820
我知道  你也知道
Yes, I do, and so do you.

855
00:37:08,820 --> 00:37:10,480
我们说的可是路易
This is Louis we're talking about.

856
00:37:10,480 --> 00:37:12,170
而且你已经拒绝了他的第一个要求
And you rejected his first request.

857
00:37:12,170 --> 00:37:13,780
因为那是不合理的
Because it was unreasonable.

858
00:37:13,780 --> 00:37:15,310
而你能说服他那不合理的唯一办法
And the only way you're gonna convince him

859
00:37:15,310 --> 00:37:18,030
是告诉他为什么
that this is unreasonable is to tell him why.

860
00:37:18,030 --> 00:37:18,720
哈维
Harvey--

861
00:37:18,720 --> 00:37:21,320
杰西卡  要想让他收回工作邀约
Jessica, the only way to make him take that offer back

862
00:37:21,320 --> 00:37:22,410
只能强迫他
is to force him to do it

863
00:37:22,410 --> 00:37:25,050
因为他会一遍又一遍地问你为什么
Because he's gonna ask you why again and again.

864
00:37:25,050 --> 00:37:26,460
而且不管你回答什么
And no matter what you say,

865
00:37:26,460 --> 00:37:27,970
他都会知道你在胡说八道
he's gonna know you're full of shit.

866
00:37:27,970 --> 00:37:29,800
你觉得他会花多长时间
And then how long do you think it's gonna take him

867
00:37:29,800 --> 00:37:31,660
想起来去年
to remember that last year,

868
00:37:31,660 --> 00:37:34,080
他怀疑过迈克没有上过哈佛
he wondered if Mike even went to Harvard.

869
00:37:36,920 --> 00:37:40,020
你至少可以假装不那么开心
You could at least pretend to hide how happy you are.

870
00:37:40,750 --> 00:37:42,410
我确实很开心
I may be happy about it,

871
00:37:42,410 --> 00:37:43,830
但你知道我是对的
but you know I'm right.

872
00:37:43,830 --> 00:37:45,400
而事实是
And the truth is,

873
00:37:45,890 --> 00:37:48,310
我本来就不该让他走
I never should have let him go in the first place.

874
00:37:57,710 --> 00:37:59,740
你看起来比我上次见你的时候好多了
You look a lot better than the last time I saw you.

875
00:37:59,740 --> 00:38:00,910
你没听说吗
Well, didn't you hear?

876
00:38:00,910 --> 00:38:02,020
我找到了份新工作
I got a new job.

877
00:38:02,020 --> 00:38:03,580
我听说了
Oh, I heard.

878
00:38:04,200 --> 00:38:05,610
你想说什么  哈维
What're you getting at there, Harvey?

879
00:38:05,610 --> 00:38:07,230
我想说什么
What am I getting at?

880
00:38:07,430 --> 00:38:08,450
路易雇了你
Louis hires you.

881
00:38:08,450 --> 00:38:09,630
你没问我的意见
You don't run it by me.

882
00:38:09,630 --> 00:38:11,840
你甚至都没和我说一声
You don't even tell me it's happening.

883
00:38:11,950 --> 00:38:15,060
我对你而言只是用来借宿的
All I am anymore to you is a clean set of sheets.

884
00:38:15,060 --> 00:38:17,050
说起来你该换条好点的床单了
Speaking of which, you might want to up the thread count.

885
00:38:17,050 --> 00:38:18,940
而且问你的意见
And run it by you?

886
00:38:18,940 --> 00:38:20,850
你昨天都求着我回来了
You were practically begging me to come back yesterday.

887
00:38:20,850 --> 00:38:22,060
我才没有求
I didn't beg shit.

888
00:38:22,060 --> 00:38:23,410
我只是提了一个方案
I posited a theory.

889
00:38:23,410 --> 00:38:24,890
我们都知道那不可能
We both knew it was never gonna happen.

890
00:38:24,890 --> 00:38:26,380
我只是想让你好受点
I was just trying to make you feel better.

891
00:38:26,380 --> 00:38:28,910
看来路易做到你做不到的了
I guess it took Louis to do what you couldn't do.

892
00:38:29,070 --> 00:38:31,340
雇一个不合格的骗子
Hire an unqualified fraud?

893
00:38:31,650 --> 00:38:33,380
我已经做过了
I did that already.

894
00:38:34,640 --> 00:38:35,560
说真的  迈克
Seriously, Mike,

895
00:38:35,560 --> 00:38:37,400
一切回到正常真好
It's good to have things back to normal.

896
00:38:37,950 --> 00:38:39,770
是啊  正常
Yeah. Normal.

897
00:38:44,110 --> 00:38:45,350
迈克  我要说一些
Mike, I'm gonna say something to you

898
00:38:45,350 --> 00:38:47,210
我从来没和你说过的话
that I have never told you before.

899
00:38:47,210 --> 00:38:49,300
我羡慕你和瑞秋所拥有的
I admire what you have with Rachel.

900
00:38:49,300 --> 00:38:51,340
-哈维  -不  让我说完
- Harvey-- - No, let me finish.

901
00:38:51,480 --> 00:38:52,820
那是真实的
It's real.

902
00:38:53,050 --> 00:38:54,050
那很难得到
It's hard to come by,

903
00:38:54,050 --> 00:38:56,550
而你只要原谅她就可以留住这一切
and all you have to do to keep it is forgive her.

904
00:38:56,690 --> 00:39:00,130
所以如果你今晚还想留下  当然可以
So if you want to stay here tonight, by all means,

905
00:39:00,130 --> 00:39:02,080
但我认为你应该回家
but I think you should go home.

906
00:39:07,080 --> 00:39:08,360
你要去哪
Where are you going?

907
00:39:09,700 --> 00:39:10,930
我要去处理一件
I have to take care of something

908
00:39:10,930 --> 00:39:12,650
几天前就该处理的事情
I should have days ago.

909
00:39:20,700 --> 00:39:22,570
哈维  你想见我
Harvey. You wanted to see me?

910
00:39:22,570 --> 00:39:23,300
是的
Yes.

911
00:39:23,300 --> 00:39:25,710
我想让你看一下完成交易所需的
I wanted you to take a look at a draft of the paperwork

912
00:39:25,710 --> 00:39:27,130
文件初稿
to wrap up your deal.

913
00:39:28,200 --> 00:39:28,800
你为什么要
Why would you--

914
00:39:28,800 --> 00:39:29,770
因为我想让你知道
Because I wanted to let you know

915
00:39:29,770 --> 00:39:31,820
接下来会发生什么
how things are gonna be moving forward.

916
00:39:32,270 --> 00:39:35,250
你会在明天早上八点签署这份文件
You're gonna sign these papers at 8:00 a.m tomorrow,

917
00:39:35,250 --> 00:39:36,870
而在八点零一分
and at 8:01,

918
00:39:38,260 --> 00:39:39,560
你就彻底离开了
you're gone.

919
00:39:42,630 --> 00:39:43,720
哈维
Harvey.

920
00:39:43,720 --> 00:39:44,830
我根本不关心
Look, I don't give a shit

921
00:39:44,830 --> 00:39:46,400
你能给我的事务所带来多少生意
how much business you give my firm.

922
00:39:46,400 --> 00:39:48,050
我再也不想见到你了
I never want to see you again.

923
00:39:48,050 --> 00:39:49,220
你真的要放弃我吗
You're really gonna drop me?

924
00:39:49,220 --> 00:39:50,500
当然了
You're damn right I am.

925
00:39:50,500 --> 00:39:53,360
如果你跑去找杰西卡来对付我
And if you go to Jessica to try to overrule me,

926
00:39:53,360 --> 00:39:56,250
下一次和你打架的就不会是迈克了
the next time, it won't be Mike you get in a fight with.

927
00:39:56,250 --> 00:39:57,700
而是我
It'll be me.

928
00:40:53,810 --> 00:40:55,230
你回家了
You're home.

929
00:40:56,330 --> 00:40:57,580
是的
I am.

930
00:41:00,670 --> 00:41:02,180
你怎么没去工作
Why aren't you at work?

931
00:41:03,460 --> 00:41:04,850
因为我今天一天
Because I spent the whole day moving

932
00:41:04,850 --> 00:41:06,060
都在到处跑
from one place to another,

933
00:41:06,060 --> 00:41:08,010
我必须和你谈谈
and I just had to talk to you.

934
00:41:09,120 --> 00:41:10,720
你怎么知道我会在这里
How'd you know I'd be here?

935
00:41:11,520 --> 00:41:15,000
我不知道  我去了哈维家
I didn't. I just went to Harvey's.

936
00:41:17,320 --> 00:41:18,590
是的
Yeah.

937
00:41:18,830 --> 00:41:20,310
我不在那儿了
Not there anymore.

938
00:41:21,580 --> 00:41:22,930
你要回来了吗
Are you back here?

939
00:41:22,930 --> 00:41:24,260
不
No.

940
00:41:27,120 --> 00:41:31,170
不  我会在其它地方待一段时间
No, I'm going to stay somewhere for a while.

941
00:41:31,170 --> 00:41:32,890
-迈克  -瑞秋  不管你想说什么
- Mike-- - Rachel, whatever you're going to say,

942
00:41:32,890 --> 00:41:34,650
现在都不是说的时候
now is not the time to say it.

943
00:41:38,550 --> 00:41:40,900
如果你希望我们之间还能
If you want there to be a chance for us...

944
00:41:43,130 --> 00:41:44,400
有机会
at all,

945
00:41:46,510 --> 00:41:48,190
那就再出去一段时间
just go back out a little longer

946
00:41:48,190 --> 00:41:49,920
让我收拾完我的东西
and let me get my things together.

947
00:41:58,390 --> 00:41:59,700
还有一件事
One more thing.

948
00:42:03,180 --> 00:42:05,100
我明天就回去上班了
I'm coming back to work tomorrow.

949
00:42:07,760 --> 00:42:08,750
如果你不能接受的话
If you can't accept that,

950
00:42:08,750 --> 00:42:10,800
不管你想和我说什么
then whatever you were going to say to me

951
00:42:12,080 --> 00:42:13,360
都不重要了
won't matter.

