1
00:00:01,070 --> 00:00:02,380
《诉讼双雄》前情提要

2
00:00:02,380 --> 00:00:04,020
卡特里娜·班尼特说了你若聘她
Katrina Bennett said she'd put the deal through

3
00:00:04,020 --> 00:00:05,390
她就签协议
if you offered her a job.

4
00:00:05,390 --> 00:00:06,520
你贿赂了她
You bribed her.

5
00:00:06,520 --> 00:00:08,120
你一口咬定我贿赂
You bet your ass I did.

6
00:00:08,120 --> 00:00:10,090
我把案子外包了
I decided to farm out the case.

7
00:00:10,090 --> 00:00:12,650
我猜是  丹尼尔·哈德曼
Let me guess-- Daniel Hardman.

8
00:00:12,650 --> 00:00:14,890
他想引诱你违反保密协议
He's baiting you into breaching confidentiality.

9
00:00:14,890 --> 00:00:16,890
我准备好咬住他  同归于尽了
And I'm ready to bite down and drag him in with me.

10
00:00:16,890 --> 00:00:18,900
莫妮卡比你年轻漂亮
She was younger than you, prettier than you,

11
00:00:18,900 --> 00:00:20,700
正值生育年龄
and of child-bearing age--

12
00:00:20,700 --> 00:00:24,160
这些你都没有  所以炒了她
all of the things you are not, and you fired her for it.

13
00:00:24,160 --> 00:00:27,770
在我们因性别歧视起诉福尔松食品公司时
You can't be the named defendant on a gender-discrimination case

14
00:00:27,770 --> 00:00:30,390
你不能成为一个类似案件的被告
while we're suing folsom foods for the same thing.

15
00:00:30,640 --> 00:00:33,210
我不会向他投降的
I am not capitulating to that man.

16
00:00:33,210 --> 00:00:36,230
你们有根本负担不起的45桩官司
You have 45 cases you can't afford.

17
00:00:36,280 --> 00:00:38,680
不管你怎么玩  我都会把你们榨干
Any way you slice it, I'm going to bleed you dry.

18
00:00:38,680 --> 00:00:41,000
我以自己的名誉向玛丽亚替你说好话
I put my reputation on the line to close Maria.

19
00:00:41,000 --> 00:00:42,610
希拉  别这样
Sheila, please.

20
00:00:42,610 --> 00:00:43,770
你还是走吧
I think you should go.

21
00:00:45,410 --> 00:00:47,040
来见一下达娜·斯科特
Meet Ms. Dana Scott.

22
00:00:47,040 --> 00:00:48,360
-斯科特  -哈维
- Scottie. - Harvey.

23
00:00:48,360 --> 00:00:49,320
你们原来认识啊
Oh, you two know each other?

24
00:00:49,320 --> 00:00:50,550
我们是哈佛法学院的同学
We went to harvard law together.

25
00:00:50,550 --> 00:00:53,270
我在这里比75%的助理待得都久
I've been here longer than 75% of our associates,

26
00:00:53,270 --> 00:00:54,310
而且我喜欢这里
and I love it,

27
00:00:54,310 --> 00:00:56,060
在论文里我就是这么说的
And that's what I told them in my essay.

28
00:00:56,150 --> 00:00:57,440
我要去哈佛啦
I'm going to harvard.

29
00:00:57,440 --> 00:00:59,990
我回到伦敦后  就要结婚了  哈维
When I get back to london, I'm getting married, Harvey.

30
00:01:00,280 --> 00:01:01,740
你想要我说什么
What would you like me to say?

31
00:01:04,270 --> 00:01:06,920
我是汉利·福尔松  福尔松食品公司总裁
I'm Hanley Folsom, president of Folsom Foods.

32
00:01:07,240 --> 00:01:10,110
最近我们成了受害者
Recently we've been victim to terrible allegations

33
00:01:10,110 --> 00:01:12,700
被严重指控歧视女性
that we've been discriminating against women.

34
00:01:12,700 --> 00:01:14,580
我们在马里斯维尔有公司
We're in places like Marysville,

35
00:01:14,580 --> 00:01:17,830
在这里  女性不只想要工作
places where women want more than just jobs.

36
00:01:17,830 --> 00:01:21,550
她们也想要住宅和家庭  我们很支持
They want homes, families, and we support that.

37
00:01:21,870 --> 00:01:24,990
如果她们想晋升  我们也同意
And if they want advancement, we support that too.

38
00:01:25,000 --> 00:01:25,740
不得不佩服啊
Got to give it to him.

39
00:01:25,740 --> 00:01:26,630
他公司的食物也许很糟糕
His food might suck,

40
00:01:26,630 --> 00:01:28,590
但他这低劣的屁话都能做出个馅饼了
But he makes a mean bullshit pie.

41
00:01:28,590 --> 00:01:30,530
别让我想像那画面
Okay, please don't put that image in my mind.

42
00:01:30,530 --> 00:01:31,740
我在吃东西呢  谢谢
I'm eating. Thank you.

43
00:01:31,740 --> 00:01:34,130
你在吃什么  呕吐物百吉饼吗
What've you got there-- vomit bagel...

44
00:01:34,580 --> 00:01:36,020
排泄物薄煎饼吗
feces pancakes?

45
00:01:36,400 --> 00:01:37,700
我不在乎他说了什么
Look, I don't care what he says.

46
00:01:37,700 --> 00:01:39,320
他不会提拔女性的
This is a man who won't promote women.

47
00:01:39,320 --> 00:01:40,780
我想听听你的意见
I want to steal a page from your book.

48
00:01:40,780 --> 00:01:42,900
我检查过了  这录像里没什么噱头
I already checked. There's no hot-mic footage from this.

49
00:01:42,900 --> 00:01:44,360
那就采访摄影师
Then interview the cameraman

50
00:01:44,360 --> 00:01:45,990
或者录音师  想尽一切办法
or the sound guy, whatever it takes.

51
00:01:45,990 --> 00:01:47,300
我们要把他逮个正着
We need to catch this guy in a lie.

52
00:01:47,300 --> 00:01:49,320
我想着要雇个调查员
I already tried to hire an investigator.

53
00:01:49,320 --> 00:01:50,750
但上面不批准
The authorization got kicked back.

54
00:01:50,750 --> 00:01:52,700
雇吧  我会搞定
Do it anyway. I'll take care of it.

55
00:01:54,190 --> 00:01:56,270
我们要谈谈资源问题
We need to talk about resources.

56
00:01:56,630 --> 00:01:57,630
是得谈谈
We do.

57
00:01:58,030 --> 00:01:59,790
我听说客户的电话都没有回复呢
I hear clients' calls aren't being returned.

58
00:01:59,790 --> 00:02:02,240
哈德曼的７桩官司优先
Hardman put seven cases on the fast track.

59
00:02:02,240 --> 00:02:03,550
其他案子只能往后推
The rest have to take a backseat.

60
00:02:03,550 --> 00:02:05,380
我们不能把客户晾在一边
We can't just hang our clients out to dry.

61
00:02:05,380 --> 00:02:06,190
不会的
We won't.

62
00:02:06,190 --> 00:02:08,920
上午10点  客户将挤满图书室
At 10:00 a.m., the library will be packed.

63
00:02:08,920 --> 00:02:11,260
与其回复113个电话
Instead of returning 113 calls,

64
00:02:11,260 --> 00:02:12,110
我不如花１个小时
I'm going to take an hour

65
00:02:12,110 --> 00:02:13,810
把案情进展告诉客户
and give them the state of the union.

66
00:02:13,810 --> 00:02:15,510
-很好  -还不够好
- Oh, good. - Not good enough.

67
00:02:15,510 --> 00:02:18,480
我还需要40位合约律师  一打律师助理
I need 40 more contract lawyers, a dozen paralegals.

68
00:02:18,480 --> 00:02:19,560
但迈克·罗斯刚告诉我
And Mike Ross just told me

69
00:02:19,560 --> 00:02:21,430
他都不能雇一个调查员
he couldn't even hire an investigator.

70
00:02:21,430 --> 00:02:22,550
没错  是不行
That's right. He can't.

71
00:02:22,550 --> 00:02:23,800
-我们必须这样做  -不
- We have to. - No.

72
00:02:23,800 --> 00:02:26,290
-我们得投入资源  -你没听到我说的吗
- We need to invest in this. - Did you hear me?

73
00:02:26,290 --> 00:02:28,520
我们既然硬撑了下来  就得认真对待
We bit this off. We need to chew.

74
00:02:28,520 --> 00:02:30,380
你就像个学步小孩  不行
You're like a toddler. No.

75
00:02:30,400 --> 00:02:32,340
这些都是账单啊
All of these are bills.

76
00:02:32,340 --> 00:02:34,060
我们早知如此
We knew what we were getting into.

77
00:02:34,370 --> 00:02:35,710
莫妮卡·伊顿让我们遭受重击
And then we took a hit from Monica Eton.

78
00:02:35,710 --> 00:02:37,370
如果再雇合约律师
And hired the contract lawyers,

79
00:02:37,370 --> 00:02:38,190
我们就没钱了
we are out of money.

80
00:02:38,190 --> 00:02:39,440
那就用信用贷款的最高限额
Use the line of credit.

81
00:02:40,310 --> 00:02:41,230
没有了
It's gone.

82
00:02:42,770 --> 00:02:43,710
什么
What?

83
00:02:44,810 --> 00:02:47,410
他们评估了现状
They have evaluated the situation,

84
00:02:48,090 --> 00:02:49,360
知道我们岌岌可危
and they know we're bleeding.

85
00:02:50,240 --> 00:02:53,090
我们在接下来的２个月里
So we've got seven cases in seven cities

86
00:02:53,090 --> 00:02:54,980
在７个城市有７桩官司
over the next two months.

87
00:02:56,190 --> 00:02:57,880
你觉得我要怎么办
So what are you proposing I do?

88
00:02:59,930 --> 00:03:01,420
有什么要给我的吗
Okay, what do you have for me?

89
00:03:02,880 --> 00:03:03,740
瑞秋
Rachel.

90
00:03:04,050 --> 00:03:05,020
瑞秋
Rachel?

91
00:03:05,700 --> 00:03:06,980
怎么了  你在干嘛
What's going on? What are you doing?

92
00:03:06,980 --> 00:03:09,260
-我在工作  -忙什么
- I'm working. - On what?

93
00:03:09,480 --> 00:03:11,280
七个官司中的一个在马萨皮夸
One of the seven cases is in Massapequa,

94
00:03:11,280 --> 00:03:12,800
我在看附近的城市里
so I'm seeing if one of the cities nearby

95
00:03:12,800 --> 00:03:14,450
有没有私家侦探
might have a private investigator.

96
00:03:14,450 --> 00:03:16,390
好  这是波士顿的地图
Okay, so that's a map of Boston.

97
00:03:16,390 --> 00:03:19,520
你现在忙的就是我们俗话说的网络
You're on what we commonly refer to as the Internet.

98
00:03:19,520 --> 00:03:20,180
在这上面
And then, up here,

99
00:03:20,180 --> 00:03:22,400
你可以输入“私家侦探”
you would just write "Private investigator."

100
00:03:22,400 --> 00:03:23,750
但我就看不到
But then I wouldn't be able to see

101
00:03:23,750 --> 00:03:25,380
当我上哈佛法学院时
what part of town I want to live in

102
00:03:25,380 --> 00:03:27,870
我想住在哪一块了
when I go to Harvard.

103
00:03:28,210 --> 00:03:30,450
所以在刚才的15分钟内
Okay, so basically you haven't been working

104
00:03:30,450 --> 00:03:32,650
你没在工作吧
for the last, what, 15 minutes?

105
00:03:33,350 --> 00:03:34,300
其实是半小时
Half hour...

106
00:03:35,530 --> 00:03:36,170
45分钟
45 minutes.

107
00:03:36,170 --> 00:03:37,230
-拜托  -抱歉
- Come on. - I am sorry.

108
00:03:37,230 --> 00:03:39,160
我不擅长等待
I don't deal well with waiting.

109
00:03:39,710 --> 00:03:41,480
你已经做了所有该做的
You've done everything that you can do, all right?

110
00:03:41,480 --> 00:03:42,840
你的法学院入学考试考得很好
You killed the LSATs.

111
00:03:42,840 --> 00:03:44,940
你面试得很好  你就是财富
You had a great interview. You're a legacy.

112
00:03:44,940 --> 00:03:46,250
你超性感
You're smoking hot.

113
00:03:46,250 --> 00:03:47,820
他们又不会因为性感录取我
They don't let people in because they're hot.

114
00:03:47,820 --> 00:03:48,740
我会
I would.

115
00:03:48,950 --> 00:03:51,810
你知道我们在忙性别歧视的案子吧
You do realize we're working on a gender-discrimination case.

116
00:03:51,810 --> 00:03:53,170
对  我在工作呢
That's what I'm doing-- working.

117
00:03:53,170 --> 00:03:55,320
希望从现在开始你也是
And hopefully that's what you'll be doing now too.

118
00:03:56,410 --> 00:03:57,530
计划有变
Change of plans.

119
00:03:58,640 --> 00:04:00,200
欢迎加入  辣妹
Welcome to the team, hottie.

120
00:04:00,500 --> 00:04:02,410
我们要合并资源
We're consolidating resources.

121
00:04:02,410 --> 00:04:03,770
杰西卡不同意雇调查员吗
Jessica didn't approve the investigator?

122
00:04:03,770 --> 00:04:05,640
杰西卡会满足我们的一切要求
Jessica approved anything we want,

123
00:04:05,700 --> 00:04:06,940
对于一个案子
for one case.

124
00:04:06,940 --> 00:04:08,560
不  所有的案子都得反击
What? No, we have to fight them all.

125
00:04:08,560 --> 00:04:09,500
我们会的
And we will.

126
00:04:09,630 --> 00:04:11,390
不管其他６个案子吗
By letting six of them go?

127
00:04:12,330 --> 00:04:13,900
你知道我们怎么赢得第二次世界大战吗
Do you know how we won World War II?

128
00:04:13,900 --> 00:04:15,970
当然   斯波克不让科克
Yeah, of course. Spock didn't let Kirk save Joan Collins

129
00:04:13,900 --> 00:04:17,020
在《星际迷航》中  琼·柯林斯饰演的女主本死于车祸
精神失常的麦考伊想回到过去防止她死去  则二战结果会大相迳庭

130
00:04:15,970 --> 00:04:17,020
阻止琼·柯林斯的车祸
from getting hit by that car.

131
00:04:17,020 --> 00:04:18,600
错  那样早赢了
Wrong. We'd already won.

132
00:04:17,060 --> 00:04:19,600
科克也回到过去以防历史改变  却爱上了女主
但最终斯波克阻止了他  历史终未改变

133
00:04:18,620 --> 00:04:20,750
科克也将改变历史
Kirk just would have changed the course of history.

134
00:04:20,830 --> 00:04:21,700
我同意
I accept that.

135
00:04:21,700 --> 00:04:24,240
艾森豪威尔在８个可能的入侵据点
Eisenhower had 156,000 men

136
00:04:24,240 --> 00:04:27,290
一共派出156000人  意味着
for 8 possible invasion points, which means--

137
00:04:27,290 --> 00:04:29,690
每个据点有19500人
19,500 men per point.

138
00:04:29,690 --> 00:04:31,330
其实就等于没人
Otherwise known as nothing.

139
00:04:31,510 --> 00:04:34,700
他必须把所有力量集中到一次袭击上
He had to put everything that he had into one attack...

140
00:04:35,640 --> 00:04:36,580
诺曼底
Normandy.

141
00:04:36,670 --> 00:04:39,340
问题是  我们的诺曼底在哪
So the question is, where the hell is our Normandy?

142
00:04:39,340 --> 00:04:41,170
很简单  贝克尔斯菲
That's easy. Bakersfield.

143
00:04:41,670 --> 00:04:43,190
最低的女性提拔率
Lowest percentage of female promotions,

144
00:04:43,190 --> 00:04:44,880
而女性申请者的百分比最高
highest percentage of female applicants.

145
00:04:44,880 --> 00:04:47,590
汉利·福尔松的姐夫管理那间工厂
And Hanley Folsom's brother-in-law runs the plant.

146
00:04:47,590 --> 00:04:48,250
没错
Exactly.

147
00:04:48,250 --> 00:04:50,920
如果想进攻  那就从贝克尔斯菲开始
You want to launch an attack, you launch it from Bakersfield.

148
00:04:51,610 --> 00:04:53,160
我是斯波克还是科克
Hey, am I Spock or Kirk?

149
00:04:53,290 --> 00:04:54,190
你是乌胡拉
Uhura.

150
00:04:53,290 --> 00:04:54,190
还是电影《星际迷航》人物  是舰队中的通讯官

151
00:04:54,190 --> 00:04:55,430
正中你下怀啊
Walked right into it.

152
00:04:57,210 --> 00:04:59,700
帮你拿了杯浓缩咖啡  四倍量的
I got you an espresso, quad shot.

153
00:04:59,700 --> 00:05:01,440
-我不需要咖啡  -你也许会要
- I don't need coffee. - You might.

154
00:05:03,240 --> 00:05:04,190
我很好
I'm fine.

155
00:05:05,520 --> 00:05:06,280
怎么
What?

156
00:05:06,280 --> 00:05:07,820
你的西装有点…
Oh, your suit's a little--

157
00:05:08,970 --> 00:05:11,290
是个客户会面  又不是单身汉拍卖
It's a client meeting, not a bachelor auction.

158
00:05:11,290 --> 00:05:12,550
关于那个…
Yeah, about that--

159
00:05:12,550 --> 00:05:14,800
怎么  客户太多图书馆挤不下了吗
What, are there too many clients to fit in the library?

160
00:05:14,800 --> 00:05:15,940
我们用的会议室
We're using the conference room.

161
00:05:15,940 --> 00:05:17,940
-他们挤不下的  -足够了
- They won't all fit. - They will.

162
00:05:18,960 --> 00:05:20,610
有点小麻烦
There's been a slight complication.

163
00:05:20,610 --> 00:05:21,540
唐娜
Donna--

164
00:05:22,340 --> 00:05:23,950
你到那就会懂的
You will understand when you get there.

165
00:05:33,620 --> 00:05:34,620
现在可以了
Now you're ready.

166
00:05:35,800 --> 00:05:36,740
唐娜
Donna.

167
00:05:37,320 --> 00:05:39,700
-斯科特  -哈维
- Scottie? - Harvey.

168
00:05:39,700 --> 00:05:40,990
婚后生活怎么样
How's married life?

169
00:05:41,580 --> 00:05:42,520
我可不知道
I wouldn't know.

170
00:05:43,260 --> 00:05:44,390
这么快就离婚了吗
Divorced so soon?

171
00:05:44,590 --> 00:05:46,200
我就没陷进去过
I never took the plunge.

172
00:05:47,460 --> 00:05:48,690
别得瑟了
Oh, get over yourself.

173
00:05:48,690 --> 00:05:50,470
我知道上次我临阵退缩
I know I came here last time with cold feet

174
00:05:50,470 --> 00:05:52,230
像个15岁女孩  在你面前哭诉
and blubbered over you like a 15-year-old.

175
00:05:52,230 --> 00:05:53,680
但那不是因为你
But it wasn't about you.

176
00:05:54,230 --> 00:05:55,060
而是因为我
It was about me.

177
00:05:55,060 --> 00:05:56,440
你这次来有什么事
So what's it about this time?

178
00:05:57,370 --> 00:05:58,660
贝克尔斯菲
Bakersfield.

179
00:05:58,830 --> 00:06:00,060
不准抢走我的客户  斯科特
You are not taking my clients, Scottie.

180
00:06:00,060 --> 00:06:01,100
已成定局
We already did.

181
00:06:02,210 --> 00:06:04,470
抢你的客户  就像抢小孩嘴里的糖
Like taking candy from a little Harvard baby.

182
00:06:04,470 --> 00:06:05,700
你还说不是因为我
You just said it wasn't about me.

183
00:06:05,700 --> 00:06:07,770
哈维  贝克尔斯菲事关重要  已被我拿下
Harvey, Bakersfield is everything, and I've got them.

184
00:06:07,770 --> 00:06:09,140
也跟其他人约好了会面
I've also got appointments with the rest.

185
00:06:09,140 --> 00:06:11,240
这样我就能逐一拿下其他20个
So I can spend time going after them and get 20 more,

186
00:06:11,240 --> 00:06:14,960
或者你让给我10个  我们休战
or you could let me have 10 and we call it a day.

187
00:06:14,960 --> 00:06:16,190
我干脆把所有东西都给你算了
Well, why don't I just give it all to you?

188
00:06:16,190 --> 00:06:18,050
所有案子  办公室  钱包  钥匙
My cases, office, my wallet, my keys--

189
00:06:18,050 --> 00:06:20,540
不是针对你  只是为了客户
It's not personal. It's just business.

190
00:06:20,540 --> 00:06:23,290
-是  那也是我的  -很诱人
- Yeah, my business. - Good business.

191
00:06:23,290 --> 00:06:24,880
我拒绝
The answer is no.

192
00:06:25,420 --> 00:06:27,760
好吧  问问总没坏处
Well, there's no harm in asking.

193
00:06:27,870 --> 00:06:29,140
不过见到你很高兴
It's good to see you, though.

194
00:06:30,540 --> 00:06:31,660
气色不错
You look great.

195
00:06:31,810 --> 00:06:33,120
不过有点打扮过头
A bit overworked, but...

196
00:06:33,500 --> 00:06:35,520
考虑到你都这个年纪了
Not bad for a guy your age.

197
00:06:38,210 --> 00:06:41,210
人人影视
YYeTs.com

198
00:06:38,210 --> 00:06:41,210
原创翻译  双语字幕

199
00:06:38,210 --> 00:06:41,210
■

200
00:06:38,210 --> 00:06:41,210
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

201
00:06:41,210 --> 00:06:46,210
 翻译：贺天天  月月  一不二  某豚  陈小圈  小饭

202
00:06:41,210 --> 00:06:46,210
■

203
00:06:46,210 --> 00:06:51,210
时间轴：贝贝  小猫  校对：油炸电风扇  月月

204
00:06:46,210 --> 00:06:51,210
■

205
00:06:51,210 --> 00:06:56,210
后期 & 特效：仓鼠sama     总监：月月

206
00:06:51,210 --> 00:06:56,210
■

207
00:07:02,870 --> 00:07:05,040
第二季 第十五集

208
00:07:02,870 --> 00:07:05,040
诉 讼 双 雄

209
00:07:02,870 --> 00:07:05,040
蓝光-1080P-SHORTBREHD版调轴风格微修：字幕雷哥

210
00:07:13,890 --> 00:07:16,430
你开玩笑吧  她抢了贝克尔斯菲吗
You've got to be kidding me. She took Bakersfield?

211
00:07:16,430 --> 00:07:18,240
她还想再抢10个
And she's looking for ten more.

212
00:07:19,000 --> 00:07:21,050
女人的欲望  挡也挡不住
A woman that goes after what she wants.

213
00:07:21,050 --> 00:07:23,290
-听起来你很欣赏她  -你没有吗
- You sound impressed. - You don't.

214
00:07:23,490 --> 00:07:25,620
和我共事的女人也是如此
I already work with a woman like that every day.

215
00:07:26,170 --> 00:07:28,000
也许当年有机会时  我应该雇佣她
Maybe I should have hired her when I had the chance.

216
00:07:28,000 --> 00:07:29,350
什么机会
What chance?

217
00:07:29,350 --> 00:07:30,730
那年有个职位空缺
There was one opening that year,

218
00:07:30,730 --> 00:07:32,470
她是简历中最突出的
and she was the best on paper,

219
00:07:32,470 --> 00:07:34,250
但鉴于我已在你身上下了血本
but I had already invested so much in you

220
00:07:34,250 --> 00:07:36,650
我就觉得要先收回投资才行
that I decided to get a return on my investment.

221
00:07:36,650 --> 00:07:38,380
这正是我要提供的
Which is what I'm going to give you right now,

222
00:07:38,380 --> 00:07:40,870
尽管你已经没钱再做投资了
even though you don't have any more money to invest.

223
00:07:40,870 --> 00:07:42,500
你别又提资源一事
Are you back to resources?

224
00:07:42,500 --> 00:07:46,010
关于我们的弱点  我已经听够了
Because I've had enough of hearing about our weaknesses.

225
00:07:46,010 --> 00:07:48,830
我要说的是化弱为强
I'm talking about turning it into one of our strengths.

226
00:07:50,370 --> 00:07:51,810
继续说
I'm listening.

227
00:07:52,070 --> 00:07:53,260
哈德曼知道我们快破产了
Hardman knows we're tapped out.

228
00:07:53,260 --> 00:07:54,140
他就指望着呢
He's counting on it.

229
00:07:54,140 --> 00:07:56,460
如果不如他所愿呢  反而壮大了呢
What if we're not? What if we're flush?

230
00:07:56,470 --> 00:07:58,570
你是说与她联盟吗
Are you talking about joining forces with her?

231
00:07:58,650 --> 00:07:59,860
是和她的事务所
With her firm...

232
00:08:00,150 --> 00:08:03,180
她背后资源近乎无穷的事务所
Her infinitely deep-pocketed firm.

233
00:08:03,230 --> 00:08:05,750
哈维  她想要10个案子
Harvey, she wanted ten cases.

234
00:08:05,860 --> 00:08:08,260
而你是想分享45个
You're talking about sharing 45,

235
00:08:08,260 --> 00:08:09,760
我从不知道你也会分享
and I've never known you to share.

236
00:08:09,760 --> 00:08:12,180
对方总部在伦敦  我们还是主导
They're based in London, so we'll be running the show.

237
00:08:12,180 --> 00:08:13,640
他们出钱资助就行了
They'll just be signing the checks.

238
00:08:13,640 --> 00:08:15,490
也要分走很多胜利的果实
And taking a cut of the winnings.

239
00:08:15,550 --> 00:08:17,440
正是  胜利
Exactly. Winnings.

240
00:08:17,460 --> 00:08:18,950
这是击退哈德曼的最好方法
It's the best way to beat Hardman.

241
00:08:19,570 --> 00:08:22,190
额外的好处就是你也没输给斯科特
And the side benefit is you don't lose to Scottie.

242
00:08:22,480 --> 00:08:24,340
有额外的好处总没错
Nothing wrong with a side benefit.

243
00:08:25,050 --> 00:08:27,010
行  别输给她
Fine. Don't lose to her.

244
00:08:27,350 --> 00:08:30,230
但你最好给我确保你别跟她一起输
But you better make damn sure that you don't lose with her.

245
00:08:42,660 --> 00:08:43,670
很好  你来了
Good. You're here.

246
00:08:43,670 --> 00:08:45,070
我负责人事档案
I'm taking the personnel files,

247
00:08:45,070 --> 00:08:46,420
你来看公司会议记录
you go through the corporate minutes, and--

248
00:08:46,420 --> 00:08:47,430
你是说什么
Excuse me?

249
00:08:48,660 --> 00:08:50,830
贝克尔斯菲  时间不多了
Bakersfield. We don't have all day.

250
00:08:52,730 --> 00:08:56,670
不好意思  我不知道你也被分到这个案子
I'm--I'm sorry. I didn't know you were on Bakersfield.

251
00:08:57,000 --> 00:08:59,190
现实就是这样  开始吧
Well, I am. Let's go.

252
00:08:59,190 --> 00:09:00,250
记录都在那边
The minutes are over there,

253
00:09:00,250 --> 00:09:01,680
可它们不会自己翻完
and they're not going to read themselves.

254
00:09:01,680 --> 00:09:04,140
你可以也被分到贝克尔斯菲一案
Okay, well, you may be on Bakersfield,

255
00:09:04,140 --> 00:09:06,070
但是我来主管此案
but I'm the lead on Bakersfield,

256
00:09:06,070 --> 00:09:07,430
而我们在哈维拿到最新的
and we're not going to do any of that stuff

257
00:09:07,430 --> 00:09:10,250
统计数据前  不会开始看
until we get Harvey some up-to-date statistics.

258
00:09:10,630 --> 00:09:14,180
4.7%的高管是女性  最新数据
4.7% female executives. Up to date.

259
00:09:14,850 --> 00:09:15,500
这才一个数据
That's a number.

260
00:09:15,500 --> 00:09:17,630
我们需要在45个州22个部门内
We need the probability of that ratio being chance

261
00:09:17,630 --> 00:09:20,630
这一比例出现的概率  即…
across 22 divisions in 45 states, which is one--

262
00:09:20,630 --> 00:09:22,730
83亿分之一
One in 8.3 billion.

263
00:09:23,310 --> 00:09:24,480
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?

264
00:09:24,480 --> 00:09:25,780
我问过统计员了
I checked with the statistician.

265
00:09:25,780 --> 00:09:27,450
好  不过他错了  因为他没…
Yeah, well, he's wrong, because he didn't--

266
00:09:27,450 --> 00:09:29,530
调整异常值  也就变成
Adjust for outliers, which takes it to--

267
00:09:29,530 --> 00:09:31,790
64亿分之一
One in 6.4 billion.

268
00:09:32,970 --> 00:09:35,360
-你怎么知道的  -我自己算的
- How did you know that? - I did it in my head.

269
00:09:36,220 --> 00:09:37,300
这是我的本事
It's what I do.

270
00:09:37,710 --> 00:09:39,020
也是我主导此案的原因
It's why I'm lead,

271
00:09:39,260 --> 00:09:41,920
若你不知道  你最好去问问
and if you don't know, you better ask somebody.

272
00:09:42,350 --> 00:09:43,990
我不需问任何人
I don't need to ask anybody

273
00:09:43,990 --> 00:09:46,180
就知道若我们用第一个数字
to know that if we use the 8.3 billion number,

274
00:09:46,180 --> 00:09:48,980
也站得住脚  对我们也更有利
it's defensible, and it skews the results in our favor.

275
00:09:48,980 --> 00:09:49,880
真让我吃惊
Oh, what a shock.

276
00:09:49,880 --> 00:09:51,350
你为了结果应有利
You want to skew the results

277
00:09:51,350 --> 00:09:53,010
而要牺牲数据的可靠性
at the expense of our credibility.

278
00:09:53,010 --> 00:09:54,460
我们不能这么做
We're not doing it.

279
00:09:54,460 --> 00:09:57,530
-我是第五年了  迈克  -而我给哈维干活
- I am a fifth year, Mike. - And I work for Harvey.

280
00:09:57,530 --> 00:10:00,010
这么说  杰西卡让我来的
Well, Jessica assigned me.

281
00:10:00,010 --> 00:10:03,320
若你不满意  你跟她理论去
And if you don't like that, why don't you go talk to her?

282
00:10:04,880 --> 00:10:06,540
我不想与卡特里娜共事
I don't want to work with Katrina.

283
00:10:06,540 --> 00:10:07,560
半路插足  自作主张
She comes in. She takes over.

284
00:10:07,560 --> 00:10:09,260
好像万事都要她做主
She acts like everything is her idea.

285
00:10:09,260 --> 00:10:10,170
我们真是难兄难弟
Then we're in the same boat,

286
00:10:10,170 --> 00:10:11,760
因为我也不想与斯科特共事
'cause I don't want to work with Scottie.

287
00:10:11,760 --> 00:10:12,810
我们要与斯科特合作
We're working with Scottie?

288
00:10:12,970 --> 00:10:13,760
是我和她
I'm working with Scottie.

289
00:10:13,760 --> 00:10:15,190
她在贝克尔斯菲一案上与我们一起吗
She's coming to Bakersfield with us?

290
00:10:15,190 --> 00:10:16,840
是在此案上  与我一起
She's coming to Bakersfield with me.

291
00:10:16,840 --> 00:10:17,990
你怎么能这么对我
How can you do that to me?

292
00:10:17,990 --> 00:10:20,030
不是我干的  是她  她抢走了客户
I didn't do it to you. She did. She stole them.

293
00:10:20,030 --> 00:10:22,170
-等下  什么  -放松
- Wait. What? - Relax, okay?

294
00:10:22,170 --> 00:10:23,660
我将来会再给你外派案子的
You're going to go on another road trip someday.

295
00:10:23,660 --> 00:10:25,270
不  哈维  你没懂我的意思
No, Harvey, you're not getting it.

296
00:10:25,590 --> 00:10:27,110
这回二战我们要输了
We're going to lose World War II.

297
00:10:29,250 --> 00:10:30,210
你想要什么
What do you want?

298
00:10:31,390 --> 00:10:32,680
喝咖啡  还是茶
Coffee? Tea?

299
00:10:32,740 --> 00:10:34,270
不用了  谢谢
I'm good, thanks.

300
00:10:34,550 --> 00:10:37,770
没有欲望的女人  我可不信
A woman who wants nothing-- I distrust that.

301
00:10:38,210 --> 00:10:39,610
谁说我什么都不要了
Who said I want nothing?

302
00:10:39,610 --> 00:10:41,300
可没人这么说过你
Oh, no one's ever said that about you.

303
00:10:41,300 --> 00:10:42,780
那他们怎么说我的
Oh, what have they said?

304
00:10:42,780 --> 00:10:43,700
“他们”是指
"They"?

305
00:10:44,730 --> 00:10:45,630
你
You.

306
00:10:46,570 --> 00:10:47,800
你关心我的想法吗
My opinion matters to you?

307
00:10:47,800 --> 00:10:49,360
他在乎你的想法
Your opinion matters to him.

308
00:10:50,040 --> 00:10:52,260
我只说过你的好话  斯科特
I've only ever said good things about you, Scottie.

309
00:10:52,260 --> 00:10:53,520
但你怎么想的呢
But what have you thought?

310
00:10:55,430 --> 00:10:56,750
别玩弄他
Just don't screw with him.

311
00:10:56,750 --> 00:10:59,120
别玩弄他  还是别和他好上
Don't screw with him, or don't screw him?

312
00:10:59,120 --> 00:11:01,020
这两者你还能分开吗
Are you able to do one without the other?

313
00:11:01,970 --> 00:11:02,910
分开什么
The other what?

314
00:11:03,570 --> 00:11:05,090
你们谈公事吧
I'll leave you two to business.

315
00:11:07,170 --> 00:11:09,030
你是会接受我的建议
So are you going to take me up on my offer,

316
00:11:09,030 --> 00:11:10,510
还是准备反抗呢
or are you going to fight me?

317
00:11:10,790 --> 00:11:11,790
你说呢
You tell me.

318
00:11:11,790 --> 00:11:12,840
我想二者皆不是
I think neither.

319
00:11:13,740 --> 00:11:15,510
你想让我们合作处理这些案子
I think you want us to try the cases together

320
00:11:15,510 --> 00:11:17,630
而我的事务所来掏腰包
and let my firm bankroll the litigation.

321
00:11:17,630 --> 00:11:20,050
而这正是你所期望的
Which is exactly what you wanted the whole time.

322
00:11:20,160 --> 00:11:23,170
你说对了  我们从贝克尔斯菲开始吧
You got me. We'll start with Bakersfield.

323
00:11:23,600 --> 00:11:25,370
你就不能直接说吗
You couldn't just go for the direct approach?

324
00:11:25,370 --> 00:11:28,130
哈维  直截了当对你不管用
You don't respond to the direct approach, Harvey.

325
00:11:28,130 --> 00:11:30,130
你只对你自己的想法有动力
You like to feel you can come to things on your own.

326
00:11:30,400 --> 00:11:32,480
所以我们不要从贝克尔斯菲开始
Which is why we're not starting with Bakersfield.

327
00:11:32,920 --> 00:11:35,070
-那是不二之选  -正是
- It's the clear choice. - Exactly.

328
00:11:35,100 --> 00:11:37,090
你知道  我的助理知道
You knew it, my first year knew it,

329
00:11:37,130 --> 00:11:37,910
哈德曼也知道
and so will Hardman.

330
00:11:37,910 --> 00:11:40,120
-我不怕哈德曼  -你应该有所警惕
- I'm not afraid of Hardman. - You should be.

331
00:11:40,220 --> 00:11:42,150
所以我们要瞄准帕克维尔
And that's why we're going to Parkville.

332
00:11:42,150 --> 00:11:44,150
你是说在整个公司中
You mean the one division with a female manager

333
00:11:44,150 --> 00:11:45,830
女性经理与高管比例
and the best ratio of women executives

334
00:11:45,830 --> 00:11:46,970
最高的那个部门吗
in the entire company?

335
00:11:46,970 --> 00:11:48,370
不  我是指哈德曼
No, I mean the one division

336
00:11:48,370 --> 00:11:50,440
最想不到我们会下手的那个部门
where Hardman will never think to find us.

337
00:11:50,440 --> 00:11:51,860
因为那是最蠢的入手点
Because it's the dumbest place to start

338
00:11:51,860 --> 00:11:53,290
也最难赢
and the hardest place to win.

339
00:11:53,290 --> 00:11:56,440
而若我们赢了  其他的都会投降
And when we win it, all the others will surrender.

340
00:11:56,840 --> 00:11:58,130
真让人惊奇
What a surprise--

341
00:11:58,130 --> 00:12:00,360
哈维·斯佩克特竟想从最难处入手
Harvey Specter wants to do things the hard way.

342
00:12:00,360 --> 00:12:01,670
真让人惊奇
What a surprise--

343
00:12:01,670 --> 00:12:03,880
达娜·斯科特竟想走捷径
Dana Scott's looking for the shortcut.

344
00:12:03,880 --> 00:12:05,990
那你凭什么认为  他不会发现
And what makes you think that he's not going to find out

345
00:12:05,990 --> 00:12:07,600
我们没去贝克尔斯菲
that we're not still going to Bakersfield?

346
00:12:07,600 --> 00:12:09,080
我们还是要去那
We're still going to Bakersfield.

347
00:12:09,080 --> 00:12:10,850
订好飞机  宾馆
We book a plane, a hotel,

348
00:12:10,850 --> 00:12:13,700
在七个城市里安排好取证
line up depositions there and in all seven cities.

349
00:12:13,700 --> 00:12:16,540
这个计划不值得扔这么多钱
That plan isn't worthy of our kind of money.

350
00:12:17,190 --> 00:12:18,920
若你想让哈德曼晕头
If you want to overwhelm Hardman...

351
00:12:20,600 --> 00:12:22,710
我们45个城市都去
we go to all 45 cities...

352
00:12:24,140 --> 00:12:27,530
这才是你想要的吧
Which is exactly what you wanted the whole time.

353
00:12:27,890 --> 00:12:29,040
被你说对了
You got me.

354
00:12:31,620 --> 00:12:35,000
我就是想说  对不起
Hey, um, I just wanted to say I'm sorry

355
00:12:35,540 --> 00:12:36,730
你说对了
and that you were right.

356
00:12:36,730 --> 00:12:37,930
杰西卡分派的你
Jessica assigned you,

357
00:12:37,930 --> 00:12:40,470
所以你应该来主导贝克尔斯菲
So you should take the lead on Bakersfield.

358
00:12:41,860 --> 00:12:42,980
那你去做什么
What are you going to do?

359
00:12:43,690 --> 00:12:45,320
我有其他任务  不用管我
I've got other things. I'll be fine.

360
00:12:45,320 --> 00:12:47,840
很好  你们都在  计划有变
Good. You're both here. Change of plan.

361
00:12:47,840 --> 00:12:49,730
不用说  我已经知道
Uh, no need. I already know, so...

362
00:12:49,730 --> 00:12:51,190
与帕克维尔无关
This isn't about Parkville.

363
00:12:51,400 --> 00:12:53,220
我在36小时后对哈利·福尔松取证
I'm deposing Hanley Folsom in 36 hours,

364
00:12:53,220 --> 00:12:55,520
而我要在他到达前  非常了解他
and I need to know more about him than his mistress does

365
00:12:55,520 --> 00:12:56,820
程度甚至要超过他的情人
before he gets here.

366
00:12:56,820 --> 00:12:58,110
他有情人吗
He has a mistress?

367
00:12:58,110 --> 00:12:59,780
若如此肯定有帮助  不是吗
That would help, wouldn't it?

368
00:13:00,190 --> 00:13:03,530
既然你要求跟这个案子  你就应该知道
And you should already know, since you asked on this case.

369
00:13:04,460 --> 00:13:05,880
找点有用的东西给我
Now find me something.

370
00:13:08,610 --> 00:13:09,650
你现在又生什么气
What are you pissed about now?

371
00:13:09,650 --> 00:13:11,390
杰西卡派你跟这个案子
Jessica assigned you?

372
00:13:11,390 --> 00:13:12,880
不  是你主动要求的
No, you asked.

373
00:13:12,880 --> 00:13:14,460
我要求了  然后她就派给我了
I asked, and she assigned me.

374
00:13:14,460 --> 00:13:15,710
这是正常步骤
That's how it works.

375
00:13:15,710 --> 00:13:17,910
但你告诉我时  听起来并非如此
When you phrased it to me, you picked language

376
00:13:17,910 --> 00:13:20,490
净挑了对你有利的话
that skewed a little bit in your favor.

377
00:13:20,980 --> 00:13:23,360
就像你刚刚说  “我有其他任务”
Like you just said, "I've got other things,"

378
00:13:23,360 --> 00:13:25,650
而不是告诉我  这个案子的焦点很明显
instead of telling me the focus of the entire case

379
00:13:25,650 --> 00:13:27,460
已转移到了帕克维尔
apparently just moved to Parkville,

380
00:13:27,460 --> 00:13:29,280
这点我是觉得没什么
which I don't have a problem with,

381
00:13:29,280 --> 00:13:31,020
可很明显你对我有意见
but clearly you have a problem with me.

382
00:13:31,020 --> 00:13:33,790
那就是你为什么会来这工作
My problem with you is how you got here.

383
00:13:34,090 --> 00:13:34,740
有意思
That's funny,

384
00:13:34,740 --> 00:13:36,670
因为我的问题也是这个
because my problem with you is how I got here.

385
00:13:36,670 --> 00:13:37,930
你在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?

386
00:13:37,930 --> 00:13:39,330
哈维让我来工作
Harvey offered me a job,

387
00:13:39,330 --> 00:13:40,780
我以为是因为我让他很欣赏
and I thought it was because I'd impressed him.

388
00:13:40,780 --> 00:13:42,430
接着你出现了  准备违反保密特权
Then you showed up, ready to break privilege,

389
00:13:42,430 --> 00:13:43,990
我才知道真正的原因
and I knew the real reason.

390
00:13:43,990 --> 00:13:46,470
他雇我是想保护你
He was hiring me to protect you.

391
00:13:46,470 --> 00:13:47,560
是  当你发现
Right, and then after you found out

392
00:13:47,560 --> 00:13:49,020
这个真相之后
the real reason for the offer,

393
00:13:49,020 --> 00:13:50,070
你去找哈维  跟他说
you went to Harvey, and you said,

394
00:13:50,070 --> 00:13:52,760
“我不能接受以这种目的为前提的工作”
"I can't possibly accept employment under those circumstances."

395
00:13:52,760 --> 00:13:54,140
等等  不  你没去
Oh, wait. No, you didn't.

396
00:13:54,140 --> 00:13:55,940
你还真说对了  因为我不能去
You're damn right I didn't, because I couldn't,

397
00:13:55,940 --> 00:13:57,830
因为我已经要求递了辞呈
because I had already given notice.

398
00:13:58,180 --> 00:13:59,850
不要总以为什么都和你有关
Stop taking everything so personally

399
00:13:59,850 --> 00:14:01,330
让这事过去
and get over it.

400
00:14:06,500 --> 00:14:08,670
别跟我说你是在享受
Tell me you are not having...

401
00:14:09,650 --> 00:14:10,570
飞机还不错
It's nice.

402
00:14:10,570 --> 00:14:11,430
“还不错”
"Nice"?

403
00:14:11,430 --> 00:14:12,870
那是不是该坐你的飞机
Should we have taken your jet?

404
00:14:12,870 --> 00:14:14,920
等等  你们没有飞机
Oh, wait. You don't have a jet.

405
00:14:15,390 --> 00:14:16,830
很难在曼哈顿降落
It's hard to park them in Manhattan.

406
00:14:16,830 --> 00:14:19,660
忘了皮尔逊·哈德曼律所有多中心了
Oh, right. I forgot how provincial Pearson Hardman was--

407
00:14:19,660 --> 00:14:21,210
只有一个城市  只有一家
One office, one city.

408
00:14:21,460 --> 00:14:24,680
只有一家在纽约
One office, the city.

409
00:14:26,510 --> 00:14:27,380
怎么了
What?

410
00:14:27,490 --> 00:14:28,690
突然想起来了
It just occurred to me.

411
00:14:29,100 --> 00:14:30,420
让我猜猜
Oh, let me guess.

412
00:14:30,420 --> 00:14:32,990
成为同伙有个好处
There's an advantage to being on the same side.

413
00:14:33,040 --> 00:14:37,440
不用让生意挡着我们
Well, we don't have to get the business out of the way

414
00:14:38,020 --> 00:14:39,250
获得快乐啊
before getting to the pleasure.

415
00:14:39,250 --> 00:14:40,600
也有弊端
There's also a disadvantage.

416
00:14:40,600 --> 00:14:42,730
我猜猜  你有什么规定吧
Oh, let me guess. You have some rule.

417
00:14:42,730 --> 00:14:44,140
我不在自己家做饭
I don't cook in my own kitchen.

418
00:14:44,140 --> 00:14:45,820
-你还做饭  -这叫比喻
- You cook? - It's a metaphor.

419
00:14:45,820 --> 00:14:47,840
我明白  但是你很幸运
Yeah, I got that. But you're in luck.

420
00:14:47,840 --> 00:14:50,090
我们不在同一个厨房
We are not in the same kitchen.

421
00:14:50,090 --> 00:14:52,390
我们在一起办这个案子
We are on this case.

422
00:14:54,080 --> 00:14:55,800
某人没看文件哦
Somebody didn't read the paperwork.

423
00:14:56,010 --> 00:14:57,830
我什么时候看过
When do I ever read the paperwork?

424
00:14:59,010 --> 00:15:00,320
我们仍然是独立的个体
We're still separate entities.

425
00:15:00,320 --> 00:15:02,390
这只是个法律结合行动
It's just a combined legal action.

426
00:15:02,500 --> 00:15:03,890
我喜欢这种说法
Mm, I like the sound of that.

427
00:15:03,890 --> 00:15:05,170
希望你喜欢
I was hoping you would.

428
00:15:05,170 --> 00:15:07,560
你会因为我和你上床起诉我吗
Are you going to litigate me into sleeping with you?

429
00:15:08,610 --> 00:15:10,990
我会让你欲仙欲死
I'm going to lead you right where you're dying to go.

430
00:15:13,850 --> 00:15:15,200
还有多久着陆
How long until we land?

431
00:15:15,530 --> 00:15:16,500
够长了
Long enough.

432
00:15:18,220 --> 00:15:21,660
法律结合行动
Combined legal action.

433
00:15:21,990 --> 00:15:23,010
等一下
You know, wait.

434
00:15:23,580 --> 00:15:25,780
我们还没决定谁来主持取证
We didn't decide who's taking the lead on the deposition.

435
00:15:25,780 --> 00:15:28,330
可以石头剪子布啊
Well, we could rock, paper, scissors for it.

436
00:15:29,280 --> 00:15:30,550
或者就这样吧
Or we can do this.

437
00:15:30,550 --> 00:15:31,890
怎么判断输赢
How will we know who won?

438
00:15:36,210 --> 00:15:37,310
会知道的
Oh, we'll know.

439
00:15:51,790 --> 00:15:53,270
我的贴心小妹妹
Hey, sweetpants.

440
00:15:53,310 --> 00:15:54,330
感觉好久不见了
I feel like I never see you anymore,

441
00:15:54,330 --> 00:15:55,330
想不想一起去
so I was wondering if you want--

442
00:15:55,330 --> 00:15:58,040
我的天  怎么了
Oh, my God. What happened?

443
00:16:04,130 --> 00:16:05,150
你没被录取
You didn't get in.

444
00:16:05,230 --> 00:16:06,680
我不想谈这件事
I don't want to talk about it.

445
00:16:06,840 --> 00:16:07,940
我懂
I understand.

446
00:16:08,530 --> 00:16:10,290
瑞秋  我需要你帮个忙
Hey, Rachel, I need your help.

447
00:16:10,510 --> 00:16:12,430
好  你要干嘛
Um, yes. What do you need?

448
00:16:12,430 --> 00:16:13,850
我可以开始工作了
I'm ready to work.

449
00:16:14,590 --> 00:16:16,120
如果你需要任何帮助
Listen, if you need help with any of it,

450
00:16:16,120 --> 00:16:17,610
我就在我位子上
I'm going to be at my desk.

451
00:16:18,370 --> 00:16:19,290
谢谢  唐娜
Thanks, Donna.

452
00:16:20,830 --> 00:16:22,220
不要以为什么都和你有关
Don't take it so personally.

453
00:16:23,530 --> 00:16:24,280
什么
What?

454
00:16:24,280 --> 00:16:25,660
这是别人告诉我的
That's what someone said to me.

455
00:16:25,760 --> 00:16:27,370
不管什么时候  别人说没有个人原因
And whenever someone says something's not personal,

456
00:16:27,370 --> 00:16:29,060
其实是有  因为事事都涉及人
it is, because everything is personal.

457
00:16:29,060 --> 00:16:29,990
我知道
I know.

458
00:16:30,350 --> 00:16:31,300
你觉得汉利·福尔松在聘用女性上的
What do you think Hanley Folsom's

459
00:16:31,300 --> 00:16:33,490
私人标准是什么
personal opinion is on hiring women?

460
00:16:34,420 --> 00:16:36,730
他觉得我们不够优秀
Uh, that he doesn't think we're good enough,

461
00:16:36,730 --> 00:16:38,780
但是  他不会摆在明面儿上
but, I mean, it's not like he would say it out loud.

462
00:16:38,780 --> 00:16:39,850
在公司不会
Not at work.

463
00:16:41,730 --> 00:16:44,940
所以你需要拿到他的私人信件
Which is why you need access to his personal correspondence.

464
00:16:44,940 --> 00:16:46,780
-答对了  -但那是违法的
- Exactly. - That's outside the scope.

465
00:16:46,780 --> 00:16:48,400
那我们找个不违法的办法
Well, let's find a way to put it inside the scope.

466
00:16:48,400 --> 00:16:49,180
你有什么想法吗
Do you have any ideas?

467
00:16:49,180 --> 00:16:50,540
没有  但是我有62个盒子
No, but I have 62 boxes

468
00:16:50,540 --> 00:16:52,330
和12个小时去发现个想法
and 12 hours to find an idea.

469
00:16:52,330 --> 00:16:54,080
正是我要做的  走吧
Exactly what I need to do-- let's go.

470
00:16:57,330 --> 00:17:00,160
-告诉过你我能赢  -是我让着你
- I told you I'd win. - Maybe I let you win.

471
00:17:00,160 --> 00:17:02,170
你这辈子就没让过别人
You've never let anybody win anything in your whole life.

472
00:17:02,170 --> 00:17:03,560
现在怎么开始让着别人了
Why would you start now?

473
00:17:04,280 --> 00:17:05,770
那我要求重新比赛
Now I get to demand a rematch.

474
00:17:05,770 --> 00:17:07,780
我来主持取证
And I get to lead the deposition.

475
00:17:08,310 --> 00:17:09,970
帕克维尔  密苏里
Parkville, Missouri--

476
00:17:10,310 --> 00:17:12,710
这么多地方却在这碰到你  哈维
of all the places to run into you, Harvey.

477
00:17:13,750 --> 00:17:14,970
很高兴你来了
Glad you could make it.

478
00:17:14,970 --> 00:17:15,760
差点来不了
I almost didn't.

479
00:17:15,760 --> 00:17:17,160
我正在去贝克尔斯菲的路上
I was on my way to Bakersfield--

480
00:17:17,160 --> 00:17:20,000
毕竟  哈维·斯佩克特订了去那儿的机票
after all, Harvey Specter had a flight booked there--

481
00:17:20,150 --> 00:17:21,800
突然我想到一件事
When, suddenly, I had a thought.

482
00:17:21,800 --> 00:17:23,170
哈维会怎么做
What would Harvey do?

483
00:17:23,170 --> 00:17:24,840
所以我查了一下
So I checked,

484
00:17:24,960 --> 00:17:27,200
达娜·斯科特的飞机是飞来这的
and Dana Scott's flight plan was here.

485
00:17:27,850 --> 00:17:31,780
谁都逃不了联邦航空局的管制啊
Can't get around those pesky F.A.A. regulations, can you?

486
00:17:31,780 --> 00:17:32,940
希望你最好把每个城市都掌控了
I hope you've got all the cities covered,

487
00:17:32,940 --> 00:17:34,540
因为我们每个地方都派了人
'cause we've got people everywhere.

488
00:17:34,640 --> 00:17:36,560
财力雄厚
Deep pockets.

489
00:17:36,810 --> 00:17:38,430
达娜·斯科特  很荣幸见到你
Dana Scott. A pleasure.

490
00:17:38,430 --> 00:17:39,620
我可说不出这种话
I can't say the same.

491
00:17:39,620 --> 00:17:41,140
你的确喜欢女强人啊  哈维
You do like strong women, Harvey.

492
00:17:41,140 --> 00:17:42,390
你根本不喜欢女人
And you don't like women at all.

493
00:17:42,490 --> 00:17:44,030
她真可爱
Oh, she's cute.

494
00:17:44,130 --> 00:17:44,960
一定很有趣
This should be fun.

495
00:17:44,960 --> 00:17:46,790
我外甥女给我打电话
Oh, I'm just getting a call from my niece

496
00:17:46,790 --> 00:17:48,430
要我帮她做作业
who needs help with her homework.

497
00:17:50,460 --> 00:17:51,390
有什么发现
What do you got?

498
00:17:51,400 --> 00:17:53,630
我知道他们为什么提拔凯瑟琳·米切尔了
I know why they promoted Cathleen Mitchell.

499
00:17:55,340 --> 00:17:56,790
米切尔女士  您的职位是
What is your title, Ms. Mitchell?

500
00:17:56,790 --> 00:17:58,730
区域副总裁
Vice president, regional services.

501
00:17:58,730 --> 00:18:01,220
在你的区域管理层人员有多少
And how many management positions are there in your region?

502
00:18:01,220 --> 00:18:02,610
612
612.

503
00:18:02,610 --> 00:18:03,970
其中有多少是女性
And how many of those are women?

504
00:18:04,320 --> 00:18:05,200
41个
41.

505
00:18:05,220 --> 00:18:09,390
612里的41人  才6.6%
41 out of 612-- that's, uh, 6.6%.

506
00:18:09,390 --> 00:18:11,380
-四舍五入是6.7%  -还是别了
- 6.7%, if you round up. - Let's not.

507
00:18:11,380 --> 00:18:13,170
是谁制定的聘用政策
And who sets the hiring policy?

508
00:18:13,240 --> 00:18:14,510
聘用政策就是
The hiring policy is that we hire

509
00:18:14,510 --> 00:18:16,820
雇佣最适合这些岗位的人
the best applicant for each job.

510
00:18:16,930 --> 00:18:18,180
我有点糊涂了
I'm confused.

511
00:18:18,180 --> 00:18:20,750
女性天生就比不上男的吗
Are women inherently inferior, then?

512
00:18:20,750 --> 00:18:21,260
不是
No.

513
00:18:21,260 --> 00:18:22,890
那为什么你的公司
Well, then why is it that your company

514
00:18:22,890 --> 00:18:25,180
不希望女性担任有实权的岗位
doesn't want to promote women into positions of power?

515
00:18:25,180 --> 00:18:26,820
我就是实权的女人
I am in a position of power.

516
00:18:26,820 --> 00:18:30,920
是  但你和其他女人并不完全一样  对吗
Yes, but you're not exactly like other women, are you?

517
00:18:30,920 --> 00:18:31,670
哈维
Harvey?

518
00:18:31,670 --> 00:18:34,740
你申请了四次升职
You applied four times for management,

519
00:18:34,740 --> 00:18:36,550
每次都被拒绝
and you've been rejected every time,

520
00:18:36,550 --> 00:18:38,690
因为这些评价
due to reviews containing the terms

521
00:18:38,690 --> 00:18:42,570
“好胜心强”  “不友好”  “野心大”
"aggressive," "hostile," and "overly ambitious."

522
00:18:42,570 --> 00:18:44,440
但突然就变成了“勇于奉献”
and then, suddenly, you were "dedicated,"

523
00:18:44,440 --> 00:18:46,040
“勤劳肯干”  “乐于合作”
"hardworking," and "a team player."

524
00:18:46,040 --> 00:18:47,450
人是会变的  哈维
People change, Harvey.

525
00:18:47,450 --> 00:18:49,320
最后说一遍  你需要问正常的问题
And the last I checked, you have to ask a question.

526
00:18:49,320 --> 00:18:51,650
我会问  就是关于这个转变
I will, and it's about that change.

527
00:18:51,650 --> 00:18:54,290
09年你是不是患上子宫癌
Were you diagnosed with uterine cancer in 2009?

528
00:18:54,290 --> 00:18:56,230
-这和本案无关  -你结婚了吗
- That is not relevant. - Are you married?

529
00:18:56,230 --> 00:18:57,430
-这有什么  -你有孩子吗
- What does that-- - Do you have any children?

530
00:18:57,430 --> 00:18:58,810
-没有  -你能怀孩子吗
- No. - Can you have any children?

531
00:18:58,810 --> 00:19:01,190
哈维  你过分了
This is beyond the pale, Harvey, even for you.

532
00:19:01,190 --> 00:19:02,970
要不要我把两周前  杰西卡·皮尔逊
Should I read your deposition of Jessica Pearson

533
00:19:02,970 --> 00:19:03,990
取证时的话读给你听
from two weeks ago?

534
00:19:03,990 --> 00:19:06,380
那是另一个案子  不可采纳为证据
That's a different case and inadmissible here.

535
00:19:06,380 --> 00:19:09,410
你是否在升职九个月之前
Did you or did you not have a hysterectomy

536
00:19:09,410 --> 00:19:11,350
做过子宫切除手术
that rendered you unable to have children

537
00:19:11,350 --> 00:19:12,820
使得你以后都不可能有孩子
nne months before you were promoted?

538
00:19:12,820 --> 00:19:14,810
-她不会回答的  -也许今天不回答
- She is not going to answer. - Maybe not today.

539
00:19:14,810 --> 00:19:16,760
但是记载在案
But it will become part of the record.

540
00:19:16,760 --> 00:19:18,930
汉利·福尔松只提拔
Hanley Folsom only promotes

541
00:19:18,930 --> 00:19:23,540
不会为家庭挂心的女人
women whose attention to home and family isn't in question.

542
00:19:23,810 --> 00:19:25,090
除了一件事
Except for one thing.

543
00:19:25,090 --> 00:19:28,290
-福尔松先生之前不知道  -那是你说的
- Mr. Folsom didn't know. - So you say.

544
00:19:28,290 --> 00:19:30,400
他不知道  因为我没告诉任何人
He didn't know because I didn't tell anybody,

545
00:19:30,400 --> 00:19:31,740
因为这是我的私事
because it's my business.

546
00:19:31,740 --> 00:19:35,580
但他还是发现了  所以你才得到了晋升
Still, he found out, and that's why you were promoted.

547
00:19:35,580 --> 00:19:36,910
哈维  够了
Harvey, that's enough.

548
00:19:36,910 --> 00:19:38,460
自己看看  哈维
Will you look at that, Harvey?

549
00:19:38,520 --> 00:19:41,700
甚至斯科特女士都知道  未婚无后
Even Ms. Scott understands that being childless and unmarried

550
00:19:41,700 --> 00:19:43,970
并不是什么残疾
doesn't make you damaged goods.

551
00:19:45,340 --> 00:19:47,700
但如果你要依此构建辩论
But if that's how you're framing your argument,

552
00:19:48,000 --> 00:19:48,980
祝你好运
good luck.

553
00:19:49,700 --> 00:19:51,330
贝克尔斯菲见
We'll see you in Bakersfield...

554
00:19:52,140 --> 00:19:53,500
无处不见
And everywhere else.

555
00:20:00,140 --> 00:20:02,490
你怎么能不告诉我她做过子宫切除呢
How could you not tell me that she'd had a hysterectomy?

556
00:20:02,490 --> 00:20:05,020
因为我在来的路上才知道这个消息
Because I just got the information on my way into the room.

557
00:20:05,020 --> 00:20:07,630
你可以花五秒钟告诉我的
You could have taken five seconds to fill me in.

558
00:20:07,630 --> 00:20:10,270
我没告诉你  因为不确信你能唱好红脸
I didn't fill you in because I wasn't sure you could play good cop.

559
00:20:10,270 --> 00:20:11,700
你是不确信我能唱好红脸
Because you weren't sure that I could play it,

560
00:20:11,700 --> 00:20:13,870
还是就算我们在统一战线  你还是想赢我
or because even when we're on the samside, you still want to win?

561
00:20:13,870 --> 00:20:16,040
如果我之前告诉你  你可能是不会生气
If I told you, you wouldn't be pissed off.

562
00:20:16,040 --> 00:20:18,820
那就去找她  把我说成实打实的混蛋吧
Now you can go to her and call me an asshole with conviction.

563
00:20:18,820 --> 00:20:20,260
你真是混蛋
You're an asshole.

564
00:20:21,350 --> 00:20:23,110
等下
Wait a second.

565
00:20:24,270 --> 00:20:27,370
你在指责我求胜心太强吗
You're accusing me of still trying to win?

566
00:20:27,710 --> 00:20:29,980
你才是处处求胜的那个
You're the one who's still trying to win something.

567
00:20:29,980 --> 00:20:31,830
我早该想到
You know, I should have known.

568
00:20:32,050 --> 00:20:33,090
你永远都不会说明全部真相
It's never the whole story with you.

569
00:20:33,090 --> 00:20:34,710
到底发生了什么事
What the hell's really going on?

570
00:20:36,960 --> 00:20:38,700
上次你打败了我
You beat me last time.

571
00:20:38,980 --> 00:20:41,600
从此以后  爱德华·达比就不再认为我
And ever since then, Edward Darby hasn't seen me

572
00:20:41,600 --> 00:20:43,940
有资格当上冠名合伙人
as worthy of being a name partner.

573
00:20:43,940 --> 00:20:46,210
无论如何  库克绝不会让这种事情发生
Cooke would never allow that to happen, anyway.

574
00:20:46,210 --> 00:20:47,770
他受不了美国人
He can't stand Americans.

575
00:20:47,770 --> 00:20:48,800
库克退休了
Cooke retired,

576
00:20:48,800 --> 00:20:50,840
他觉得生活不仅仅是工作
and he decided there's more to life than work.

577
00:20:51,670 --> 00:20:53,480
如果你送上一场大胜仗
So, if you deliver a huge win...

578
00:20:54,610 --> 00:20:56,310
我就能将名字印在门上
I get my name on the door.

579
00:20:56,720 --> 00:20:58,050
你为什么之前不告诉我
Why didn't you just tell me that?

580
00:21:00,400 --> 00:21:04,280
你总是吃硬不吃软
You always respond to strength, not weakness.

581
00:21:05,600 --> 00:21:07,480
你看看  还真的糊弄到了我呢
Look at that. You really did fool me.

582
00:21:09,530 --> 00:21:11,920
要是我知道  你的演技那么好
If I had known that you were that good a performer,

583
00:21:11,920 --> 00:21:13,550
我肯定会让你唱红脸
I would've let you be good cop.

584
00:21:19,480 --> 00:21:21,970
库克真的觉得生活不仅仅是工作吗
Cooke really decided there's more to life than work?

585
00:21:21,970 --> 00:21:22,840
是啊
Yep.

586
00:21:24,720 --> 00:21:25,670
-懦夫  -懦夫
- Pussy. - Pussy.

587
00:21:31,250 --> 00:21:32,520
你去哪儿了
Um, where have you been?

588
00:21:32,520 --> 00:21:33,930
-我一直在这儿  -我一直在等你
- I've been right here. - I've been waiting for you.

589
00:21:33,930 --> 00:21:34,870
我看完了所有东西
I finished going through everything.

590
00:21:34,870 --> 00:21:36,800
我也是  都分类标记好了  就在这儿
Me too. It's all catalogued. It's right there.

591
00:21:36,800 --> 00:21:38,590
很好  因为我要用它…
Okay, good, 'cause I got to get it to--

592
00:21:39,210 --> 00:21:40,660
15到20呢
Where's 15 through 20?

593
00:21:42,620 --> 00:21:44,110
盒子就摆在这儿  瑞秋
The boxes are right there, Rachel.

594
00:21:44,110 --> 00:21:46,010
你怎么回事  别这样
What's the matter with you? Come on.

595
00:21:46,010 --> 00:21:47,010
你迟到了
You're late.

596
00:21:47,220 --> 00:21:49,130
卡特里娜一小时以前就把她的简报交给我了
Katrina handed me her briefs an hour ago.

597
00:21:49,130 --> 00:21:51,810
是  我把…大部分都搞定了
Um, yeah, I've, uh-- I got most of mine.

598
00:21:51,810 --> 00:21:52,750
大部分吗
Most?

599
00:21:54,040 --> 00:21:55,570
如果我不能指望你尽力
If I can't count on you for the effort,

600
00:21:55,570 --> 00:21:58,270
又怎么能指望你出成果呢
how the hell am I supposed to count on you for the results?

601
00:21:59,150 --> 00:22:01,580
抱歉  是我的错
I'm sorry. It was my fault.

602
00:22:01,580 --> 00:22:04,560
-我会做好的  -太晚了
- Um, I'll get it done. - Too late.

603
00:22:04,750 --> 00:22:05,720
现在我得联系丹尼尔·哈德曼
Now I have to call Daniel Hardman

604
00:22:05,720 --> 00:22:07,170
推迟计划  颜面尽失
and postpone and look like a fool.

605
00:22:07,170 --> 00:22:08,800
谢谢你啊  罗斯先生
Thank you, Mr. Ross.

606
00:22:11,780 --> 00:22:13,520
-迈克  -我不想听
- Mike-- - I don't want to hear it.

607
00:22:13,790 --> 00:22:15,170
干活吧
Get it done.

608
00:22:24,950 --> 00:22:27,030
-瑞秋  -在
- Rachel? - Yes.

609
00:22:27,030 --> 00:22:28,880
我是卡特里娜·班尼特  我们还没见过
Katrina Bennett. We haven't met yet.

610
00:22:28,880 --> 00:22:30,720
我知道你是谁  欢迎
Oh, I-I know who you are. Welcome.

611
00:22:30,860 --> 00:22:32,900
路易说你是这里最棒的律师助理
Louis says you're the best paralegal around.

612
00:22:33,830 --> 00:22:34,820
谢谢
Thank you.

613
00:22:36,200 --> 00:22:37,420
我需要把这个复印四十份
I need 40 copies of these,

614
00:22:37,420 --> 00:22:38,740
如果你能把标签也复制好
And if you can duplicate the tabs

615
00:22:38,740 --> 00:22:40,340
一小时内交给我
and have it back to me within in an hour,

616
00:22:40,340 --> 00:22:42,440
我感激不尽
I will be eternally in your debt.

617
00:22:43,250 --> 00:22:46,030
卡特里娜  抱歉  我做不到
Uh, Katrina, I'm so sorry. I just can't.

618
00:22:46,030 --> 00:22:47,510
我现在太忙了
I'm too busy right now.

619
00:22:48,230 --> 00:22:49,390
忙着干什么呢
Too busy on what?

620
00:22:49,450 --> 00:22:51,590
我在回顾文件  看看能不能找到门路
I'm going back through discovery to see if I can find a door

621
00:22:51,590 --> 00:22:53,990
进入福尔松的私人信件
into Folsom's personal correspondence.

622
00:22:53,990 --> 00:22:55,990
那可真是白费力气  谁让你干这事的
That's a wild-goose chase. Who put you on that?

623
00:22:55,990 --> 00:22:56,940
迈克·罗斯
Mike Ross.

624
00:22:56,940 --> 00:22:57,870
真遗憾你正忙着
Well, I'm sorry you're busy

625
00:22:57,870 --> 00:22:59,470
给一个第一年的新人干活儿
working on something for a first year.

626
00:22:59,470 --> 00:23:02,050
但经营合伙人要我做点事
But the managing partner asked me to do something,

627
00:23:02,050 --> 00:23:03,900
我可没告诉她我正忙着
and I didn't tell her I was too busy.

628
00:23:04,720 --> 00:23:05,670
是啊
Right.

629
00:23:05,850 --> 00:23:07,880
这是给同一个经营合伙人的
This is for the same managing partner.

630
00:23:08,790 --> 00:23:10,010
是  但不是她直接交办的
Yes, but she didn't ask for it.

631
00:23:10,010 --> 00:23:11,210
是迈克交给你的
Mike Ross did.

632
00:23:11,950 --> 00:23:14,500
我知道你考了法学院入学考试
Look, I know you've taken your LSATs,

633
00:23:14,500 --> 00:23:16,510
可能已经准备好成为律师了
and you may well be ready to be a lawyer.

634
00:23:16,650 --> 00:23:18,290
但眼下你还不是
But right now you're not.

635
00:23:18,450 --> 00:23:19,500
你就是个律师助理
You're a paralegal.

636
00:23:21,110 --> 00:23:24,030
我做我的工作  你最好也做好你的工作
I'm doing my job, and I need you to do yours.

637
00:23:36,490 --> 00:23:37,420
瑞秋  帮我个忙好吗
Rachel, do me a favor?

638
00:23:37,420 --> 00:23:38,520
你能暂停一下吗
Can you just put that on pause for a sec?

639
00:23:38,520 --> 00:23:39,380
因为我要复印一份文件
'Cause I need to make a copy.

640
00:23:39,380 --> 00:23:41,950
路易  不行  我正忙着做好本职工作
No, Louis, I can't. I'm busy doing my job.

641
00:23:43,400 --> 00:23:44,110
你说什么
Excuse me?

642
00:23:44,110 --> 00:23:45,600
你要像解雇哈罗德一样解雇我吗
What, do you want to fire me like you fired Harold?

643
00:23:45,600 --> 00:23:48,160
说实话  我不在乎
Because honestly, I-I-I don't give a shit.

644
00:23:52,310 --> 00:23:53,270
我懂了
I get it.

645
00:23:53,960 --> 00:23:56,830
瑞秋  我听说了哈佛的事
Rachel, listen, I know about the Harvard thing.

646
00:23:57,970 --> 00:23:59,620
-我觉得好极了  -你说什么
- And I think it's great. - What?

647
00:23:59,780 --> 00:24:00,980
是的  诺玛告诉我的
Yeah, Norma told me.

648
00:24:01,120 --> 00:24:03,040
瑞秋  我知道等待很艰难
Rachel, I know the waiting is hard,

649
00:24:03,040 --> 00:24:04,760
但你不会在这儿待太久了
but you're not going to be here for much longer.

650
00:24:05,370 --> 00:24:07,750
我对你有百分之百的信心
I got 100% faith in you.

651
00:24:09,350 --> 00:24:10,570
我没被录取
I didn't get in.

652
00:24:11,640 --> 00:24:12,170
什么
What?

653
00:24:12,170 --> 00:24:13,510
我就不明白了  我什么都…
I don't understand. I had everything--

654
00:24:13,510 --> 00:24:15,800
我的分数  入学考试成绩  家庭背景
My grades, the LSATs, I'm a legacy,

655
00:24:15,800 --> 00:24:17,090
我甚至都没自吹自擂
and I don't even puff myself up,

656
00:24:17,090 --> 00:24:18,810
面试顺风顺水
but I killed it at that interview.

657
00:24:18,810 --> 00:24:19,730
这没道理啊
That doesn't make any sense.

658
00:24:19,730 --> 00:24:21,320
你记得那个从哈佛来的女人吗
And do you remember that woman who came from Harvard?

659
00:24:21,320 --> 00:24:23,750
她谁都不喜欢  但我发誓她喜欢我
She didn't like anyone, but I swear, she loved me.

660
00:24:24,240 --> 00:24:25,190
希拉吗
Sheila?

661
00:24:25,580 --> 00:24:28,100
是的  希拉  希拉·赛斯
Yeah. Sheila--Sheila Zass.

662
00:24:28,100 --> 00:24:29,090
你记得
You remember.

663
00:24:29,820 --> 00:24:31,430
是啊  我记得
Yeah, I remember.

664
00:24:32,300 --> 00:24:33,640
有什么问题吗
Is there something wrong?

665
00:24:33,640 --> 00:24:35,180
是  的确有问题
Yep, there is something wrong.

666
00:24:36,180 --> 00:24:37,410
我相信你被冤枉了
I believe you were wronged.

667
00:24:38,140 --> 00:24:38,840
我相信你是
I believe you suffered

668
00:24:38,840 --> 00:24:41,010
一场误会的牺牲品
the slings and arrows of outrageous wrongness.

669
00:24:41,170 --> 00:24:42,580
而我不会接受
and I will not have it.

670
00:24:43,220 --> 00:24:44,250
这话什么意思
What does that mean?

671
00:24:44,250 --> 00:24:46,200
意思是我会纠正局面
That means that I'm going to rectify this situation,

672
00:24:46,200 --> 00:24:48,180
因为你  赞恩小姐  你会进入哈佛的
Because you, Miss Zane, you're going to Harvard.

673
00:24:52,870 --> 00:24:54,060
看起来有人旅行愉快啊
Looks like somebody had a good trip.

674
00:24:54,060 --> 00:24:56,380
-并不尽然  -尽管航程挺有意思
- Not exactly. - Though the plane ride was fun.

675
00:24:56,580 --> 00:24:58,970
只要没碰上气流颠簸
As long as you didn't hit any turbulence.

676
00:25:00,290 --> 00:25:01,380
杰西卡要见你
Jessica wants to see you.

677
00:25:02,690 --> 00:25:03,670
我一会儿就回来
I'll be right back.

678
00:25:04,070 --> 00:25:05,660
其实  她想见你们两个
Actually, she wants to see both of you.

679
00:25:05,970 --> 00:25:07,650
杰西卡也要见我吗
Jessica wants to see me too?

680
00:25:07,970 --> 00:25:10,990
也不是  你老板要见你
Not exactly. Your boss wants to see you.

681
00:25:13,630 --> 00:25:15,860
我会让礼宾部去找找…
I'll just ask the concierge to find something--

682
00:25:15,860 --> 00:25:18,450
-你好  -达娜
- Hello. - Ah, Dana.

683
00:25:18,450 --> 00:25:21,170
这大概就是他本人了
And this must be the man himself.

684
00:25:21,170 --> 00:25:22,480
爱德华·达比
Edward Darby.

685
00:25:22,740 --> 00:25:25,860
他似乎一点不乏味  也没那么老
He doesn't seem stodgy at all, or that old.

686
00:25:25,860 --> 00:25:28,300
你真该见见我的全部
You should see me in my altogether.

687
00:25:28,300 --> 00:25:29,000
算了吧
Pass.

688
00:25:29,000 --> 00:25:30,130
非常好
Fair enough.

689
00:25:32,320 --> 00:25:35,110
爱德华过来评估他的投资
Edward stopped in to take stock of his investment.

690
00:25:35,110 --> 00:25:36,310
进行得怎么样了
So how are we?

691
00:25:36,310 --> 00:25:37,400
按照计划执行着
We're right on schedule.

692
00:25:38,700 --> 00:25:39,730
达娜
Dana?

693
00:25:39,730 --> 00:25:42,240
我们扔了手榴弹  只等爆炸
We've dropped a grenade. We're just waiting for it to go off.

694
00:25:42,240 --> 00:25:44,950
-就是还没爆炸  -罗马不是一天建成的
- Meaning it hasn't. - Rome wasn't built in a day.

695
00:25:44,950 --> 00:25:47,250
说得好  我不用飞跃大西洋了
Excellent point. I needn't have crossed the pond.

696
00:25:47,250 --> 00:25:48,660
但你还是来了
And yet, here you are.

697
00:25:51,140 --> 00:25:53,770
正如我向杰西卡坦言的
Well, as I confessed to Jessica,

698
00:25:53,770 --> 00:25:56,310
在我们的小投机中  我有个隐藏的动机
I have an ulterior motive in our little venture.

699
00:25:57,450 --> 00:25:58,640
丹尼尔·哈德曼
Daniel Hardman.

700
00:26:00,490 --> 00:26:02,650
我已经明确表达过不满了
I've had the distinct displeasure.

701
00:26:02,650 --> 00:26:05,250
所以我请求他提升一个等级
So I have asked him to step it up a notch.

702
00:26:08,470 --> 00:26:11,370
很好  全线出击
Nice. Attack him on all fronts.

703
00:26:11,370 --> 00:26:13,060
我们的客户遍布全球
We have clients everywhere.

704
00:26:13,060 --> 00:26:14,800
找他的茬
Finding a bone of contention with him

705
00:26:14,800 --> 00:26:17,050
是我能做的最简单的贡献了
seemed the least I could contribute.

706
00:26:17,050 --> 00:26:19,130
还有那1200万英磅
Along with 12 million pounds.

707
00:26:19,130 --> 00:26:22,150
我讨厌谈论钱  我更喜欢挣钱
I hate talking numbers. I prefer raking them in.

708
00:26:22,710 --> 00:26:25,140
我达成了此行的目的
Well, I've done what I came to do.

709
00:26:25,140 --> 00:26:27,230
就不给你们添麻烦了
Now I'm going to get out of your way.

710
00:26:27,230 --> 00:26:29,850
真高兴来到这里
Nice to put a face to all this.

711
00:26:29,850 --> 00:26:31,890
还有一副美丽的面容
And a lovely face, it turns out.

712
00:26:32,540 --> 00:26:33,540
谢谢称赞  爱德华
Thank you, Edward.

713
00:26:33,540 --> 00:26:34,950
我说的是你的男部下
I was referring to your man.

714
00:26:36,480 --> 00:26:39,180
我就等着手榴弹爆炸了
I'll be waiting for that detonation.

715
00:26:39,720 --> 00:26:42,140
我相信那是迟早的事
I trust it will come through.

716
00:26:46,920 --> 00:26:48,020
你找我
You wanted to see me?

717
00:26:48,350 --> 00:26:48,950
对
Yeah.

718
00:26:51,160 --> 00:26:53,160
我想解释一下之前的情况
I wanted to explain about earlier.

719
00:26:53,160 --> 00:26:54,960
不必了  没事  是我小题大做了
You don't have to. It's fine. I overreacted.

720
00:26:54,960 --> 00:26:56,380
行  那就不说这个
Okay, then I won't.

721
00:26:56,380 --> 00:26:58,370
我就告诉你我找到你需要的东西了
I will just tell you I found what you needed.

722
00:26:58,370 --> 00:27:00,240
怎么  你看完剩下的全部文件了
What, like you went through the rest of the files?

723
00:27:00,240 --> 00:27:02,530
不  我找到你需要的东西了
No. I found what you needed.

724
00:27:03,720 --> 00:27:04,720
-权限  -汉利·福尔松
- Access? - Hanley Folsom.

725
00:27:04,720 --> 00:27:05,760
-私人的  -正确
- Personal? - Bingo.

726
00:27:05,760 --> 00:27:07,770
天呐  这时机真是再好不过了
Oh, my God, that couldn't have come at a better time.

727
00:27:07,770 --> 00:27:08,820
我本可以早点搞定的
I would have found them for you sooner,

728
00:27:08,820 --> 00:27:10,530
但我得帮卡特里娜复印什么鬼文件
but I had to copy some bullshit for Katrina.

729
00:27:10,530 --> 00:27:12,760
你为何不直接跟她说你在帮我的忙
Why didn't you just tell her you were working for me?

730
00:27:12,760 --> 00:27:14,410
我就是告诉了她我在帮你做什么
I told her exactly what I was doing for you.

731
00:27:14,410 --> 00:27:16,370
但她没有…  老天
And she didn't-- Oh, God.

732
00:27:16,370 --> 00:27:18,770
别放心上  我懂  她也对我如法炮制过
Never mind. I get it. She did the same thing to me.

733
00:27:18,770 --> 00:27:19,830
说一通第五年律师的屁话
She pulls that fifth-year crap,

734
00:27:19,830 --> 00:27:20,950
你就完全不想再跟她争辩了
and then you don't feel like dealing.

735
00:27:20,950 --> 00:27:22,410
谁说不是啊
You have no idea.

736
00:27:22,410 --> 00:27:23,530
你发现了什么
What do we have?

737
00:27:24,010 --> 00:27:25,620
足够你起草动议了
Enough for you to write a motion.

738
00:27:27,280 --> 00:27:29,490
-他看起来人挺好的  -他生气了
- He seems nice. - He was pissed.

739
00:27:29,490 --> 00:27:32,090
那模样是生气  那他开心时什么样
That was pissed? What does happy look like?

740
00:27:32,090 --> 00:27:33,770
英国佬嘛  差不多一样吧
He's British-- pretty much the same thing.

741
00:27:33,770 --> 00:27:34,880
你怎么知道他生气了
Then how'd you know he was pissed?

742
00:27:34,880 --> 00:27:36,870
-换作你不气吗  -我的确生气
- Wouldn't you be? - I am.

743
00:27:36,870 --> 00:27:38,350
我们还没搞定凯瑟琳·米切尔
We haven't turned Cathleen Mitchell yet.

744
00:27:38,350 --> 00:27:39,870
你这个红脸唱砸了
Your good cop failed.

745
00:27:39,870 --> 00:27:41,430
不  是你的计划砸了
No, your move failed.

746
00:27:42,640 --> 00:27:44,020
杰西卡倒是没发火
Well, Jessica took it well.

747
00:27:44,020 --> 00:27:46,480
那是因为刚才有人在  之后够我受的
Because she had company. I'll hear about it later.

748
00:27:46,880 --> 00:27:47,910
他经常这样吗
Does he do that--

749
00:27:47,910 --> 00:27:49,830
顺道来喝壶茶
just pop in for a spot of tea?

750
00:27:49,830 --> 00:27:51,310
那可是1200万英镑
It's 12 million pounds.

751
00:27:53,040 --> 00:27:54,380
你没料到他会来
You weren't expecting him.

752
00:27:55,380 --> 00:27:56,190
不
No...

753
00:27:56,190 --> 00:27:57,490
我没料到
I wasn't.

754
00:27:58,870 --> 00:28:01,090
但这对他是笔大投资  哈维
But this is a big investment for him, Harvey.

755
00:28:01,090 --> 00:28:02,980
他投入的只是钱
His investment is only money.

756
00:28:02,980 --> 00:28:05,660
对我来说  可是整间律所
For me, it's my whole firm.

757
00:28:06,790 --> 00:28:08,840
打扰一下  哈维  你有空吗
Excuse me. Harvey, do you have a minute?

758
00:28:12,850 --> 00:28:15,700
你来得正好  我拿到权限了
You got here just in time. I'm getting us access.

759
00:28:15,700 --> 00:28:17,630
-汉利·福尔松吗  -正是
- Hanley Folsom? - Bingo.

760
00:28:17,630 --> 00:28:19,920
如果你说的是７月29日他工作邮箱
Well, if you're talking about the July 29th reference

761
00:28:19,920 --> 00:28:21,750
发到私人邮箱的内容
in his business email to his personal email,

762
00:28:21,750 --> 00:28:23,530
-那你就太晚了  -什么
- then you're too late. - What?

763
00:28:23,530 --> 00:28:25,750
卡特里娜一小时前就把传票给我了
Katrina gave me the subpoena an hour ago.

764
00:28:26,600 --> 00:28:27,860
看来杰西卡让她参与此案
I guess it's a good thing Jessica put her

765
00:28:27,860 --> 00:28:29,070
的确是明智之举
on the case after all.

766
00:28:42,140 --> 00:28:44,460
如果别人偷我的东西  我就认为是针对我
When people steal from me, I take it personally.

767
00:28:45,510 --> 00:28:47,520
-你是要传讯我吗  -你支开了瑞秋
- Are you subpoenaing me? - You diverted Rachel.

768
00:28:47,520 --> 00:28:49,800
然后私自盗用了我的想法
And then you pursued my idea yourself.

769
00:28:49,800 --> 00:28:51,100
你的想法
Your idea?

770
00:28:51,100 --> 00:28:52,410
你想否认吗
Are you denying it?

771
00:28:52,410 --> 00:28:55,400
不  你说我们得起飞  我就造了架飞机
No, you said we needed to fly, so I built an airplane.

772
00:28:55,400 --> 00:28:56,930
然后直接飞进了哈维的办公室
And then flew it right into Harvey's office

773
00:28:56,930 --> 00:28:58,300
正好把功劳据为己有
just in time to take credit.

774
00:28:58,300 --> 00:29:00,040
我提议过跟你合作
I offered you a chance to work together.

775
00:29:00,040 --> 00:29:01,360
是你不愿意的
You didn't want to take it.

776
00:29:01,360 --> 00:29:02,520
你就会狡辩
You've always got an answer.

777
00:29:02,520 --> 00:29:04,570
你就知道指责别人
And you've always got an accusation.

778
00:29:05,010 --> 00:29:06,220
要么你现在
So either run to Harvey

779
00:29:06,220 --> 00:29:07,780
去找哈维  向他诉苦
and tell him your little tale of woe,

780
00:29:07,780 --> 00:29:09,210
要么老老实实为福尔松一案做准备
or get to work prepping for Folsom,

781
00:29:09,210 --> 00:29:10,390
像我这样
like I am.

782
00:29:21,810 --> 00:29:22,720
路易
Louis.

783
00:29:22,720 --> 00:29:23,750
希拉
Sheila.

784
00:29:24,780 --> 00:29:27,470
-我要面试的人呢  -被我打发走了
- Where's my interviewee? - I dispatched him.

785
00:29:27,470 --> 00:29:28,650
这太无理取闹了
That's unacceptable.

786
00:29:28,650 --> 00:29:30,880
-你才无理取闹  -什么
- You are unacceptable. - Excuse me?

787
00:29:33,130 --> 00:29:34,440
你这么做非常不专业
You behaved unprofessionally.

788
00:29:34,440 --> 00:29:36,530
我从来都很专业
I never behave unprofessionally.

789
00:29:36,530 --> 00:29:38,590
行  好吧
Okay, fine.

790
00:29:38,590 --> 00:29:39,550
滑雪面罩和椰子油
Ski mask and coconut oil?

791
00:29:39,550 --> 00:29:40,760
那是私下的事
That was personal.

792
00:29:40,910 --> 00:29:43,270
但是你让私人情绪影响了专业判断
But you let the personal color the professional,

793
00:29:43,270 --> 00:29:44,890
瑞秋·赞恩不应该成为你
and Rachel Zane will not be a casualty

794
00:29:44,890 --> 00:29:46,020
胡乱泄愤的炮灰
of your misplaced anger.

795
00:29:46,020 --> 00:29:49,030
“胡乱”  你让我像傻瓜一样
"Misplaced"? You made me look the fool.

796
00:29:49,030 --> 00:29:50,330
是我像傻瓜
I looked the fool.

797
00:29:50,330 --> 00:29:52,900
你是受到了附加伤害  不是我的错
You were collateral damage-- not my fault.

798
00:29:52,900 --> 00:29:54,280
就更不是赞恩女士的错
And it certainly wasn't Ms. Zane's fault.

799
00:29:54,280 --> 00:29:57,160
所以你是来这当她护卫骑士的吗
So you're here to be her knight in shining armor.

800
00:29:57,160 --> 00:29:58,460
我是来纠正这个错误的
I'm here to right a wrong.

801
00:29:58,460 --> 00:30:00,180
-真是非常…  -非常什么
- How very-- - very what?

802
00:30:02,010 --> 00:30:02,770
高尚
Noble.

803
00:30:07,530 --> 00:30:08,940
是  没错
Yeah, it is.

804
00:30:11,310 --> 00:30:12,720
你必须撤回你的决定〔双关：解开扣子〕
And you're going to undo this.

805
00:30:15,510 --> 00:30:16,300
好啊
I am.

806
00:30:18,220 --> 00:30:19,330
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.

807
00:30:20,490 --> 00:30:22,130
但你是始作俑者
But it's what you've caused.

808
00:30:24,070 --> 00:30:24,970
我
I...

809
00:30:25,680 --> 00:30:26,880
不接受拒绝
will not be denied.

810
00:30:26,880 --> 00:30:28,350
那就来收取你种下的果实吧
Then come reap what you've sowed.

811
00:30:28,350 --> 00:30:30,060
-看招  -来吧
- Have at you. - Joust me.

812
00:30:34,050 --> 00:30:35,150
我不在乎代价是什么
I don't care what it takes.

813
00:30:35,150 --> 00:30:37,720
我们要赶在卡特里娜之前找到制胜关键
We need to get to that smoking gun before Katrina does.

814
00:30:37,720 --> 00:30:39,610
她已经找到了
She already found it.

815
00:30:41,840 --> 00:30:43,720
卡特里娜拿去给米西·迪特勒复印了
Katrina gave it to Missy Dietler to make copies.

816
00:30:43,720 --> 00:30:45,810
我确定现在杰西卡已经拿到手了
I'm sure it's already in Jessica's hands by now.

817
00:30:47,920 --> 00:30:49,930
等等  米西·迪特勒
Wait a minute. Missy Dietler?

818
00:30:50,870 --> 00:30:53,210
她完工之前得休息四次喝咖啡
She's going to take four coffee breaks before she's done.

819
00:30:53,210 --> 00:30:54,110
还得再休息四次才能
She's going to take four coffee breaks

820
00:30:54,110 --> 00:30:55,450
喝完她的咖啡
before she finishes her coffee break.

821
00:30:55,450 --> 00:30:56,620
也就是说文件可能
Which means it's probably still

822
00:30:56,620 --> 00:30:58,420
还在复印机里
in the copy machine right now.

823
00:30:58,420 --> 00:31:00,040
米西怎么可能
Missy's not going to leave the documents

824
00:31:00,040 --> 00:31:01,320
把文件留在复印机里
just sitting in the copy machine.

825
00:31:01,320 --> 00:31:03,140
对  但她可能已经扫瞄过了
No, but she probably already scanned them.

826
00:31:03,960 --> 00:31:06,260
我们只需要她的密码就行
So all we need is her code.

827
00:31:07,100 --> 00:31:09,850
你这可是要窃取别人的成果
You're talking about stealing someone's work.

828
00:31:09,850 --> 00:31:13,640
这人骗过你  偷过我的东西
Mm, someone who lied to you, stole from me,

829
00:31:13,640 --> 00:31:15,910
还让我俩跟傻瓜一样
and made us both look like fools.

830
00:31:15,910 --> 00:31:17,610
你要是觉得不安  想想那些事
Look, if you have any qualms, think about it.

831
00:31:17,610 --> 00:31:18,430
我们是一条船上的
We're all on the same team.

832
00:31:18,430 --> 00:31:20,510
这事越早结束  对大家都越好
The faster this gets done, the better for everyone.

833
00:31:20,510 --> 00:31:21,830
你真会狡辩
Oh, you got an answer for everything.

834
00:31:21,830 --> 00:31:22,820
她也一样
Well, so does she.

835
00:31:24,330 --> 00:31:25,530
你真要这么做吗
Are you sure you want to do this?

836
00:31:25,530 --> 00:31:26,220
没错
Yes.

837
00:31:28,830 --> 00:31:31,270
喂喂  你这是干什么
Uh, whoa. What are you doing?

838
00:31:31,270 --> 00:31:33,200
曼宁汉从我来第一天就喜欢我了
Manningham's had a crush on me since the day I got here.

839
00:31:33,200 --> 00:31:35,430
就是我想知道的话  他连他妈妈的
He would give me his mother's social security number

840
00:31:35,430 --> 00:31:36,230
社保帐号都会告诉我
if I asked him for it.

841
00:31:36,230 --> 00:31:37,960
瑞秋  我们时间不多了
Okay, Rachel, we don't have much time.

842
00:31:37,960 --> 00:31:39,280
我需要百分百的把握
I need a sure thing here.

843
00:31:39,280 --> 00:31:40,370
迈克
Mike...

844
00:31:42,820 --> 00:31:44,370
我就是百分百的把握
I am a sure thing.

845
00:31:51,800 --> 00:31:52,970
好吧  姑且试一试吧
Yeah, I mean, give it a shot.

846
00:31:52,970 --> 00:31:54,970
也许不会成功的  但…
It probably won't work, but, um...

847
00:31:58,180 --> 00:32:01,900
你真暴力  不过暴力得很甜美
That was brutal, deliciously brutal.

848
00:32:01,900 --> 00:32:04,540
而你的报复之举让我愈发恼羞成怒
And your act of vengeance raised my ire.

849
00:32:05,760 --> 00:32:08,280
先生  你真不愧是骑士
You, sir, are a knight.

850
00:32:09,340 --> 00:32:11,140
现在是时候纠正你的错误了
And now it is time to right what is wrong.

851
00:32:14,240 --> 00:32:16,330
希拉  你公报私仇让我很荣幸
Look, Sheila, I'm flattered by what you did,

852
00:32:16,330 --> 00:32:18,290
但这不公平
but this is not fair,

853
00:32:18,640 --> 00:32:20,050
你也知道这站不住脚
and you know it can't stand.

854
00:32:21,590 --> 00:32:25,030
路易  随便从这堆简历里挑一张
Louis, pull a resume from the stack--any one.

855
00:32:25,550 --> 00:32:26,270
读读看
Read it.

856
00:32:29,460 --> 00:32:30,220
好吧
Sure.

857
00:32:33,630 --> 00:32:36,190
耶鲁大学  优等成绩  均分3.9
Magna Cum Laude, Yale, 3.9 GPA.

858
00:32:36,190 --> 00:32:36,930
再挑一个
Another one.

859
00:32:40,440 --> 00:32:43,490
乔治城大学  最优成绩  均分4.3
Summa Cum Laude, Georgetown, 4.3 GPA.

860
00:32:43,490 --> 00:32:45,060
听着  我懂  我知道你是想…
Listen, I get it. I know what you're trying--

861
00:32:45,060 --> 00:32:46,840
这都是被我拒绝的
That's my reject pile.

862
00:32:51,920 --> 00:32:53,280
我是个专业人士
I am a professional.

863
00:32:53,280 --> 00:32:54,720
绝不会因为我对的感情
I would never let my feelings for you

864
00:32:54,720 --> 00:32:56,340
妨碍我录取学生
sway me against a candidate.

865
00:32:56,340 --> 00:32:57,970
好吧  但你得为了那感情
Okay, but you have to let them

866
00:32:57,970 --> 00:33:00,440
录取一个学生
sway you for a candidate.

867
00:33:01,070 --> 00:33:02,510
你不能要求我这么做
You can't ask me that.

868
00:33:02,920 --> 00:33:05,010
我们是纽约最好的律师事务所
Rachel Zane is the best paralegal

869
00:33:05,010 --> 00:33:06,800
而瑞秋·赞恩是其中最好的法律助理
in the best law firm in New York.

870
00:33:06,800 --> 00:33:09,610
出身于最著名学府的顶尖律师
She is relied upon by the best lawyers

871
00:33:09,610 --> 00:33:11,890
都依赖于她
who have graduated from the best university.

872
00:33:11,890 --> 00:33:13,320
她是最棒的
The woman is crimson.

873
00:33:13,320 --> 00:33:14,650
那让我把谁踢出去呢
So who do I knock out?

874
00:33:17,700 --> 00:33:18,890
我答应过她
I promised her.

875
00:33:18,890 --> 00:33:22,740
路易  我喜欢这姑娘  真的
Louis, I liked her. I did.

876
00:33:23,890 --> 00:33:25,780
你只能据实相告了
You're just going to have to tell her the truth.

877
00:33:27,340 --> 00:33:29,850
有时候优秀还远远不够
Sometimes good isn't good enough.

878
00:33:33,650 --> 00:33:36,210
什么时候才能看到爆炸
So how's that detonation coming?

879
00:33:36,480 --> 00:33:37,690
引线很长
Long fuse.

880
00:33:37,690 --> 00:33:39,840
你这是告诉我永远不会引爆了吗
Is that your way of telling me that it's never going off?

881
00:33:39,840 --> 00:33:40,620
要是真不引爆
Well, if it doesn't,

882
00:33:40,620 --> 00:33:42,990
你不是还有詹姆士·邦德帮你摆平吗
you could always have James Bond take care of it for you.

883
00:33:40,620 --> 00:33:42,990
哈维是的指爱德华·达比

884
00:33:42,990 --> 00:33:43,880
这倒提醒了我
That reminds me.

885
00:33:43,880 --> 00:33:45,660
普茜·格罗进展得如何
How are things going with Pussy Galore?

886
00:33:43,880 --> 00:33:50,870
在007电影《金手指》中  普茜·格罗是金手指的机师  后爱上邦德

887
00:33:46,110 --> 00:33:48,420
我想这个时候
Um, I believe, at this point,

888
00:33:48,420 --> 00:33:50,870
她还在为金手指〔邦德的对手〕发射导弹呢
she's still flying missions for Goldfinger.

889
00:33:52,250 --> 00:33:54,370
“不  邦德先生  我希望你死”
"No, Mr. Bond, I expect you to die."

890
00:33:54,370 --> 00:33:55,620
你来干什么
What the hell are you doing here?

891
00:33:55,620 --> 00:33:57,120
我们可以赢下帕克维尔
We can win Parkville.

892
00:34:00,130 --> 00:34:01,390
这是一切的关键
This is the key to everything.

893
00:34:02,880 --> 00:34:05,490
那我们得让普茜·葛罗尔回到飞机上
Well, then we need to get Pussy Galore back on that plane.

894
00:34:20,300 --> 00:34:21,540
记住我跟你说的
Just remember what I told you.

895
00:34:21,540 --> 00:34:23,020
无论发生什么
No matter what happens--

896
00:34:24,430 --> 00:34:27,540
三个臭皮匠啊
Well, if it isn't the three stooges.

897
00:34:26,830 --> 00:34:29,330
三个臭皮匠分别是  蘑菇头  商普和胖子

898
00:34:27,540 --> 00:34:29,180
我要当那个胖子
Oh, dibs on Curly.

899
00:34:29,180 --> 00:34:30,700
二位能否和我们
Would you gentlemen mind accompanying us

900
00:34:30,700 --> 00:34:31,760
一起去会议室
to the conference room?

901
00:34:33,530 --> 00:34:34,880
她在这里干什么
What is she doing here?

902
00:34:35,450 --> 00:34:36,330
达娜·斯科特吗
Dana Scott?

903
00:34:36,330 --> 00:34:38,490
她是这件案子的出庭律师
She's the attorney of record on the case.

904
00:34:38,490 --> 00:34:40,260
他指的是我的员工
He's referring to my employee.

905
00:34:40,260 --> 00:34:42,970
她现在正在读这个
Oh, well, at the moment, she's reading this.

906
00:34:42,970 --> 00:34:44,990
你用私人账号发出的
An email you wrote from your personal account

907
00:34:44,990 --> 00:34:46,860
有关聘请米切尔小姐的电邮
on the subject of hiring Ms. Mitchell.

908
00:34:47,380 --> 00:34:49,570
接下来  我们就拿附件给她看
And next, we'll show her the attachment.

909
00:34:49,570 --> 00:34:51,140
不在你们的副本上
It wasn't on your copy.

910
00:34:51,140 --> 00:34:52,860
奇怪的是  这也不在我们的
Oddly enough, it wasn't on ours either.

911
00:34:52,860 --> 00:34:54,650
但迈克找到了原版
Mike managed to find the original.

912
00:34:54,650 --> 00:34:55,920
我们得花点时间回顾一下
We'll need time to review this.

913
00:34:55,920 --> 00:34:57,690
回顾  这是他写的
Review it? He wrote it.

914
00:34:57,690 --> 00:34:59,170
你知道她不可能有孩子
You knew she couldn't have children.

915
00:34:59,170 --> 00:35:01,030
所以你改了她的评议
That's why you changed her review,

916
00:35:01,030 --> 00:35:02,510
还提拔了她
and that's why you promoted her.

917
00:35:02,510 --> 00:35:04,640
她一旦看到  就会加入诉讼
And when she sees it, she'll join the suit,

918
00:35:04,640 --> 00:35:06,400
你不可能赢的
and you won't stand a chance.

919
00:35:09,450 --> 00:35:10,930
那封电邮又不能证明他的想法
That email doesn't prove a pattern.

920
00:35:10,930 --> 00:35:13,250
-证明了他对她做了什么  -一个案子而已
- It proves what he did to her. - It's one case.

921
00:35:13,790 --> 00:35:15,360
还有44个  咱们等着瞧
We'll see you at the next 44.

922
00:35:15,360 --> 00:35:16,490
同时
In the meantime,

923
00:35:16,490 --> 00:35:18,120
我们不会参与这次取证
we won't be participating in that deposition

924
00:35:18,120 --> 00:35:20,460
除非你们把米切尔女士送上飞机
until you put Ms. Mitchell back on a plane.

925
00:35:25,500 --> 00:35:27,680
皮尔逊

926
00:35:37,630 --> 00:35:38,590
怎么样了
How'd it go?

927
00:35:38,590 --> 00:35:39,810
还没结束
It's not over yet.

928
00:35:39,810 --> 00:35:41,310
但你不会再受杰西卡冷遇了吧
But you're out of the doghouse with Jessica?

929
00:35:41,310 --> 00:35:42,070
不会了
Out.

930
00:35:43,990 --> 00:35:44,600
什么
What?

931
00:35:44,700 --> 00:35:47,370
你还没说是怎么搞定曼宁汉的
You never said how it went with Manningham.

932
00:35:48,320 --> 00:35:50,270
我不会告诉你的
And I never will.

933
00:35:51,800 --> 00:35:54,240
这不是雌雄大盗吗
Well, if it isn't Bonnie and Clyde.

934
00:35:54,240 --> 00:35:55,710
你在我的办公室里干什么
What are you doing in my office?

935
00:35:55,710 --> 00:35:58,380
我以为你不关心你的东西
Well, I didn't think you cared to respect what's yours

936
00:35:58,380 --> 00:36:01,560
或者更应该说是我的东西
or, more to the point, what's mine.

937
00:36:01,560 --> 00:36:03,420
你的问题不是她  而是我
Your problem's not with her. It's with me.

938
00:36:03,420 --> 00:36:04,210
好的
Okay.

939
00:36:05,110 --> 00:36:07,180
你偷走了我的发现  自己也知道
You stole my discovery, and you know it.

940
00:36:07,180 --> 00:36:08,340
你是指被我转换行动计划的
Oh, you mean that piece of paper

941
00:36:08,340 --> 00:36:09,910
那篇文章吗
that I turned into a strategy?

942
00:36:09,910 --> 00:36:12,240
或是你称之为飞机的东西
Or, as you like to call it, an airplane.

943
00:36:12,650 --> 00:36:13,790
好的  没事
Okay, fine.

944
00:36:14,040 --> 00:36:16,110
我只是压线犯规
I put my toe over the line.

945
00:36:16,450 --> 00:36:17,450
你可是完全无视规则
You obliterated it.

946
00:36:17,450 --> 00:36:18,710
我很抱歉
Yeah. I'm so sorry.

947
00:36:18,710 --> 00:36:21,390
但昨天你可是以五年的资历
But yesterday you were the fifth-year authority

948
00:36:21,390 --> 00:36:23,520
来断定是非啊  所以我
on right and wrong, so I...

949
00:36:23,870 --> 00:36:25,350
我只是听取了你的意见
I was just taking your advice.

950
00:36:25,990 --> 00:36:27,030
那跟律师助理睡觉
And which side of right and wrong

951
00:36:27,030 --> 00:36:29,110
是对还是错呢
does sleeping with the paralegals fall on?

952
00:36:29,110 --> 00:36:31,070
从我的办公室滚出去
Get the hell out of my office.

953
00:36:32,320 --> 00:36:34,540
你说得对  那跟我没关系
You're right. That's none of my business.

954
00:36:35,540 --> 00:36:37,520
你要去上法学院是件好事
But it's a good thing you're going to law school,

955
00:36:37,520 --> 00:36:39,750
因为他们可能会和律师助理睡觉
Because they may sleep with the paralegals,

956
00:36:39,750 --> 00:36:41,360
但最终还得跟律师结婚
but they end up with the lawyers.

957
00:36:45,430 --> 00:36:46,430
当然  你一打电话
Of course, when you called,

958
00:36:46,430 --> 00:36:48,180
我就直接赶过来了  但必须说
I popped straight over, but I must say,

959
00:36:48,180 --> 00:36:51,230
在这个小苹果里  的确还有野蛮的影子
you do keep uncivilized hours in the little apple.

960
00:36:51,850 --> 00:36:53,440
应该说是大苹果〔纽约〕
It's the Big Apple.

961
00:36:53,440 --> 00:36:56,270
刚刚有人卖了我一件假Ｔ恤
Well, then someone's just sold me a counterfeit T-shirt.

962
00:36:56,270 --> 00:36:58,790
真幽默  我喜欢男人有幽默感
A sense of humor-- I love that in a man,

963
00:36:58,790 --> 00:37:01,240
因此我准备
which is why I'm prepared to consider

964
00:37:01,240 --> 00:37:02,770
接受你的提议
taking you up on your offer.

965
00:37:02,770 --> 00:37:04,800
我能问问是什么让你改变主意吗
Might I inquire what changed your mind?

966
00:37:08,490 --> 00:37:09,550
这是什么
What's this?

967
00:37:09,550 --> 00:37:11,990
我们过去五年的公司账目
Our books from the last five years.

968
00:37:11,990 --> 00:37:13,810
如果我们要合作  我希望你清楚
If we're going to do this, I want you to know

969
00:37:13,810 --> 00:37:16,170
你要投资的是什么样的公司
exactly what it is you're getting yourself into.

970
00:37:16,170 --> 00:37:17,700
现在从头开始吧
Now, start at the beginning.

971
00:37:17,900 --> 00:37:19,360
值得一读
It's a great read.

972
00:37:19,980 --> 00:37:22,070
你真是个了不起的女人
You are an impressive woman.

973
00:37:22,130 --> 00:37:24,900
你还了解不到一半呢
Oh, you don't know the half.

974
00:37:24,900 --> 00:37:26,990
那就承蒙教诲了
Well, here's to my further education.

975
00:37:44,690 --> 00:37:45,600
你迟到了
You're late.

976
00:37:46,330 --> 00:37:48,700
得先给我买杯饮料哦
That's not going to get you out of buying me a drink first.

977
00:37:50,190 --> 00:37:51,630
别扯淡了
No more bullshit.

978
00:37:52,440 --> 00:37:53,020
什么
What?

979
00:37:53,020 --> 00:37:55,020
我刚从杰西卡和你老板那里过来
I just left Jessica and your boss,

980
00:37:55,020 --> 00:37:56,510
我清楚我看到的是什么
and I know what I saw.

981
00:37:56,510 --> 00:37:57,640
他们勾搭到一块儿了
They're in bed together,

982
00:37:57,640 --> 00:37:59,130
我不是说他们发生关系
and I don't mean having sex.

983
00:37:59,130 --> 00:38:00,360
他们在讨论合并
They're talking merger.

984
00:38:00,360 --> 00:38:01,580
不是你看到的那样
It's not what it looks like.

985
00:38:01,580 --> 00:38:03,880
哈德曼可以另谋高就  我也可以
Hardman can check a plane, and I can check a plane.

986
00:38:03,880 --> 00:38:05,820
爱德华·达比跟你同一天飞过来
Edward Darby flew here the day you did.

987
00:38:05,820 --> 00:38:07,100
他不是偶然出现的
He didn't just pop in.

988
00:38:07,100 --> 00:38:08,720
他不该那样
He wasn't supposed to do that.

989
00:38:08,720 --> 00:38:09,640
你不只是想把名字印在公司大门上而已
You don't want your name on the door.

990
00:38:09,640 --> 00:38:11,260
而是想印在我的公司大门
You want your name on my door.

991
00:38:11,260 --> 00:38:14,050
我希望我们的名字印在同一扇门上
I want to see our names on the same door.

992
00:38:14,050 --> 00:38:15,500
是啊  如我所言
Yeah, like I said,

993
00:38:15,950 --> 00:38:17,200
你永远都不会说明全部真相
it's never the full story with you.

994
00:38:17,200 --> 00:38:18,600
我想亲口跟你说的
I wanted to be able to tell you myself.

995
00:38:18,600 --> 00:38:19,520
那你为什么没说
Then why didn't you tell me?

996
00:38:19,520 --> 00:38:21,450
因为他不让我说  除非他决定了
Because he wouldn't let me until he decided.

997
00:38:21,450 --> 00:38:23,160
显然  他没有跟你一起做决定
Well, evidently, he decided without you.

998
00:38:23,160 --> 00:38:24,890
对对  他提前行动了
Okay, okay. He jumped the gun.

999
00:38:24,890 --> 00:38:26,680
但他已经答应我了  哈维
But I have his promise, Harvey.

1000
00:38:26,680 --> 00:38:28,390
如果并购  他会提名我为合伙人
If we merge, he names me as partner,

1001
00:38:28,390 --> 00:38:30,750
而你是杰西卡唯一的选择
and Jessica's only choice is you.

1002
00:38:31,470 --> 00:38:33,500
我不需要你帮我把名字印到公司大门上
I don't need you to get my name on the door

1003
00:38:33,500 --> 00:38:35,690
就像我不需要你帮我赢这件案子一样
any more than I need you to win this case.

1004
00:38:35,690 --> 00:38:36,990
你知道吗  哈维
You know what, Harvey?

1005
00:38:37,090 --> 00:38:39,480
哈德曼离开以后 你一直被压制着
You have been outgunned ever since Hardman left.

1006
00:38:39,480 --> 00:38:40,970
而我是来帮你翻身的
I am bringing the guns.

1007
00:38:40,970 --> 00:38:42,690
这不就是你一直想要的吗
This is exactly what you've always wanted.

1008
00:38:42,690 --> 00:38:43,920
克服你的骄傲
Get over your pride.

1009
00:38:43,920 --> 00:38:46,400
我不会克服任何事
I'm not getting over anything.

1010
00:38:46,400 --> 00:38:48,460
这次合并也不可能成功
And this merger isn't happening.

1011
00:39:01,940 --> 00:39:04,460
杰西卡  爱德华
Jessica. Edward.

1012
00:39:04,460 --> 00:39:07,270
丹尼尔  米兰那件案子后就再没见过你
Daniel, haven't seen you since that business in Milan.

1013
00:39:07,270 --> 00:39:09,260
-那里气候很好 -够了
- Beautiful weather. - Oh, enough.

1014
00:39:09,260 --> 00:39:11,000
咱们可不是什么友好的对手  丹尼尔
We are not friendly adversaries, Daniel.

1015
00:39:11,000 --> 00:39:12,220
而且你要输了
And you're about to lose.

1016
00:39:12,220 --> 00:39:13,780
我的客户已经拒绝了
My client already said no.

1017
00:39:13,780 --> 00:39:15,840
我告诉他你以前挪用公款的事情后
He may no longer listen to you

1018
00:39:15,840 --> 00:39:18,610
他不会再相信你了
when I inform him of your prior embezzlement.

1019
00:39:19,470 --> 00:39:20,470
你告诉他的
You told him.

1020
00:39:20,470 --> 00:39:22,420
我什么都没对他说
I didn't tell him anything.

1021
00:39:22,420 --> 00:39:24,170
我自己发现的
I found it on my own.

1022
00:39:24,540 --> 00:39:25,430
爱德华和我要合并了
Edward and I are merging.

1023
00:39:25,440 --> 00:39:26,730
我得让他看看公司账目
I had to show him the books.

1024
00:39:26,730 --> 00:39:29,590
法律规定我必须看她的账目
Legally required to show me her books.

1025
00:39:29,590 --> 00:39:32,260
可不像你  我没有违法
And unlike you, I don't break the law.

1026
00:39:32,260 --> 00:39:36,360
汉利·福尔松必须要知道的一个事实
A fact that Hanley Folsom could be made acutely aware of.

1027
00:39:36,360 --> 00:39:38,950
你的确违法了  杰西卡
You do break the law, Jessica.

1028
00:39:38,950 --> 00:39:41,010
瞒报挪用公款也是种犯罪
Not reporting embezzlement is a crime.

1029
00:39:41,740 --> 00:39:44,270
在你的宣判听证会上再提出来吧
Why don't you bring that up at your sentencing hearing?

1030
00:39:44,270 --> 00:39:45,870
我可以起诉你
Why don't I sue you?

1031
00:39:46,350 --> 00:39:48,110
你可以啊
You could.

1032
00:39:49,370 --> 00:39:51,110
任何人都能起诉任何人
Anybody could sue anybody.

1033
00:39:51,110 --> 00:39:53,070
但你没有证据证明我告诉了他
But you still don't have proof that I told him.

1034
00:39:53,070 --> 00:39:55,200
我们的公司合并后的财力
And our firms combined have ten times

1035
00:39:55,200 --> 00:39:57,230
将十倍于你的…
the resources that yours d--

1036
00:39:58,460 --> 00:40:00,360
等等  你还没有公司
oh, wait. You don't have a firm.

1037
00:40:00,360 --> 00:40:03,480
你还只是住在赞恩的办公室里
You're just here, living in Zane's offices,

1038
00:40:03,480 --> 00:40:06,180
一旦结案  你所做的案子
working on those cases that will no longer be yours

1039
00:40:06,180 --> 00:40:07,840
就不再是你的了
when we're done with you.

1040
00:40:09,790 --> 00:40:11,650
再见  丹尼尔
Good-bye, Daniel.

1041
00:40:16,630 --> 00:40:18,790
让你的客户签一下那些文件  好吗
Get your client to sign those papers, will you?

1042
00:40:45,320 --> 00:40:46,470
怎么了  路易
What is it, Louis?

1043
00:40:48,180 --> 00:40:49,880
有个不幸的消息要告诉你
Got a hard truth to tell you.

1044
00:40:52,790 --> 00:40:54,950
-我去不了哈佛了  -对  去不了
- I'm not going to Harvard. - No, you're not.

1045
00:40:56,980 --> 00:40:58,250
我明白了
I get it.

1046
00:40:58,670 --> 00:41:00,370
我还不够好  一直如此
I'm not good enough. I never have been.

1047
00:41:00,370 --> 00:41:02,110
这不是我要说的
That is not the hard truth.

1048
00:41:02,110 --> 00:41:03,530
你是个很棒的申请人
You are an amazing candidate,

1049
00:41:03,530 --> 00:41:05,680
这一点你要深深记住
and you need to know this in your heart.

1050
00:41:05,680 --> 00:41:07,650
重点是  你没能被选上
The truth is, you did not get in...

1051
00:41:09,920 --> 00:41:11,470
是我害的
because I let you down.

1052
00:41:16,400 --> 00:41:17,980
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?

1053
00:41:18,180 --> 00:41:20,780
我和希拉曾有一段恋情
Sheila and I had a relationship.

1054
00:41:21,100 --> 00:41:23,630
我伤害了她
I hurt her, and...

1055
00:41:25,080 --> 00:41:26,680
所以她拿我泄愤吗
And she took it out on me?

1056
00:41:27,110 --> 00:41:29,340
我可以为你向任何地方写推荐信
I'm going to write you a recommendation for anywhere,

1057
00:41:29,650 --> 00:41:31,010
任何法学院
any law school.

1058
00:41:31,420 --> 00:41:32,390
只是
It just...

1059
00:41:32,390 --> 00:41:33,850
不可能是哈佛
won't be Harvard.

1060
00:41:49,910 --> 00:41:51,190
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry.

