1
00:00:00,040 --> 00:00:01,300
《訴訟雙雄》前情提要
Previously on Suits.

2
00:00:01,450 --> 00:00:02,860
明天你名字就將掛在墻上
It's going up on the wall tomorrow.

3
00:00:02,870 --> 00:00:07,020
這是你拉我到你一邊的手段
This is your way of getting me on your side.

4
00:00:08,220 --> 00:00:10,010
我是希望我們在同一邊
I want us to be on the same side.

5
00:00:10,120 --> 00:00:11,890
我證明艾娃·海辛頓無罪
I get ava hessington acquitted.

6
00:00:11,890 --> 00:00:13,890
達比支持我當經營合伙人
Darby backs me for managing partner.

7
00:00:13,890 --> 00:00:15,890
我是來告訴你我不想接受
I'm here to tell you I don't want it anymore.

8
00:00:15,890 --> 00:00:17,040
你趕快從我眼前消失
Get out of my sight.

9
00:00:17,270 --> 00:00:18,880
你給我聽清楚了
Let me spell it out for you, okay?

10
00:00:19,280 --> 00:00:21,590
不準背著我做我的案子
You don't work my case without me.

11
00:00:21,590 --> 00:00:23,030
既然你對這句話理解有困難
And since you seem to be having trouble

12
00:00:23,030 --> 00:00:25,450
你完全不準碰我的案子
understanding that, you don't work my case at all.

13
00:00:25,520 --> 00:00:26,530
你和史蒂芬
You and Stephen.

14
00:00:27,280 --> 00:00:28,320
讓我很鬧心
It bothers me.

15
00:00:28,360 --> 00:00:29,800
我都不知道原來你也喜歡貓
I didn't know you were a cat man.

16
00:00:29,910 --> 00:00:31,130
我有腦子嗎
Do I have brains in my head?

17
00:00:31,200 --> 00:00:32,460
我有心嗎
Do I have a heart in my chest?

18
00:00:32,460 --> 00:00:34,170
-這只漂亮的小生命是...  -米卡度
- Who is this stunning creature? - Mikado.

19
00:00:34,170 --> 00:00:36,150
香港辦公室方面緊急召我
The Hong Kong office urgently requires me

20
00:00:36,150 --> 00:00:37,160
過去幾周時間
for a few weeks.

21
00:00:37,160 --> 00:00:39,930
那里肯定會有貓咪專屬的奢華酒店
I'm sure there is a suitable luxury feline hotel.

22
00:00:39,930 --> 00:00:42,250
-別逗了  -那你答應了
- Don't play games, okay? - So you'll do it?

23
00:00:42,260 --> 00:00:43,540
沒有  才怪  貓咪呢
n-yes. Can I have her?

24
00:00:43,850 --> 00:00:44,970
你想要什么 史蒂芬
What do you want, Stephen?

25
00:00:45,730 --> 00:00:47,190
我聽說卡梅隆找到了一個目擊者
I hear Cameron got a witness.

26
00:00:47,400 --> 00:00:49,920
是  你想怎樣
He did. What do you want?

27
00:00:49,920 --> 00:00:51,040
我只是來看看  有沒有什么
I'm just checking to see if there's anything

28
00:00:51,040 --> 00:00:51,730
我能幫忙的
I can do to help.

29
00:00:51,730 --> 00:00:53,470
-沒有  -不可能
- there isn't. - no way.

30
00:00:53,540 --> 00:00:55,010
你昨天沒拿下馬里加
If you didn't have Mariga yesterday,

31
00:00:55,010 --> 00:00:56,360
今天也沒有
you don't have him today.

32
00:00:56,360 --> 00:00:58,100
你怎么不問問你們的朋友史蒂芬·亨特利
Why don't you ask your friend Stephen Huntley?

33
00:00:58,920 --> 00:01:00,630
就是他幫我找上馬里加的
He's the one that led me right to him.

34
00:01:09,520 --> 00:01:11,560
你也許是個完美的男人
You know, you might just be the perfect man.

35
00:01:11,590 --> 00:01:13,310
你現在才知道嗎
You're just coming to realize that now?

36
00:01:22,530 --> 00:01:23,530
唐娜
Donna.

37
00:01:24,100 --> 00:01:25,760
我要和史蒂芬單獨談一下
I need a minute alone with Stephen.

38
00:01:26,590 --> 00:01:28,500
就談一下  還是我該打車走了
Is it just a minute? Or do I need to get a cab?

39
00:01:29,080 --> 00:01:31,520
不用多久的  不過走不走看你了
It won't take long. But the rest is up to you.

40
00:01:38,570 --> 00:01:40,960
你不是來跟我們一起吃甜點的吧
Well, I'm guessing you're not here to join us for dessert.

41
00:01:40,960 --> 00:01:42,420
你給馬加里上校打電話了
You called Colonel Mariga.

42
00:01:44,670 --> 00:01:46,660
沒錯
Yeah. I called him.

43
00:01:47,780 --> 00:01:50,010
我打給他詢問卡梅隆·丹尼斯開了什么條件
Called him to find out what Cameron Dennis had offered him

44
00:01:50,010 --> 00:01:52,430
并且說明他能得到更多
and to suggest that he could do better.

45
00:01:52,530 --> 00:01:54,820
你是說你提出賄賂他
You mean you called him to offer him a bribe.

46
00:01:54,850 --> 00:01:55,840
無所謂了
Doesn't matter.

47
00:01:56,630 --> 00:01:57,740
丹尼斯在唬人
Dennis was bluffing.

48
00:01:57,740 --> 00:01:59,080
他根本就沒找到馬加里上校
He never had him in the first place.

49
00:01:59,080 --> 00:02:01,210
一開始是沒有  但現在找到了
He didn't but he does now

50
00:02:01,860 --> 00:02:02,900
多虧了你
because of you.

51
00:02:04,210 --> 00:02:06,220
你是說他追蹤了我的電話
You're saying he traced my call?

52
00:02:06,220 --> 00:02:07,550
沒錯
You're damn right I am.

53
00:02:07,710 --> 00:02:09,270
你生我氣了
And you're angry with me?

54
00:02:09,380 --> 00:02:11,270
你本該捍衛艾娃的
You're supposed to be looking out for Ava.

55
00:02:11,270 --> 00:02:12,500
如果我不知情  肯定以為
If I didn't know any better, I'd think

56
00:02:12,500 --> 00:02:14,220
你是卡梅隆·丹尼斯的人
that you were working for Cameron Dennis.

57
00:02:14,220 --> 00:02:16,960
而且  那人躲起來了
And by the way, the man is in hiding.

58
00:02:16,960 --> 00:02:19,410
連他的祖國都找不到他  你怎么找到的
His own country can't find him. How the hell did you?

59
00:02:19,420 --> 00:02:20,460
用你也會用的方法
Same way you would.

60
00:02:21,050 --> 00:02:22,190
你在這里人面廣
You know people here.

61
00:02:22,620 --> 00:02:23,820
我全世界人面都廣
I know people everywhere.

62
00:02:23,830 --> 00:02:26,090
給這些人打電話只會害死我們
Well, calling those people just screwed us.

63
00:02:26,090 --> 00:02:28,620
哈維  我找他們是因為你什么都不做
I called them, Harvey, because you were doing nothing.

64
00:02:28,620 --> 00:02:31,400
那是因為他手頭什么都沒有
I was doing nothing because he had nothing.

65
00:02:31,400 --> 00:02:32,930
這樣他就不能把錄像帶作為證據
And then I had the tape thrown out

66
00:02:32,930 --> 00:02:34,430
會更加窮途末路
and he had less than nothing.

67
00:02:34,430 --> 00:02:36,930
他拋出了一個騙局  你就一腳踩了進去
Then he threw a Hail Mary and you just caught it.

68
00:02:37,020 --> 00:02:39,450
如果他是追蹤了我的電話才找到了馬加里
If he found Mariga by tapping my phones,

69
00:02:39,450 --> 00:02:41,180
法官會把他踢出局的
the judge will throw him out.

70
00:02:41,180 --> 00:02:42,170
你覺得我們能證明
You think we're gonna be able to prove

71
00:02:42,170 --> 00:02:43,060
他追蹤了你的電話嗎
that that's how he found him?

72
00:02:43,060 --> 00:02:44,260
你是要繼續沖我喊
You wanna carry on yelling at me?

73
00:02:44,260 --> 00:02:45,870
還是扭轉局勢
Or should we fix this?

74
00:02:45,870 --> 00:02:47,060
我受夠你那套
You know, I have had about enough

75
00:02:47,060 --> 00:02:48,200
狗屁扭轉局勢了
of your fixer crap, okay?

76
00:02:48,200 --> 00:02:50,810
你屁都沒扭轉  成事不足敗事有余
You didn't fix shit. You broke it wide open.

77
00:02:50,810 --> 00:02:52,330
那你來這里干什么
Then what the hell are you doing here?

78
00:02:52,330 --> 00:02:54,240
我來這里告訴你  你要還來插手
I'm here to tell you that if I hear your name

79
00:02:54,240 --> 00:02:55,240
我的案子
around my case again,

80
00:02:55,240 --> 00:02:57,370
我就把你揍個屁滾尿流
I am gonna beat the shit outta you.

81
00:03:04,290 --> 00:03:06,460
你說要把他揍個屁滾尿流
You told him you were gonna beat the shit out of him?

82
00:03:06,460 --> 00:03:08,120
是的  這也是我最后一次
Yeah, and that's the last time

83
00:03:08,120 --> 00:03:09,440
跟他說話了
I'm gonna tell him anything.

84
00:03:10,410 --> 00:03:11,270
怎么
What?

85
00:03:11,270 --> 00:03:12,320
你覺得我不會打他
You think I wouldn't do it?

86
00:03:12,320 --> 00:03:14,080
不  我不確定你打得過他
No, I'm not sure you could do it.

87
00:03:14,190 --> 00:03:16,060
他能用什么揍我  寬領帶嗎
What's he going to hit me with, his ascot?

88
00:03:16,060 --> 00:03:17,580
哈維  那家伙是打英式橄欖球的
Harvey, the man plays rugby.

89
00:03:17,580 --> 00:03:18,460
那可不是開玩笑的
That's no joke.

90
00:03:18,460 --> 00:03:19,670
你怎么知道的
How do you even know that?

91
00:03:19,750 --> 00:03:21,500
在達比國際的網頁上寫著呢
It's on the Darby International website.

92
00:03:21,500 --> 00:03:23,260
看來我給你的活還不夠多
I don't give you enough work.

93
00:03:23,270 --> 00:03:24,960
我現在就改正這一點
And I'm gonna change that right now.

94
00:03:25,120 --> 00:03:27,920
卡梅隆沒有禁止我們接觸馬加里
Cameron's not denying us access to Mariga,

95
00:03:27,920 --> 00:03:30,050
也就是說他現在唯卡梅隆是從
which means he's gonna sing any song Cameron wants

96
00:03:30,050 --> 00:03:31,360
來避免死刑
to avoid a firing squad--

97
00:03:31,360 --> 00:03:32,530
所以我要盡可能搜集資料
So I need to find anything I can

98
00:03:32,530 --> 00:03:34,110
擊潰馬加里
to take Mariga apart.

99
00:03:34,380 --> 00:03:35,400
這是什么
What the hell is this?

100
00:03:35,820 --> 00:03:37,000
讓我來告訴你
I'll tell you what it is.

101
00:03:37,000 --> 00:03:38,920
這是卡梅隆·丹尼斯的目擊證人名單
It's a witness list from Cameron Dennis

102
00:03:38,920 --> 00:03:40,410
馬加里上校就在里面
with Colonel Mariga on it.

103
00:03:40,410 --> 00:03:41,670
他允許我方接觸證人
And he's giving us access,

104
00:03:41,670 --> 00:03:43,370
這說明他不是在唬人
which means he's not bluffing.

105
00:03:43,500 --> 00:03:44,200
我知道
I know.

106
00:03:44,200 --> 00:03:45,500
你說他沒找到馬加里上校
You told me he didn't have him.

107
00:03:45,580 --> 00:03:46,490
是沒有
He didn't.

108
00:03:46,490 --> 00:03:47,770
那現在怎么又找到了
Then how the hell did he get him?

109
00:03:47,770 --> 00:03:50,460
是史蒂芬  他想扭轉局勢
Stephen. He was trying to fix it.

110
00:03:50,460 --> 00:03:52,660
你是說你讓史蒂芬·亨特利
Are you telling me you let Stephen Huntley

111
00:03:52,660 --> 00:03:54,780
帶卡梅隆找到了主要目擊證人嗎
lead Cameron directly to the star witness?

112
00:03:54,780 --> 00:03:56,270
我屁都沒讓史蒂芬干
I didn't let Stephen do shit.

113
00:03:56,280 --> 00:03:58,180
-他自己搞的  -他是你的人
- He did it on his own. - He's your guy.

114
00:03:58,450 --> 00:04:00,040
-你跟他結盟了  -我沒有
- You aligned with him. - I did not.

115
00:04:00,040 --> 00:04:01,560
他是愛德華·達比的人
Okay, he's Edward Darby's guy.

116
00:04:01,570 --> 00:04:03,120
你跟達比有協議
You made a deal with Darby.

117
00:04:03,120 --> 00:04:04,860
他就是你的人了
That makes him your guy.

118
00:04:07,770 --> 00:04:09,520
你真要現在扯這些嗎
You really wanna do this right now?

119
00:04:09,550 --> 00:04:11,120
你是說他不知情嗎
Are you telling me he doesn't know?

120
00:04:14,600 --> 00:04:15,680
你知道我知情
You know I know.

121
00:04:15,920 --> 00:04:17,900
我和你曾有過類似的對話
You and I had this conversation once.

122
00:04:18,270 --> 00:04:20,290
你知道我忠于誰
And you know where my loyalties lie.

123
00:04:21,180 --> 00:04:23,950
至于你的問題  史蒂芬在這里
And as for your point, Stephen is only here at all

124
00:04:23,950 --> 00:04:26,440
全是因為你當初和達比簽了協議
because you made a deal with Darby in the first place.

125
00:04:26,550 --> 00:04:29,480
我說過  我不想遵守協議了
And I told you, I don't want mine anymore.

126
00:04:31,200 --> 00:04:32,850
這么說現在還是我管事
Then I guess I'm still in charge.

127
00:04:32,850 --> 00:04:35,340
既然我也被扯進了這個案子
And since I've now been drafted onto this case,

128
00:04:35,350 --> 00:04:38,080
誰都不能跟愛德華·達比
no one tells Edward Darby

129
00:04:38,240 --> 00:04:40,440
和史蒂芬·亨特利說任何事
or Stephen Huntley a goddamn thing.

130
00:04:40,440 --> 00:04:42,940
這屋里有人對此有問題嗎
Does anyone in this room have a problem with that?

131
00:04:45,590 --> 00:04:50,590
人人影視
YYeTs.com

132
00:04:45,590 --> 00:04:50,590
原創翻譯  中文字幕

133
00:04:45,590 --> 00:04:50,590
■

134
00:04:45,590 --> 00:04:50,590
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com

135
00:04:51,560 --> 00:04:56,330
翻譯： 愛卿遛小鳥  reginamoon 某豚 宅女之后 小飯

136
00:04:56,560 --> 00:05:01,330
校對：某羽

137
00:05:01,560 --> 00:05:06,330
時間軸：憑陵新月  sinagujia

138
00:05:06,560 --> 00:05:11,330
后期：阿丟丟     總監：swears

139
00:05:13,160 --> 00:05:15,060
《訴訟雙雄》
第三季第七集

140
00:05:31,170 --> 00:05:32,120
查到什么了
What did you get me?

141
00:05:32,160 --> 00:05:33,500
這不是馬加里第一次撒謊
This isn't the first time Mariga lied

142
00:05:33,500 --> 00:05:34,660
以逃脫起訴了
to get out of prosecution.

143
00:05:34,660 --> 00:05:35,500
還有其他謀殺罪
Other murders?

144
00:05:35,500 --> 00:05:38,340
謀殺  勒索  侵占
Murder. Extortion. Embezzlement.

145
00:05:38,720 --> 00:05:39,690
想找個犯了罪
You want someone to commit a crime

146
00:05:39,690 --> 00:05:41,610
再推卸給別人的人  就是他
and blame it on someone else, he's your guy.

147
00:05:41,620 --> 00:05:43,350
列出問題了嗎
You got the questions lined up?

148
00:05:43,350 --> 00:05:44,280
都在這里了
Right here.

149
00:05:44,730 --> 00:05:46,560
你應該知道我最想問的是什么
But I think you know what my biggest question is.

150
00:05:49,410 --> 00:05:50,500
你要我說什么
What do you want me to say?

151
00:05:50,500 --> 00:05:52,770
我不想跟達比合作了  我告訴了杰西卡
I changed my mind about Darby. I told Jessica.

152
00:05:52,770 --> 00:05:53,960
而我還沒來得及告訴你
And I didn't get a chance to tell you

153
00:05:53,960 --> 00:05:55,480
因為我們現在有更要緊的事要辦
because we had bigger fish to fry.

154
00:05:55,480 --> 00:05:57,490
我明白你為什么沒來得及告訴我
I understand why you didn't get a chance to tell me.

155
00:05:57,490 --> 00:05:59,100
我不明白的是  你為什么要告訴她
What I don't get is why you told her.

156
00:05:59,100 --> 00:06:01,780
要是我無法相信她能在我坦白之后放下這件事
If I can't trust her to get over it after I tell her,

157
00:06:01,830 --> 00:06:04,750
那我還不如跟著達比干了
I might as well have stuck with Darby in the first place.

158
00:06:04,780 --> 00:06:06,240
看樣子她還是很介意
Doesn't look like she's over it.

159
00:06:06,240 --> 00:06:08,110
因為她知道了這案子的事
Because she knows what we know.

160
00:06:08,110 --> 00:06:09,990
現在我們有更要緊的事
Right now, we got bigger fish to fry.

161
00:06:23,760 --> 00:06:25,160
開什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?

162
00:06:28,700 --> 00:06:29,410
諾瑪
Norma?

163
00:06:29,410 --> 00:06:30,910
我跟你說過多少次了
I've told you a million goddamn times.

164
00:06:30,910 --> 00:06:32,700
米卡度的下午牛奶只要2%脫脂奶
2% of Mikado's afternoon milk.

165
00:06:32,700 --> 00:06:33,820
她能嘗出多余的
She's gonna taste the extra skim.

166
00:06:33,830 --> 00:06:35,380
你覺得她會沖誰發脾氣
And who do you think she's gonna take it out on?

167
00:06:35,740 --> 00:06:36,660
是我
Me.

168
00:06:37,450 --> 00:06:38,660
在Litt up上查一下
Oh, and find out what the holdup is

169
00:06:38,660 --> 00:06:40,050
我那件商標索賠案怎么耽擱了
on my trademark claim on "Litt up".

170
00:06:40,650 --> 00:06:42,290
奈杰爾  你提前一周回來了
Nigel, you're back a week early.

171
00:06:42,290 --> 00:06:43,910
我本來還要再度假一周
I was gonna holiday an extra week.

172
00:06:43,910 --> 00:06:45,920
但在廣州的當地泥浴里泡了兩天
But I was rejuvenated after only two days

173
00:06:45,920 --> 00:06:48,180
我就精神煥發了
in the native clays at Guangzhou.

174
00:06:48,850 --> 00:06:49,780
你渾身散發著光芒
You're glowing.

175
00:06:50,100 --> 00:06:52,090
我等不及要見米卡度了
And I can't wait to see Mikado.

176
00:06:53,340 --> 00:06:54,730
我家美妞在這里吧
The lovely lass is here, I see.

177
00:06:54,730 --> 00:06:55,840
不在
Uh, no, she's not here.

178
00:06:57,440 --> 00:06:58,600
那是給誰的
Then who's that for?

179
00:07:01,120 --> 00:07:02,030
給我的
That's for me.

180
00:07:03,430 --> 00:07:04,510
是我的下午牛奶
It's my afternoon milk.

181
00:07:14,030 --> 00:07:15,470
喝過癮了  我得走了
Hits the spot. Gotta run.

182
00:07:16,820 --> 00:07:17,770
路易
Louis.

183
00:07:18,580 --> 00:07:19,570
她在哪
Where is she?

184
00:07:20,870 --> 00:07:22,300
在全市最好的貓貓水療館
At the best cat SPA in the city,

185
00:07:22,390 --> 00:07:24,150
拋光指甲  擦亮爪子呢
getting her nails buffed and her paws polished.

186
00:07:24,860 --> 00:07:25,960
你真把她寵壞了
You spoil her.

187
00:07:25,980 --> 00:07:27,940
-是她把我寵壞了  -她回來了給我打電話
- She spoils me. - Call me when she's back.

188
00:07:27,940 --> 00:07:28,970
好的
I will.

189
00:07:34,510 --> 00:07:36,360
瑞秋  我是路易  紅色警報
Rachel, Louis. Code Red.

190
00:07:43,080 --> 00:07:43,700
路易·利特
資深合伙人

191
00:07:58,840 --> 00:07:59,650
最高機密
粉碎文件日

192
00:08:02,540 --> 00:08:03,800
有人看到你離開我辦公室嗎
Did anybody see you leave my office?

193
00:08:03,800 --> 00:08:05,730
-諾瑪看了我一眼  -她是我們的人
- Norma gave me a look. - She's on our side.

194
00:08:05,730 --> 00:08:06,420
瑞秋  集中精神
Rachel, concentrate.

195
00:08:06,420 --> 00:08:07,450
我都不確定自己是不是跟你同一戰線的
I don't even know if I'm on your side.

196
00:08:07,450 --> 00:08:09,660
-這樣是不對的  -她想做我的貓
- This isn't right. - She wants to be my cat.

197
00:08:09,680 --> 00:08:11,230
不  是你想讓她成為你的貓
No. You want her to be your cat.

198
00:08:11,230 --> 00:08:12,300
你不明白
You don't understand.

199
00:08:12,300 --> 00:08:14,010
上周是我這輩子最棒的一周  自從...
This past week has been the best week of my life, ever since--

200
00:08:14,010 --> 00:08:15,430
布魯諾  我明白
Bruno, I understand.

201
00:08:15,430 --> 00:08:17,230
但你不能霸著米卡度不還啊
But you can't keep Mikado.

202
00:08:17,230 --> 00:08:18,700
她是奈杰爾的貓
She's Nigel's cat.

203
00:08:18,700 --> 00:08:21,860
-說得好  -奈杰爾  你怎么...
- Well said. - Ah, Nigel, how did you--

204
00:08:21,860 --> 00:08:24,370
我做了每個自重的貓主人都會做的事
By doing what any self-respecting cat owner would do,

205
00:08:24,670 --> 00:08:26,540
給貓裝上RFID
equipping her with an RFID.

206
00:08:26,960 --> 00:08:29,230
無線射頻識別器
A radio-frequency-identifier integrated circuit.

207
00:08:29,230 --> 00:08:31,240
你為什么要把我珍貴的財產藏起來
Why would you hide my prize possession?

208
00:08:31,280 --> 00:08:33,790
她對你來說就是一件財產嗎
Is that what she is to you? A possession?

209
00:08:33,930 --> 00:08:36,860
這是我和她之間的事
What she is to me is between me and her.

210
00:08:40,000 --> 00:08:40,830
你說得對
You're right.

211
00:08:43,020 --> 00:08:44,070
他說得對
He's right.

212
00:08:47,260 --> 00:08:48,220
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

213
00:08:53,120 --> 00:08:54,520
-我還沒準備好  -路易
- I'm not ready. - Louis.

214
00:08:54,520 --> 00:08:55,640
他本應離開兩周的
He was supposed to be gone for two weeks.

215
00:08:55,640 --> 00:08:58,230
我們有口頭合約我本應享有兩周的撫養權
We had a verbal contract I would have custody for two weeks.

216
00:08:58,240 --> 00:08:59,970
那只是安排你臨時照顧
It was a baby-sitting arrangement.

217
00:08:59,970 --> 00:09:01,050
我為這個安排在精神上  情感上
One that I was mentally, emotionally,

218
00:09:01,050 --> 00:09:02,340
和身體上都做好了準備
and physically prepared for.

219
00:09:02,340 --> 00:09:03,840
因此  我可以合法
And accordingly, I am legally entitled

220
00:09:03,840 --> 00:09:04,990
擁有米卡度一周
to Mikado for one more week.

221
00:09:05,090 --> 00:09:07,170
那可不是法律
That is not the law.

222
00:09:07,620 --> 00:09:08,880
實際上是有判例的
There's actually precedent.

223
00:09:09,770 --> 00:09:11,600
1974年  瓦明斯基訴米切爾案
Warminsky V. Mitchell, 1974.

224
00:09:15,050 --> 00:09:16,020
我有個會要開
I have a meeting,

225
00:09:16,650 --> 00:09:20,180
開完會我會收回我的合法擁有物
After which I will collect what is rightfully mine.

226
00:09:27,010 --> 00:09:27,660
那招可真天才
That was genius.

227
00:09:27,660 --> 00:09:28,630
不是的  路易
No, Louis.

228
00:09:28,630 --> 00:09:29,700
那是拖延時間
That was a stall.

229
00:09:30,370 --> 00:09:32,250
因為事實上奈杰爾是對的
Because the truth is Nigel's right.

230
00:09:32,640 --> 00:09:34,170
她不是你的貓
She's not your cat.

231
00:09:35,530 --> 00:09:36,870
你必須得放她走
You've gotta let her go.

232
00:09:39,610 --> 00:09:41,000
你想談談昨晚的事情嗎
Hey, do you wanna talk about last night?

233
00:09:41,000 --> 00:09:42,280
不  唐娜  我不想
No, Donna, I don't.

234
00:09:42,330 --> 00:09:44,830
哈維  你說我和史蒂芬在一起使你困擾
Harvey, you said my being with Stephen bothered you.

235
00:09:44,830 --> 00:09:46,140
而我只是想確定
And I just wanna make sure that--

236
00:09:46,140 --> 00:09:48,520
確定他做了什么值得打斷你約會的事
- that what he did deserved interrupting your date?

237
00:09:49,210 --> 00:09:49,810
真值得嗎
Did it?

238
00:09:49,810 --> 00:09:51,140
我不知道  唐娜  你說吧
I don't know, Donna. You tell me.

239
00:09:51,140 --> 00:09:53,060
我們整個案子進入了僵局
I mean, we had this entire case locked up.

240
00:09:53,100 --> 00:09:54,660
你的男友給了卡梅隆
I mean, your boyfriend gave Cameron

241
00:09:54,670 --> 00:09:56,280
一張"自由逃出監獄"卡
a get-out-of-jail-free card

242
00:09:56,530 --> 00:09:58,530
而且是在我讓他別他媽插手這個案子之后
after I told him to stay the hell out of it.

243
00:09:58,780 --> 00:09:59,460
他做了什么
What'd he do?

244
00:09:59,470 --> 00:10:00,690
他找到了馬里加
He tracked down Mariga

245
00:10:00,690 --> 00:10:02,330
然后把他送到了卡梅隆面前
and led Cameron right to him.

246
00:10:02,330 --> 00:10:03,000
哈維  我
Harvey, I'm--

247
00:10:03,000 --> 00:10:05,710
知道嗎  相比起討論史蒂芬床上的事
You know what? Instead of discussing Stephen shoot in the bed,

248
00:10:05,710 --> 00:10:07,720
如今  我得盡力給他擦屁股
right now, I have to try to clean it up.

249
00:10:14,510 --> 00:10:15,440
在哥旺巴
Gwambaa.

250
00:10:16,780 --> 00:10:17,790
馬凱瓦
Makaiwa.

251
00:10:18,790 --> 00:10:19,960
伊法港
Port Eefa.

252
00:10:20,370 --> 00:10:21,560
有四十個人被殺了
40 people killed.

253
00:10:21,670 --> 00:10:23,110
你是來這里回答問題的
Are you here to answer questions

254
00:10:23,110 --> 00:10:24,060
還是來向他們提問的
or ask them?

255
00:10:24,540 --> 00:10:25,960
你見過這些照片嗎
Are you familiar with these photos?

256
00:10:25,960 --> 00:10:27,620
我對照片中發生的事情負責
I'm responsible for these photos.

257
00:10:27,690 --> 00:10:29,120
你看起來對此深感自豪
You seem proud of yourself.

258
00:10:29,120 --> 00:10:31,260
我是個暴力國家的軍人
I am a military man in a violent country.

259
00:10:31,570 --> 00:10:33,320
我做必須要做的事
I do what needs to be done.

260
00:10:33,790 --> 00:10:35,230
那不會讓我成為殺人兇手
That doesn't make me a murderer.

261
00:10:35,310 --> 00:10:38,060
因為你是遵照你們政府的指示殺人的
Because you kill people under orders from your government.

262
00:10:38,060 --> 00:10:39,150
完全正確
Precisely.

263
00:10:39,150 --> 00:10:40,250
你在海辛頓石油的工地做的事
Isn't that exactly what you did

264
00:10:40,250 --> 00:10:41,490
不也一樣嗎
on Hessington Oil's land?

265
00:10:41,540 --> 00:10:43,270
不  我殺那些人
No, I killed those people

266
00:10:43,270 --> 00:10:45,370
是因為你們的客戶付了我錢
because I was paid by your client.

267
00:10:45,370 --> 00:10:46,850
那你就是兇手了
Well, that does make you a murderer.

268
00:10:46,850 --> 00:10:48,860
而你說艾娃知道這件事
And you're only saying that Ava knew about it

269
00:10:48,860 --> 00:10:50,360
僅僅是因為你敬愛的政府
because your precious government

270
00:10:50,570 --> 00:10:52,740
不再有能力保護你了
is no longer in power to protect you.

271
00:10:52,860 --> 00:10:54,010
那可不對
That is not true.

272
00:10:54,010 --> 00:10:55,600
那么假如在你的國家因謀殺被定罪
And what exactly is the penalty

273
00:10:55,600 --> 00:10:57,530
到底會有什么樣的懲罰
if you're found guilty of murder in your country?

274
00:10:58,180 --> 00:10:59,110
死刑
Death.

275
00:10:59,120 --> 00:11:01,340
那你為什么還沒有被引渡回去
And why is it you haven't been sent back there?

276
00:11:01,340 --> 00:11:03,370
我來回答這個問題  他和我達成了協議
I'll take this one. He cut a deal with me.

277
00:11:03,460 --> 00:11:05,830
因為我更在乎下命令殺人的人
Because I care more about the person who ordered this

278
00:11:05,830 --> 00:11:07,150
而不是執行謀殺的人
than the person who carried it out.

279
00:11:07,150 --> 00:11:08,200
只有一個問題
There's only one problem.

280
00:11:08,200 --> 00:11:09,850
他只見過艾娃一次
He only met with Ava once.

281
00:11:09,980 --> 00:11:11,740
而你對于那次會面的唯一證據
And your only proof of that meeting

282
00:11:11,740 --> 00:11:12,820
是不被承認的
is inadmissible.

283
00:11:12,820 --> 00:11:13,910
錯了
Wrong.

284
00:11:14,230 --> 00:11:16,220
他和艾娃不止談了一次
He didn't only talk to Ava once.

285
00:11:17,150 --> 00:11:19,310
我們電話聯系的時候
I told your client about what needed to be done

286
00:11:19,310 --> 00:11:20,630
我告訴了你的客戶要做什么
when we spoke on the phone.

287
00:11:25,690 --> 00:11:27,990
海辛頓女士沒告訴你們這事兒
Ms. Hessington didn't tell you about that.

288
00:11:27,990 --> 00:11:30,250
她沒告訴我們是因為這件事從沒發生過
She didn't tell us about that because that never happened.

289
00:11:30,250 --> 00:11:31,510
你們指望她做什么
What'd you expect her to do?

290
00:11:31,510 --> 00:11:32,950
來和你們說"是我做的"
Come to you and say "I did it?"

291
00:11:33,620 --> 00:11:37,530
這是艾娃私人保密線路的一條通話記錄
A record of the call from Ava's private, secure line.

292
00:11:38,380 --> 00:11:41,310
在那個電話里我們討論了修建管道的障礙
A call in which we discussed the impediments to the pipeline,

293
00:11:41,640 --> 00:11:43,610
那六個擋道的領頭人
the six leaders who stood in its way,

294
00:11:43,610 --> 00:11:45,760
還有除掉他們的代價
and the cost for their removal.

295
00:11:46,140 --> 00:11:49,210
三百萬美金  是她承諾的酬金
$3 million, which she admitted paying.

296
00:11:49,330 --> 00:11:51,130
就在你們讓她簽署的聲明里
In the admission you had her sign.

297
00:11:51,550 --> 00:11:52,620
我不需要錄像帶
I don't need the tape

298
00:11:52,620 --> 00:11:54,760
是因為我已經有了所需的一切
because I have everything I need,

299
00:11:55,560 --> 00:11:58,100
包括她在電話的事上撒謊的事實
including the fact that she lied about that phone call.

300
00:12:11,010 --> 00:12:11,960
你昨晚怎么了
What happened to you last night?

301
00:12:11,960 --> 00:12:13,370
我想你知道是怎么回事
I think you know what happened.

302
00:12:13,770 --> 00:12:14,990
我看到你倆朝對方大吼
I saw you two yelling at each other

303
00:12:14,990 --> 00:12:16,390
而我不想攪合進去
and I didn't want any part of it.

304
00:12:16,570 --> 00:12:19,320
相信我  我也不想攪合進去
Well, believe me, I didn't want any part of it either.

305
00:12:19,360 --> 00:12:20,640
你覺得他發現你毀了他的案子之后
Well, what did you think he was gonna do

306
00:12:20,640 --> 00:12:22,670
會怎么做
when he found out you screwed up his case?

307
00:12:23,460 --> 00:12:25,660
你知道我不是有意要搞破壞的
I think you know that I wasn't trying to screw it up.

308
00:12:25,660 --> 00:12:26,620
當你就是搞了破壞
But you did.

309
00:12:26,620 --> 00:12:28,580
他還特地說了讓你別插手
And he specifically told you to stay away.

310
00:12:28,580 --> 00:12:31,120
而你說過別和他討論你
And you told me not to discuss you with him.

311
00:12:31,120 --> 00:12:33,350
那你為什么要跟我討論他
So why are you discussing him with me?

312
00:12:33,350 --> 00:12:35,300
因為我和他交情匪淺
Because I have a relationship with him.

313
00:12:35,300 --> 00:12:36,960
可比幾個星期長多了
That's a lot longer than a few weeks.

314
00:12:36,960 --> 00:12:39,050
你和他鬧僵  你和我也就黃了
And when you mess with him, you mess with me.

315
00:12:39,050 --> 00:12:40,510
唐娜  我不是有意和他鬧僵的
Donna, I wasn't trying to mess with him.

316
00:12:40,510 --> 00:12:41,540
我本想幫他
I was trying to help him.

317
00:12:41,560 --> 00:12:43,270
既然我們談到這個話題
And as long as we're on the subject,

318
00:12:43,400 --> 00:12:46,010
我相信他提過要不是因為我之前的幫助
I'm sure he mentioned if it wasn't for my previous help,

319
00:12:46,100 --> 00:12:48,070
艾娃不會依然是他的客戶
he wouldn't still have Ava as a client.

320
00:12:49,140 --> 00:12:51,150
他或許是提到過一些關于這個的事
You know, he might've mentioned something about that.

321
00:12:52,620 --> 00:12:55,580
那我們可以回到不談論他的狀態嗎
Then can we get back to not discussing him?

322
00:12:56,940 --> 00:12:58,420
只要你保證不做出任何
As long as you promise not to do anything

323
00:12:58,420 --> 00:13:01,370
讓我們討論他的事
to make us not discuss him ever again.

324
00:13:02,510 --> 00:13:03,510
我保證
I promise.

325
00:13:06,040 --> 00:13:07,100
乖孩子
Good boy.

326
00:13:09,460 --> 00:13:10,660
我只問你一次
I'm gonna ask you once.

327
00:13:11,000 --> 00:13:12,250
他說的是真的嗎
Is he telling the truth?

328
00:13:13,350 --> 00:13:14,230
對
Yes.

329
00:13:14,820 --> 00:13:16,380
我們在電話上聊過
We had a conversation on the phone

330
00:13:16,380 --> 00:13:18,660
但不是關于謀殺
but not about murder.

331
00:13:19,220 --> 00:13:20,890
你不認為我們有必要知道這件事
You didn't think we needed to know?

332
00:13:22,300 --> 00:13:23,530
我不記得了
I didn't remember.

333
00:13:23,890 --> 00:13:25,880
這謊話在法庭上可不起作用
That lie won't play well in court.

334
00:13:25,940 --> 00:13:27,410
我告訴過你們會面的事了
I told you about the meeting.

335
00:13:27,450 --> 00:13:29,200
我沒想到要告訴你們電話的事
I didn't think to tell you about the call

336
00:13:29,200 --> 00:13:30,410
我們只確定了見面地點
where we agreed to meet.

337
00:13:30,410 --> 00:13:31,870
整件事就是那樣
That's all it was.

338
00:13:31,870 --> 00:13:33,530
什么時候  在哪  多少錢呢
When? Where? How much money?

339
00:13:33,530 --> 00:13:35,870
都沒談  這些事先都說好了的
Not even that. That was settled beforehand.

340
00:13:35,870 --> 00:13:37,090
只是禮節性見面  尼克安排的
It was a formality, Nick arranged.

341
00:13:37,090 --> 00:13:39,070
尼克·豪厄爾  你的前任門生
Nick Howell? Your former protege?

342
00:13:39,070 --> 00:13:41,440
他和這些人打交道  他知道他們想要什么
He dealt with these people. He knew what's expected.

343
00:13:41,730 --> 00:13:44,970
只是一個社交細節  并不重要
It was a social nicety, so insignificant,

344
00:13:44,970 --> 00:13:46,850
你們不提我都想不起來
I didn't remember until you brought it up.

345
00:13:46,850 --> 00:13:47,840
是他們提的
They brought it up.

346
00:13:47,850 --> 00:13:49,900
而如今  他們要指出你沒提的失誤
And now, they're gonna point out that you didn't.

347
00:13:50,070 --> 00:13:52,200
我明白這看起來很糟糕
I understand it looks bad.

348
00:13:52,640 --> 00:13:54,620
但是愛德華說了這個男人是個殺人兇手
But Edward said that this man is a murderer.

349
00:13:54,620 --> 00:13:55,850
而我也無須擔心
And there's no need for me to be concerned--

350
00:13:55,860 --> 00:13:57,560
愛德華·達比說了很多
Edward Darby says a lot of things

351
00:13:57,560 --> 00:13:59,510
你想相信但不應該相信的事
you want to believe but shouldn't.

352
00:13:59,650 --> 00:14:00,760
你不相信我
You don't believe me.

353
00:14:01,260 --> 00:14:02,460
隱瞞一次談話
Hiding a conversation

354
00:14:02,460 --> 00:14:03,850
然后過后再坦白
and then coming clean about it later

355
00:14:03,850 --> 00:14:05,250
這樣可是會妨礙信任的
tends to get in the way of trust.

356
00:14:05,250 --> 00:14:05,980
杰西卡
Jessica--

357
00:14:05,980 --> 00:14:07,590
這讓你顯得不真誠
It makes you disingenuous.

358
00:14:07,810 --> 00:14:09,210
讓你看起來像是有罪的
It makes you look guilty.

359
00:14:11,390 --> 00:14:12,330
我是無辜的
I'm not.

360
00:14:12,330 --> 00:14:14,820
你有發現有人經常不用你開口
Do you find that people usually kill your enemies

361
00:14:14,820 --> 00:14:16,060
就幫你殺了你的敵人嗎
for you without your asking?

362
00:14:16,060 --> 00:14:16,940
杰西卡
Jessica.

363
00:14:16,940 --> 00:14:18,560
艾娃  我們得失陪一陣了
Ava, You'll have to excuse us.

364
00:14:19,060 --> 00:14:20,440
我們得另想一個計劃
We have to come up with another plan

365
00:14:20,440 --> 00:14:22,640
因為我們原先的計劃剛剛變得屁都不是了
because the one we had just went to shit.

366
00:14:27,330 --> 00:14:29,030
簡直不可理喻[粵語]

367
00:14:32,070 --> 00:14:33,240
就這樣

368
00:14:37,590 --> 00:14:40,020
我不禁注意到你是空手而來的
I can't help but notice you've come empty-handed.

369
00:14:40,020 --> 00:14:40,940
不算空手
Not exactly.

370
00:14:51,050 --> 00:14:53,460
你為了米卡度的所有權起訴我
You're suing me for ownership of Mikado.

371
00:14:54,660 --> 00:14:55,350
憑什么
On what grounds?

372
00:14:55,350 --> 00:14:57,210
憑我提供了一個更好的家
On the grounds that I provide a better home

373
00:14:57,210 --> 00:14:59,010
因為你總是滿世界飛來飛去
because you're constantly flying around the world.

374
00:14:59,010 --> 00:15:02,360
《歡樂滿人間》劇情

375
00:14:59,040 --> 00:15:00,960
瑪麗·波平斯也沒得到她照看的
Mary Poppins doesn't get custody

376
00:15:00,960 --> 00:15:02,360
小孩的撫養權
of the children in her care.

377
00:15:02,360 --> 00:15:04,070
馮·特拉普家的小孩愛死瑪利亞了
The Von Trapp children fell in love with Maria.

378
00:15:02,360 --> 00:15:05,070
《音樂之聲》劇情

379
00:15:04,070 --> 00:15:05,080
她成了他們的母親
She became their mother.

380
00:15:05,080 --> 00:15:06,360
那是因為他們的母親去世了
Because their mother was dead.

381
00:15:07,250 --> 00:15:08,830
這玩意沒有法律依據
There's no legal basis for this.

382
00:15:08,870 --> 00:15:10,180
你確定
You're confident in that fact?

383
00:15:11,020 --> 00:15:12,260
毫無疑問
Most assuredly.

384
00:15:12,330 --> 00:15:13,790
那我們就自己裁決這件事吧
Then let's put it to our own jury.

385
00:15:15,680 --> 00:15:17,600
你是想來一場模擬法庭
You're suggesting a mock trial.

386
00:15:17,650 --> 00:15:18,660
你得在我們的律師面前
You get to prove you're the better man

387
00:15:18,660 --> 00:15:20,050
證明你是一個更好的人選
in front of our associates.

388
00:15:20,710 --> 00:15:22,870
你同意一有判決就把她還給我嗎
You agree to hand her back the moment the verdict is in?

389
00:15:22,870 --> 00:15:23,620
我同意
I agree to

390
00:15:23,620 --> 00:15:25,580
允許你在被打敗的時候向她道別
let you say good-bye to her the moment that you're defeated.

391
00:15:26,910 --> 00:15:28,680
法庭見[粵語]

392
00:15:32,280 --> 00:15:33,510
管你什么意思
Whatever the hell that means.

393
00:15:34,390 --> 00:15:36,660
很高興你沒和客戶失去聯系
Glad to see you haven't lost your touch with the clients.

394
00:15:36,660 --> 00:15:37,810
我沒必要對她和顏悅色的
I don't have to be nice to her.

395
00:15:37,810 --> 00:15:39,590
我只需在她滿口大話之后給她擦屁股
I just have to clean up after her bullshit.

396
00:15:39,600 --> 00:15:41,740
她沒撒謊  她只是犯了一個錯誤
She didn't lie. She just made a mistake.

397
00:15:41,740 --> 00:15:43,110
我們還是要為她擦屁股
We still have to clean it up.

398
00:15:43,540 --> 00:15:45,330
而且她剛剛給了我們一份路線圖
And she just handed us a road map.

399
00:15:45,730 --> 00:15:46,630
你想去找尼克·豪厄爾
You wanna go after Nick Howell.

400
00:15:46,630 --> 00:15:48,770
目前他是個合理的懷疑對象
He's reasonable doubt staring us right in the face.

401
00:15:48,840 --> 00:15:49,770
這是個壞主意
It's a bad idea.

402
00:15:50,330 --> 00:15:52,410
他承認了賄賂  他安排了那通電話
He admitted to the bribe, he set up the call,

403
00:15:52,410 --> 00:15:54,250
而且他曾經是她的人
and he was her man on the ground.

404
00:15:54,250 --> 00:15:55,660
把這個推到尼克身上就相當于承認
Laying it on Nick would be admitting

405
00:15:55,660 --> 00:15:58,280
海辛頓石油給馬里加錢讓他殺了那些人
Hessington Oil paid Mariga to kill those people.

406
00:15:58,280 --> 00:16:00,380
我們已經承認艾娃給他錢了
We already admitted that Ava paid him.

407
00:16:00,380 --> 00:16:02,200
而馬里加也已經承認了謀殺
And Mariga already admitted to the murders.

408
00:16:02,200 --> 00:16:04,200
這恰恰是我們為什么必須按照計劃
This is exactly why we should stick to the plan

409
00:16:04,200 --> 00:16:06,050
來摧毀馬里加的證詞
to destroy Mariga's testimony.

410
00:16:06,060 --> 00:16:07,260
不想被槍決
Not wanting to be shot

411
00:16:07,260 --> 00:16:08,970
可他媽是撒謊的好動機
is a hell of an incentive to lie.

412
00:16:08,970 --> 00:16:10,770
也很容易被陪審團理解
And an easy thing for a jury to understand.

413
00:16:10,770 --> 00:16:12,410
我清楚點跟你說
Let me spell this out for you.

414
00:16:13,170 --> 00:16:16,120
你能指出誰是兇手的時候
You don't just show that your client didn't do it

415
00:16:16,120 --> 00:16:18,010
才能完完全全證明你客戶是無罪的
when you can point to someone who did.

416
00:16:18,010 --> 00:16:19,580
但你永遠別指望說服陪審團
But you're never gonna convince a jury

417
00:16:19,590 --> 00:16:21,940
一把手不知道二把手要做什么
the number one didn't know what the number two was up to.

418
00:16:23,770 --> 00:16:25,430
你竟敢對我說這句話
You have the balls to say that to me?

419
00:16:25,430 --> 00:16:26,200
我不是在說
I'm not saying--

420
00:16:26,200 --> 00:16:27,430
我不在乎你想說什么
I don't care what you're saying.

421
00:16:28,320 --> 00:16:30,090
我是案子的負責人
I'm the one in charge of this case.

422
00:16:30,230 --> 00:16:32,720
相信我  我能說服任何人相信
And believe me, I can convince anyone

423
00:16:32,720 --> 00:16:34,210
二把手能背著一把手
of the fact that a number two

424
00:16:34,500 --> 00:16:36,600
做出背叛她的事
can betray a number one behind her back.

425
00:16:39,180 --> 00:16:40,220
出去
Out.

426
00:16:56,920 --> 00:16:58,600
-你還在躲著奈杰爾嗎  -什么
- You still hiding from Nigel? - What?

427
00:16:58,600 --> 00:16:59,730
不  我在找卡特里娜
No, I'm looking for Katrina.

428
00:16:59,730 --> 00:17:01,040
她剛剛去了巴塞羅那
She just left for Barcelona.

429
00:17:05,120 --> 00:17:06,310
抱歉  她什么
Sorry? She what?

430
00:17:06,340 --> 00:17:07,580
那個培訓項目
The training program.

431
00:17:08,720 --> 00:17:11,120
-是奈斯比特干的  -他為什么要把她送走
- Nesbitt. - why would he send her away?

432
00:17:11,120 --> 00:17:12,520
因為他知道在米卡度的撫養權聽證會上
Because he knew I'd pick her to represent me

433
00:17:12,520 --> 00:17:13,750
我會選她代表我
at Mikado's custody hearing.

434
00:17:13,750 --> 00:17:16,460
你為了撫養權起訴了嗎  路易  你瘋了
You're suing for custody? Louis, that's insane.

435
00:17:16,530 --> 00:17:18,600
-瑞秋  他拋棄了她  -他出差去了
- Rachel, he abandoned her. - He went on a business trip.

436
00:17:18,600 --> 00:17:20,110
-拜托  你站哪邊啊  -你這邊
- Okay, whose side are you on? - Yours.

437
00:17:20,110 --> 00:17:21,660
但法律可沒站你這邊
But the law is not with you.

438
00:17:21,670 --> 00:17:22,720
怎么  你覺得當你當上了律師以后
What, you think when you become a lawyer,

439
00:17:22,730 --> 00:17:24,790
就只用接那些有法律支持的案子嗎
you're gonna be trying cases where the law is always on your side?

440
00:17:24,790 --> 00:17:25,600
-路易  -瑞秋
- Louis. - Rachel.

441
00:17:25,600 --> 00:17:28,410
你得告訴我  現在哪個助理對奈杰爾最不忠誠
You need to tell me which associate is least loyal to Nigel now.

442
00:17:30,350 --> 00:17:32,090
-考夫曼  -不行  太菜了
- Kaufman. - No, too green.

443
00:17:32,090 --> 00:17:34,060
-科克倫  -那家伙把倉鼠當小孩養
- Corcoran. - the guy owned a hamster as a child.

444
00:17:34,060 --> 00:17:35,380
他會把貓當做捕食者的
He'll view a cat as a predator.

445
00:17:36,980 --> 00:17:39,040
-唐納修呢  -唐  唐  唐納修
- Donahue? - D-d-d-d-d-donahue?

446
00:17:39,080 --> 00:17:41,110
我不僅會失去撫養權  最后還要蹲監獄的
I'll not only lose custody, I may end up in jail.

447
00:17:41,110 --> 00:17:43,400
-為什么  -瑞秋  我偷了那貨的貓
- For what? - Rachel, I stole the man's cat.

448
00:17:43,400 --> 00:17:45,170
我需要找個理解我的人
And I need someone who understands why.

449
00:17:45,280 --> 00:17:46,380
那還能有誰  路易
Then who, Louis?

450
00:17:50,360 --> 00:17:51,750
瑞秋·贊恩
律師助理

451
00:17:52,790 --> 00:17:53,910
你
You.

452
00:17:54,560 --> 00:17:56,950
-我可不是律師  路易  -很快就是了
- I'm not a lawyer, Louis. - You're gonna be soon enough.

453
00:17:57,080 --> 00:17:58,860
你繞著這些小丑轉圈
You run circles around those clowns.

454
00:17:58,860 --> 00:18:00,790
奈杰爾拿你一點辦法都沒有
And Nigel holds no sway over you.

455
00:18:03,040 --> 00:18:04,120
好吧
Okay.

456
00:18:04,880 --> 00:18:07,930
你這是要我幫你偷奈杰爾的貓啊
You are asking me to help you steal Nigel's cat.

457
00:18:10,240 --> 00:18:12,160
瑞秋  你不知道我今年過得多坎坷
Rachel, you know how tough it's been for me this year.

458
00:18:13,520 --> 00:18:15,220
我失去了管理助理的資格
I lost the associates.

459
00:18:16,230 --> 00:18:17,600
邁克耍了我
Mike made a fool of me.

460
00:18:19,180 --> 00:18:20,920
我還看到哈維的名字上了墻
I saw Harvey's name go up on the wall.

461
00:18:20,920 --> 00:18:23,000
然后我回到家
And I went home.

462
00:18:23,930 --> 00:18:25,020
但你知道發生了什么嗎
But you know what happened?

463
00:18:27,170 --> 00:18:32,250
米卡度看出了我的痛苦  叼給我一只老鼠
Mikado saw my pain, and she brought me a mouse.

464
00:18:37,420 --> 00:18:39,800
路易  我們還有一場謀殺案庭審呢
Louis, we have a murder trial going on.

465
00:18:39,800 --> 00:18:41,430
那審判和我半毛錢關系沒有
A trial that I have nothing to do with.

466
00:18:46,050 --> 00:18:47,470
瑞秋  我愛她
Rachel, I love her.

467
00:18:49,900 --> 00:18:52,200
我曾經奮不顧身地為你的夢想奮斗
Now, I once fought valiantly for your dream.

468
00:18:52,210 --> 00:18:55,740
就算我失去了...
And even though I lost...

469
00:18:58,230 --> 00:18:59,480
現在我問你
I'm asking you.

470
00:19:02,570 --> 00:19:03,750
愿意為我奮斗嗎
Fight for mine?

471
00:19:10,740 --> 00:19:11,710
杰西卡
Jessica!

472
00:19:12,360 --> 00:19:13,800
尼克·豪厄爾的事你有什么消息嗎
You have something for me on Nick Howell?

473
00:19:13,800 --> 00:19:15,330
這是不是他干的
Nick Howell didn't do this.

474
00:19:15,330 --> 00:19:16,590
是啊  那又怎么樣啊
Yeah, what the hell does that have to do with anything?

475
00:19:16,590 --> 00:19:18,070
聽著  哈維不同意找尼克麻煩
Look, Harvey's problem with going after Nick

476
00:19:18,070 --> 00:19:20,050
是因為可能反而對艾娃不利  對吧
is that it might backfire on Ava, right?

477
00:19:20,050 --> 00:19:21,470
而就算沒有壞處  我們也在
But even if it doesn't, we're still putting

478
00:19:21,470 --> 00:19:22,920
把無辜的人推上風口浪尖
An innocent man in the cross hairs.

479
00:19:22,920 --> 00:19:24,070
他還真是無辜
An innocent man.

480
00:19:24,760 --> 00:19:26,640
他一有機會就把艾娃賣了
He sold out Ava the second he had a chance.

481
00:19:26,650 --> 00:19:28,350
我就坐在那兒  眼睜睜看著他賣
And I sat there and watched him do it.

482
00:19:28,350 --> 00:19:29,940
卡梅隆逼他做的
Cameron had him backed against a wall.

483
00:19:29,940 --> 00:19:31,140
他只是做了必須做的事
He just did what he had to do.

484
00:19:31,140 --> 00:19:32,680
現在我們被逼得走投無路的
And now, we're backed up against a wall.

485
00:19:32,680 --> 00:19:35,280
我才不在意艾娃的二號人物
And I don't give a shit about Ava's number two.

486
00:19:35,530 --> 00:19:37,240
他就自生自滅去吧
He can rot in hell for all I care.

487
00:19:38,370 --> 00:19:39,550
我有一個問題
I just have one question.

488
00:19:42,240 --> 00:19:44,960
你揪著他不放的原因  是因為他賣了艾娃
Are you going after him because he tried to sell Ava out

489
00:19:46,400 --> 00:19:48,170
還是因為哈維想把你賣了
or because Harvey tried to sell you out?

490
00:19:50,190 --> 00:19:51,590
你剛剛說什么
What did you just say to me?

491
00:19:52,120 --> 00:19:53,450
我只是想確定  沒有不經意間
I just wanna make sure we're not potentially

492
00:19:53,450 --> 00:19:54,610
就隨便處置了一個人的生命
throwing a man's life away

493
00:19:54,610 --> 00:19:56,770
僅僅因為你對另外一個人生氣
just because you're mad at someone else.

494
00:19:58,420 --> 00:20:02,090
你與其來這兒  跟我說該生誰的氣
Instead of you coming down here and telling me who to be mad at,

495
00:20:02,450 --> 00:20:03,980
不如好好干你的活兒
why don't you do your job?

496
00:20:03,980 --> 00:20:06,630
看看卡梅隆到底抓住了尼克·豪厄爾什么把柄
And find out what the hell Cameron has on Nick Howell

497
00:20:06,630 --> 00:20:09,770
能讓他一開始就背叛艾娃
that had him turn on Ava in the first place

498
00:20:10,120 --> 00:20:12,360
如果你覺得就只是那盤帶子
because if you think all it was was that tape,

499
00:20:12,620 --> 00:20:14,380
那你還真是不知道自己在做什么
then you don't know what the hell you're doing.

500
00:20:26,560 --> 00:20:29,270
他們想談和解  所以派了你過來嗎
They wanna talk settlement and they sent you?

501
00:20:29,660 --> 00:20:31,400
不是
No, they didn't.

502
00:20:31,570 --> 00:20:33,750
-那你是叛變了嗎  -胡說
- So you're going rogue? - Bullshit.

503
00:20:33,760 --> 00:20:35,880
-我才不信...  -愛信不信
- I don't buy it-- - you can buy whatever you want.

504
00:20:35,880 --> 00:20:37,770
是事實上  你  哈維  和杰西卡
The fact is you, Harvey, and Jessica

505
00:20:37,770 --> 00:20:39,360
全部心思都放在打倒對方上
are so busy trying to beat each other,

506
00:20:39,360 --> 00:20:41,400
都沒小心著自己的身后
you can't see you all have your heads up your asses.

507
00:20:41,400 --> 00:20:43,510
夠自大  我懂了  哈維把你教得很好嘛
Cocky, I get it. Harvey taught you well.

508
00:20:43,510 --> 00:20:46,500
不  哈維教我的是幫助我的客戶
No, what Harvey taught me is to help my client.

509
00:20:47,570 --> 00:20:50,660
聽著  我不能向你保證  我們會同意任何事
Now, look. I can't guarantee you that we'll agree to anything,

510
00:20:50,660 --> 00:20:53,360
但艾娃應該得到協議
but Ava deserves an offer.

511
00:20:53,360 --> 00:20:55,130
我一個禮拜之前就白紙黑字地說明了我的條件
I spelled out my offer a week ago.

512
00:20:55,130 --> 00:20:56,650
是啊  夸大了的條件
Yeah, an offer based on a bluff.

513
00:20:56,650 --> 00:21:00,070
現在我可貨真價實的  當時是9  現在是12
Huh, now, I've got the real deal. It was 9. Now, it's 12.

514
00:21:00,070 --> 00:21:02,210
你貨真價實的是供認不諱的謀殺
Your real deal is a confessed murderer

515
00:21:02,210 --> 00:21:03,870
和一個復仇心切的前雇員
and a vindictive ex-employee.

516
00:21:03,870 --> 00:21:06,360
我聽到個說法  說艾娃付錢讓你們做的
I've got one saying that Ava paid for it.

517
00:21:06,360 --> 00:21:09,580
還有種說法  她知道自己為了什么付錢
And another saying she knew what she was paying for.

518
00:21:09,590 --> 00:21:11,620
行了  給我個該死的條件吧  9以下的
Great, then get me a goddamn offer under nine,

519
00:21:11,620 --> 00:21:12,660
我就幫你達成和解
And I'll get you a deal.

520
00:21:12,660 --> 00:21:16,390
談判結束了  初級合伙人  愛咋咋地去吧
This negotiation is over, junior. Take your ball and go home.

521
00:21:16,390 --> 00:21:18,180
你真是個混蛋
You really are a dick.

522
00:21:18,430 --> 00:21:20,700
-你剛剛說什么  -我說  你是個混蛋
- What did you say? - I said you're a dick.

523
00:21:20,790 --> 00:21:23,690
你就帶著你的條件滾回家去吧
And you can take your offer and shove it up your ass.

524
00:21:29,310 --> 00:21:31,860
-抱歉  -你這個小破蟲子
- I am so sorry. - You little piss ant.

525
00:21:31,860 --> 00:21:33,890
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this shit.

526
00:21:34,040 --> 00:21:35,770
你以為你在和誰打交道
Who the hell do you think you're dealing with?

527
00:21:35,770 --> 00:21:38,500
要知道  憑侮辱罪我就能把你送進監獄
You know, I could have you locked up for assault right now?

528
00:21:38,500 --> 00:21:41,900
抱歉  我只是...只是昏了頭腦
Yeah, I'm sorry. You know, I just-- I lost my head.

529
00:21:41,900 --> 00:21:42,900
拜托了
Please.

530
00:21:43,810 --> 00:21:45,330
我...我只想盡力做好工作
I-I was just trying to do my job.

531
00:21:45,330 --> 00:21:49,020
帶著你的調解書滾出我的辦公室
Take your mediation and get the hell out of my office.

532
00:21:49,210 --> 00:21:50,290
是  先生
Yes, sir.

533
00:21:56,090 --> 00:21:57,490
利特先生  您會怎么形容
Mr. Litt, how would you describe

534
00:21:57,490 --> 00:22:00,630
米卡度在您監護下的良好表現呢
Mikado's well-being when she came under your care?

535
00:22:01,080 --> 00:22:04,820
我會認真照看米卡度的生理需求
Well, Mikado's physical needs were taken care of.

536
00:22:04,820 --> 00:22:06,800
但對一只貓來說  生理需求僅僅是很小一部分
But there's more to a cat than its physical condition.

537
00:22:06,800 --> 00:22:08,080
他們是感情非常豐富的動物
They're highly emotional creatures.

538
00:22:08,080 --> 00:22:09,850
她的情感需求得到了滿足嗎
And were her emotional needs tended to?

539
00:22:09,850 --> 00:22:12,180
反對  請做推測  他不懂貓語
Calls for speculation. He's not the cat whisperer.

540
00:22:12,180 --> 00:22:14,380
他不能檢測米卡度的想法
He can't testify to Mikado's thoughts,

541
00:22:14,900 --> 00:22:16,610
這一點上你應該做出反對
which you should've objected to.

542
00:22:17,100 --> 00:22:19,050
-抱歉  先生  -很好
- Sorry, sir. - Very well.

543
00:22:19,370 --> 00:22:22,280
利特先生  在無法和米卡度對話的情況下
Mr. Litt, without speaking for Mikado,

544
00:22:22,280 --> 00:22:25,870
你能為大家描述一下她的情緒狀況嗎
would you describe for the court her emotional condition?

545
00:22:25,870 --> 00:22:31,200
當米卡度第一次到我家時  她很冷漠傲慢
When Mikado first entered my home, she was aloof and standoffish.

546
00:22:31,200 --> 00:22:32,350
她是只貓
She's a cat.

547
00:22:33,100 --> 00:22:34,770
抱歉  我會等輪到我的
Sorry. I'll wait my turn.

548
00:22:34,770 --> 00:22:35,760
她就是懶洋洋的  懂了吧
She was listless, you know?

549
00:22:35,760 --> 00:22:40,860
好比  我會帶她出去見見鳥  見見狗
Like, I would take her out to see a bird or a dog.

550
00:22:40,860 --> 00:22:43,340
但她一點反應都沒有
And there'd just be nothing.

551
00:22:44,190 --> 00:22:45,160
-你知道我怎么想的嗎  -請說
- You know what I think? - hm?

552
00:22:45,160 --> 00:22:47,530
我覺得是由于長期缺乏父親的撫養
I think that she was the victim of neglect

553
00:22:47,530 --> 00:22:49,040
她被忽視太久了
due to the absence of a consistent father figure

554
00:22:49,050 --> 00:22:50,140
因為他一直在出差
because he's traveling all the time.

555
00:22:50,140 --> 00:22:51,630
-我反對  -反對什么
- I object. - to what?

556
00:22:51,630 --> 00:22:54,200
反對你讓他那樣說我的貓
To you letting him talk about my cat that way.

557
00:22:54,200 --> 00:22:56,040
你改變了規則  來讓贊恩女士代表你
You changed the rules to get Ms. Zane.

558
00:22:56,040 --> 00:22:58,700
那我也要改變規則  我要代表我自己
I'm changing the rules. I'm gonna represent myself.

559
00:22:58,940 --> 00:23:00,790
-但...-你被解雇了
- Dut-- - You're dismissed.

560
00:23:05,780 --> 00:23:07,270
情況變得激動人心了吧  奈斯比特
Getting hot in here, Nesbitt?

561
00:23:07,270 --> 00:23:10,080
利特先生  我會要求你不要自己擔當辯護律師
Mr. Litt, I'll ask you not to address the defendant directly.

562
00:23:10,270 --> 00:23:13,750
我不是辯護律師  這不是罪案審判
I'm not the defendant. This isn't a criminal trial.

563
00:23:13,750 --> 00:23:15,080
本來應該是的
Well, it should be.

564
00:23:16,130 --> 00:23:16,850
說到哪兒了
Where were we?

565
00:23:16,850 --> 00:23:18,920
你在描述  當你發現奈斯比特先生的貓時
You were describing the deplorable condition

566
00:23:18,920 --> 00:23:20,850
她所處的悲慘境界
in which you found mr. Nesbitt's cat.

567
00:23:20,850 --> 00:23:21,960
對的
Oh, yeah.

568
00:23:24,450 --> 00:23:26,730
杰西卡  我一直在等你電話
Jessica, I've been expecting your call.

569
00:23:26,740 --> 00:23:28,760
你才沒有在等這通電話
You aren't expecting this call.

570
00:23:28,890 --> 00:23:32,440
有人向我指出  我似乎發火找錯了對象
It was pointed out to me that I had misplaced some of my anger.

571
00:23:32,440 --> 00:23:34,390
那我決定轉移一點給你
So I've decided to place some of it on you.

572
00:23:34,390 --> 00:23:36,190
那么  這就是我在等的電話
Then this is the call I was expecting.

573
00:23:36,190 --> 00:23:37,300
你聽說了史蒂芬的事
You've heard about Stephen?

574
00:23:37,300 --> 00:23:40,430
我聽說了你  以及你和哈維的協議
I heard about you. And your deal with Harvey.

575
00:23:41,300 --> 00:23:42,830
我還在想你什么時候會發現
I was wondering when you'd find out.

576
00:23:42,830 --> 00:23:43,990
得了
Save it.

577
00:23:44,250 --> 00:23:45,660
我在想  當我擺脫丹尼爾·哈德曼的時候
I thought when I got rid of Daniel Hardman,

578
00:23:45,660 --> 00:23:47,520
我絕對不會找我不信任的合伙人了
I was done with partners I couldn't trust.

579
00:23:47,520 --> 00:23:49,100
我猜你說的是哈維
I assume you're referring to Harvey

580
00:23:49,100 --> 00:23:51,640
因為那協議可不是我提的
because I'm not the one who proposed that deal.

581
00:23:51,650 --> 00:23:54,650
他提和你接受不是一回事
Him asking isn't the same as you accepting.

582
00:23:54,650 --> 00:23:57,380
確實不是  但他想退出就是因為你
No, it isn't, but he was going to quit because of you.

583
00:23:57,380 --> 00:23:58,910
但那個協議強迫他留下了
And that deal made him stay.

584
00:23:58,910 --> 00:24:01,760
正如你自己說的那樣  他對律所至關重要
And as you said yourself, he is essential to the firm.

585
00:24:01,770 --> 00:24:03,930
不如我重要
Not more essential than me.

586
00:24:03,980 --> 00:24:05,440
而你和哈維訂的協議
And as for your deal with Harvey,

587
00:24:05,440 --> 00:24:08,230
已經不存在了  因為他不想要了
it doesn't exist because he doesn't want it anymore.

588
00:24:08,230 --> 00:24:10,730
這正是我一開始就希望的
Which was my hope from the beginning.

589
00:24:10,730 --> 00:24:13,260
你真是個圣人  對吧
You are a saint, aren't you?

590
00:24:13,590 --> 00:24:17,100
我不確定我完全理解你為什么打這通電話
I'm not sure I fully understand the purpose of this call.

591
00:24:17,100 --> 00:24:18,570
我希望史蒂芬·亨特利消失
I want Stephen Huntley gone.

592
00:24:18,570 --> 00:24:20,450
我不會再容許他做更多破壞
I won't allow him to do any more damage.

593
00:24:20,450 --> 00:24:23,550
你有了問題  會去找哈維
When you have a problem, you turn to Harvey.

594
00:24:23,550 --> 00:24:26,040
斯蒂芬就像我的哈維
Stephen fills that role for me.

595
00:24:26,420 --> 00:24:28,380
你想讓他消失  那就打贏這個案子
You want him gone? Win the case.

596
00:24:28,380 --> 00:24:30,330
他馬上坐下一班飛機離開
He'll be on the next flight out.

597
00:24:30,330 --> 00:24:34,500
愛德華  哈維和我會贏的
Edward, Harvey and I are going to win this case.

598
00:24:34,680 --> 00:24:37,060
到時候咱倆就得好好談談
And then you and I are going to have a conversation

599
00:24:37,060 --> 00:24:39,550
這場合并的未來了
about the future of this merger.

600
00:24:40,150 --> 00:24:42,070
現在我懂了
Ah, now I understand.

601
00:24:43,270 --> 00:24:43,900
什么
What?

602
00:24:43,900 --> 00:24:46,330
通過告訴你我在協議里扮演的角色
By telling you about my part in his deal,

603
00:24:46,330 --> 00:24:48,320
哈維使你反對這次合并
he's turned you against the very merger

604
00:24:48,320 --> 00:24:50,420
他從一開始就不想合并
he never wanted in the first place.

605
00:24:50,420 --> 00:24:53,970
-哈維和這件事毫無關系  -是嗎
- Harvey had nothing to do with this. - Hadn't he?

606
00:24:55,420 --> 00:24:56,810
再見  愛德華
Good-bye, edward.

607
00:25:07,520 --> 00:25:09,730
你把自己塑造成了
You have portrayed yourself

608
00:25:09,730 --> 00:25:12,580
貓咪靈魂的 
as the kindhearted savior

609
00:25:12,580 --> 00:25:14,780
善良拯救者
of this feline soul.

610
00:25:15,290 --> 00:25:16,990
是嗎
Is that correct?

611
00:25:17,350 --> 00:25:19,090
對  我找出了她的善良本性
Yeah, I believe I've brought out the best in her.

612
00:25:19,090 --> 00:25:21,010
所以你有自己對待下屬的辦法
So you have a way with your charges?

613
00:25:21,010 --> 00:25:23,920
比如  外柔內剛
A velvet glove, so to speak?

614
00:25:24,000 --> 00:25:26,200
可以這么說  我就是這樣的人
I guess you could say I'm built that way.

615
00:25:26,200 --> 00:25:27,730
所以說你是個盡責的家長
So you're a good parent?

616
00:25:27,820 --> 00:25:29,680
一個榜樣嗎
Um, a role model?

617
00:25:29,870 --> 00:25:31,590
人人都這樣說
No one could say otherwise.

618
00:25:31,930 --> 00:25:35,440
如果說你其中一個對待下屬的特點是
So if one of your charges were to say you were hostile,

619
00:25:35,640 --> 00:25:39,070
不友好  冷酷  喜歡嘲笑他人
cruel, prone to kicking the proverbial dog,

620
00:25:40,270 --> 00:25:41,510
這是真的嗎
would that be a lie?

621
00:25:41,680 --> 00:25:43,810
我對待貓的態度才是重點
My treatment of felines is what's of issue here.

622
00:25:43,810 --> 00:25:45,340
你的教育方法和耐心培養
I thought it was your parenting skills,

623
00:25:45,340 --> 00:25:47,250
這才是重點
your ability to mold and shape gently.

624
00:25:47,250 --> 00:25:48,230
但這不是
But that's not--

625
00:25:48,230 --> 00:25:51,050
陪審團都很清楚你的教育方法
This jury knows all about your parenting skills,

626
00:25:51,070 --> 00:25:53,750
包括責怪  貶低
which involve berating, belittling,

627
00:25:53,750 --> 00:25:55,670
吼叫  虐待
screaming, sadism--

628
00:25:55,670 --> 00:25:56,970
反對
Objection!

629
00:25:57,270 --> 00:25:58,770
隨便你怎么反對
You can object all you like.

630
00:25:58,770 --> 00:26:02,950
正如我說的  陪審團知道
But as I said, this jury knows

631
00:26:03,270 --> 00:26:06,490
你沒你說的那么好
that that man is not what he portrays himself to be.

632
00:26:06,490 --> 00:26:07,840
那你呢
And what about you?

633
00:26:07,910 --> 00:26:09,840
你以為不管他們
You think molding and shaping is accomplished

634
00:26:09,840 --> 00:26:11,020
偶爾寫個備忘錄給他們
by abandoning your charges

635
00:26:11,020 --> 00:26:12,410
然后自己跑去揚子江泡泥浴
and sending the occasional memo

636
00:26:12,410 --> 00:26:14,610
這樣就算培養他們嗎
while you're off mudding in the Yangtze?

637
00:26:15,810 --> 00:26:17,350
我請求傳召下一位證人
I'd like to call my next witness.

638
00:26:17,350 --> 00:26:18,380
真的嗎  什么證人
Oh, really? What witness?

639
00:26:18,380 --> 00:26:19,610
你沒說有證人啊
You didn't declare a witness.

640
00:26:19,610 --> 00:26:21,270
他是個惡意證人
He's a hostile witness.

641
00:26:21,990 --> 00:26:24,580
而他的惡意  只怕是對你的
And I'm afraid he's hostile to you.

642
00:26:24,970 --> 00:26:28,170
請哈羅德·甘德森上庭作證
I call Harold Gunderson to the stand.

643
00:26:32,670 --> 00:26:34,300
我去  有麻煩了
Holy sh--. We're in trouble.

644
00:26:34,300 --> 00:26:36,080
我們請求十分鐘休庭
We need a ten-minute recess.

645
00:26:40,020 --> 00:26:41,580
不  瑞秋  抱歉
No, no, Rachel, I'm sorry,

646
00:26:41,580 --> 00:26:42,810
現在沒時間
but I can't talk right now.

647
00:26:42,810 --> 00:26:45,070
我憑記憶把卡梅隆文件的內容打出來
I am typing up Cameron's files from memory.

648
00:26:45,070 --> 00:26:47,550
邁克  我第一次打官司就要輸了...
Mike, I am going to lose my first case...

649
00:26:47,550 --> 00:26:48,780
模擬庭審...
A mock case...

650
00:26:48,780 --> 00:26:50,390
-好  -是關于一只貓
- Okay. - About a cat.

651
00:26:52,660 --> 00:26:55,060
那我還是有幾分鐘時間的
Okay, that, I have a couple of minutes for.

652
00:26:55,630 --> 00:26:57,380
奈杰爾找來哈羅德
Nigel dug up Harold.

653
00:26:57,660 --> 00:26:59,440
什么  他肯定不會放過路易
What? He's gonna throw Louis under the bus.

654
00:26:59,440 --> 00:27:00,140
所以我才要你幫忙啊
Which is why I need your help.

655
00:27:00,140 --> 00:27:00,950
我需要你想想
I need you to remember

656
00:27:00,950 --> 00:27:03,130
他說過的所有關于路易的好話
anything good he said about Louis.

657
00:27:03,130 --> 00:27:05,410
-不能  -你說什么
- I can't. - What are you talking about?

658
00:27:05,410 --> 00:27:06,850
你不是有那驚人的記憶力嗎
You were just referring to your amazing memory.

659
00:27:06,850 --> 00:27:08,260
不是我想不起來
No, it's not that I can't remember it.

660
00:27:08,260 --> 00:27:10,350
是他從來沒說過
It's that he never said anything good.

661
00:27:10,700 --> 00:27:11,950
天啊  這回我慘了
Oh, my god. I'm screwed.

662
00:27:11,950 --> 00:27:13,410
對不起  瑞秋  我得走了
I'm so sorry, Rachel, but I have to go.

663
00:27:13,410 --> 00:27:14,990
開玩笑吧  一點忙都幫不上嗎
What--are you kidding? You've got--you've got nothing?

664
00:27:14,990 --> 00:27:16,590
我對你有信心
What I have is complete faith in you.

665
00:27:16,590 --> 00:27:18,100
在你想出法子對付哈羅德之前
So say hi to Harold for me

666
00:27:18,100 --> 00:27:19,930
幫我問聲好
before you figure out a way to screw him.

667
00:27:27,350 --> 00:27:29,690
杰西卡沒錯  尼克是幕后黑手 
Jessica was right. There's dirt on Nick.

668
00:27:30,220 --> 00:27:31,080
你怎么拿到的
Where'd you get this?

669
00:27:31,080 --> 00:27:32,410
感謝卡梅隆·丹尼斯吧
It's courtesy of Cameron Dennis.

670
00:27:32,420 --> 00:27:33,900
-我去了他那  -我去
- I actually went in there-- - Holy sh--.

671
00:27:33,900 --> 00:27:36,320
有足夠證據指證他了
I know, there's enough there to point the finger at him.

672
00:27:36,320 --> 00:27:38,480
有足夠證據讓我懷疑真是他做的
There's enough here to make me think that he really did it.

673
00:27:38,540 --> 00:27:39,810
你想怎么做
So what do you wanna do?

674
00:27:40,180 --> 00:27:41,450
跟杰西卡說她是對的
Go tell Jessica she was right

675
00:27:41,460 --> 00:27:42,550
然后把尼克·豪厄爾找來
and then get Nick Howell in here.

676
00:27:42,550 --> 00:27:44,120
在上法庭之前
And make sure he doesn't have an answer for this

677
00:27:44,120 --> 00:27:45,000
確保他不知道這事
before we get to court.

678
00:27:45,000 --> 00:27:46,080
馬上辦
On it.

679
00:27:49,460 --> 00:27:53,680
甘德森先生  你現在是布萊頓-古爾德的律師
Mr. Gunderson, you're currently an associate at Bratton Gould.

680
00:27:53,680 --> 00:27:56,060
你之前在哪工作呢
At what firm did you previously work?

681
00:27:56,660 --> 00:27:57,800
在這
I worked here.

682
00:27:57,950 --> 00:28:00,010
誰是你的上司
And who was your supervisor?

683
00:28:00,280 --> 00:28:02,260
那位  路易·利特
That man, Louis Litt.

684
00:28:02,260 --> 00:28:03,380
真的嗎  哈羅德
Really, Harold?

685
00:28:03,380 --> 00:28:05,050
記錄顯示甘德森先生
Let the record show that Mr. Gunderson

686
00:28:05,060 --> 00:28:06,690
投訴利特先生
indicated Mr. Litt.

687
00:28:06,990 --> 00:28:09,330
說說利特先生是怎么教導下屬的
Tell me about Mr. Litt's guidance.

688
00:28:10,480 --> 00:28:12,480
路易認為要采用恐嚇的方式
Louis believes in teaching by fear.

689
00:28:12,480 --> 00:28:14,190
法官大人  我想說明一下
Your Honor, I'd just like to state for the record

690
00:28:14,190 --> 00:28:16,230
證人在對著假想的麥克風說話
that the witness is speaking into an imaginary microphone.

691
00:28:16,230 --> 00:28:17,740
你在對著假想的麥克風說話
You're speaking into an imaginary microphone.

692
00:28:17,740 --> 00:28:18,540
看吧  就是這樣
That's what I mean. -

693
00:28:18,540 --> 00:28:20,230
算了  繼續吧
you know what? Fine, I'm done. Proceed.

694
00:28:20,240 --> 00:28:23,310
你覺得他是個喜歡大喊大叫的人嗎
Would you characterize him as a-a screamer?

695
00:28:23,310 --> 00:28:26,590
暴君  小氣  報復心強
A tyrant? Petty and vindictive?

696
00:28:26,690 --> 00:28:27,860
全部符合
All of the above.

697
00:28:27,860 --> 00:28:32,140
他沒有像吹玻璃一樣耐心的栽培你嗎
He didn't try to gently sculpt your future like blown glass?

698
00:28:32,140 --> 00:28:34,680
他叫我笨蛋腦殘
He called me an idiot, an imbecile,

699
00:28:34,680 --> 00:28:37,060
還說我是律師界的恥辱
and an embarrassment to the legal profession.

700
00:28:37,060 --> 00:28:38,060
真殘忍啊
That sounds harsh.

701
00:28:38,060 --> 00:28:40,540
我的心理醫生說我精神受創了
My therapist says that I have scars on my psyche.

702
00:28:40,550 --> 00:28:42,780
-道聽途說  -我能打電話給那心理醫生
- Hearsay. - I could call said therapist.

703
00:28:42,780 --> 00:28:43,820
太好了
Oh, that'd be lovely,

704
00:28:43,820 --> 00:28:45,550
不過這跟貓有什么關系
except it still has nothing to do with the cat.

705
00:28:45,550 --> 00:28:47,820
再等等  我就要說到貓的事了
Uh, bear with me. I'm getting there.

706
00:28:48,200 --> 00:28:52,740
說說布魯諾吧
Uh, tell me about Bruno.

707
00:28:55,160 --> 00:28:58,630
它是路易的貓  我負責照顧它
He was Louis's cat. I was made to take care of him.

708
00:28:59,010 --> 00:29:00,990
-他不自己照顧貓嗎  -不
- He didn't do it himself? - No.

709
00:29:01,770 --> 00:29:03,680
你喜歡貓嗎  哈羅德
Do you like cats, Harold?

710
00:29:03,690 --> 00:29:04,770
不喜歡
No.

711
00:29:05,810 --> 00:29:07,180
我對貓過敏
I'm allergic.

712
00:29:07,600 --> 00:29:09,100
我都不知道要怎么照顧貓
I don't even know what to do with them.

713
00:29:09,100 --> 00:29:11,810
但他把自己的貓  自己的貓
But he left this cat, his cat,

714
00:29:12,110 --> 00:29:13,460
交給你照顧
in your care?

715
00:29:13,850 --> 00:29:15,740
-之后發生什么事了  -嘿
- What happened? - Hey, you know what?

716
00:29:15,740 --> 00:29:16,440
是時候反對了
This would be a good time to object.

717
00:29:16,440 --> 00:29:18,410
不行  路易  他的問題有道理
I can't, Louis, it's a valid line of questioning.

718
00:29:18,410 --> 00:29:21,040
發生什么事了  甘德森先生
What happened, Mr. Gunderson?

719
00:29:22,720 --> 00:29:24,900
他一天后就死了
He died a day later.

720
00:29:25,020 --> 00:29:28,240
他在那天前跟你說了什么
And what did he say to you prior to that day?

721
00:29:28,240 --> 00:29:30,780
他說他還不如把貓
He said he might as well have left his cat

722
00:29:30,780 --> 00:29:32,430
交給邁克爾·維克
with Michael Vick.

723
00:29:30,780 --> 00:29:33,430
 費城老鷹四分衛

724
00:29:41,480 --> 00:29:42,840
她怎么會來
I didn't realize she'd be here.

725
00:29:42,840 --> 00:29:44,950
你就不想面對我嗎
Didn't want to look me in the eye?

726
00:29:44,950 --> 00:29:46,210
艾娃  對不起
Ava, I'm sorry.

727
00:29:46,210 --> 00:29:48,000
我很高興能當你的品格見證人
I'm glad I can help you as a character witness.

728
00:29:48,000 --> 00:29:50,170
我不知道承認賄賂
I had no idea admitting to the bribe

729
00:29:50,170 --> 00:29:51,230
會導致這些謊言
would lead to this nonsense.

730
00:29:51,230 --> 00:29:53,650
教唆殺人是謊言嗎
Solicitation of murder is nonsense?

731
00:29:53,970 --> 00:29:55,810
你知道我的意思  艾娃絕不會這樣做
You know what I meant, that Ava would never do that.

732
00:29:55,820 --> 00:29:58,080
我們同意  她的確不會
Oh, we agree. We don't think she would.

733
00:29:58,080 --> 00:29:59,440
但你會
We think you would.

734
00:30:00,760 --> 00:30:02,510
什么意思  你們想把罪名推給我
What? You're trying to blame the murders on me?

735
00:30:02,510 --> 00:30:04,470
你在艾娃之前  就見過馬加里
You met with Mariga before Ava did.

736
00:30:04,470 --> 00:30:07,160
這些都是你安排的  你也同意給錢
You made the arrangements. You agreed on the payments.

737
00:30:07,160 --> 00:30:08,520
你們都知道這些
You know all this.

738
00:30:08,530 --> 00:30:10,100
但我們不知道這個
But we didn't know this.

739
00:30:10,460 --> 00:30:13,080
記錄顯示兇案發生一星期后
Mr. Howell is being shown a record of deposits

740
00:30:13,080 --> 00:30:14,770
豪厄爾先生開了幾個瑞士銀行賬戶
into a numbered Swiss bank account

741
00:30:14,770 --> 00:30:16,700
并往里邊匯錢
opened one week after the murders.

742
00:30:16,710 --> 00:30:17,550
你們怎么拿到這個的
How did you get this?

743
00:30:17,550 --> 00:30:18,490
你是說這不是你的嗎
Are you saying it's not yours?

744
00:30:18,490 --> 00:30:19,810
不是你們看到這樣的
It's not what it seems.

745
00:30:19,810 --> 00:30:21,180
那告訴我們是什么
Then tell us what it is.

746
00:30:21,180 --> 00:30:23,790
因為這看起來像是在分贓
Because what it looks like is a split of the take.

747
00:30:23,790 --> 00:30:25,770
馬加里給你多少錢
How much did Mariga cut you in for?

748
00:30:25,770 --> 00:30:26,730
這是獎金
These are bonuses.

749
00:30:26,730 --> 00:30:27,510
獎金
Bonuses?

750
00:30:27,510 --> 00:30:28,780
是我合約上的條款
Part of my deal,

751
00:30:28,780 --> 00:30:30,350
為了鼓勵我
incentive payments for getting the job done

752
00:30:30,350 --> 00:30:31,690
完成了困難的任務
under hardship conditions.

753
00:30:31,690 --> 00:30:34,460
唯一的困難是找人去殺人吧
The only hardship you had was finding someone to kill those people.

754
00:30:34,460 --> 00:30:37,470
你與馬加里分贓  然后把錢藏起來
You split the take with Mariga then hid your share.

755
00:30:37,470 --> 00:30:39,240
這錢不是馬加里上校分給我的
This money didn't come from Colonel Mariga.

756
00:30:39,250 --> 00:30:41,640
是海辛頓石油的錢  她知道的
It came from Hessington Oil and she knows it.

757
00:30:41,640 --> 00:30:43,500
你不能一直說是艾娃的錯
You can't keep pointing the finger at Ava.

758
00:30:43,500 --> 00:30:44,890
這是你自己一個人干的
You acted alone on this.

759
00:30:44,890 --> 00:30:47,130
我有發郵件請她批準
I have emails asking for her authorization

760
00:30:47,130 --> 00:30:48,680
給我發獎金
to make bonus payments.

761
00:30:48,690 --> 00:30:51,670
那些郵件沒有提到瑞士銀行賬戶
Those emails didn't mention Swiss bank accounts.

762
00:30:51,670 --> 00:30:53,590
因為我知道你不想我提出來
Because I knew you wouldn't want them to.

763
00:30:53,590 --> 00:30:54,750
胡扯
Bullsh--.

764
00:30:54,780 --> 00:30:56,620
你沒有提到瑞士銀行賬戶
It didn't mention Swiss bank accounts

765
00:30:56,620 --> 00:30:59,830
因為你去找了馬加里和安排了一切
because you went to Mariga and arranged everything.

766
00:31:00,150 --> 00:31:01,800
我根本不認識馬加里
I didn't even know Mariga.

767
00:31:01,850 --> 00:31:03,740
他來找我  他提出要受賄
He came to me. He laid out a bribe.

768
00:31:03,740 --> 00:31:06,060
我接受了  我干了什么艾娃都知道
I accepted it. And Ava knew everything I did.

769
00:31:06,060 --> 00:31:07,530
-騙人  -她知道
- That's a lie. - She knew.

770
00:31:07,530 --> 00:31:09,640
她只是不知道細節
She just didn't know the specifics.

771
00:31:09,640 --> 00:31:10,740
你們現在像是在指責我
And now, you're acting like this means

772
00:31:10,740 --> 00:31:13,240
下令殺了那些人
that I ordered the killing of those people.

773
00:31:13,240 --> 00:31:15,010
我沒有
Well, I didn't.

774
00:31:15,470 --> 00:31:18,120
如果你們要試著指責我背著她干這些
And if you try to make it look like I did it without her knowledge,

775
00:31:18,120 --> 00:31:21,430
沒有陪審團會相信  因為這不是真的
no jury's ever going to believe it because it's not true.

776
00:31:30,440 --> 00:31:32,210
甘德森先生  你在本事務所的工作
Mr. Gunderson, your tenure at this law firm

777
00:31:32,210 --> 00:31:34,060
不是非常成功  是吧
wasn't very successful, was it?

778
00:31:34,060 --> 00:31:35,420
我工作很努力
I worked very hard.

779
00:31:35,420 --> 00:31:37,050
有次你沒能把動議書送到法庭
Is it true that you once failed to deliver

780
00:31:37,050 --> 00:31:38,720
因為你以為惡劣天氣導致法庭關閉
a motion to the court because you thought

781
00:31:38,720 --> 00:31:40,340
這是真的嗎
they were closed due to inclement weather?

782
00:31:40,340 --> 00:31:42,020
有人跟我說那天會下雪呢
Someone told me that it was a snow day.

783
00:31:42,020 --> 00:31:43,400
你曾經把我們的辯護策略
Did you ever give opposing counsel

784
00:31:43,400 --> 00:31:45,010
給對方律師看嗎
a copy of our trial strategy?

785
00:31:45,010 --> 00:31:46,460
我以為那是可以公開的
I thought it was part of disclosure.

786
00:31:46,470 --> 00:31:48,920
你是不是在霍普金斯調解書里少寫了個零
Did you leave a zero off the Hopkins settlement,

787
00:31:48,920 --> 00:31:52,110
差點讓客戶損失90萬
nearly costing the client $900,000?

788
00:31:54,340 --> 00:31:56,200
沒人知道這事的
No one was supposed to know about that.

789
00:31:56,200 --> 00:31:57,870
因為路易幫你瞞過去了
Because Louis covered for you.

790
00:31:58,220 --> 00:31:59,880
-他罵了我  -沒有
- He berated me. - No.

791
00:31:59,880 --> 00:32:01,310
他沒把這事說出來
He kept it private.

792
00:32:01,310 --> 00:32:02,900
讓你有機會去補救
And he allowed you to go back and fix it.

793
00:32:02,900 --> 00:32:04,960
-是嗎  -是的
- Did he not? - He did.

794
00:32:04,960 --> 00:32:06,670
這讓你從錯誤中學習
Which allowed you to learn from your mistakes.

795
00:32:06,670 --> 00:32:08,660
-是嗎  -是吧
- Did it not? - I guess.

796
00:32:08,660 --> 00:32:10,380
你說你在布萊頓-古爾德事務所工作
You testified that you now work at Bratton Gould.

797
00:32:10,380 --> 00:32:11,850
-是嗎  -是的
- Is that correct? - Yes.

798
00:32:11,850 --> 00:32:12,980
當他們雇傭你的時候
And when they hired you,

799
00:32:12,980 --> 00:32:15,230
他們知道是路易·利特教導你的嗎
did they know you'd been trained by Louis Litt?

800
00:32:15,380 --> 00:32:16,110
有提到
It came up.

801
00:32:16,110 --> 00:32:18,250
所以他們知道是路易培養你
So they knew that you were nurtured by Louis.

802
00:32:18,330 --> 00:32:19,660
他們雇傭了你
They hired you.

803
00:32:19,790 --> 00:32:22,930
現在你開心嗎
And now, are you happy?

804
00:32:24,310 --> 00:32:25,060
開心
Yes.

805
00:32:25,060 --> 00:32:26,550
由于路易的寬容
So with Louis' nurturance,

806
00:32:26,550 --> 00:32:27,940
你犯的錯誤沒被人知道
your mistakes were covered,

807
00:32:27,950 --> 00:32:29,780
你找到了另一份工作
you landed another job,

808
00:32:29,920 --> 00:32:31,140
而且很開心
and you're happy.

809
00:32:31,360 --> 00:32:32,670
是這樣嗎
Isn't that correct?

810
00:32:33,010 --> 00:32:34,090
但他對我好刻薄
But he was mean to me.

811
00:32:34,090 --> 00:32:36,310
不  這無關他這么對你  哈羅德
No, this isn't about how he treated you, Harold.

812
00:32:36,310 --> 00:32:38,930
這關乎于他怎么對待他的貓
This is about how he treated his cat.

813
00:32:39,010 --> 00:32:42,120
他愛那只貓
And isn't the truth that he loved that cat

814
00:32:42,120 --> 00:32:44,460
并且全心全意地照顧它  是不是真的
and cared for him with all of his heart?

815
00:32:49,620 --> 00:32:51,910
-哈羅德  你宣過誓了  -不  我沒有
- Harold, you're under oath. - No, I'm not.

816
00:32:51,910 --> 00:32:53,160
哈羅德
Harold.

817
00:32:55,490 --> 00:32:58,300
是的  他全心全意地愛著布魯諾
Yes, he loved Bruno with all of his heart.

818
00:33:04,800 --> 00:33:06,620
我沒有問題了
I have no further questions.

819
00:33:22,970 --> 00:33:24,260
真叫人驚喜啊
What a lovely surprise.

820
00:33:24,260 --> 00:33:26,060
我帶禮物來了
And I come bearing gifts.

821
00:33:26,160 --> 00:33:27,180
不必這么麻煩
Oh, you didn't have to do that.

822
00:33:27,180 --> 00:33:28,710
沒事啦
Oh, well, it's only right.

823
00:33:29,020 --> 00:33:30,190
你送給我這么多東西了
You've given me so many things.

824
00:33:30,190 --> 00:33:32,230
我還從來沒送東西給你
And I've never given you anything.

825
00:33:33,000 --> 00:33:35,530
送這樣的東西
Well, anything like this.

826
00:33:35,830 --> 00:33:36,950
這是什么
What is it?

827
00:33:37,400 --> 00:33:39,100
你沒認出來我很意外啊
I'm surprised you don't recognize it.

828
00:33:40,270 --> 00:33:42,510
這是馬加里上校的證詞副本
It's a copy of Colonel Mariga's deposition.

829
00:33:44,170 --> 00:33:46,530
我的復印頁數跟復印機上的不一致
My copy count didn't reconcile with the machine.

830
00:33:46,530 --> 00:33:48,320
復印完七頁就停了
It was off by seven pages,

831
00:33:48,970 --> 00:33:50,920
這才是證詞的真正頁數
the exact amount of that.

832
00:33:53,400 --> 00:33:55,050
你以為我不會注意
You thought I wouldn't notice.

833
00:33:56,160 --> 00:33:57,230
我注意了
I would.

834
00:33:58,140 --> 00:33:59,020
你暗中監視我
You spied on me.

835
00:33:59,020 --> 00:34:01,090
不  我信任過你
Oh, no. I trusted you.

836
00:34:01,270 --> 00:34:02,010
唐娜
Donna...

837
00:34:02,010 --> 00:34:03,390
別再叫我唐娜了
Don't Donna me.

838
00:34:03,620 --> 00:34:05,890
你面對著我發過誓的
You looked me in the face and you made me a promise.

839
00:34:06,630 --> 00:34:08,490
我也對愛德華·達比發過誓了
I also made a promise to Edward Darby.

840
00:34:08,490 --> 00:34:10,000
我對哈維發過誓
And I made a promise to Harvey.

841
00:34:10,000 --> 00:34:11,390
如果是我  知道只能忠于一人
And I wouldn't make another one

842
00:34:11,390 --> 00:34:12,980
我就不會再發對另一人發誓
if I knew I could only keep one.

843
00:34:12,980 --> 00:34:15,270
所以你現在要選擇你跟他不能擁有的東西
So you're choosing what you don't have with him

844
00:34:15,270 --> 00:34:17,030
而放棄你我擁有的東西
over something that you do have with me?

845
00:34:17,040 --> 00:34:19,030
這跟他沒關系
This has nothing to do with him.

846
00:34:19,670 --> 00:34:21,870
我不在乎你是否說過你不會插手諾瑪的事情
I don't care if you said you'd stay out of Norma's business

847
00:34:21,870 --> 00:34:23,210
然后又食言了
and you went back on it.

848
00:34:23,210 --> 00:34:24,490
重點是你對我撒謊了
You lied to me.

849
00:34:26,570 --> 00:34:27,650
我們分手吧
We're done.

850
00:34:30,740 --> 00:34:33,540
對了  不客氣
And by the way, you're welcome.

851
00:34:35,520 --> 00:34:36,590
為什么
For what?

852
00:34:36,650 --> 00:34:38,390
沒跟哈維說這一切
For not telling Harvey about this.

853
00:34:39,120 --> 00:34:40,080
因為他要是發現了
Because if he found out,

854
00:34:40,080 --> 00:34:41,960
會把你打得屁滾尿流
he would beat the shit outta you.

855
00:34:50,980 --> 00:34:51,980
小心點
Watch what you're doing.

856
00:34:51,980 --> 00:34:53,320
我壓根沒動
I wasn't actually moving.

857
00:34:53,320 --> 00:34:55,170
好吧  我壓根不在乎
Yeah, well, I don't actually care.

858
00:34:56,020 --> 00:34:57,840
-唐娜  你還好嗎  -我很好
- Donna, are you okay? - Yeah, I'm fine.

859
00:34:57,840 --> 00:34:59,140
唐娜
Hey, Donna.

860
00:34:59,350 --> 00:35:01,160
我現在不想說  行嗎
I don't wanna talk about it, okay?

861
00:35:01,330 --> 00:35:03,070
你會告訴哈維  他會暴跳如雷
You'll tell Harvey. He'll get furious--

862
00:35:03,070 --> 00:35:04,150
我不會告訴哈維的
I won't tell Harvey.

863
00:35:04,150 --> 00:35:05,520
好啊  又在發誓
Yeah, another promise.

864
00:35:05,520 --> 00:35:06,720
唐娜
Donna.

865
00:35:08,530 --> 00:35:11,190
他就是不能不聞不問呢
He just couldn't keep his nose out of it.

866
00:35:11,200 --> 00:35:13,000
誰不能不聞不問
Who couldn't keep his nose out of what?

867
00:35:13,790 --> 00:35:15,740
史蒂芬拿了馬里加的證詞
Stephen got Mariga's deposition.

868
00:35:18,420 --> 00:35:20,030
已經不重要了
You know what? It doesn't matter.

869
00:35:20,910 --> 00:35:22,430
我跟他分手了
I'm done with him anyway.

870
00:35:23,250 --> 00:35:24,350
我很遺憾
I'm so sorry.

871
00:35:34,780 --> 00:35:36,130
瑞秋  剛才太棒了

872
00:35:37,230 --> 00:35:38,360
我們要贏了
We're gonna win.

873
00:35:38,360 --> 00:35:39,900
你確實贏了
You did win.

874
00:35:41,880 --> 00:35:44,480
別擔心  我不會搶走你的貓的
Don't worry. I'm not going to take your cat.

875
00:35:44,770 --> 00:35:46,360
我是講信譽的人
I am a man of honor.

876
00:35:46,470 --> 00:35:47,710
你還真是高尚
Well, that's very gracious of you.

877
00:35:47,710 --> 00:35:49,310
其實我很高興我們進行了這次審判
In fact, I'm glad we had this trial

878
00:35:49,310 --> 00:35:51,170
因為你我都知道  從法律層面看
because you and I both know you didn't win

879
00:35:51,170 --> 00:35:52,330
你我都輸了
on the merits of the case.

880
00:35:52,330 --> 00:35:54,240
你贏是因為助理們更推崇你的嚴厲的愛
You won because the associates prefer

881
00:35:54,240 --> 00:35:57,760
而非我的低干涉管理模式
your tough love to my light touch.

882
00:35:58,490 --> 00:35:59,260
是啊  他們喜歡這樣
Yeah, they do.

883
00:35:59,260 --> 00:36:01,030
但米卡度還是屬于我
But Mikado belongs with me.

884
00:36:01,980 --> 00:36:03,550
這場庭審讓我知道  比起她
And this trial showed me there's something

885
00:36:03,550 --> 00:36:05,310
你更在乎別的事情
you care about more than her.

886
00:36:06,050 --> 00:36:08,110
-沒有  -有
- Nothing. - Yes.

887
00:36:08,520 --> 00:36:10,010
就是助理們
The associates.

888
00:36:12,170 --> 00:36:14,170
我現在提出一個協議
I'm offering you a settlement.

889
00:36:16,310 --> 00:36:17,270
不行
No.

890
00:36:17,520 --> 00:36:19,410
你重新掌管助理
You get back the associates.

891
00:36:20,640 --> 00:36:22,910
-但要把貓還給我  -不行
- I get back my cat. - No.

892
00:36:24,500 --> 00:36:26,880
我  我需要點時間跟我的客戶協商
I-I need a moment to confer with my client.

893
00:36:26,970 --> 00:36:27,960
沒問題
Of course.

894
00:36:32,490 --> 00:36:34,440
我真的很愛她  你知道嗎
I do love her, you know?

895
00:36:47,280 --> 00:36:50,060
路易  作為你的律師  我必須說
Louis, as your attorney, I need to say this...

896
00:36:50,850 --> 00:36:52,470
求你別逼我做選擇
Please don't make me choose.

897
00:36:53,900 --> 00:36:55,530
她是奈杰爾的貓
She's Nigel's cat.

898
00:36:58,530 --> 00:36:59,580
你說得對
You were right.

899
00:37:00,650 --> 00:37:01,820
沒人會相信
No one's ever going to believe

900
00:37:01,820 --> 00:37:04,540
艾娃不知道她的副手有何目的
that Ava didn't know what her number two was up to.

901
00:37:04,550 --> 00:37:05,740
值得一試
It was worth trying.

902
00:37:06,290 --> 00:37:08,840
因為她真的不知道  所以值得一試
It was worth trying because she really didn't know.

903
00:37:09,730 --> 00:37:11,620
沒人會相信的
And no one's ever going to believe it

904
00:37:11,760 --> 00:37:13,340
因為她應該知道的
because she should've known.

905
00:37:13,420 --> 00:37:16,690
杰西卡  艾娃和尼克之間與你我之間不一樣
Jessica, Ava and Nick are not the same as you and me.

906
00:37:16,770 --> 00:37:19,060
我知道  是不一樣
I know. They're not.

907
00:37:20,520 --> 00:37:23,180
她不想知道她眼皮底下發生的事情
She didn't wanna know what was happening under her nose.

908
00:37:23,190 --> 00:37:24,420
而我想
I do.

909
00:37:24,450 --> 00:37:26,510
這次我沒看出來的唯一原因是
And the only reason why I didn't see it this time

910
00:37:26,510 --> 00:37:28,360
我以為你不會那樣對我
is because I never thought you'd do that to me.

911
00:37:28,360 --> 00:37:30,280
-我沒那樣對你  -你都提動議了
- I didn't do it to you. - You put it in motion.

912
00:37:30,280 --> 00:37:32,600
然后我又放棄了  還跟你坦白了
And then I stopped it. And then I told you about it.

913
00:37:32,600 --> 00:37:34,270
我想知道的是原因
What I wanna know is why.

914
00:37:35,440 --> 00:37:37,890
你可以隨它去就好
You coulda just let it go,

915
00:37:38,230 --> 00:37:39,440
不用向我提起
never said a word.

916
00:37:40,280 --> 00:37:42,210
我告訴你是因為秘密適可而止
I told you because enough was enough

917
00:37:42,210 --> 00:37:44,640
我不希望我們之間又有什么秘密
and I didn't want anymore secrets between us.

918
00:37:44,640 --> 00:37:46,940
不  你先對人撒謊  之后又坦白
No, when you cheat on someone and tell them about it,

919
00:37:46,940 --> 00:37:48,800
不是為了讓他們好受些
it's not to make them feel better.

920
00:37:49,360 --> 00:37:51,280
而是為了讓你自己好受些
It's to make yourself feel better.

921
00:37:51,840 --> 00:37:53,370
是啊  除非你認為
Yeah, unless you think there's a chance

922
00:37:53,380 --> 00:37:54,590
對方有可能發現
that they're gonna find out.

923
00:37:54,590 --> 00:37:56,300
或者你認為告訴對方
Or you think telling them

924
00:37:56,300 --> 00:37:59,370
會讓對方放棄合并
is going to make them wanna get out of their merger.

925
00:37:59,370 --> 00:38:01,360
我想有關謊言的推理可以停了
I guess we've stopped with the cheating analogy.

926
00:38:01,360 --> 00:38:02,780
對  可以停了
Yes, we have.

927
00:38:03,650 --> 00:38:07,310
那么你全盤托出的到底是為了修復我們的關系
Now, did you come clean to heal our relationship

928
00:38:07,310 --> 00:38:09,470
還是為了逼我放棄合并
or to make me want out of the merger?

929
00:38:10,390 --> 00:38:11,980
就像我剛跟你說的
Like I just told you,

930
00:38:12,940 --> 00:38:15,660
我那樣做是因為我不想再隱藏什么秘密了
I did it because I didn't want to keep anymore secrets.

931
00:38:15,660 --> 00:38:17,310
但我從沒隱藏
But I have never kept it a secret

932
00:38:17,310 --> 00:38:19,020
我不想合并的想法
that I want out of this merger.

933
00:38:19,020 --> 00:38:20,520
你沒有回答問題
You didn't answer the question.

934
00:38:20,520 --> 00:38:22,790
好  如果你是想問我  我是否知道
Okay, if you're asking if I knew

935
00:38:22,790 --> 00:38:26,700
向你坦白有關達比的事情會讓你生他的氣
that coming clean about Darby would make you furious with him,

936
00:38:27,400 --> 00:38:28,930
我如果說從沒想過
I'd be lying if I didn't say

937
00:38:28,930 --> 00:38:30,150
那是撒謊
it crossed my mind.

938
00:38:30,150 --> 00:38:31,160
所以你就陷害我
So you set me up.

939
00:38:31,160 --> 00:38:33,290
不  我做的只是你長期以來
No, all I did is what you've taught me to do

940
00:38:33,290 --> 00:38:34,630
教我做的而已
for a long time.

941
00:38:34,630 --> 00:38:36,290
而且那并沒有改變你的想法
And it didn't change your mind.

942
00:38:36,290 --> 00:38:38,600
只是讓你了解到你已經感覺到的事情
It just put you in touch with what you already felt.

943
00:38:43,570 --> 00:38:45,630
你真的能去當執行合伙人
You really could be managing partner.

944
00:38:45,630 --> 00:38:46,990
但我不是
But I'm not.

945
00:38:47,520 --> 00:38:49,080
我也不想當
And I don't wanna be.

946
00:38:51,050 --> 00:38:52,090
所以
So...

947
00:38:55,580 --> 00:38:57,480
這次庭審我們要怎么做
What are we gonna do about this trial?

948
00:39:00,850 --> 00:39:03,350
盡管米卡度對你意義重大
As much as Mikado means to you,

949
00:39:03,350 --> 00:39:05,550
我知道助理們對你更重要
I know the associates mean more.

950
00:39:05,550 --> 00:39:06,820
不  沒有更重要
No, not more.

951
00:39:07,980 --> 00:39:12,780
多數的需要比個人的需要更重要
The needs of the many outweigh the needs of one.

952
00:39:12,780 --> 00:39:13,990
這是什么哲學家說的
What philosopher said that?

953
00:39:13,990 --> 00:39:16,200
史波克  《可汗怒吼》里頭說的[星際迷航主角及系列電影]
Spock. The wrath of Khan?

954
00:39:17,270 --> 00:39:19,980
我會幫你把貓還給奈杰爾
I will take her back to Nigel for you.

955
00:39:20,030 --> 00:39:21,980
謝謝你為我做的這一切  瑞秋
Well, thanks for doing this for me, Rachel.

956
00:39:23,390 --> 00:39:26,970
但我想先為你做點事情
But I want to do something for you first,

957
00:39:27,160 --> 00:39:30,290
算是你初戰告捷的獎勵
a reward of sorts for your victory.

958
00:39:31,660 --> 00:39:33,270
瞧  我選你作為我的律師是明智的選擇
See, I was right to pick you to be my lawyer.

959
00:39:33,280 --> 00:39:36,000
現在結果就是
And as it turns out,

960
00:39:37,730 --> 00:39:39,580
哥倫比亞大學法學院同意了
Columbia law school agrees.

961
00:39:42,190 --> 00:39:42,800
路易  什么
Louis, what--

962
00:39:42,800 --> 00:39:44,170
我今天在郵車上看到的
I saw it on mail cart this morning.

963
00:39:44,170 --> 00:39:45,830
我想先幫你保管
I wanted to save it for you.

964
00:39:48,620 --> 00:39:50,870
恭喜你  瑞秋  你要成為一名律師了
Congratulations, Rachel. You're gonna be a lawyer.

965
00:39:53,910 --> 00:39:55,380
一名真正的律師
A real lawyer.

966
00:40:01,360 --> 00:40:02,500
唐娜  哈維在哪兒
Donna, where's Harvey?

967
00:40:02,510 --> 00:40:03,560
他跟杰西卡在一起
He's with Jessica.

968
00:40:03,560 --> 00:40:04,750
在哪兒  他們沒在她的辦公室里
Where? They're not in her office.

969
00:40:04,750 --> 00:40:05,800
-在天臺上呢  -好的
- They're on the roof. - okay.

970
00:40:05,800 --> 00:40:06,920
馬上把他們叫下來
Get them down here right now.

971
00:40:06,920 --> 00:40:08,170
-邁克  出什么事了  -立刻馬上
- Mike, what's wrong? - I said now.

972
00:40:08,180 --> 00:40:09,410
邁克
Mike.

973
00:40:09,870 --> 00:40:10,720
出什么事了
What's wrong?

974
00:40:10,730 --> 00:40:11,960
我知道史蒂芬找
I know why Stephen needed to know

975
00:40:11,960 --> 00:40:13,780
馬里加證詞的原因了
what Mariga said in his deposition.

976
00:40:13,980 --> 00:40:14,910
為什么
Why?

977
00:40:15,310 --> 00:40:17,460
他擔心馬里加會說出實話
He was afraid that Mariga would tell the truth.

978
00:40:19,470 --> 00:40:21,730
史蒂芬才是下令殺人的幕后黑手
Stephen was the one who ordered those killings.

979
00:40:31,430 --> 00:40:33,270
這是伊曼紐爾·馬里加20年前
Emmanuel Mariga 20 years ago

980
00:40:33,270 --> 00:40:35,690
在開普敦大學攻讀經濟學時的照片
at the University of Cape Town as an econ major.

981
00:40:35,690 --> 00:40:37,060
他很有生意頭腦
Always had a head for business.

982
00:40:37,060 --> 00:40:39,290
他還是英式橄欖球隊隊員
He was also on the rugby team.

983
00:40:39,810 --> 00:40:41,100
你知道還有誰也打英式橄欖球嗎
You know who else played rugby?

984
00:40:41,100 --> 00:40:41,920
史蒂芬·亨特利
Stephen Huntley.

985
00:40:41,920 --> 00:40:43,750
史蒂芬在劍橋的記錄顯示
Stephen's record from Cambridge included

986
00:40:43,750 --> 00:40:46,940
他從到開普敦大學交流一個學期
a semester abroad at the University of Cape Town.

987
00:40:47,300 --> 00:40:49,020
這是那年的球隊
That year's team.

988
00:40:50,930 --> 00:40:52,410
他們那個賽季打得很糟糕
They had a hell of a season.

989
00:40:52,760 --> 00:40:53,910
他們現在還是搭檔
They're still a team.

990
00:40:54,140 --> 00:40:55,340
達比知道這情況
Darby was clear.

991
00:40:55,340 --> 00:40:56,360
他一碰到問題
Whenever he has a problem,

992
00:40:56,360 --> 00:40:58,220
就派史蒂芬去解決
Stephen's the one he sends in to fix it.

993
00:40:58,220 --> 00:40:59,670
而艾娃的問題就是他的問題
And Ava's problem was his problem.

994
00:40:59,670 --> 00:41:01,600
所以當艾娃去找他鋪設她的輸油管道時
So when she came to him to get her pipeline built--

995
00:41:01,600 --> 00:41:02,460
他又去找史蒂芬
he went to Stephen.

996
00:41:02,460 --> 00:41:04,760
你知道這些謀殺都是如何開始的嗎
And you wanna know what it took to set up those murders?

997
00:41:04,930 --> 00:41:06,370
從達比國際
One phone call to Mariga,

998
00:41:06,370 --> 00:41:08,570
史蒂芬·亨特利的倫敦辦公室
from the offices of Darby international,

999
00:41:08,570 --> 00:41:10,910
打一通電話給馬里加
from Stephen Huntley's London office.

1000
00:41:10,910 --> 00:41:13,160
馬里加又從那里打電話給尼克  尼克打給艾娃
From there, Mariga calls Nick, Nick calls Ava,

1001
00:41:13,170 --> 00:41:14,490
這一切就算起步了
and the whole thing is set in motion.

1002
00:41:14,490 --> 00:41:15,970
他們以為他們只是花球去賄賂
They thought they were paying for a bribe.

1003
00:41:15,970 --> 00:41:17,390
但其實是在雇兇殺人
But they were actually paying for murder.

1004
00:41:17,390 --> 00:41:18,600
而且他們完全不知道其中的聯系
And they never knew the connection.

1005
00:41:18,600 --> 00:41:20,340
而當艾娃被起訴謀殺時
And when Ava's about to be charged for murder,

1006
00:41:20,340 --> 00:41:23,240
史蒂芬又出場了  以確保我們不會發現
Stephen shows up to make sure we'd never find out.

1007
00:41:23,990 --> 00:41:25,510
我很抱歉  哈維
I'm so sorry, Harvey.

1008
00:41:34,870 --> 00:41:35,980
哈維

1009
00:41:35,980 --> 00:41:37,340
哈維  你要干什么
Harvey, what are you gonna do?

