1
00:00:01,010 --> 00:00:02,140
《诉讼双雄》前情提要

2
00:00:02,140 --> 00:00:05,380
录取比例低于十二分之一
Less than 1 out of every 12 people who applies gets in.

3
00:00:05,380 --> 00:00:06,710
如果我不是那一个呢
What if I'm not one of those people?

4
00:00:06,720 --> 00:00:09,140
不知道  或许你可以去别的学校
I don't know. Maybe you'll get in somewhere else.

5
00:00:09,390 --> 00:00:10,670
我不是只想读法学院
I don't want to go to law school.

6
00:00:10,670 --> 00:00:12,080
我想读哈佛
I want to go to Harvard.

7
00:00:12,080 --> 00:00:13,740
我对你有百分之百的信心
I got 100% faith in you.

8
00:00:16,080 --> 00:00:17,480
我没被录取
I didn't get in.

9
00:00:18,100 --> 00:00:19,320
我答应过她
I promised her.

10
00:00:19,380 --> 00:00:21,470
路易  我喜欢这姑娘
Louis, I liked her.

11
00:00:21,500 --> 00:00:23,480
你只能据实相告了
You're just going to have to tell her the truth.

12
00:00:24,030 --> 00:00:25,420
我的名字要挂在门口
I want my name on the door.

13
00:00:27,600 --> 00:00:29,880
如果你送上一场大胜仗
So if you deliver a huge win...

14
00:00:30,230 --> 00:00:31,820
我就能将名字印在门上
I get my name on the door.

15
00:00:32,060 --> 00:00:34,060
你是说与她联盟吗
Are you talking about joining forces with her?

16
00:00:34,060 --> 00:00:36,660
不是只和她  是和她的事务所
Not just with her, with her firm--

17
00:00:36,890 --> 00:00:39,750
她背后资源近乎无穷的事务所
Her infinitely deep-pocketed firm.

18
00:00:39,750 --> 00:00:40,730
爱德华和我要合并了
Edward and I are merging.

19
00:00:40,730 --> 00:00:41,710
我得让他看看公司账目
I had to show him the books.

20
00:00:41,710 --> 00:00:42,810
你不只是想把名字印在公司大门上而已
You don't want your name on the door.

21
00:00:42,810 --> 00:00:44,320
而是想印在我的公司大门
You want your name on my door.

22
00:00:44,320 --> 00:00:47,070
我希望我们的名字印在同一扇门上
I want to see our names on the same door.

23
00:00:47,070 --> 00:00:49,120
这次合并也不可能成功
And this merger isn't happening.

24
00:00:53,990 --> 00:00:54,940
-我不会那么做的  -你会的
- I won't. - You will.

25
00:00:54,940 --> 00:00:56,300
哈维不会原谅我的
Harvey will never forgive me.

26
00:00:56,300 --> 00:00:58,520
现在你的问题不是哈维
Right now your problem isn't with Harvey.

27
00:00:58,990 --> 00:01:00,300
而是我
Your problem is with me.

28
00:01:04,080 --> 00:01:07,650
六天前

29
00:01:17,270 --> 00:01:18,550
要香槟吗
Champagne?

30
00:01:19,250 --> 00:01:20,940
-看情况  -比如
- Depends. - On what?

31
00:01:20,940 --> 00:01:22,700
看里面有没有下药
On whether or not there's a roofie in there.

32
00:01:23,130 --> 00:01:24,480
我不需要给你下药
I wouldn't need a roofie.

33
00:01:24,480 --> 00:01:26,950
杰西卡  能私下说两句吗
Jessica, uh, might I have a private word?

34
00:01:27,000 --> 00:01:28,420
实际上  哈维和我正在
Actually, Harvey and I were--

35
00:01:28,420 --> 00:01:29,590
别介意
Don't mind me.

36
00:01:29,980 --> 00:01:31,430
我的女伴刚来
My date just got here.

37
00:01:31,860 --> 00:01:33,260
-爱德华  -哈维
- Edward. - Harvey.

38
00:01:33,290 --> 00:01:34,360
聚会真不错
Hell of a party.

39
00:01:47,560 --> 00:01:48,680
你看上去
You look...

40
00:01:48,680 --> 00:01:50,190
真漂亮  我知道
Beautiful. I know.

41
00:01:50,300 --> 00:01:51,990
实际上  我想说的是“端庄”
Actually, I was going to say "Sophisticated."

42
00:01:51,990 --> 00:01:54,290
-不可能  -我现在就能说
- No, you weren't. - I can now.

43
00:01:58,570 --> 00:02:01,040
-你看上去不太一样  -我感觉也不太一样
- You seem different. - I feel different.

44
00:02:01,830 --> 00:02:02,910
有什么事
What's going on?

45
00:02:04,110 --> 00:02:05,940
帮我拿一杯酒吧
You know, why don't you get me a drink?

46
00:02:06,210 --> 00:02:07,100
这可是个聚会啊
It's a party.

47
00:02:07,100 --> 00:02:08,040
好
Okay.

48
00:02:09,700 --> 00:02:10,750
哈维
Harvey.

49
00:02:11,490 --> 00:02:12,480
瑞秋
Rachel.

50
00:02:13,000 --> 00:02:14,010
你看上去真棒
You look nice.

51
00:02:14,060 --> 00:02:16,200
谢谢  我也这么觉得
Thank you. So do I.

52
00:02:16,270 --> 00:02:18,310
我终于知道你为什么总那么说了
Now I see what you're always talking about.

53
00:02:20,590 --> 00:02:21,750
那是什么意思
What was that supposed to mean?

54
00:02:21,750 --> 00:02:23,870
你觉得是什么意思  他是说你是个笨蛋
What do you think it means? It means you're a dick.

55
00:02:23,870 --> 00:02:25,020
说得对
Fair point.

56
00:02:25,020 --> 00:02:27,470
-带来了吗  -就在这里
- You bring it? - Right here.

57
00:02:29,330 --> 00:02:31,030
你确定想这么对她吗
You sure you want to do this to her?

58
00:02:31,720 --> 00:02:33,280
你应该是站在我这一边的
You're supposed to be on my side.

59
00:02:33,280 --> 00:02:34,990
我在啊  我支持你
I am. I've got your back.

60
00:02:35,080 --> 00:02:36,750
那你怎么还为难我
Then why are you giving me such a hard time about it?

61
00:02:36,760 --> 00:02:38,450
我不仅不会为难你
Not only am I not giving you a hard time,

62
00:02:38,450 --> 00:02:40,350
我还要给你这个
but I am giving you this...

63
00:02:41,230 --> 00:02:44,220
还有这个  和这个
And this and this.

64
00:02:44,820 --> 00:02:48,690
好了  如果不介意的话
Now, if you'll excuse me.

65
00:02:54,550 --> 00:02:56,640
-你好  能否  -打扰一下
- Hi, may I-- - Excuse me, good sir.

66
00:02:56,650 --> 00:02:58,200
能否给我一杯…
Would you be so kind as to prepare me...

67
00:02:58,200 --> 00:03:00,790
-弗拉潘窖藏  -别急  查尔斯王子
- A frapin cuvee? - Easy, Prince Charles.

68
00:03:01,010 --> 00:03:02,940
在我的家乡  是要排队的
Where I'm from, you wait your turn in line.

69
00:03:03,230 --> 00:03:04,250
非常抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry,

70
00:03:04,250 --> 00:03:05,750
我以为你已经拿到酒了
but I thought you'd been served.

71
00:03:06,020 --> 00:03:08,270
酒保如此耐心的等你
The barman is patiently waiting on you,

72
00:03:08,270 --> 00:03:11,500
就别像个猩猩那样傻站着了
so I'd stop standing there like some sort of baboon.

73
00:03:11,500 --> 00:03:14,200
点你的米勒淡啤吧
And order your Miller Lite.

74
00:03:14,800 --> 00:03:16,270
25年麦卡伦  不掺水
Macallan 25, neat.

75
00:03:16,300 --> 00:03:18,460
请为这位先生在酒里加一个香蕉
Why don't you put a banana in it for my man here?

76
00:03:18,460 --> 00:03:20,630
那样喝的话  也会像是在动物园里
With a drink like that, you might as well be in a zoo,

77
00:03:20,630 --> 00:03:21,920
在烂泥里打滚
playing about in the mud.

78
00:03:21,920 --> 00:03:23,140
你对烂泥可是一点都不懂
Oh, you wouldn't know anything about mud.

79
00:03:23,140 --> 00:03:24,750
那不是在玩  那是在清洁
It's not for playing. It's for cleansing.

80
00:03:25,950 --> 00:03:27,050
你也在烂泥里打滚吗
You mud?

81
00:03:28,800 --> 00:03:30,170
我走过的泥地
I've taken mud in more places

82
00:03:30,170 --> 00:03:32,140
多到你这个小脑袋数不过来
than your snooty little mind can fathom.

83
00:03:32,730 --> 00:03:34,310
-加来  -塞多纳
- Calais. - Sedona.

84
00:03:32,730 --> 00:03:34,830
两人提到的这些地方都有泥浴

85
00:03:34,310 --> 00:03:35,770
-怀特岛  -约书亚之树
- Isle of wight. - Joshua tree.

86
00:03:35,770 --> 00:03:37,310
-达利安  -巴登-巴登
- Dalyan. - Baden-baden.

87
00:03:38,470 --> 00:03:41,170
那不是泥地  那是湿泥地
That isn't mud. It's wet dirt.

88
00:03:41,820 --> 00:03:43,140
我不知道你以为你自己是什么人
You know, I don't know who you think you are--

89
00:03:43,140 --> 00:03:45,910
我的名字是奈杰尔·亚历山大·奈斯比特
My moniker is Nigel Alexander Nesbitt.

90
00:03:46,150 --> 00:03:48,540
好吧  奈杰尔  你敢质疑
Well, Nigel, when you impugn

91
00:03:48,540 --> 00:03:50,680
巴登巴登泥地的权威性
the life-affirming muds of Baden-Baden,

92
00:03:50,680 --> 00:03:52,530
就等同于
You're on the precipice of the equivalent

93
00:03:52,530 --> 00:03:56,750
看不起亲爱的英格兰烂泥地
of someone taking a shit on the royal muds of England.

94
00:04:00,500 --> 00:04:01,530
哈维
Ah, Harvey.

95
00:04:01,530 --> 00:04:03,490
我还在想和你单独聊聊
I was hoping we might have a moment alone.

96
00:04:03,520 --> 00:04:04,540
我也是
So was I.

97
00:04:04,560 --> 00:04:06,030
我有东西要呈给您呢
I wanted to run something by you.

98
00:04:07,290 --> 00:04:10,730
-是个案件  -是三件
- This is a lawsuit. - Three lawsuits.

99
00:04:10,890 --> 00:04:12,790
我又有什么麻烦了啊
What have I gotten up to now?

100
00:04:13,040 --> 00:04:15,210
不是你  是你的客户
Not you, your clients.

101
00:04:15,300 --> 00:04:17,900
似乎他们很喜欢固定价格
Looks like one of their hobbies is fixing prices.

102
00:04:17,950 --> 00:04:19,470
我想这意味着
I take it this means

103
00:04:19,470 --> 00:04:21,340
你知道合并的事了
you've discovered we're in merger talks?

104
00:04:21,340 --> 00:04:22,240
知道了又怎么样
And what are you going to do about it?

105
00:04:22,240 --> 00:04:24,740
-你想我怎么办  -我想你滚蛋
- What would you have me do? - I'd have you kiss my ass.

106
00:04:24,830 --> 00:04:26,050
挺诱人的
Tempting.

107
00:04:26,430 --> 00:04:29,860
可惜  我还是要让你彻底后悔
However, what I can do is proceed to make you permanently regret

108
00:04:29,860 --> 00:04:32,230
刚刚这些充满敌意的举动
the hostile action you've just set in motion.

109
00:04:32,280 --> 00:04:34,960
怎么  你要杀了我不成
What, are you going to kill me?

110
00:04:34,960 --> 00:04:36,040
太低俗
Nonsense.

111
00:04:36,270 --> 00:04:38,610
我只会再使出我的杀手锏
I'll simply do what I've done to so many before.

112
00:04:38,610 --> 00:04:40,490
在法庭里击败你
I'll defeat you in open court.

113
00:04:40,520 --> 00:04:43,380
我从来都不用上法庭
The way I work, it's never going to get to open court.

114
00:04:44,160 --> 00:04:46,140
你将会坐上回伦敦的飞机
You'll be on your steamer back to London,

115
00:04:46,140 --> 00:04:48,190
好奇究竟问题在何处  而后发现
wondering what happened, and you'll know

116
00:04:48,190 --> 00:04:49,900
你惹了不该惹的人
that you picked a fight with the wrong guy.

117
00:04:50,450 --> 00:04:52,700
你难道是想赌一场吗
Are you suggesting a wager?

118
00:04:52,700 --> 00:04:55,780
你输了  合并免谈
You lose, we don't merge.

119
00:04:56,250 --> 00:04:58,710
我知道你的赌注了  你赢我就走人
I've heard your terms. You win, I go.

120
00:04:58,770 --> 00:04:59,660
听听我的
Care to hear mine?

121
00:04:59,670 --> 00:05:00,950
不必了
Don't need to

122
00:05:00,980 --> 00:05:02,400
因为你肯定赢不了
'cause you're never going to win.

123
00:05:04,240 --> 00:05:07,030
看起来你们相处得不错
Well, it looks like you two are getting along.

124
00:05:11,250 --> 00:05:12,220
哈维
Harvey...

125
00:05:13,920 --> 00:05:16,020
想想他们能带来什么
Look at what they can give us.

126
00:05:16,080 --> 00:05:17,510
你怎么知道能带来什么
How do you know what they can give us?

127
00:05:17,510 --> 00:05:18,800
因为他给我看了账簿
Because he showed me their books.

128
00:05:18,800 --> 00:05:21,410
-他为何会给  -因为我先给他看了我们的
- Why did he do that? - Because I showed him ours.

129
00:05:21,410 --> 00:05:22,540
你怎么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?

130
00:05:22,990 --> 00:05:24,550
我们需要支援
- We needed their help.

131
00:05:24,550 --> 00:05:27,220
你不能因为对方强势  就与之结合
You don't marry someone just because they knock you up.

132
00:05:27,650 --> 00:05:29,840
好了  哈维
All right, Harvey, here it is.

133
00:05:30,090 --> 00:05:31,130
你输了
You lose,

134
00:05:31,190 --> 00:05:34,120
就要无保留地支持这次合并
you embrace this partnership with no reservations.

135
00:05:34,250 --> 00:05:35,340
他能打败我
He can beat me,

136
00:05:35,340 --> 00:05:38,810
我就敞开怀抱欢迎他
I'll welcome him with arms wide open.

137
00:05:38,840 --> 00:05:41,220
若不能  就把他赶回英格兰
He can't, we send him back to England,

138
00:05:41,460 --> 00:05:43,150
让他自己吞下苦果
And he can spend his time fixing his teeth.

139
00:05:43,160 --> 00:05:44,330
行
Fine.

140
00:05:44,650 --> 00:05:47,050
你击败爱德华  这事就作废
You beat Edward, we don't do this.

141
00:05:47,740 --> 00:05:49,770
既然你不想听他的条件
And since you didn't want to hear Darby's terms,

142
00:05:49,800 --> 00:05:51,040
听听我的吧
these are mine.

143
00:05:51,290 --> 00:05:53,040
你赢了  随你怎么闹
You win, you get what you want.

144
00:05:53,290 --> 00:05:55,160
输了  就老实留下
You lose, you stay,

145
00:05:55,160 --> 00:05:56,690
延长你的不竞争条款
You extend your noncompete,

146
00:05:56,690 --> 00:05:59,980
也给自己赢得一个机会  来挣得冠名合伙人
and you get a chance to earn your name on the door

147
00:06:01,150 --> 00:06:03,040
因为这事眼下不会发生了
because it's not going up there now.

148
00:06:07,060 --> 00:06:10,060
人人影视
YYeTs.com

149
00:06:07,060 --> 00:06:10,060
原创翻译  双语字幕

150
00:06:07,060 --> 00:06:10,060
■

151
00:06:07,060 --> 00:06:10,060
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

152
00:06:10,060 --> 00:06:15,060
 翻译：一不二  风扇  月月  小饭 妄想的绒布熊  陈小圈  allenlovestar

153
00:06:10,060 --> 00:06:15,060
■

154
00:06:15,060 --> 00:06:20,060
时间轴：迟迟  凭陵新月    校对：油炸电风扇  月月

155
00:06:15,060 --> 00:06:20,060
■

156
00:06:20,060 --> 00:06:25,060
后期 & 特效：仓鼠sama     总监：月月

157
00:06:20,060 --> 00:06:25,060
■

158
00:06:31,720 --> 00:06:33,890
第二季 第十六集

159
00:06:31,720 --> 00:06:33,890
诉 讼 双 雄

160
00:06:31,720 --> 00:06:33,890
蓝光-1080P-SHORTBREHD版调轴风格微修：字幕雷哥

161
00:06:49,360 --> 00:06:50,430
上车
Get in the car.

162
00:06:50,430 --> 00:06:51,740
我喜欢走路
I prefer to walk.

163
00:06:52,320 --> 00:06:53,360
哪有这回事
Since when?

164
00:06:53,380 --> 00:06:54,660
医生建议的
Doctor recommended it.

165
00:06:54,700 --> 00:06:57,420
被人背后捅了一刀  这有助于康复
Helps me work out the kinks since I got stabbed in the back.

166
00:06:57,420 --> 00:06:58,560
捅你
You?

167
00:06:59,320 --> 00:07:01,510
昨晚是你对我人身攻击吧
Last night was a personal attack on me.

168
00:07:01,640 --> 00:07:03,550
有趣了  杰西卡也觉得
Oh, that's funny because Jessica seemed to think

169
00:07:03,550 --> 00:07:05,190
是对她人身攻击
it was a personal attack on her,

170
00:07:05,380 --> 00:07:07,540
你们都知道合并的事
Yet both of you knew about the merger

171
00:07:07,540 --> 00:07:08,970
还都瞒着我
and chose not to tell me.

172
00:07:08,970 --> 00:07:10,740
你们真该一起吃顿饭  很有共同语言啊
You should get lunch--seems like you have a lot in common.

173
00:07:10,750 --> 00:07:11,740
哈维  哈维
Harvey. Harvey.

174
00:07:11,740 --> 00:07:14,160
你能不能别这么冲
Can you stop being so defensive for one second?

175
00:07:14,160 --> 00:07:15,500
是你逼我的
You put me on the defensive.

176
00:07:15,500 --> 00:07:17,600
我不会傻站在这  光听你说
And I'm not just going to stand here and listen to you

177
00:07:17,600 --> 00:07:18,950
因为我要反击
because I went on the attack.

178
00:07:19,450 --> 00:07:20,110
哈维
Harvey--

179
00:07:20,110 --> 00:07:21,760
别  别这么叫我  行吗
No, don't "Harvey" me, okay?

180
00:07:21,930 --> 00:07:22,980
你种的因
You made your bed,

181
00:07:22,980 --> 00:07:24,720
现在得自己吞苦果了
and now you're going to sleep in it alone.

182
00:07:25,890 --> 00:07:28,110
我到底做了什么
What did I do that was so terrible?

183
00:07:28,330 --> 00:07:30,890
这九个月  我击退了丹尼尔·哈德曼
For the past nine months, I have been fending off attacks

184
00:07:30,890 --> 00:07:34,380
艾莉森·霍特和罗伯特·赞恩
from Daniel Hardman, Allison Holt, and Robert Zane.

185
00:07:34,400 --> 00:07:35,630
我告诉过你
I told you before.

186
00:07:35,690 --> 00:07:37,140
你想让门上写的是你的名字
You want to get your name on the door,

187
00:07:37,150 --> 00:07:39,300
自己开家事务所
get it at your own goddamn firm.

188
00:07:40,380 --> 00:07:41,850
好
Okay. Fine.

189
00:07:41,880 --> 00:07:43,110
如果这是公事
If it's not personal,

190
00:07:43,140 --> 00:07:44,150
当我们打败你的时候
you're not going to hold it against me

191
00:07:44,150 --> 00:07:45,170
你可不能怀恨在心
when we beat you.

192
00:07:45,170 --> 00:07:47,050
零对无数  斯科特
0 and everything, Scottie.

193
00:07:47,060 --> 00:07:48,390
这是你和我交手的记录
That's your record against me--

194
00:07:48,390 --> 00:07:50,170
我是常胜
0 and everything.

195
00:07:54,930 --> 00:07:56,540
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey. - Hey.

196
00:07:56,830 --> 00:07:58,700
我昨晚还没请你喝酒呢
I never got to buy you that drink last night.

197
00:07:58,720 --> 00:08:00,320
-酒是免费的  -我知道
- They were free. - I know.

198
00:08:02,280 --> 00:08:03,160
你先走了
You left.

199
00:08:03,170 --> 00:08:04,680
-是的  -派对很棒
- I did. - It was a nice party.

200
00:08:04,680 --> 00:08:06,250
是
It was.

201
00:08:07,100 --> 00:08:09,000
你还是没告诉我为什么
Okay, so I see you're still not going to tell me why--

202
00:08:09,000 --> 00:08:10,720
哈佛没有录取我
I didn't get into Harvard.

203
00:08:14,090 --> 00:08:15,560
别这么看着我
Don't look at me that way.

204
00:08:16,050 --> 00:08:16,710
同情地
With sympathy?

205
00:08:16,710 --> 00:08:18,630
-可怜地  -我没有  瑞秋
- With pity. - I wasn't. Rachel...

206
00:08:20,350 --> 00:08:21,720
听着  还有其他学校
Listen to me. There are other schools.

207
00:08:21,720 --> 00:08:22,720
别
Don't.

208
00:08:24,520 --> 00:08:26,020
我不说
Yeah. I won't.

209
00:08:29,290 --> 00:08:31,390
不是因为我不够好
It wasn't that I wasn't good enough.

210
00:08:32,220 --> 00:08:33,360
我知道
I know that.

211
00:08:33,610 --> 00:08:35,660
-是因为路易  -什么
- It was Louis. - What?

212
00:08:35,660 --> 00:08:36,760
面试官
The interviewer--

213
00:08:37,060 --> 00:08:40,840
很显然和路易有过一段
um, apparently she and Louis had a history, and--

214
00:08:40,850 --> 00:08:42,620
等一下  她因为他就没录你
Wait. She didn't let you in because of him?

215
00:08:42,890 --> 00:08:43,710
-这真  -我知道
- That's... - I know.

216
00:08:43,710 --> 00:08:45,480
-不公平的  -我知道
- Not right. - I know.

217
00:08:49,070 --> 00:08:50,810
告诉我你收到录取通知书的心情吧
Tell me about the day you found out.

218
00:08:53,330 --> 00:08:55,070
-瑞秋  别这样  -不
- Rachel, come on. - No.

219
00:08:55,480 --> 00:08:58,980
我想听听被录取的人的感觉
I need to hear how it felt from someone who got in

220
00:08:58,980 --> 00:09:03,020
因为我永远也感觉不到
because I'll--I'll never hear that for myself.

221
00:09:08,080 --> 00:09:10,160
你又那样看我了
You're looking at me like that again.

222
00:09:10,160 --> 00:09:11,260
我没有
I'm not.

223
00:09:11,260 --> 00:09:11,980
那怎么了
Then what?

224
00:09:11,980 --> 00:09:14,760
这太不公平了
It's just not right.

225
00:09:25,280 --> 00:09:27,110
见到你是我的荣幸
It was a pleasure meeting you.

226
00:09:32,620 --> 00:09:33,860
刚才是怎么回事
What the hell was that?

227
00:09:34,540 --> 00:09:35,500
什么怎么回事
What was what?

228
00:09:35,500 --> 00:09:36,630
你和唐娜在做什么
What were you doing with Donna?

229
00:09:37,040 --> 00:09:38,610
我在用我的柔唇
I was caressing her lovely hand

230
00:09:38,610 --> 00:09:39,930
亲吻她的柔荑
with my lovely lips.

231
00:09:39,930 --> 00:09:41,240
你知道我的意思
You know what I mean.

232
00:09:41,460 --> 00:09:43,800
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?

233
00:09:43,800 --> 00:09:46,140
那个啊  你的哨兵带我转了一下
Oh, that. I was being treated to a tour of your little outpost.

234
00:09:46,400 --> 00:09:47,040
我同意
I'll grant you this,

235
00:09:47,040 --> 00:09:48,980
你办公室的视野很不错
you've got quite the spectacular view...

236
00:09:49,670 --> 00:09:51,590
不过我要说实话
Though truth be told,

237
00:09:51,590 --> 00:09:54,070
我还是喜欢保尔森女士隔间的视野
my favorite spot was inside Ms. Paulsen's cubicle.

238
00:09:59,390 --> 00:10:00,270
你怎么能这样
How could you?

239
00:10:00,270 --> 00:10:01,980
-我怎么了  -别狡辩了
- How could I what? - Don't.

240
00:10:02,450 --> 00:10:04,270
你让那个人进了你的隔间
You let that man inside your cubicle.

241
00:10:04,280 --> 00:10:05,960
进了我的什么
Inside my what?

242
00:10:05,970 --> 00:10:07,790
奈杰尔·奈斯比特  你让他
Nigel Nesbitt-- I mean, you let him...

243
00:10:09,900 --> 00:10:11,900
我从来没进过你的隔间
I have never crossed the boundary of your cubicle.

244
00:10:11,900 --> 00:10:13,690
那种荣幸不应该赐予给我吗
And should that honor ever be bestowed on me,

245
00:10:13,720 --> 00:10:15,870
起码我不会说出去的
at least I'd be gentleman enough to keep it between us.

246
00:10:15,920 --> 00:10:17,020
我是说  我那么尊敬你
I mean, I have too much respect for you.

247
00:10:17,020 --> 00:10:19,710
路易  他不过是靠过来拿文件
Louis, he leaned over to get a file.

248
00:10:20,100 --> 00:10:21,440
他在做效率清单
He's doing an efficiency list.

249
00:10:23,160 --> 00:10:24,210
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.

250
00:10:24,830 --> 00:10:27,270
等一下  他们是叫我做效率清单啊
Wait a second. I've been asked to do an efficiency list.

251
00:10:27,270 --> 00:10:29,430
-那就做呗  -你没听懂
- So do one. - No, you don't get it.

252
00:10:29,430 --> 00:10:31,370
让两个人都做效率清单是效率低下的
It's inefficient to have two people doing efficiency lists.

253
00:10:32,410 --> 00:10:33,440
这是个测验
It's a test.

254
00:10:33,520 --> 00:10:35,260
-看看谁更强  -他们竟然这样
- To see who's better. - How dare they?

255
00:10:35,260 --> 00:10:37,620
老天  知道吗  本来那个混蛋
Man, you know, it's bad enough

256
00:10:37,620 --> 00:10:38,790
认为他在我之上
that smug bastard thinks

257
00:10:38,790 --> 00:10:39,970
就够糟糕的了
he's higher up on the mud chain than me.

258
00:10:40,190 --> 00:10:41,070
是吗
Is he?

259
00:10:41,980 --> 00:10:43,170
又这样吗
Again?

260
00:10:43,810 --> 00:10:45,370
你没告诉他卡塔赫纳的事吗
Didn't you tell him about Cartagena?

261
00:10:45,370 --> 00:10:47,220
在巴登巴登之后我就情绪失控了
I was on tilt after he nullified Baden-Baden.

262
00:10:47,220 --> 00:10:48,460
你脑子进水了啊
What the hell is wrong with you?

263
00:10:48,460 --> 00:10:49,660
我“斗泥”都斗不过他
I let him out-mud me.

264
00:10:53,260 --> 00:10:54,070
我该怎么做
What am I going to do?

265
00:10:54,070 --> 00:10:55,810
我告诉你该怎么做
Okay, I'm going to tell you exactly what you're going to do.

266
00:10:55,810 --> 00:10:57,040
你给我振作起来
You're going to pull your shit together,

267
00:10:57,040 --> 00:10:58,600
把那个英国佬打得落花流水
and you're going to kick his limey ass.

268
00:10:59,340 --> 00:11:00,930
说的太他妈对了
You're goddamn right.

269
00:11:07,200 --> 00:11:08,580
有事需要帮忙吗
Uh, can I help you?

270
00:11:08,900 --> 00:11:10,280
不用  不用我很好
No, no. I'm fine.

271
00:11:10,660 --> 00:11:14,570
刚喝过摩卡  我在等哈维
Just had a mochaccino. Waiting to see Harvey.

272
00:11:15,000 --> 00:11:16,070
他就这么让你等着吗
He's making you wait?

273
00:11:16,070 --> 00:11:18,210
我想他应该不知道我来了
Oh, I don't actually believe he's aware I'm here.

274
00:11:18,780 --> 00:11:20,170
那你为什么不进去
So why don't you go in?

275
00:11:20,190 --> 00:11:22,400
他的秘书不在  不能通传
Well, his secretary isn't present to announce me.

276
00:11:22,400 --> 00:11:23,360
这不合适
It wouldn't be proper.

277
00:11:23,360 --> 00:11:24,920
今年是几几年啊
What year is it?

278
00:11:25,640 --> 00:11:26,350
迈克
Mike?

279
00:11:26,350 --> 00:11:28,100
-到  -怎么回事啊
- Yeah? - What's going on out there?

280
00:11:28,100 --> 00:11:30,750
很难解释清楚
Um, it's kind of hard to explain.

281
00:11:30,940 --> 00:11:32,510
你看过《唐顿庄园》吗
Have you ever seen Downton Abbey?

282
00:11:32,520 --> 00:11:33,310
什么
What?

283
00:11:33,310 --> 00:11:34,880
我还没看  不过听说评价不错
I haven't caught it, but I've heard great things.

284
00:11:34,880 --> 00:11:35,760
好看极了
Yeah, it's terrific.

285
00:11:35,760 --> 00:11:36,750
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.

286
00:11:38,650 --> 00:11:41,120
请允许我介绍爱德华·达比先生
May I present Mr. Edward Darby of--

287
00:11:41,120 --> 00:11:42,900
-快滚出去  -遵命
- Get the hell out of here. - Okay.

288
00:11:43,520 --> 00:11:45,640
-我会去网飞租来看的  -该看看
- Oh, I'll netflix it. - You should.

289
00:11:46,770 --> 00:11:47,930
我不是想打听什么
I don't mean to pry,

290
00:11:47,930 --> 00:11:49,690
但是你就这是这么对待下属的啊
but is that how you treat all your underlings?

291
00:11:50,370 --> 00:11:51,620
听着  班尼·希尔〔英国著名喜剧演员〕
Listen, Benny Hill,

292
00:11:51,820 --> 00:11:52,660
我正忙着
I'm a little busy

293
00:11:52,660 --> 00:11:54,580
酝酿情绪把你打得落花流水
preparing a motion to kick your ass.

294
00:11:54,580 --> 00:11:55,740
介意说重点了吗
You mind getting to the point?

295
00:11:55,740 --> 00:11:56,900
这就是重点
Well, that is the point.

296
00:11:56,900 --> 00:12:00,150
你的情绪也许应该酝酿得快一点了
You may have to expedite that motion a little faster than you think.

297
00:12:00,580 --> 00:12:03,050
明天我就会冻结你们的资产
Tomorrow I'll be freezing your assets.

298
00:12:03,250 --> 00:12:04,520
让我来理理
Let me get this straight.

299
00:12:04,910 --> 00:12:06,190
你来警告我
You're coming in here to warn me

300
00:12:06,190 --> 00:12:08,170
会冻结我客户的财产
that you're going to freeze my client's assets?

301
00:12:08,180 --> 00:12:09,120
是啊
Of course.

302
00:12:09,310 --> 00:12:10,680
这样的话  你就会有时间
This way, you'll have time

303
00:12:10,690 --> 00:12:13,870
为以后的诉讼转移出一些钱
to transfer a bit of currency to fund your legal battle.

304
00:12:13,870 --> 00:12:15,610
不然就不公平了
It wouldn't be sporting, otherwise.

305
00:12:15,610 --> 00:12:17,390
-“公平”  -是啊
- "Sporting"? - Certainly.

306
00:12:17,650 --> 00:12:20,500
狐狸不出动  猎人是不会打猎的
One doesn't hunt the fox while it's still in its den.

307
00:12:20,770 --> 00:12:22,020
猎人吹响号角
One sounds the horn

308
00:12:22,020 --> 00:12:23,050
以便在狩猎开始前
and allows the poor creature a head start

309
00:12:23,050 --> 00:12:24,950
让这个可怜的小东西先跑
before giving chase.

310
00:12:25,710 --> 00:12:27,210
你认为我是猎物
You think I'm the fox?

311
00:12:27,210 --> 00:12:28,350
认为
Think it?

312
00:12:28,690 --> 00:12:31,530
事实如此  只有你不知道
The only one who doesn't know that is you.

313
00:12:47,210 --> 00:12:48,340
我和你
You and me...

314
00:12:48,560 --> 00:12:49,890
就现在
right now...

315
00:12:49,890 --> 00:12:51,850
效率清单的比拚
game of efficiency list.

316
00:12:52,730 --> 00:12:55,430
文件我没有随身带
I'm afraid I don't have my files with me.

317
00:12:55,430 --> 00:12:57,140
娘们儿才要看文件
Files are for pussies.

318
00:12:57,220 --> 00:12:58,710
说得对
Right you are.

319
00:12:59,690 --> 00:13:01,520
我以预期寿命开始
I begin with life expectancy.

320
00:13:01,520 --> 00:13:02,480
我以营养情况开始
I begin with nutrition.

321
00:13:02,480 --> 00:13:04,520
你觉得我怎么得出预期寿命的
How do you think I determine life expectancy?

322
00:13:04,520 --> 00:13:05,800
床伴的数量
Number of sexual partners.

323
00:13:05,800 --> 00:13:08,590
-和母亲的关系  -是否有宠物
- Relationship to mother. - Pet ownership.

324
00:13:08,590 --> 00:13:11,020
这三件事是分割不开的
The three things are inextricably linked,

325
00:13:11,020 --> 00:13:14,010
而计算公式就在这里
and I have the formula right here.

326
00:13:14,010 --> 00:13:16,270
那我
Yeah, well, I...

327
00:13:16,390 --> 00:13:17,920
就记得有一场取证
just remembered that I have a deposition

328
00:13:17,920 --> 00:13:19,950
在Ｄ会议室等着我参加
that I have to go to in conference room "D".

329
00:13:20,990 --> 00:13:22,340
哪有Ｄ会议室
There is no conference room "D".

330
00:13:22,340 --> 00:13:23,570
他们重新编号了
They're re-lettering.

331
00:13:31,170 --> 00:13:32,880
你这么急是赶着去哪儿
Where are you off to in such a hurry?

332
00:13:32,890 --> 00:13:35,460
我得看完这本引人入胜的书
Uh, I have to finish this page-turner.

333
00:13:35,460 --> 00:13:36,340
《哈利·波特》
Harry potter?

334
00:13:36,350 --> 00:13:38,630
不是  但也是个英国人写的
No, but it is by a British author.

335
00:13:38,700 --> 00:13:40,860
我有点别的东西想让你读
Well, I've got something else for you to read.

336
00:13:40,860 --> 00:13:41,970
-是什么  -一封信
- What? - A letter.

337
00:13:41,970 --> 00:13:43,820
你真好  我的生日还没到呢
Oh, sweet. It's not even my birthday.

338
00:13:43,820 --> 00:13:47,160
不是写给你的  是由你写的
It's not to you. It's from you.

339
00:13:50,520 --> 00:13:51,390
是写给哈佛的
This is to Harvard.

340
00:13:51,390 --> 00:13:52,960
我要越过希拉·赛斯
I'm going over Sheila Sazs' head

341
00:13:52,960 --> 00:13:54,900
告诉学校事情的原委
and telling them everything that happened.

342
00:13:54,900 --> 00:13:56,600
准确来说是你
Well, you are.

343
00:13:56,600 --> 00:13:57,850
-瑞秋  你不能…  -拜托
- Rachel, you can't-- - No, come on.

344
00:13:57,850 --> 00:13:58,780
你也说了
You said it yourself.

345
00:13:58,780 --> 00:14:01,050
因为有人想惩罚路易而让我
It is not right that I'm being denied admission

346
00:14:01,050 --> 00:14:02,410
无法入学这太不公平了
because someone's punishing Louis.

347
00:14:02,410 --> 00:14:04,380
的确如此  但我不能签字
It's not, but I can't sign this.

348
00:14:04,380 --> 00:14:06,250
-为什么  -只是听说的
- Why not? - It's hearsay.

349
00:14:06,250 --> 00:14:09,510
迈克  我是想念哈佛的人
Mike, I'm someone who wants to go to Harvard.

350
00:14:09,510 --> 00:14:11,510
而你是从哈佛毕业的人
You're someone who went to Harvard.

351
00:14:11,510 --> 00:14:13,790
你觉得谁会更有说服力
Who do you think they're going to listen to more?

352
00:14:15,590 --> 00:14:17,370
你到底要不要帮我
Are you going to help me or not?

353
00:14:22,750 --> 00:14:23,920
我会帮你的
I'll help you.

354
00:14:30,480 --> 00:14:32,150
不管你找我干什么  我都没心情
Whatever it is, I'm not in the mood.

355
00:14:32,150 --> 00:14:35,240
我知道瑞秋  希拉还有哈佛的事了
I know about Rachel and Sheila and Harvard.

356
00:14:37,500 --> 00:14:38,280
你怎么知道
How?

357
00:14:38,280 --> 00:14:39,570
瑞秋告诉我的
Rachel told me.

358
00:14:40,500 --> 00:14:43,100
她要我越过希拉把这封信寄出去
She wants me to send this letter going over Sheila's head,

359
00:14:43,110 --> 00:14:45,460
但我不能寄这信
But it can't come from me.

360
00:14:49,490 --> 00:14:51,920
对  谁都不能寄
Yeah, it can't come from anyone.

361
00:14:57,200 --> 00:14:58,150
她没被录取
She didn't get in

362
00:14:58,150 --> 00:15:00,450
是因为他们觉得她不够好
because they didn't think she was good enough.

363
00:15:01,040 --> 00:15:02,930
-你骗了她  -不  我从没骗过她
- You lied to her. - No, I never lied to her.

364
00:15:02,930 --> 00:15:05,240
我说她足够优秀  这是实话
I told her she was good enough, which she is,

365
00:15:05,240 --> 00:15:07,280
但我没能说服希拉  让她失望了
but I let her down because I couldn't persuade Sheila,

366
00:15:07,280 --> 00:15:08,280
这也是事实
which is the truth.

367
00:15:08,280 --> 00:15:10,720
路易  你必须告诉她事实
Louis, you have to tell her the real truth.

368
00:15:10,720 --> 00:15:13,630
迈克  我见过她失落的样子
Mike, I saw the look on her face,

369
00:15:13,630 --> 00:15:14,740
然后让她振奋起来
and I took it away.

370
00:15:14,740 --> 00:15:15,890
我不想让她再次失落了
I do not want to put it back.

371
00:15:18,150 --> 00:15:19,560
你会后悔的
You'll regret it.

372
00:15:21,180 --> 00:15:22,990
听着  我再给你一天时间考虑
Look, I'll give you another day to think about it,

373
00:15:22,990 --> 00:15:26,790
但那之后  我就会亲自告诉她
but after that, I have to tell her myself.

374
00:15:33,830 --> 00:15:36,140
先生们  很高兴你们过来
Gentlemen, I'm glad you stopped by.

375
00:15:36,140 --> 00:15:37,500
我想告诉你们
I wanted to inform you

376
00:15:37,500 --> 00:15:39,630
明天一早我就会离开
I'm leaving town on the morrow.

377
00:15:39,630 --> 00:15:42,150
我会把案子交由我的副手处理
I'll be having my number two handle the case for me.

378
00:15:42,150 --> 00:15:43,690
我希望你也这么做
I expect you'll do the same.

379
00:15:43,690 --> 00:15:44,860
我为什么要照做
Why would I do that?

380
00:15:44,860 --> 00:15:46,720
这是传统  你决定吧
It's tradition. I leave it to you.

381
00:15:46,730 --> 00:15:49,550
-是否遵循随你的意  -我看遵循吧
- Honor it or don't. - I say we honor it.

382
00:15:49,550 --> 00:15:52,570
对了  《唐顿庄园》
Oh, by the by, Downton Abbey--

383
00:15:52,570 --> 00:15:53,830
我已经拿到了
Got it in my briefcase.

384
00:15:53,830 --> 00:15:55,390
准备在飞机上欣赏
Plan to watch it on the plane.

385
00:15:55,390 --> 00:15:56,680
天呐  你会…
Oh, my god. You are going to--

386
00:15:56,680 --> 00:16:00,820
别  别  千万不要剧透
Please, please. I abhor spoilers.

387
00:16:01,010 --> 00:16:03,380
第三集  我就说这么多
Episode three-- that's all I'll say.

388
00:16:03,390 --> 00:16:04,850
干脆你们俩一边玩弹片游戏
Why don't you two watch it together

389
00:16:04,850 --> 00:16:06,760
一边共同看剧好了
over a game of tiddlywinks?

390
00:16:06,760 --> 00:16:08,540
你似乎对我提议的
You seem to be upset over my game

391
00:16:08,540 --> 00:16:10,800
“效率评选”游戏很有意见啊
of "Let's put the peacock in its place".

392
00:16:10,800 --> 00:16:12,090
真高兴你提起这事了
I'm glad you mentioned that.

393
00:16:12,090 --> 00:16:15,890
我给你带了点离别礼物
I brought a little going-away present for you.

394
00:16:19,500 --> 00:16:21,370
这就是块饼干外加一瓶水
This is a biscuit and a bottle of water.

395
00:16:21,370 --> 00:16:23,880
我猜英国的监狱也就这待遇了
It's what I assume they serve in English prison,

396
00:16:23,890 --> 00:16:25,320
你的委托人就要因为
which is where your client's going

397
00:16:25,320 --> 00:16:27,590
冻结我委托人的资产前去享受一番
for freezing our client's assets.

398
00:16:27,590 --> 00:16:29,450
通过冻结资产来胁迫当事人
It's a violation of international law

399
00:16:29,450 --> 00:16:31,430
接受和解
to intimidate a litigant into settling

400
00:16:31,430 --> 00:16:33,360
触犯了国际法
by choking their funding.

401
00:16:36,800 --> 00:16:39,710
你大概以为你抓到了我的把柄
You seem to think you've got me by the short hairs.

402
00:16:39,710 --> 00:16:43,210
但如果你翻到此书的693页
However, if you turn to page 693 in this tome,

403
00:16:43,210 --> 00:16:45,270
你会发现那条法律也有例外
you'll find an exception to that very law.

404
00:16:45,270 --> 00:16:46,580
不会的
No, I won't.

405
00:16:47,190 --> 00:16:49,220
这书我都背下来了
I've memorized this book.

406
00:16:49,250 --> 00:16:51,500
没错  我听说你的超凡能力了
Yes, I was told of your prowess,

407
00:16:51,500 --> 00:16:55,310
所以我才选了一条从未正式出版过
which is why I chose a law not published in any book,

408
00:16:55,310 --> 00:16:59,230
但在英国执行了几十年的惯例
but a long-standing provision honored in England for decades.

409
00:16:59,420 --> 00:17:02,880
我们想怎样都可以  只要提前给予通知
We can do what we like, as long as notice is given.

410
00:17:02,880 --> 00:17:04,490
你根本不在乎是否公平
You don't give a shit about being sporting.

411
00:17:04,490 --> 00:17:05,830
你只是想要玩弄法律
You just wanted to skirt the law.

412
00:17:05,830 --> 00:17:09,040
胡说  两样我都要
Nonsense. I wanted to do both.

413
00:17:09,050 --> 00:17:11,120
因为起诉
By filing this action,

414
00:17:11,120 --> 00:17:12,830
你让你的委托人
you have opened your clients up

415
00:17:12,830 --> 00:17:14,920
面临恶意诉讼的指控
to a charge of malicious litigation.

416
00:17:14,920 --> 00:17:17,220
所以你之前才会冻结资产
Which is why you froze the assets in the first place.

417
00:17:17,220 --> 00:17:18,730
你给我们设了套
You baited us.

418
00:17:19,140 --> 00:17:23,630
不管怎样  你们似乎已被逼到墙角了
In any case, you seem to be backed up against the wall.

419
00:17:23,630 --> 00:17:25,280
我在那舒服得很呢
I'm comfortable there.

420
00:17:25,280 --> 00:17:28,150
让我反击的时候正好有所依靠
Gives me back support for when I come out swinging.

421
00:17:28,150 --> 00:17:31,280
你最好尽快采取行动
Well, you'd better do something quickly.

422
00:17:31,280 --> 00:17:32,610
恐怕你的委托人
Your clients don't have the funds

423
00:17:32,610 --> 00:17:35,990
没有足够的资金撑到这周结束了
to proceed beyond, I'd say, this week's end.

424
00:17:36,220 --> 00:17:38,440
我先告辞了  二位
Now, if you'll excuse me...

425
00:17:47,120 --> 00:17:49,280
我能跟你说几句吗
Hey, can I, uh, talk to you for a sec?

426
00:17:49,290 --> 00:17:52,340
什么事  路易  我现在有点忙呢
What is it, Louis? I'm just a little busy now.

427
00:17:52,800 --> 00:17:54,780
我只想说我知道杰西卡
I just wanted to say that I know you've been taking

428
00:17:54,780 --> 00:17:56,450
对你发了很大火
a lot of heat from Jessica, and...

429
00:17:57,040 --> 00:17:58,620
但我很高兴你这么做了
I'm glad you did what you did.

430
00:17:58,630 --> 00:18:00,470
这事不应该有人知道
That's not supposed to be public knowledge.

431
00:18:00,470 --> 00:18:01,300
是唐娜告诉我的
Well, no, Donna told me

432
00:18:01,310 --> 00:18:03,830
因为她知道我完全力挺你
because she knows that I support you 100%.

433
00:18:05,720 --> 00:18:06,930
是吗
Do you?

434
00:18:07,560 --> 00:18:10,850
奈杰尔·奈斯比特  英国版的我
Nigel Nesbitt-- my British counterpart.

435
00:18:10,850 --> 00:18:12,050
他怎么了
What about him?

436
00:18:12,050 --> 00:18:13,160
他“斗泥”比我强
He out-mudded me.

437
00:18:13,160 --> 00:18:14,480
你跟他提卡塔赫纳了吗
Didn't you tell him about Cartagena?

438
00:18:14,480 --> 00:18:16,450
我要是说了还用得着来找你吗
Oh, would we be having this conversation if I had?

439
00:18:16,450 --> 00:18:17,270
冷静点  路易
Louis, relax.

440
00:18:17,270 --> 00:18:19,120
我知道你这点爱好很在乎
I know how seriously you take your mudding,

441
00:18:19,120 --> 00:18:20,730
但那是私事
but that's personal.

442
00:18:20,730 --> 00:18:22,470
这不代表他是个更棒的律师
It doesn't mean he's a better lawyer.

443
00:18:22,470 --> 00:18:24,480
对  可不仅是这项  哈维
Yeah, but he didn't just out-mud me, Harvey.

444
00:18:24,480 --> 00:18:27,220
他做清单赢了我  学历也比我高
He out-listed me. He out-educated me.

445
00:18:27,230 --> 00:18:28,500
他…
He...

446
00:18:28,910 --> 00:18:30,500
完全就是我的升级版
Out-me'd me.

447
00:18:31,310 --> 00:18:32,680
哈维  我好怕
Harvey, I'm scared.

448
00:18:34,780 --> 00:18:36,580
拜托你告诉我这案子能赢
Please tell me we're going to win this thing.

449
00:18:36,580 --> 00:18:38,790
我们已经无路可退
Our backs are against the wall.

450
00:18:43,410 --> 00:18:44,200
你需要什么
What do you need?

451
00:18:44,200 --> 00:18:46,560
现在我要争取些时间
Right now I need to buy some time.

452
00:18:46,960 --> 00:18:49,000
-简单的很  -什么
- That's easy. - What?

453
00:18:49,260 --> 00:18:50,810
你曾告诉过我
You once told me what to do

454
00:18:50,810 --> 00:18:52,500
无路可退该怎么做
when your back's against the wall.

455
00:18:53,420 --> 00:18:54,910
自己开出一条路来
Break the goddamn thing down.

456
00:18:54,910 --> 00:18:56,090
这就对了
That's right.

457
00:18:56,940 --> 00:18:59,350
-你有办法弄到那些吗  -应有尽有
- You have access to that shit? - All of it.

458
00:18:59,350 --> 00:19:01,590
他们让我做一份效率清单
They needed me to do an efficiency list.

459
00:19:02,910 --> 00:19:04,040
拿下他们了
We got 'em.

460
00:19:06,840 --> 00:19:08,800
你好像不是张先生中餐馆的
You're not Mr. Chong's Chinese Food.

461
00:19:10,470 --> 00:19:11,150
这是什么
What's this?

462
00:19:11,150 --> 00:19:11,800
你明天早上
It's what you're going to use

463
00:19:11,800 --> 00:19:13,820
用来对付斯科特的
against Scottie tomorrow morning.

464
00:19:14,130 --> 00:19:15,220
让我来
Me?

465
00:19:15,220 --> 00:19:16,760
你是去当副辩律师的
You're going in as number two.

466
00:19:16,760 --> 00:19:18,400
我可不想让爱德华找任何借口
I don't want to give Edward any excuses.

467
00:19:18,410 --> 00:19:19,770
其实是你不想面对斯科特
You mean you don't want to deal with Scottie.

468
00:19:19,770 --> 00:19:22,280
-那只是顺带的好处而已  -好吧
- Well, that's just a side benefit. - Right.

469
00:19:23,830 --> 00:19:24,660
等等
Whoa, wait a second.

470
00:19:24,660 --> 00:19:27,110
这是合并的保密信息
This is confidential information from the merger.

471
00:19:27,110 --> 00:19:28,810
你用它来给我们拖延时间
Which you're going to use to get us a reprieve.

472
00:19:28,810 --> 00:19:30,350
你准备违反保密规则吗
You broke the Chinese Wall?

473
00:19:30,350 --> 00:19:31,180
不然你觉得我在干嘛
Why do you think I'm here?

474
00:19:31,180 --> 00:19:33,540
哈维  这是不予采信的
Harvey, this is inadmissible stuff.

475
00:19:33,550 --> 00:19:34,420
而且这和坦纳指控你
And it's in the ballpark

476
00:19:34,420 --> 00:19:36,640
在科斯特尔汽车公司一案中欺诈大同小异
of what Tanner accused you of with Coastal Motors.

477
00:19:36,640 --> 00:19:38,530
但这是让我们得以喘息的
But it's the only way I see us

478
00:19:38,530 --> 00:19:39,220
唯一方法
getting a little breathing room,

479
00:19:39,220 --> 00:19:40,750
我宁愿撞得头破血流
and I'd rather cross my own line

480
00:19:40,750 --> 00:19:42,150
也不要走他们画好的路
than sign their dotted one.

481
00:19:42,430 --> 00:19:43,490
好吧
Okay.

482
00:19:43,490 --> 00:19:44,520
看起来我明早
Then it looks like I have a date

483
00:19:44,520 --> 00:19:46,510
和你的女朋友要有个约会了
with your girlfriend in the morning.

484
00:20:09,060 --> 00:20:10,960
你不是应该等通知再进来吗
Weren't you supposed to be announced?

485
00:20:10,960 --> 00:20:12,870
我不关心那些规矩
I don't play by those rules.

486
00:20:12,870 --> 00:20:15,590
这我倒不觉得惊讶
Somehow that doesn't surprise me.

487
00:20:15,590 --> 00:20:16,600
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?

488
00:20:16,600 --> 00:20:17,740
你不是斯科特
You're not Scottie.

489
00:20:17,740 --> 00:20:20,190
你也不是杰米·史密兹  但也凑合
And you're not Jimmy Smits, but we make do.

490
00:20:17,740 --> 00:20:20,190
《洛城法网》主演

491
00:20:20,190 --> 00:20:21,950
你是在引用《洛城法网》吗
Are you making L.A. Law reference?

492
00:20:21,950 --> 00:20:24,290
不  我只是说我想和杰米·史密兹约会
No, I'm saying I wish I had a date with Jimmy Smits.

493
00:20:24,290 --> 00:20:26,470
-原来如此  -但我在这里
- Ah. - But instead I'm here...

494
00:20:26,470 --> 00:20:28,890
是来告诉你爱德华和你不是一个档次的
to tell you that Edward's in another league.

495
00:20:28,890 --> 00:20:29,800
你输定了
You're going to lose.

496
00:20:29,800 --> 00:20:30,900
不过问题在于
Well, there's only one problem.

497
00:20:30,900 --> 00:20:32,580
从你嘴里说出来的话
Words are coming out of your mouth,

498
00:20:32,580 --> 00:20:34,330
全都不是实话
which means the real story isn't.

499
00:20:34,340 --> 00:20:35,410
你想听实话是吗
Okay, you want the real story?

500
00:20:35,410 --> 00:20:37,190
你客户的资金就要耗尽了
Your clients are running out of funds.

501
00:20:37,190 --> 00:20:38,950
-你还有机会  -做什么
- You have a window. - To do what?

502
00:20:38,950 --> 00:20:40,230
投降
Give up.

503
00:20:41,200 --> 00:20:43,820
我不觉得这能让我们退缩
No, I don't think that's going to cut it for us.

504
00:20:43,820 --> 00:20:44,930
为什么
Why not?

505
00:20:44,930 --> 00:20:46,100
因为
Because...

506
00:20:46,110 --> 00:20:47,470
我们有这个
We have this.

507
00:20:50,460 --> 00:20:53,350
哈维  我们之后还是得在一起工作的
Harvey, we still have to work together after this.

508
00:20:53,350 --> 00:20:54,520
我给你指了一条出路
I am giving you a way out.

509
00:20:54,520 --> 00:20:56,100
我们都能当冠名合伙人
We can still both be name partners.

510
00:20:56,110 --> 00:20:57,420
不  不行的
No, we can't.

511
00:20:57,430 --> 00:20:58,920
我和杰西卡说好了
I made a deal with Jessica.

512
00:20:58,920 --> 00:21:00,100
我赢  你走人
I win, you're out.

513
00:21:00,100 --> 00:21:01,090
我放弃
I give up,

514
00:21:01,090 --> 00:21:03,450
你自己独享冠名合伙人
you're going to be name partner all by yourself.

515
00:21:06,170 --> 00:21:07,950
我要的不是这个
That's not what I want.

516
00:21:09,440 --> 00:21:11,070
-哈维  你还不懂吗  -等等
- Harvey, don't you get it? - Wait a second.

517
00:21:11,070 --> 00:21:14,240
如果你在这儿  那谁和迈克在一起
If you're here, who the hell's in with Mike?

518
00:21:17,360 --> 00:21:18,520
出去
Get out.

519
00:21:25,310 --> 00:21:26,430
你生气了
You're angry.

520
00:21:26,430 --> 00:21:29,020
这不是开玩笑  哈维  你犯法了
This isn't funny, Harvey. You just broke the law.

521
00:21:29,020 --> 00:21:30,970
民法而已  没人会被判入狱
It's a civil law. No one's going to go to jail.

522
00:21:30,970 --> 00:21:33,310
随你怎么狡辩  但是你作弊了
Justify it all you want, but you cheated.

523
00:21:33,320 --> 00:21:35,530
你不也是代替斯科特了吗
Like you, subbing in for Scottie?

524
00:21:35,530 --> 00:21:37,100
我懂你的把戏了
I see what you're doing.

525
00:21:37,100 --> 00:21:40,210
你清楚  达比按规矩出牌
You know damn well Darby plays by the rules.

526
00:21:40,220 --> 00:21:42,280
所以你靠作弊获胜  你就赢了
So if you win by cheating, you win.

527
00:21:42,280 --> 00:21:44,490
但要是你输了  他们到时会觉得你卑鄙
And if you lose, then they think you're dirty,

528
00:21:44,500 --> 00:21:45,760
然后不愿意合并
and they won't want to merge.

529
00:21:45,760 --> 00:21:46,970
你真的想和
You really want to merge with a man

530
00:21:46,980 --> 00:21:48,420
向你求助的人合并吗
who's asking for your help to win?

531
00:21:48,420 --> 00:21:49,910
不是他提出的
He didn't ask.

532
00:21:49,910 --> 00:21:50,710
是我坚持的
I insisted.

533
00:21:50,720 --> 00:21:52,750
做他的二把手
On being his number two.

534
00:21:52,760 --> 00:21:54,580
我预测事情就会这么发展
I guess that's a preview of things to come.

535
00:21:54,580 --> 00:21:56,630
那你对你耍的小伎俩
And is that little stunt you pulled

536
00:21:56,630 --> 00:21:58,340
有什么预测的吗
a preview of things to come?

537
00:21:58,390 --> 00:22:00,110
霍特  赞恩  哈德曼
Holt, Zane, Hardman.

538
00:22:00,110 --> 00:22:01,420
我们刚把他们打跑
We just fought them off.

539
00:22:01,750 --> 00:22:04,730
我们赢了  我们强大  我们有钱
We won. We're strong. We've got money.

540
00:22:04,730 --> 00:22:07,520
但如果我们合并  我们就又上一层台阶
And if we do this, we go to the next level.

541
00:22:07,520 --> 00:22:10,500
我们会成为律师界最大最强的霸主
We'll be the biggest, baddest fish in the sea.

542
00:22:10,500 --> 00:22:12,830
如果我赢了达比会怎么样
And what's going to happen after I beat Darby?

543
00:22:12,830 --> 00:22:14,510
你觉得我在和你闹着玩吗
You think I'm playing with you?

544
00:22:14,510 --> 00:22:17,320
你的那些小伎俩  “毒树之果”
That stunt you pulled-- fruit from the poison tree.

545
00:22:14,510 --> 00:22:17,320
根据非法手段所获得的被告人的口供  并获得的第二手证据

546
00:22:17,320 --> 00:22:19,030
我会在周二把它撤销
I will have that reversed on Tuesday.

547
00:22:19,030 --> 00:22:20,210
你觉得我会从现在到周二
You think I'm not going to find anything

548
00:22:20,210 --> 00:22:21,270
都一无所获吗
between now and Tuesday?

549
00:22:21,270 --> 00:22:22,920
-你找不到的  -这算是威胁吗
- I know you won't. - Is that a threat?

550
00:22:22,920 --> 00:22:24,450
这算是预见
It's a prediction.

551
00:22:27,070 --> 00:22:28,540
我能走人
I can go.

552
00:22:29,730 --> 00:22:31,150
你打算走去哪儿呢
Where you going to go?

553
00:22:32,800 --> 00:22:34,330
就算我让你走了
Even if I let you out,

554
00:22:34,640 --> 00:22:37,440
外面的情况是一样的  只会更糟
it's the same out there, only worse.

555
00:22:37,440 --> 00:22:39,930
你最多也只能打赢案子  不会成为领导者
And you'll be a winner, but not a leader,

556
00:22:39,930 --> 00:22:41,510
而且你还没有我这个靠山
and you won't have me.

557
00:22:41,510 --> 00:22:43,390
你不了解这些人
You don't know these people.

558
00:22:43,400 --> 00:22:45,710
他们说我掌控不了你
I know they said I couldn't control you.

559
00:22:46,140 --> 00:22:48,300
你会明白我可以
You're going to learn that I can.

560
00:23:07,730 --> 00:23:09,300
合并还没完成
The merger hasn't gone through yet,

561
00:23:09,310 --> 00:23:10,410
所以严格地说
so technically,

562
00:23:10,410 --> 00:23:12,340
你不能在我们的文件室里四处打探
you're not allowed to be lurking around our files.

563
00:23:12,340 --> 00:23:15,590
我不是在打探  我是在找你
I'm not lurking. I'm looking for you.

564
00:23:16,230 --> 00:23:17,120
我就在这儿
And here I am.

565
00:23:17,120 --> 00:23:18,670
我觉得你对我撒谎了
I think that you lied to me.

566
00:23:19,920 --> 00:23:21,120
我觉得你错了
I think that you're wrong.

567
00:23:21,120 --> 00:23:22,540
你都不知道我在说什么
You don't even know what I'm talking about.

568
00:23:22,540 --> 00:23:24,040
可我知道我不是骗子
I know I'm not a liar.

569
00:23:24,230 --> 00:23:26,490
你说你没有说过我的坏话
You told me you never said a bad thing about me.

570
00:23:26,860 --> 00:23:27,910
我的确没有
And I never have.

571
00:23:27,910 --> 00:23:29,370
但你不喜欢我
But you don't like me.

572
00:23:30,470 --> 00:23:32,570
我不喜欢对哈维撒谎的人
I don't like people who lie to Harvey.

573
00:23:33,220 --> 00:23:34,880
你爱他吗  唐娜
Are you in love with him, Donna?

574
00:23:37,480 --> 00:23:40,060
我真受够了  人人都来问我这个
I am so frickin' tired of people asking me that,

575
00:23:40,060 --> 00:23:41,720
这不关你的事
and it is none of your business.

576
00:23:43,910 --> 00:23:45,040
而且  我不爱他
But, no.

577
00:23:47,040 --> 00:23:48,630
我过去挺喜欢你的
And I did like you,

578
00:23:48,640 --> 00:23:51,280
直到你拿着那份扯淡议程走进这里
until you walked in here with that bullshit agenda and--

579
00:23:51,280 --> 00:23:52,210
这不是扯淡
It's not bullshit.

580
00:23:52,210 --> 00:23:54,440
那你觉得叫什么比较好
Okay, then what would you call it?

581
00:23:55,710 --> 00:23:58,200
你觉得我上次为什么回来
Why do you think I came back last time?

582
00:23:58,530 --> 00:24:00,190
为什么我把我俩扯进福尔松的案子里
Why do you think I brought us in on Folsom?

583
00:24:00,190 --> 00:24:02,370
我不知道怎么引起他的注意
I don't know how to get his attention

584
00:24:02,370 --> 00:24:04,050
除了让我起诉他
unless I sue him.

585
00:24:05,120 --> 00:24:06,400
你爱上他了
You're in love with him.

586
00:24:07,500 --> 00:24:10,320
他总是对我那么生气
He's-- he's just so angry at me,

587
00:24:10,320 --> 00:24:12,480
我不知道怎么让他相信我
and I-I don't know how to make him believe it.

588
00:24:12,480 --> 00:24:14,180
是啊  他怎么会信你
Well, why would he believe you?

589
00:24:14,380 --> 00:24:15,970
除了骗他你还做了什么
All you've ever done is lie to him.

590
00:24:15,970 --> 00:24:17,280
这次不是
This is not...

591
00:24:18,810 --> 00:24:20,010
这次是真的
This is not a lie.

592
00:24:20,770 --> 00:24:23,830
达娜  如果你想让他走出愤怒
Look, Dana, if you want to break through his anger,

593
00:24:23,830 --> 00:24:25,450
你必须有所行动
you're going to have to do something.

594
00:24:29,360 --> 00:24:30,510
合并的事
The merger.

595
00:24:30,940 --> 00:24:32,000
放弃吧
Walk away.

596
00:24:33,100 --> 00:24:34,680
放弃我的冠名合伙人资格
From my name on the door.

597
00:24:35,070 --> 00:24:36,230
如果你想让他听见你的心声
If you want him to hear you,

598
00:24:36,230 --> 00:24:37,860
你就得做出牺牲
you're going to have to make a sacrifice.

599
00:24:37,860 --> 00:24:39,120
所以我得
So I just...

600
00:24:40,370 --> 00:24:43,670
冒着失去所有的风险  却毫无保证
risk everything with no guarantee.

601
00:24:44,380 --> 00:24:46,060
不然还叫牺牲吗
That's what sacrifice is.

602
00:24:56,000 --> 00:24:57,220
收到你的短信了
I got your message.

603
00:24:58,650 --> 00:24:59,880
为什么在这儿见面
Why are we meeting here?

604
00:24:59,920 --> 00:25:01,550
听上去你不相信我
You sound like you don't trust me.

605
00:25:01,620 --> 00:25:03,180
你用杰西卡来堵我
Well, you did sandbag me with Jessica.

606
00:25:03,180 --> 00:25:05,200
是杰西卡自己要来堵你
Jessica sandbagged you with Jessica.

607
00:25:05,430 --> 00:25:07,540
还是没解释我们在这儿见面的原因
Still doesn't explain why we're meeting here.

608
00:25:10,700 --> 00:25:11,770
哈维的翻版
Baby Harvey.

609
00:25:13,080 --> 00:25:14,320
这可是莫大的嘉奖
That's a huge compliment.

610
00:25:14,320 --> 00:25:16,520
-实话实说而已  -我是说对他而言
- Call it like I see it. - I meant for him.

611
00:25:17,440 --> 00:25:19,400
我们会面是因为单靠你
We're meeting here because you

612
00:25:19,400 --> 00:25:21,170
是永远找不到这个的
will never find this.

613
00:25:26,210 --> 00:25:28,290
如果这派上用场  会为我们赢下官司
If this checks out, it'll win the case for us.

614
00:25:28,290 --> 00:25:29,450
我知道
I know.

615
00:25:31,060 --> 00:25:32,970
你为什么把它交给我呢
And why am I the one you're giving this to?

616
00:25:34,660 --> 00:25:36,180
我们还在法学院的时候
When we were in law school,

617
00:25:37,020 --> 00:25:38,810
哈维的弟弟病了
Harvey's brother got sick.

618
00:25:39,450 --> 00:25:42,000
他急需钱  他父亲身无分文
He needed money. His father didn't have any.

619
00:25:42,000 --> 00:25:43,410
他母亲不知所踪
His mother wasn't in the picture.

620
00:25:43,410 --> 00:25:44,180
别说让我猜
Don't tell me.

621
00:25:44,180 --> 00:25:45,940
哈维找到办法帮他了
Harvey found a way to help him out.

622
00:25:45,940 --> 00:25:47,410
他用了他的学费
He used his tuition.

623
00:25:47,910 --> 00:25:48,880
不管怎样
Anyway...

624
00:25:50,120 --> 00:25:52,690
他母亲发现后  和他联系
When his mother found out, she contacted him.

625
00:25:53,250 --> 00:25:55,180
但是哈维不肯拿她一分钱
Harvey wouldn't take a nickel from her.

626
00:25:55,190 --> 00:25:57,040
所以她把钱给了他弟弟
So she gave his brother the money.

627
00:25:57,040 --> 00:25:58,690
他弟弟再把钱还给他
Who used it to pay him back.

628
00:25:58,960 --> 00:26:01,130
我不知道哈维还有个弟弟
I didn't even know Harvey had a brother.

629
00:26:01,130 --> 00:26:02,260
你会喜欢他的
You'd like him.

630
00:26:02,850 --> 00:26:04,090
他和你很像
He's like you.

631
00:26:08,080 --> 00:26:10,450
你让我怎么和哈维说
So are you saying that I have to tell Harvey

632
00:26:10,450 --> 00:26:12,130
就说我自己找到这份材料的
I found this on my own?

633
00:26:12,580 --> 00:26:13,980
没让你非这么说
You don't have to.

634
00:26:14,790 --> 00:26:17,540
但这么说的话  他更有可能会用这材料
But it'll definitely increase your odds of him using it.

635
00:26:21,220 --> 00:26:22,810
-我有所发现  -我看看
- I found something. - Let me see.

636
00:26:22,810 --> 00:26:24,180
还没完成  我们得赶紧了
It's not done. We have to hurry.

637
00:26:24,180 --> 00:26:26,030
明早之前我能完成
But I can get it done before tomorrow morning.

638
00:26:26,030 --> 00:26:27,210
这个太好了
This is good.

639
00:26:27,320 --> 00:26:28,290
我知道
I know.

640
00:26:29,240 --> 00:26:31,640
加紧去做吧  从哪里得来的
Get on it. Where'd you get it?

641
00:26:33,790 --> 00:26:35,420
你明知故问
You know where I got it.

642
00:26:35,660 --> 00:26:37,700
问题是你允许我用吗
The question is, are you going to let me use it?

643
00:26:37,700 --> 00:26:39,700
-出去  -哈维  有了这材料我们就能赢
- Get out. - Harvey, we can win with this.

644
00:26:39,700 --> 00:26:42,070
你还不懂吗  你不能相信她
Here's what you don't get. You can't trust her.

645
00:26:42,070 --> 00:26:42,990
如果是她给的
If it came from her,

646
00:26:42,990 --> 00:26:44,560
最终她会倒打我们一耙
it'll come back to bite us in the ass.

647
00:26:44,560 --> 00:26:46,960
明天期限将至  除此我们一无所有
Tomorrow morning is coming, and we don't have anything else.

648
00:26:46,960 --> 00:26:50,230
-那就去给我找出点东西来  -好的
- Then go find me something. - Okay.

649
00:26:53,680 --> 00:26:54,890
劳驾  
Pardon me. Excuse me.

650
00:26:54,890 --> 00:26:56,430
能再加点柠檬吗
Do you mind if I have a little more lemon?

651
00:26:56,430 --> 00:26:57,360
谢谢
Thanks.

652
00:27:02,750 --> 00:27:04,030
你也看演出了吗
You were at the show?

653
00:27:04,070 --> 00:27:05,400
是的  坐在4A  你呢
Seat 4-a. You?

654
00:27:05,400 --> 00:27:09,530
A-4  这出莎翁的剧演得不错
Seat a-4. Shakespeare well performed.

655
00:27:09,620 --> 00:27:10,690
没错
Indeed...

656
00:27:10,860 --> 00:27:11,840
不过那个母老虎
Though not improved

657
00:27:11,840 --> 00:27:13,720
大喊大叫真是扫人兴
by the yammering of that battle axe.

658
00:27:13,720 --> 00:27:15,680
还好第一幕结束后她就没声了
Well, thank God she stopped after the first act.

659
00:27:15,680 --> 00:27:16,750
谢谢
Thank you.

660
00:27:16,750 --> 00:27:19,090
准确地说  不是她停了
Well, she didn't precisely stop.

661
00:27:21,200 --> 00:27:22,240
是你把她支走的
You had her removed?

662
00:27:22,250 --> 00:27:23,410
我和她说她家保姆来电
Told her the baby-sitter phoned,

663
00:27:23,410 --> 00:27:25,180
家里孩子出事了
and the children were on fire.

664
00:27:26,560 --> 00:27:27,300
那是什么
What's that?

665
00:27:27,300 --> 00:27:29,620
我后面一排有个白痴一直在发短信
One row up-- some douche bag was texting.

666
00:27:29,620 --> 00:27:31,460
被我顺过来了  他还不知道
Took it from him, didn't even know.

667
00:27:32,460 --> 00:27:34,380
请坐
Oh, uh, please.

668
00:27:38,460 --> 00:27:40,680
这里“白痴”两个字用得太好了
Incidentally, excellent use of the word "Douche bag."

669
00:27:40,680 --> 00:27:42,490
怎么说呢  我和这类人打交道得太多了
Well, I've had a lot of experience with them.

670
00:27:42,490 --> 00:27:43,610
我也是
As have I.

671
00:27:44,840 --> 00:27:46,910
我这人很难交到朋友
I don't make friends very easily.

672
00:27:47,560 --> 00:27:49,600
有趣的是  我小时候
That's funny. When I was a kid...

673
00:27:51,100 --> 00:27:52,480
“朋友”还挺多
there was a bunch of them.

674
00:27:53,440 --> 00:27:54,550
他们大部分人都是跟班的
Most of them were just followers,

675
00:27:54,550 --> 00:27:58,060
但是其中有一个人叫柯克·布莱斯林
but there was that one-- Kirk Breslin.

676
00:27:58,330 --> 00:27:59,760
朱利安·亨特
Julian Hunt.

677
00:28:00,000 --> 00:28:03,280
然后有一天  我决定以牙还牙
And then one day I decided to be mean.

678
00:28:03,420 --> 00:28:05,370
我告诉那个欺负我的混蛋
I just told that bully piece of shit

679
00:28:05,370 --> 00:28:06,890
他的一生将在碌碌无为
that he'd never be anything, do anything,

680
00:28:06,890 --> 00:28:08,290
一事无成中度过
or amount to anything.

681
00:28:08,800 --> 00:28:10,960
此后  没人再取笑过我
After that, they never made fun of me again.

682
00:28:11,990 --> 00:28:12,990
好吧
Right.

683
00:28:15,230 --> 00:28:17,560
我不该说巴登巴登坏话的
I shouldn't have impugned Baden-Baden.

684
00:28:18,270 --> 00:28:20,830
我问你是不是也做泥浴时
It's just that when I asked you if you took mud,

685
00:28:20,830 --> 00:28:21,950
我只是
I was...

686
00:28:23,010 --> 00:28:26,830
在向你伸出一只满是泥垢的友谊之手
offering a warm, muddied hand of friendship,

687
00:28:27,690 --> 00:28:30,010
而你却接过来擦得干干净净
and you took that hand and wiped it clean.

688
00:28:30,010 --> 00:28:33,540
我当时不知道你是这个意图
Well, I didn't recognize the gesture.

689
00:28:33,540 --> 00:28:34,830
我理解
I understand.

690
00:28:34,830 --> 00:28:37,370
干我们这行  注定孤独
It's a lonely job, being the hatchet man.

691
00:28:37,490 --> 00:28:39,960
是啊  可能这就是我们背负的命运吧
Yeah, well, I guess it's, uh, our cross to bear.

692
00:28:45,860 --> 00:28:47,630
我能对你实话实说吗
Can I be honest with you?

693
00:28:48,310 --> 00:28:50,210
看了效率清单的结果之后
With the results of my efficiency list,

694
00:28:50,210 --> 00:28:52,270
我得出这么一个结论
I keep arriving at the same conclusion.

695
00:28:52,270 --> 00:28:53,970
你我二人  一山不容二虎
There's no room for both of us.

696
00:28:55,760 --> 00:28:56,790
除非
Unless...

697
00:28:58,230 --> 00:29:01,100
我们各自给对方生路
we made room for each other.

698
00:29:03,870 --> 00:29:05,800
我不把你写上名单
I leave you off my list.

699
00:29:06,370 --> 00:29:08,200
我也不写你
And I leave you off mine.

700
00:29:09,080 --> 00:29:10,420
你就愿意
Well, would you be willing

701
00:29:10,420 --> 00:29:12,700
牺牲你这份名单的公正性吗
to sacrifice the integrity of your list?

702
00:29:14,960 --> 00:29:16,070
为了朋友
I would...

703
00:29:18,000 --> 00:29:19,170
我愿意
for a friend.

704
00:29:29,150 --> 00:29:30,620
你这人是怎么回事
What the hell is wrong with you?

705
00:29:31,170 --> 00:29:32,790
我觉得你准备自问自答了
I have a feeling you're about to tell me.

706
00:29:32,790 --> 00:29:35,470
这个合并  你到底是赞成还是反对
Are you for this merger or against it?

707
00:29:35,880 --> 00:29:36,690
当然反对
I'm against it.

708
00:29:36,690 --> 00:29:37,990
为什么  当我没问
Why? Never mind.

709
00:29:37,990 --> 00:29:39,450
我来告诉你原因
I'm going to tell you why--

710
00:29:39,650 --> 00:29:41,100
因为斯科特
because of Scottie.

711
00:29:41,450 --> 00:29:42,590
如果我不能相信她
If I can't trust her,

712
00:29:42,590 --> 00:29:43,960
那她给的所有东西我都不信
how can I trust any of it?

713
00:29:43,960 --> 00:29:47,250
她为了博得你的信任  什么都不顾了
She's showing you you can by throwing it all away.

714
00:29:48,320 --> 00:29:50,140
这个文件不靠谱
That folder is a wild-goose chase.

715
00:29:50,140 --> 00:29:52,350
我的天啊  你平时不是总能快人三步
Oh, my God. For somebody who's usually three steps ahead,

716
00:29:52,350 --> 00:29:53,820
怎么这次如此迟钝
you are a mile behind.

717
00:29:53,820 --> 00:29:55,950
哈维  她爱上你了
She is in love with you, Harvey...

718
00:29:56,850 --> 00:29:58,070
只是她不能对你说
Only she can't tell you that.

719
00:29:58,070 --> 00:29:59,750
因为和别人一样  她知道
Because she, like everybody else,

720
00:29:59,750 --> 00:30:01,650
说出来  你只会拒她千里之外
knows that it will only drive you away.

721
00:30:01,650 --> 00:30:03,260
-唐娜  -如果她来这里
- Donna. - If she had shown up here

722
00:30:03,270 --> 00:30:04,560
要求你和她交往
and asked you to start a relationship,

723
00:30:04,560 --> 00:30:06,150
你会同意吗
would you have said yes?

724
00:30:07,180 --> 00:30:10,090
-不  你不会同意的  -事情没那么简单
- No, you wouldn't have. - It's not that simple.

725
00:30:10,090 --> 00:30:11,540
佐伊的事情也很复杂吗
Was it not that simple with Zoe?

726
00:30:11,550 --> 00:30:12,850
她和这事儿有什么关系
What the hell does that have to do with it?

727
00:30:12,860 --> 00:30:14,180
是你让她走的
You let her go.

728
00:30:14,180 --> 00:30:16,190
她是要去抚养她侄女
She left me to raise her niece.

729
00:30:16,190 --> 00:30:18,690
-你请求她留下吗  -我没有选择
- Did you ask her to stay? - It wasn't on the table.

730
00:30:18,700 --> 00:30:20,310
她想你争取她
She wanted you to fight.

731
00:30:20,310 --> 00:30:22,730
她可怜的侄女就要失去父亲了
That poor girl was losing her father,

732
00:30:22,730 --> 00:30:24,560
我不可能试着去取代
and I wasn't about to try and replace him

733
00:30:24,560 --> 00:30:25,840
当她的父亲
while it was happening.

734
00:30:25,840 --> 00:30:28,000
放屁  就是你让她走的
Bullshit! You let her go!

735
00:30:28,320 --> 00:30:30,650
看到你为公司的事情如此拚命
And I am so sick of watching you fight like hell

736
00:30:30,650 --> 00:30:32,090
而对于你内心的渴求不闻不问
for everything that happens in here

737
00:30:32,090 --> 00:30:33,780
我实在是不能理解
and nothing that happens in here.

738
00:30:33,780 --> 00:30:35,520
-这都是关于佐伊  -不是的
- Is this about Zoe? - No.

739
00:30:35,820 --> 00:30:36,820
是关于你
Is this about you?

740
00:30:37,120 --> 00:30:38,100
不是
No.

741
00:30:39,630 --> 00:30:41,180
是和斯科特有关
This is about Scottie.

742
00:30:43,500 --> 00:30:44,710
你不知道她做了什么
You don't know what she did.

743
00:30:44,710 --> 00:30:46,190
我很清楚
I do know what she did.

744
00:30:46,560 --> 00:30:49,170
她背叛了未婚夫  所以你觉得
She cheated on her fiance, so you think that that means

745
00:30:49,170 --> 00:30:50,530
早晚有一天
that there will always be a chance

746
00:30:50,530 --> 00:30:51,690
她也有可能会背叛你
that she will cheat on you.

747
00:30:51,690 --> 00:30:53,820
但区别是  她不爱她的未婚夫
The difference is, she didn't love him.

748
00:30:53,820 --> 00:30:55,370
她爱的是你
She loves you.

749
00:30:57,670 --> 00:31:00,680
我知道你母亲让你很受伤
Look, I know that your mother hurt you,

750
00:31:00,680 --> 00:31:02,780
但是你必须从中走出来
but you need to get over it.

751
00:31:02,780 --> 00:31:04,720
你认为我担心的是那事
You think that's what I'm worried about?

752
00:31:05,500 --> 00:31:07,990
她让我侮辱了一个
She made me make a fool out of him,

753
00:31:08,050 --> 00:31:09,450
我从没见过
a man I'd never met,

754
00:31:09,450 --> 00:31:12,790
和我没有任何过节的人
a man who'd never done a wrong to me.

755
00:31:12,850 --> 00:31:14,170
她让我做出这种事情
How am I going to trust someone

756
00:31:14,180 --> 00:31:16,260
我怎么还能相信她
who made me a man who did that?

757
00:31:17,380 --> 00:31:19,210
或许你不能相信她
Maybe you can't trust her.

758
00:31:20,890 --> 00:31:22,430
但如果你不想眼看合并发生
But if you want to end this merger,

759
00:31:22,430 --> 00:31:24,870
你得相信她给迈克的材料
you better trust what she gave Mike.

760
00:31:34,600 --> 00:31:35,830
你把材料给迈克吧
Give him the file.

761
00:31:38,900 --> 00:31:40,770
老娘四个小时之前就给了
What do you think I did four hours ago?

762
00:31:47,570 --> 00:31:48,570
你要见我
You wanted to see me?

763
00:31:48,570 --> 00:31:50,290
两小时之前我就找你了
That request went out two hours ago.

764
00:31:50,290 --> 00:31:52,310
那时我忙着没空
Uh, yeah, I was in the middle of something.

765
00:31:52,310 --> 00:31:53,540
你在忙什么
What were you in the middle of?

766
00:31:53,540 --> 00:31:54,760
你说什么
Excuse me?

767
00:31:55,170 --> 00:31:56,820
你说你在忙
You said you were in the middle of something.

768
00:31:57,150 --> 00:31:58,740
我猜是哈维的案子
I assume it's Harvey's case.

769
00:31:58,740 --> 00:32:00,400
我不能说  你是对立面的
I can't tell you that. You're on the other side.

770
00:32:00,400 --> 00:32:01,720
哪条规定说
Is there some rule

771
00:32:01,720 --> 00:32:04,270
我不能询问自己员工了
against my checking on my own employee?

772
00:32:08,710 --> 00:32:10,920
我保证  明天之后
I'm confident that, after tomorrow,

773
00:32:11,850 --> 00:32:13,470
你们要么选择和解  要么就吃败仗
you'll either settle or lose.

774
00:32:13,470 --> 00:32:14,680
为什么呢
And why is that?

775
00:32:14,680 --> 00:32:16,420
因为我准备了一项动议
Because I've prepared a motion

776
00:32:16,420 --> 00:32:18,810
根据一则９月14日的材料
based on a file dated September 14th.

777
00:32:19,060 --> 00:32:20,540
达比没和我说起过
Darby didn't tell me about that.

778
00:32:20,540 --> 00:32:22,030
他也不知道
He didn't know about it.

779
00:32:22,280 --> 00:32:23,560
你从哪里得来的
Where'd you get it?

780
00:32:27,660 --> 00:32:28,920
材料上怎么说
What does it say?

781
00:32:30,470 --> 00:32:32,100
说你们要输
It says you're going to lose.

782
00:32:33,430 --> 00:32:34,950
那样的话太可惜了
Then that's too bad...

783
00:32:36,360 --> 00:32:37,990
因为你得把那份材料扔了
because you're going to throw it away.

784
00:32:39,970 --> 00:32:41,760
-什么  -你听到了
- What? - You heard me.

785
00:32:42,000 --> 00:32:43,560
你现在就回家
You're going to go home.

786
00:32:43,850 --> 00:32:45,930
不准打电话  不准接电话
You don't call, you don't answer,

787
00:32:45,930 --> 00:32:49,200
最后期限过去之前不准回公司
and you don't come back until that deadline is passed.

788
00:32:49,200 --> 00:32:50,340
等等  那些可是你的客户啊
Wait a minute. These are your clients.

789
00:32:50,340 --> 00:32:51,460
是被哈维利用的客户
Who Harvey is using.

790
00:32:51,460 --> 00:32:54,460
-这个解释毫无道理  -那个文件也是
- That's a bullshit argument. - And so is that file.

791
00:32:58,100 --> 00:32:59,430
-我不会那么做的  -你会的
- I won't. - You will.

792
00:32:59,430 --> 00:33:00,430
哈维不会原谅我的
Harvey will never forgive me.

793
00:33:00,430 --> 00:33:03,040
现在你的问题不是哈维
Right now your problem isn't with Harvey.

794
00:33:03,080 --> 00:33:04,640
而是我
Your problem is with me.

795
00:33:05,440 --> 00:33:06,360
如果你不这么做
You don't do this,

796
00:33:06,360 --> 00:33:08,770
说不定你就会因为无证从业
who's to say you don't end up in a cell

797
00:33:08,770 --> 00:33:11,080
而进大牢
for practicing law without a degree?

798
00:33:15,770 --> 00:33:17,740
说不准你也会因为知情不报
And who's to say you don't share that cell with me

799
00:33:17,740 --> 00:33:19,670
和我一起入狱呢
for knowing about it the whole time?

800
00:33:19,670 --> 00:33:20,960
你愿意冒这个风险吗
You don't want to take that tact.

801
00:33:20,960 --> 00:33:22,880
-不是我挑起的  -我绝对能告赢你
- I didn't start it. - I will beat you.

802
00:33:22,880 --> 00:33:24,120
上次你那样对我说时
The last time you said that to me,

803
00:33:24,120 --> 00:33:25,960
你以为你不需要电脑
you thought you didn't need a computer.

804
00:33:26,530 --> 00:33:27,500
你错了
You were wrong.

805
00:33:27,500 --> 00:33:29,500
那是有关案例分析的知识
That was about demonstrating knowledge,

806
00:33:29,780 --> 00:33:31,300
我并没有下赌注
and the stakes were nothing.

807
00:33:31,340 --> 00:33:33,740
而这关系到我的权力
This is about my power,

808
00:33:34,220 --> 00:33:35,970
我已经赌上了一切
and the stakes are everything.

809
00:33:37,400 --> 00:33:39,540
这是一封写给地方检察官的信
This is a letter to the district attorney,

810
00:33:39,540 --> 00:33:41,660
信上写着我注意到
saying that it's come to my attention

811
00:33:41,660 --> 00:33:44,480
你违法了
that you are breaking the law.

812
00:33:44,610 --> 00:33:45,580
我想你已经见过他了
I believe you've met him--

813
00:33:45,580 --> 00:33:47,440
可不是睁一只眼闭一只眼的主
Not the type to let it slide.

814
00:33:50,560 --> 00:33:52,530
你若提交你的动议
You file your motion...

815
00:33:53,940 --> 00:33:55,540
我就提交我的
I'll file mine.

816
00:34:14,210 --> 00:34:16,240
-听着  哈维  -闭嘴
- Okay, look, Harvey-- - Shut your mouth!

817
00:34:16,240 --> 00:34:17,820
我为你赌上了一切
I risked everything for you.

818
00:34:17,820 --> 00:34:19,920
我一次又一次地这样做
Then I did it again and again.

819
00:34:19,920 --> 00:34:22,080
-等等  你不在那里  -我没必要在场
- Wait. You weren't there. - I didn't have to be.

820
00:34:22,080 --> 00:34:23,490
-杰西卡  -你不是为杰西卡效力
- Jessica-- - you don't work for Jessica.

821
00:34:23,490 --> 00:34:24,380
你为我效力
You work for me.

822
00:34:24,380 --> 00:34:25,420
我知道
I know I do,

823
00:34:25,430 --> 00:34:27,150
但我在努力帮你获得你想要的东西
But I was just trying to get you what you wanted--

824
00:34:27,160 --> 00:34:28,260
将你的名字印在公司大门上
your name on the door.

825
00:34:28,260 --> 00:34:30,640
不  你帮爱德华·达比把名字印在大门上
No, you got Edward Darby's name on the door.

826
00:34:30,640 --> 00:34:32,570
我早就出局了
My part of the deal is gone.

827
00:34:32,570 --> 00:34:34,810
什么  你从没跟我说过
What? You never told me that.

828
00:34:34,810 --> 00:34:36,740
我觉得没必要告诉你
I didn't think I needed to tell you that

829
00:34:36,740 --> 00:34:39,140
因为我从没想过你会背叛我
because I didn't think you would ever betray me.

830
00:34:39,140 --> 00:34:40,930
哈维  看看我们做了什么
Harvey, look at what we've done--

831
00:34:41,460 --> 00:34:42,720
你和我
You and me.

832
00:34:43,000 --> 00:34:44,320
你打破了界限
You broke the Chinese Wall.

833
00:34:44,320 --> 00:34:46,530
我直接从斯科特那里获得信息
I got information directly from Scottie.

834
00:34:46,530 --> 00:34:49,140
这两件缺德事放在六周前
That's two ethical violations that six weeks ago

835
00:34:49,140 --> 00:34:50,520
会让你倒胃口的
would have made your stomach turn.

836
00:34:50,520 --> 00:34:52,280
-这不是你这样做的原因  -好吧
- That's not why you did it. - Fine.

837
00:34:52,280 --> 00:34:54,530
但看着我的眼睛  告诉我这不是真的
But look me in the eye and tell me it's not true anyway.

838
00:34:54,530 --> 00:34:56,130
你知道吗  这不重要
You know what, it doesn't matter

839
00:34:56,130 --> 00:34:58,900
因为你不能替我做决定
because you don't get to make my decisions for me.

840
00:34:59,030 --> 00:35:01,190
这不就是你竭力在为我做的事吗
Isn't that what you were trying to do for me?

841
00:35:02,570 --> 00:35:03,980
这是私密谈话
This is a private conversation.

842
00:35:03,980 --> 00:35:06,130
你想敞开谈  我们就说明白吧
You want to have it out, let's have it out...

843
00:35:06,130 --> 00:35:07,250
马上
Right now.

844
00:35:07,520 --> 00:35:08,880
你该走了
You might want to go.

845
00:35:11,930 --> 00:35:13,020
抱歉
I'm sorry.

846
00:35:13,850 --> 00:35:15,360
你回去当助理吧
You're back in the associates' pool.

847
00:35:15,360 --> 00:35:16,270
哈维  拜托
Harvey, come on.

848
00:35:16,270 --> 00:35:18,910
你不是我见过最优秀的律师
Turns out you're not the best lawyer I've ever seen.

849
00:35:18,950 --> 00:35:20,470
其实  你被开除了
In fact, you're fired.

850
00:35:20,470 --> 00:35:22,210
不  不能开除他
No, he's not.

851
00:35:22,210 --> 00:35:24,700
这事儿你也想反对我吗
Oh, you going to overrule me on that too?

852
00:35:24,720 --> 00:35:25,830
你可以走了
You can go.

853
00:35:31,770 --> 00:35:34,380
我没有在别的事情上反对过你
I didn't overrule you on the other.

854
00:35:34,490 --> 00:35:36,250
我光明正大地打败了你
I beat you fair and square.

855
00:35:36,260 --> 00:35:38,810
-不  你没有  -你说得对
- No, you didn't. - You're right.

856
00:35:38,810 --> 00:35:41,480
我撒谎了  跟你一样
I cheated, like you.

857
00:35:42,560 --> 00:35:43,830
你跳到了另一边
You jumped to the other side.

858
00:35:43,830 --> 00:35:46,280
是你把我逼上了另一边
You put me on the other side.

859
00:35:46,460 --> 00:35:48,110
我本打算
I had a deal

860
00:35:48,210 --> 00:35:51,420
把你的名字放在我旁边
that put your name right next to mine.

861
00:35:51,660 --> 00:35:52,990
还没印上去呢
And it wasn't even up there yet,

862
00:35:52,990 --> 00:35:55,000
你就表现得像是印在我的名字上头了
and you started acting like it was on top of mine.

863
00:35:55,000 --> 00:35:57,440
-为了保护你  -扯淡
- To protect you. - Bullshit.

864
00:35:57,440 --> 00:35:58,660
这不是在保护我
This wasn't about protecting me.

865
00:35:58,660 --> 00:35:59,980
而是在提升你自己
This was about advancing you.

866
00:35:59,980 --> 00:36:01,590
这才是这一切的重点
That's what this whole thing is about.

867
00:36:01,590 --> 00:36:02,490
什么
What?

868
00:36:02,490 --> 00:36:04,440
哈德曼说的  我觉得不是真的
Hardman said it. I didn't think it was true.

869
00:36:04,440 --> 00:36:06,190
他说你不信任我
He said you don't trust me.

870
00:36:06,470 --> 00:36:09,340
意思是你很害怕我
He meant you're afraid of me.

871
00:36:09,660 --> 00:36:11,010
害怕你
Afraid of you?

872
00:36:12,850 --> 00:36:15,580
天哪  我刚刚把你收拾得屁滚尿流
Boy, I just kicked your ass.

873
00:36:15,580 --> 00:36:17,210
你不只是想要而已
And you didn't just want it.

874
00:36:17,240 --> 00:36:19,520
你求我这样做
You begged me for it.

875
00:36:20,090 --> 00:36:23,090
所以你得待在这里
So now you're going to stay here,

876
00:36:23,960 --> 00:36:25,550
要谦虚
be humble,

877
00:36:26,190 --> 00:36:28,180
好好想想你的位置
and learn your goddamn place.

878
00:37:17,070 --> 00:37:18,790
你可以直接告诉我你不爱我
You could have just told me that you didn't love me

879
00:37:18,790 --> 00:37:20,460
而不是出卖我
instead of selling me out.

880
00:37:20,830 --> 00:37:22,300
我没有出卖你  斯科特
I didn't sell you out, Scottie.

881
00:37:22,300 --> 00:37:23,740
一定有人出卖我
Well, somebody did

882
00:37:23,920 --> 00:37:25,740
因为达比发现了我给迈克的东西
because Darby found out what I gave Mike,

883
00:37:25,740 --> 00:37:27,860
我刚刚被炒了
and I just got fired.

884
00:37:29,000 --> 00:37:30,220
不是我
It wasn't me.

885
00:37:33,710 --> 00:37:35,190
你还真会安慰人
At least there's that.

886
00:37:37,630 --> 00:37:38,940
再见  哈维
Good-bye, Harvey.

887
00:37:51,180 --> 00:37:53,230
后来我们就举杯庆祝
And then we just toasted to it,

888
00:37:53,630 --> 00:37:55,970
两个走狗相互敬酒
one hatchet man to the other.

889
00:37:57,360 --> 00:37:58,280
路易
Wow, Louis.

890
00:37:58,280 --> 00:38:01,590
这是我听过最甜美的故事
That's the sweetest story I've ever heard.

891
00:38:03,260 --> 00:38:05,350
-我失信了  -什么
- I broke my word. - What?

892
00:38:05,360 --> 00:38:06,890
我把他放到名单上  后来交了
I put him on the list, and I handed it in.

893
00:38:06,890 --> 00:38:08,090
你怎么能这样
How could you do that?

894
00:38:08,090 --> 00:38:10,090
我发现我不能这样对我的名单
I realized I couldn't do that to my list.

895
00:38:10,090 --> 00:38:11,210
我不能一个人生活
I wouldn't be able to live with myself,

896
00:38:11,210 --> 00:38:13,420
也就是说他也不能
which means he couldn't either.

897
00:38:13,620 --> 00:38:15,400
他没把你放在他的名单上
He didn't put you on his list.

898
00:38:20,770 --> 00:38:21,790
我必须采取行动
I have to do something.

899
00:38:21,790 --> 00:38:23,550
不可能了  太迟了
You can't. It's too late.

900
00:38:23,580 --> 00:38:24,720
不是那事儿
Not that.

901
00:38:26,720 --> 00:38:28,260
我不可能当奈杰尔的好朋友
I couldn't be a good friend to Nigel,

902
00:38:28,260 --> 00:38:30,170
但我本可以当瑞秋的好朋友  但我没有
but I could've been a good friend to Rachel, and I wasn't.

903
00:38:30,170 --> 00:38:31,130
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?

904
00:38:31,130 --> 00:38:33,180
我错过了告诉她一件事的最后期限
I missed the deadline to tell her something,

905
00:38:33,680 --> 00:38:35,500
但我还有机会修正
But I can still try to make it right.

906
00:38:38,380 --> 00:38:40,850
我是个信守承诺的人
I'm a man of my word.

907
00:38:40,870 --> 00:38:42,680
承诺什么
And what word is that?

908
00:38:43,430 --> 00:38:45,770
我来正式欢迎地张开双臂
I'm here to officially welcome you to the firm

909
00:38:45,770 --> 00:38:46,990
欢迎加入公司
with open arms.

910
00:38:46,990 --> 00:38:48,580
我不太习惯拥抱
I'm not much of a hugger.

911
00:38:48,580 --> 00:38:49,590
很好
Good.

912
00:38:58,140 --> 00:39:00,590
还有一件事  杰西卡错了
One more thing-- Jessica was wrong.

913
00:39:00,590 --> 00:39:02,380
斯科特什么都没给我
Scottie didn't give me anything.

914
00:39:02,380 --> 00:39:03,270
我自己拿的
I took it.

915
00:39:03,270 --> 00:39:05,720
-你要我做什么  -把她雇回来
- What would you have me do? - Give her her job back.

916
00:39:05,770 --> 00:39:07,670
我凭什么要这样做
What reason would I have to do that?

917
00:39:07,670 --> 00:39:09,010
无论她做了什么
Whatever she did,

918
00:39:09,160 --> 00:39:11,020
没有她也不会有这次合并
you wouldn't have this merger without her.

919
00:39:12,290 --> 00:39:13,440
非常公平
Fair enough.

920
00:39:14,140 --> 00:39:17,120
你要让她在这里还是在伦敦工作
Would you have her work here or in London?

921
00:39:30,420 --> 00:39:32,440
瑞秋  听着  很抱歉  但我不
Rachel, look, I'm sorry, but I am not--

922
00:39:32,440 --> 00:39:33,940
你什么时候寄的信
When did you send that letter?

923
00:39:35,590 --> 00:39:37,000
我在
Um, I was, uh--

924
00:39:37,000 --> 00:39:39,010
我来告诉你  你没寄  
I'll tell you when-- never.

925
00:39:39,670 --> 00:39:41,430
听着  让我解释
Okay, look, let me explain.

926
00:39:42,450 --> 00:39:43,940
我去见路易的时候
When I went to see Louis,

927
00:39:43,940 --> 00:39:45,070
他告诉了我事实真相
he told me what really happened--

928
00:39:45,070 --> 00:39:47,300
我知道  他也跟我说了
I know. He told me too.

929
00:39:47,300 --> 00:39:49,050
我明白了  我不够好
And I get it. I'm not good enough.

930
00:39:49,050 --> 00:39:51,130
我不明白的是  迈克  你为什么
What I don't get, Mike, is why you didn't have the courage

931
00:39:51,130 --> 00:39:52,570
没有勇气自己来告诉我
to just come and tell me that yourself.

932
00:39:52,570 --> 00:39:53,680
听着  他欺骗了你
Look, he lied to you.

933
00:39:53,680 --> 00:39:56,510
我认为他有权自己来告诉你  好吗
I thought he deserved a chance to tell you himself, all right?

934
00:39:56,510 --> 00:39:58,500
我去他的办公室让他签这个时
When I went to his office to get him to sign the letter--

935
00:39:58,500 --> 00:39:59,780
等等
Wait.

936
00:40:00,130 --> 00:40:01,900
你让他签
You went to him to sign the letter?

937
00:40:02,970 --> 00:40:04,890
你说你会签这封信的
You told me you were going to sign the letter.

938
00:40:04,890 --> 00:40:06,310
-不是  -不  所以你也骗了我
- No-- - No, so you lied to me.

939
00:40:06,310 --> 00:40:08,280
不  我没有  我跟你说我会帮你
No, I didn't. I told you that I would help you.

940
00:40:08,280 --> 00:40:09,770
简直是扯淡
That is such bullshit!

941
00:40:09,770 --> 00:40:11,500
这不是你的本意  你知道
That's not what you meant, and you know it.

942
00:40:11,500 --> 00:40:12,640
你对我有戒心
You've been cagey with me

943
00:40:12,640 --> 00:40:14,070
从我找你签这封信的那一刻起
Since the second I came to you about the letter,

944
00:40:14,070 --> 00:40:15,430
你到现在都还对我有戒心
and you're being cagey with me right now.

945
00:40:15,430 --> 00:40:16,620
你就是这样  欺骗了我
You are. You're lying to me.

946
00:40:16,620 --> 00:40:17,730
今天不行  瑞秋
Not today, Rachel.

947
00:40:17,730 --> 00:40:18,750
-快别这样  -哪一天才合适  迈克
- Please, stop. - Then what day, Mike?

948
00:40:18,750 --> 00:40:19,760
因为总有些事
Because it's always something.

949
00:40:19,770 --> 00:40:23,080
总有些秘密  故事或者谎言
It is always some secret or some story or some lie--

950
00:40:23,080 --> 00:40:24,770
-你不理解  -我不理解什么
- You don't understand-- - I don't understand what?

951
00:40:24,770 --> 00:40:26,680
你不理解我所经历的一切
You don't understand what I have been through!

952
00:40:26,680 --> 00:40:29,200
你不理解我所失去的一切
You don't understand what I have lost!

953
00:40:29,480 --> 00:40:32,390
因为我爱的一切人和事
Because it's everything, everyone that I love--

954
00:40:32,390 --> 00:40:34,160
特雷弗  我奶奶  哈维
Trevor, my grandmother, Harvey,

955
00:40:34,160 --> 00:40:35,640
现在又是这份工作
Now, probably this job!

956
00:40:35,640 --> 00:40:38,390
我不想失去你
I am not ready to lose you...

957
00:40:41,700 --> 00:40:43,010
今天不行
Not today!

958
00:40:44,370 --> 00:40:45,610
那就告诉我
Then tell me.

959
00:40:59,480 --> 00:41:01,120
我从没上过哈佛
I never went to Harvard.

960
00:41:06,650 --> 00:41:07,960
什么
What?

961
00:41:09,190 --> 00:41:10,480
我是个冒牌货
I'm a fraud.

962
00:41:14,940 --> 00:41:16,270
瑞秋  我
Rachel, I--

963
00:41:18,730 --> 00:41:19,690
瑞秋
Rachel--

