1
00:05:14,310 --> 00:05:19,310
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:05:14,310 --> 00:05:19,310
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:05:14,310 --> 00:05:19,310
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:05:14,310 --> 00:05:19,310
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:05:14,310 --> 00:05:19,310
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:05:19,310 --> 00:05:24,310
{\an8}翻译：草草  潇湘月影  杳杳君  王大可  香茗小焙  七个柚子酱   

7
00:05:24,310 --> 00:05:29,310
{\an8}翻译：CiciXT   鱼小姐啦   CS漫画家小明   校对：油炸电风扇    潇湘月影

8
00:05:29,310 --> 00:05:34,310
{\an8}时间轴：凭陵新月   今    猫   小式

9
00:05:34,310 --> 00:05:39,310
{\an8}后期：斯人&加森      总监&精校：某羽

10
00:05:40,130 --> 00:05:42,260
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

11
00:05:40,130 --> 00:05:42,260
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第三集

12
00:00:00,930 --> 00:00:02,800
{\pos(189,213)}《诉讼双雄》前情提要

13
00:00:02,880 --> 00:00:04,960
你不介意我跟洛根在收购项目上合作吗
You're good with me working on the takeover with Logan?

14
00:00:04,960 --> 00:00:09,100
只要我们不让公事影响到私事
As long as we don't let that affect this...

15
00:00:09,100 --> 00:00:10,160
不会的
We won't.

16
00:00:10,160 --> 00:00:11,660
我确实要风得风  要雨得雨
I do always get what I want.

17
00:00:11,660 --> 00:00:14,840
而对这个公司  我就想把它拆散
And what I wanna do with this company is strip it down,

18
00:00:14,850 --> 00:00:16,170
-翻个底朝天  -好了  别说了
- flip it over-- - Okay, that's enough.

19
00:00:16,170 --> 00:00:17,100
到此为止
We're done.

20
00:00:17,100 --> 00:00:18,280
是的
You're right.

21
00:00:18,780 --> 00:00:19,460
到此为止
We are.

22
00:00:19,460 --> 00:00:20,910
我说我们的关系
When I told you that our relationship

23
00:00:20,910 --> 00:00:23,190
仅限于工作  我是认真的
is now purely professional, I was serious.

24
00:00:23,190 --> 00:00:25,350
午餐怎么不是限于工作了
What's not purely professional about lunch?

25
00:00:25,350 --> 00:00:27,620
除非你说的是饭后的亲热
Unless you mean the sex that will be following lunch?

26
00:00:27,620 --> 00:00:28,360
菲利普
Phillip.

27
00:00:28,370 --> 00:00:29,350
你儿子
Your son.

28
00:00:29,390 --> 00:00:29,980
你失去了他
You lost him,

29
00:00:29,990 --> 00:00:32,400
所以这家公司对你就意味着
and that's what this company is to you now--

30
00:00:32,400 --> 00:00:33,180
你的家人
your family.

31
00:00:33,180 --> 00:00:35,720
我十一岁的时候失去了双亲
I lost both of my parents when I was 11 years old,

32
00:00:35,720 --> 00:00:38,360
所以我明白需要亲人的感觉
so I know a little something about needing family.

33
00:00:38,360 --> 00:00:41,560
什么时候证监会开始通过盯上客户
Since when does the S.E.C. go around intimidating law firms

34
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:43,150
来威胁律所了
by going after their clients?

35
00:00:43,150 --> 00:00:44,140
现在还没有  但等下周
They don't, but they will

36
00:00:44,140 --> 00:00:46,560
埃里克·伍德尔上任就会了
when Eric Woodall starts there next week.

37
00:00:56,790 --> 00:00:58,090
又熬通宵了吗
Another all-nighter?

38
00:00:58,190 --> 00:00:59,230
是啊
Yeah.

39
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:01,330
为了工作还是学习
Work or school?

40
00:01:01,330 --> 00:01:02,300
工作
Work.

41
00:01:02,300 --> 00:01:03,800
工作内容是什么
What were you working on?

42
00:01:04,590 --> 00:01:06,550
明知故问
You know what I was working on.

43
00:01:06,550 --> 00:01:08,930
对不起  但我真的好累
I am so sorry, but I'm so tired.

44
00:01:08,930 --> 00:01:11,290
我得去睡一觉  然后去上班
I have to go get some sleep before I go back to the office.

45
00:01:11,290 --> 00:01:12,980
我都两天没见着你了
I haven't seen you in two days.

46
00:01:12,980 --> 00:01:14,550
给我五分钟嘛
Give me five minutes.

47
00:01:14,550 --> 00:01:19,180
好吧  但我现在说话不过脑子
Okay, but I can't be responsible for anything that I say.

48
00:01:19,550 --> 00:01:21,460
这样的话
Well, okay, in that case,

49
00:01:21,460 --> 00:01:23,240
洛根又要去找别的董事会成员了吗
is Logan going after another board member?

50
00:01:23,240 --> 00:01:24,230
想得美
Nice try.

51
00:01:24,230 --> 00:01:25,630
他要没钱了吗
Mm, is he running out of cash?

52
00:01:25,630 --> 00:01:27,440
我不能说
I can't tell you that.

53
00:01:27,440 --> 00:01:28,860
你爱过他吗
Did you love him?

54
00:01:30,840 --> 00:01:33,000
这问题你等了多久了
How long have you been waiting to ask me that?

55
00:01:33,940 --> 00:01:36,030
等到你最虚弱
You know, just when you were at your weakest

56
00:01:36,030 --> 00:01:37,580
最不防备的时候
and most vulnerable.

57
00:01:39,990 --> 00:01:43,770
我爱过他  但现在不了
I did love him, but I don't love him now.

58
00:01:43,770 --> 00:01:45,550
我爱着你
I love you.

59
00:01:47,340 --> 00:01:48,670
谁提出分手的
Who ended it?

60
00:01:49,410 --> 00:01:51,830
-这重要吗  -对我重要
- Does that matter? - It does to me.

61
00:01:54,850 --> 00:01:56,270
是我
I ended it.

62
00:01:56,350 --> 00:01:58,180
你还有其他讨厌的问题吗
Now, do you have any other burning questions,

63
00:01:58,180 --> 00:02:01,300
我能去睡了吗
or can I go to sleep, please?

64
00:02:01,300 --> 00:02:02,950
我想想
Um, let me see.

65
00:02:02,950 --> 00:02:05,350
你偷过的最贵的东西是什么
What's the most expensive thing you ever shoplifted?

66
00:02:05,350 --> 00:02:06,930
你以前是不是个小坏丫头
Were you a mean girl?

67
00:02:06,930 --> 00:02:09,760
你想去学钢管舞吗
Are you interested in taking a pole dancing class?

68
00:02:09,760 --> 00:02:11,470
我们回头再说吧
You know what? We'll get into that later.

69
00:02:11,590 --> 00:02:13,090
好梦
Sweet dreams.

70
00:02:14,480 --> 00:02:15,620
别老说你了
God, enough about you.

71
00:02:15,620 --> 00:02:16,930
我想说说我的事呢
I want to talk about me.

72
00:02:16,930 --> 00:02:18,580
我们才聊过你的事
We were just talking about you.

73
00:02:18,580 --> 00:02:19,880
聊得不够
Not enough.

74
00:02:21,130 --> 00:02:22,960
好吧  我们谈哈维吧
All right, fine. Let's talk about Harvey.

75
00:02:23,510 --> 00:02:25,150
猜猜他在做什么呢
So guess what he's been up to.

76
00:02:25,170 --> 00:02:26,150
什么
What?

77
00:02:26,390 --> 00:02:29,800
他找到他父亲个人专辑的母带了
He found the master tapes for his father's solo album.

78
00:02:30,330 --> 00:02:31,880
在想办法买下来呢
He's working on buying them.

79
00:02:32,920 --> 00:02:35,540
自从父亲去世后他一直在到处找
He's been trying to find them ever since he lost his father.

80
00:02:36,880 --> 00:02:39,030
我知道你为什么要说这个了
Oh, I see why you're telling me this.

81
00:02:39,420 --> 00:02:40,870
你想塑造哈维的温情形象
You're trying to humanize Harvey,

82
00:02:40,870 --> 00:02:44,370
因为你担心这场争斗会让我们翻脸
because you're afraid of what this fight is gonna do to us.

83
00:02:44,370 --> 00:02:46,740
我担心是因为这已经让你变了个人
I'm afraid because of what it's already doing to you.

84
00:02:46,740 --> 00:02:48,520
简直像阿里和弗雷泽
I'm talking Ali-Frazier.

85
00:02:48,520 --> 00:02:49,290
得了  唐娜
Come on, Donna.

86
00:02:49,290 --> 00:02:50,280
听我说
Listen to me.

87
00:02:51,350 --> 00:02:52,550
他们起初像兄弟一样
They started out like brothers.

88
00:02:52,560 --> 00:02:54,480
之后三次对决
Then they went toe-to-toe three times,

89
00:02:54,480 --> 00:02:58,050
乔·弗雷泽直到死都恨默罕默德·阿里
and Joe Frazier went to his grave hating Muhammad Ali.

90
00:02:58,150 --> 00:03:00,150
我还不知道你还是个拳击迷
I didn't know you were a boxing fan.

91
00:03:00,150 --> 00:03:01,720
我是个哈维迷
I'm a Harvey fan.

92
00:03:02,180 --> 00:03:06,590
我也是  所以我要全力以赴
So am I, and that's why I'm giving him my best.

93
00:03:08,440 --> 00:03:10,940
-谢谢请我喝咖啡  -不客气
- Thanks for the coffee. - You're welcome.

94
00:03:17,170 --> 00:03:18,450
你来迟了
You're in late.

95
00:03:18,450 --> 00:03:19,510
昨天睡晚了
I was up late.

96
00:03:19,510 --> 00:03:21,030
在忙我的事吗
Working on my stuff?

97
00:03:21,550 --> 00:03:23,690
忙的事多着呢
Working on a lot of stuff.

98
00:03:24,330 --> 00:03:25,330
有什么事吗
What can I help you with?

99
00:03:25,330 --> 00:03:27,160
我想跟你谈谈
I wanted to talk to you.

100
00:03:27,360 --> 00:03:28,420
什么事
About?

101
00:03:29,220 --> 00:03:32,440
我之前跟你说过
Well, when I told you before that I'm not the same guy

102
00:03:32,450 --> 00:03:35,220
我不是从前那种人了
that I used to be, what I meant was,

103
00:03:35,610 --> 00:03:37,750
是说我当时是被感情冲昏头脑
I got caught up in emotion back then.

104
00:03:37,850 --> 00:03:39,970
但以后不会了
I'm not caught up in emotion anymore.

105
00:03:40,530 --> 00:03:41,390
所以呢
And?

106
00:03:41,390 --> 00:03:45,700
所以我要做些很算计的事
And that means that I'm gonna have to do some calculated things,

107
00:03:45,700 --> 00:03:47,960
我需要确定你不会介意
and I needed to know that you're okay with that.

108
00:03:48,400 --> 00:03:49,790
我为什么会介意呢
Why wouldn't I be?

109
00:03:50,650 --> 00:03:51,730
你知道的
You know why.

110
00:03:51,730 --> 00:03:52,920
洛根  你不用专程跑来
Logan, you don't have to come and have

111
00:03:52,920 --> 00:03:54,640
跟我"谈心"
these little check-in talks with me.

112
00:03:54,640 --> 00:03:57,560
我不是小孩子了  我了解这种事
I am a big girl, and I know how these things work.

113
00:03:57,560 --> 00:04:01,880
做你该做的  别操心我了
So just do what you have to do, and stop worrying about me.

114
00:04:03,030 --> 00:04:03,990
好啊
Great.

115
00:04:09,960 --> 00:04:12,000
哈维  到底怎么回事
Harvey, what the hell's going on?

116
00:04:12,010 --> 00:04:13,800
再过十八分钟
At the moment, I'm 18 minutes away

117
00:04:13,800 --> 00:04:16,340
我就能得到史蒂夫·麦奎因的眼镜蛇跑车了
from owning Steve McQueen's Shelby Cobra.

118
00:04:17,220 --> 00:04:18,490
你很清楚我指的是什么
You know what I'm talking about.

119
00:04:18,490 --> 00:04:19,750
我们上次见面时
Last time I saw you, 

120
00:04:19,750 --> 00:04:21,190
你说你能拿下公司
you told me you were gonna get me this company.

121
00:04:21,190 --> 00:04:23,970
我刚刚得知沃尔特·吉利斯资助了他的养老金
I just found out Walter Gillis funded his pension.

122
00:04:23,980 --> 00:04:25,490
你觉得他们不会反击吗
Did you think they wouldn't fight back?

123
00:04:25,490 --> 00:04:27,020
我预计是他们会反击
I expected them to fight.

124
00:04:27,020 --> 00:04:28,860
但现在是我们被收拾得屁滚尿流了
Right now, we're getting our ass kicked.

125
00:04:28,860 --> 00:04:30,640
你这比分是哪里看到的
Well, what scorecard are you looking at,

126
00:04:30,640 --> 00:04:33,490
他们仅仅为了能够继续参战
because we just got them to give up half their war chest

127
00:04:33,490 --> 00:04:34,650
就放弃了一半的战争基金
just to stay in the fight.

128
00:04:34,650 --> 00:04:36,510
我不在乎比分
I don't give a shit what the scorecard says.

129
00:04:36,510 --> 00:04:37,250
我要让他们出局
I want a knockout.

130
00:04:37,250 --> 00:04:38,410
但事情的走向一般不是那样的
Well, it doesn't work that way.

131
00:04:38,410 --> 00:04:39,680
你肯下狠手就可以
It can if you hit them below the belt.

132
00:04:39,680 --> 00:04:41,400
-洛根  -省省吧
- Logan-- - Save it.

133
00:04:41,570 --> 00:04:43,310
我父亲当年和卡尔·艾康对峙时
When my father went up against Carl Icahn,

134
00:04:43,310 --> 00:04:44,850
他说你就静静等到他放松警惕
he said that you waited till he wasn't looking,

135
00:04:44,850 --> 00:04:47,630
然后走到他身后  从背后给他一击
you walked up behind him, and you shot him in the back.

136
00:04:47,630 --> 00:04:50,530
沃尔特·吉利斯不是卡尔·艾康
Walter Gillis isn't Carl Icahn.

137
00:04:50,620 --> 00:04:52,560
我说的不是沃尔特·吉利斯
I'm not talking about Walter Gillis.

138
00:04:52,560 --> 00:04:54,090
是迈克·罗斯
I'm talking about Mike Ross.

139
00:04:54,090 --> 00:04:55,840
我不在乎你说的是谁
I don't care who you're talking about.

140
00:04:55,840 --> 00:04:58,500
艾康的案子和现在完全是两种情况
That Icahn deal was completely different.

141
00:04:58,600 --> 00:05:01,950
在我看来唯一的不同就是
The only difference I see is that this deal

142
00:05:01,950 --> 00:05:04,010
我们面对的是你的干儿子
is against your surrogate son.

143
00:05:04,100 --> 00:05:08,720
你到底想不想做
So are you willing to do this or not?

144
00:05:10,070 --> 00:05:11,810
你想玩狠的
You want below the belt?

145
00:05:11,810 --> 00:05:13,550
我就出狠招让你看看
I'll give you below the belt.

146
00:05:54,900 --> 00:05:56,780
路易  这问题已经讨论清楚了
Louis, we talked about this.

147
00:05:57,360 --> 00:06:00,590
看他在我的旧办公室里感觉怪怪的
It's just so weird to see him in my old office, you know?

148
00:06:00,930 --> 00:06:03,690
就像是你开车经过你从小长大的那座房子
It's like when you drive by the house you grew up in,

149
00:06:03,690 --> 00:06:05,070
看到另一个家庭住在里面
and there's another family in there,

150
00:06:05,070 --> 00:06:07,030
就满脑子只想冲进去给自己炖个汤
and all you want to do is break in and make yourself soup.

151
00:06:07,030 --> 00:06:08,280
你懂那种感觉吗
You know that feeling?

152
00:06:08,280 --> 00:06:09,580
那要看是什么汤
Well, it depends on the soup.

153
00:06:09,580 --> 00:06:11,480
-蘑菇大麦汤  -那就不懂了
- Mushroom barley. - Then no.

154
00:06:12,020 --> 00:06:13,310
我让你给他准备的道歉礼物
Hey, did you get him that apology gift

155
00:06:13,310 --> 00:06:14,370
你准备了吗
I told you to get him?

156
00:06:14,370 --> 00:06:15,180
我没准备威士忌
Except instead of scotch, 

157
00:06:15,180 --> 00:06:17,330
但买了两张芭蕾舞头排票
I got us two front-row tickets to the ballet.

158
00:06:19,230 --> 00:06:21,150
总之  有心是最重要的
Well, it's the thought that counts.

159
00:06:22,430 --> 00:06:24,260
路易  有事需要我帮忙吗
Louis, can I help you with something?

160
00:06:24,260 --> 00:06:25,270
是的
Yes.

161
00:06:25,570 --> 00:06:29,250
你和我  初见时有些误会
You and me, we got off on the wrong foot.

162
00:06:29,520 --> 00:06:32,990
话已出口  伤已落下
Words were said, hurtful caricatures were drawn,

163
00:06:33,460 --> 00:06:35,350
我也做了些不好的事
and I did some bad things too.

164
00:06:35,350 --> 00:06:36,610
事情已经过去了  路易
Water under the bridge, Louis.

165
00:06:36,610 --> 00:06:37,930
不  对我来说不是
Well, no, not to me.

166
00:06:38,140 --> 00:06:42,650
曾经有人对我说过  行动是会有后果的
See, um, I once was told that actions have consequences,

167
00:06:42,650 --> 00:06:46,340
我想通过邀请你去美国芭蕾舞团
and I want to turn things around by inviting you...

168
00:06:47,990 --> 00:06:50,770
制作的《吉赛尔》来改变这一现状
to the American Ballet Company's production of Giselle.

169
00:06:52,200 --> 00:06:52,900
芭蕾舞
The ballet?

170
00:06:52,900 --> 00:06:54,650
咱们俩  今晚
Yeah, you and me tonight.

171
00:06:56,230 --> 00:06:58,570
路易  我很愿意和你去看芭蕾
Louis, I would love to go to the ballet with you.

172
00:06:58,570 --> 00:07:01,630
我真的愿意  但我今晚要看尼克斯的比赛
I really would, but I have Knicks tickets tonight, man,

173
00:07:01,630 --> 00:07:03,360
我一场都不落
and I never miss a game.

174
00:07:03,360 --> 00:07:05,140
好吧  放弃《吉赛尔》选择篮球
All right, I'm gonna let it go that 

175
00:07:05,140 --> 00:07:06,440
我就不计较了  
you're choosing basketball over Giselle, 

176
00:07:06,440 --> 00:07:07,870
但我真的想补偿你  杰夫
but I really need to make this up to you, Jeff.

177
00:07:07,870 --> 00:07:09,130
我的人生报表上不能出现红字[未完成]
I can't be in the red.

178
00:07:09,130 --> 00:07:11,700
要永远  永远都是黑色的[已完成]
I am always, always in the black,

179
00:07:11,700 --> 00:07:13,700
我没有种族歧视的意思
and I don't mean that in a racial sense.

180
00:07:14,130 --> 00:07:17,310
既然你这么说了  我确实需要一些建议
Well, now that you mention it, I could really use some advice.

181
00:07:19,090 --> 00:07:20,400
关于案子的吗
About a case?

182
00:07:20,400 --> 00:07:21,620
关于杰西卡
About Jessica.

183
00:07:21,620 --> 00:07:23,950
我这次遇上了亚当·格里夫斯作对方律师
I just pulled Adam Grieves as opposing counsel.

184
00:07:23,950 --> 00:07:25,930
长话短说就是  他非常恨我
And long story short, he hates me,

185
00:07:25,930 --> 00:07:28,340
我真的需要杰西卡出面干预一下
and I could really use Jessica's help to run some interference,

186
00:07:28,340 --> 00:07:32,330
但我是新来的  这只是第二个案子
but I'm the new guy, it's only my second case,

187
00:07:32,570 --> 00:07:33,820
我不知道该怎么做了
and I don't know what to do.

188
00:07:34,600 --> 00:07:36,190
我来告诉你我会怎么做
Well, I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.

189
00:07:36,390 --> 00:07:37,680
我会给你找几张杰西卡·皮尔逊帮助会的
I'm gonna get you front-row tickets

190
00:07:37,680 --> 00:07:39,380
头排门票
to Jessica Pearson's help.

191
00:07:44,230 --> 00:07:45,840
哈维  你不会只是让我来
Okay, Harvey, you didn't bring me here to make me

192
00:07:45,840 --> 00:07:47,510
吃洋白菜的吧
choke down these Brussels sprouts.

193
00:07:47,510 --> 00:07:49,470
不  我不是  但你总要
No, I didn't, but you are going to have

194
00:07:49,470 --> 00:07:51,480
吃点东西
to choke down something else.

195
00:07:51,830 --> 00:07:53,940
我猜猜  是关于沃尔特·吉利斯的事
Let me guess. This is about Walter Gillis.

196
00:07:53,940 --> 00:07:55,050
不  不是关于沃尔特
No, it's not about Walter.

197
00:07:55,050 --> 00:07:56,500
是关于你马上要停止
It's about the line of credit

198
00:07:56,500 --> 00:07:58,040
提供给他们的授信额度的事
that you're about to stop giving him.

199
00:07:58,040 --> 00:07:59,740
但我为什么要那么做呢
And why on earth would I do that?

200
00:07:59,740 --> 00:08:01,970
因为如果你拒绝  我有预感
Because if you don't, I have a feeling

201
00:08:01,970 --> 00:08:03,840
所有现在正与你合作的
that every Pearson Specter client

202
00:08:03,840 --> 00:08:05,840
皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所客户
that you currently do business with,

203
00:08:05,880 --> 00:08:08,400
会突然将他们的账户转去摩根大通
suddenly gonna move their accounts to Chase.

204
00:08:08,400 --> 00:08:10,650
你真的那么想把他的公司搞垮吗
You really want to cripple his company that badly?

205
00:08:10,650 --> 00:08:12,130
他的公司已经垮了
His company's already dead.

206
00:08:12,130 --> 00:08:13,350
他只是还不知道而已
He just doesn't know it yet.

207
00:08:13,350 --> 00:08:15,580
但这也不证明你就有资格威胁我
That doesn't give you the right to threaten me.

208
00:08:15,590 --> 00:08:18,180
如果我是在威胁你  我会直说的
If I were threatening you, I'd come right out and say it.

209
00:08:18,180 --> 00:08:20,210
如果你不这么做  明早
If you don't do this, tomorrow morning,

210
00:08:20,210 --> 00:08:23,460
你会损失二十亿美元的存款
you lose $2 billion worth of deposits.

211
00:08:23,490 --> 00:08:24,850
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch.

212
00:08:24,850 --> 00:08:26,460
他确实是
That he is.

213
00:08:26,610 --> 00:08:28,780
-迈克  你来干什么  -干嘛这么问
- What are you doing here, Mike? - What do you mean?

214
00:08:28,780 --> 00:08:30,960
我是来吃洋白菜的
I just came for the Brussels sprouts.

215
00:08:30,960 --> 00:08:32,720
你知道我是怎么知道这家的球芽甘蓝很棒的吗
You know how I know how good they are?

216
00:08:32,720 --> 00:08:33,630
怎么知道的
How?

217
00:08:33,630 --> 00:08:35,080
因为这里就是哈维常带银行家来
Because this is where Harvey brings bankers

218
00:08:35,080 --> 00:08:37,040
然后胁迫他们  欺负他们的地方
to strong-arm them into doing some bullshit.

219
00:08:37,040 --> 00:08:39,100
-别听他的  -不  他应该听我的
- Don't listen to him. - No, he should listen to me.

220
00:08:39,100 --> 00:08:40,800
我是沃尔特·吉利斯的合伙人
I'm Walter Gillis' partner, 

221
00:08:40,810 --> 00:08:41,980
这顿午餐之后的两个月内
and if he cuts off our funding

222
00:08:41,980 --> 00:08:44,500
如果他掐断资金
at any point in the next two months following this lunch,

223
00:08:44,500 --> 00:08:46,460
你再谈起洋白菜
then the next time you're talking about

224
00:08:46,460 --> 00:08:49,830
就是在大陪审团面前了
these brussels sprouts will be in front of a grand jury.

225
00:08:51,610 --> 00:08:54,180
弗农  这不是针对你
Oh, Vernon, don't take it personally.

226
00:08:54,180 --> 00:08:55,900
他对利兹的人也干过
He did the same thing to the guy from Leeds

227
00:08:55,900 --> 00:08:58,390
也是这张桌子  七个月之前
at the exact same table seven months ago.

228
00:09:09,170 --> 00:09:11,390
路易  我看到你的备忘录了
Louis, I got your memo,

229
00:09:11,660 --> 00:09:13,520
如果你想为自己的新办公室
and if you want to get an antique diving bell

230
00:09:13,520 --> 00:09:16,350
添置古董潜水钟  得自己掏钱
for your new office, it's on your dime.

231
00:09:17,580 --> 00:09:19,480
那可没门儿  先别管它
Okay, that's bullshit, but whatever.

232
00:09:19,550 --> 00:09:20,930
我是想谈谈杰夫·马龙
I'm here about Jeff Malone.

233
00:09:20,930 --> 00:09:21,830
我又不是校长
I am not the principal.

234
00:09:21,830 --> 00:09:24,320
你们自己去操场上追跑打闹吧
You two are gonna have to work your shit out on the playground.

235
00:09:24,670 --> 00:09:26,300
但你知道  就是这事
But you see, that's just it.

236
00:09:26,410 --> 00:09:27,600
我们已经谈过了
We already did.

237
00:09:28,660 --> 00:09:30,080
有蹊跷
Something's not right.

238
00:09:30,890 --> 00:09:31,790
你想说什么
Why are you here?

239
00:09:31,790 --> 00:09:34,120
我想说  你得做一下掩护阻挡[橄榄球术语]
I'm here because you need to run interference.

240
00:09:34,120 --> 00:09:35,950
你不是说已经解决了吗
I thought you just said you worked it out.

241
00:09:35,950 --> 00:09:38,370
不是对我  是对证监会的亚当·格里夫斯
No, not with me, with Adam Grieves at the S.E.C.

242
00:09:38,370 --> 00:09:39,670
他跟马龙有过节
He has it in for Malone.

243
00:09:39,670 --> 00:09:42,220
路易  我很高兴从现在起
Louis, I'm glad you two are going to be

244
00:09:42,220 --> 00:09:44,260
你和马龙就要成为一起上学的好朋友了
walking to school together from now on,

245
00:09:44,620 --> 00:09:48,060
但是我雇杰夫·马龙来处理证监会的事
but I hired Jeff Malone to handle the S.E.C.,

246
00:09:48,060 --> 00:09:50,540
不是我要为他处理这事
not to get me to handle them for him.

247
00:09:53,190 --> 00:09:56,520
你总跟我说不要树敌
You know, you're always telling me not to make enemies,

248
00:09:56,520 --> 00:09:59,720
而哈维之后  这是第一次
and for the first time since Harvey,

249
00:09:59,860 --> 00:10:01,610
我交到一个新朋友
I have just made a new friend,

250
00:10:01,610 --> 00:10:05,780
所以  我请求你
so I'm asking you...

251
00:10:07,650 --> 00:10:09,420
拜托你帮帮我的朋友
please do it for my friend.

252
00:10:09,640 --> 00:10:12,300
-路易  -如果你不想帮他
- Louis-- - If you won't do it for him, 

253
00:10:12,300 --> 00:10:13,630
请帮帮我
please do it for me.

254
00:10:15,990 --> 00:10:18,730
我刚和路易·利特进行了很有意思的谈话
I just had a very interesting chat with Louis Litt.

255
00:10:18,730 --> 00:10:20,970
路易是个很有意思的人
Louis is a very interesting guy.

256
00:10:20,970 --> 00:10:22,740
你知道他从不吃橄榄吗
Did you know he's never eaten an olive?

257
00:10:22,750 --> 00:10:25,610
不知道  但我知道你拿话骗了他
I did not, but I do know you fed him some bullshit.

258
00:10:25,610 --> 00:10:27,020
-我才不是那种人  -是吗
- That doesn't sound like me. - Really?

259
00:10:27,020 --> 00:10:28,610
可他觉得我们俩应该合作
'Cause he thinks we need to work together

260
00:10:28,610 --> 00:10:30,950
因为你和亚当·格里夫斯不合
because there's bad blood between you and Adam Grieves.

261
00:10:30,960 --> 00:10:31,660
我不喜欢谈这个
I don't like to talk about it.

262
00:10:31,660 --> 00:10:33,640
当然  因为你和亚当·格里夫斯
Of course not, because you and Adam Grieves

263
00:10:33,640 --> 00:10:35,850
每周三一起打篮球
play basketball every Wednesday.

264
00:10:36,200 --> 00:10:38,540
法庭上的事  杰西卡  不要带出法庭
What happens on the court, Jessica, stays on the court.

265
00:10:38,540 --> 00:10:41,040
我以为我已经把界限说得很清楚了
And I thought I was clear about boundaries.

266
00:10:42,200 --> 00:10:43,780
如果你真那么想
Well, listen, if that's really how you feel,

267
00:10:43,780 --> 00:10:45,820
为什么不直接告诉路易你不想掺合进来
why don't you just tell Louis that you want to bow out

268
00:10:45,820 --> 00:10:48,140
因为害怕在我身边把持不住自己
because you don't trust yourself around me?

269
00:10:49,870 --> 00:10:52,140
是啊  你还是放不下
Yeah, I didn't think so.

270
00:10:52,740 --> 00:10:54,040
明天见
See you tomorrow.

271
00:11:00,400 --> 00:11:02,120
你的狠招进行得怎么样
What happened to going below the belt?

272
00:11:02,120 --> 00:11:03,350
我去出狠招了
I went below the belt.

273
00:11:03,350 --> 00:11:05,620
可是裁判介入  还托出了大陪审团
The referee stepped in and threw a grand jury at my face.

274
00:11:05,630 --> 00:11:07,420
我可没让你
Well, I wasn't asking you to go below the belt

275
00:11:07,430 --> 00:11:08,100
对他们公司使坏
with the company.

276
00:11:08,100 --> 00:11:10,490
我是让你对罗斯使坏
I was asking you to go below the belt with Ross.

277
00:11:10,490 --> 00:11:11,560
什么意思
What are you talking about?

278
00:11:11,560 --> 00:11:13,340
我是让你雇个私人侦探
I'm saying you hire a private investigator

279
00:11:13,340 --> 00:11:15,120
去挖他的秘密
to find every skeleton in his closet.

280
00:11:15,120 --> 00:11:17,460
让他早上一睁眼  所有报纸头版都是他
He wakes up in the morning, and it's all over the front page.

281
00:11:17,460 --> 00:11:18,730
洛根  那不是使坏
Logan, that's not going below the belt.

282
00:11:18,730 --> 00:11:20,220
那是发疯
That's just nuts.

283
00:11:20,450 --> 00:11:21,810
胡说八道
You're full of shit.

284
00:11:21,880 --> 00:11:23,300
你不愿这么做  是因为
You don't want to do this, because you don't have

285
00:11:23,300 --> 00:11:24,910
你舍不得这么对待他
the stomach to do it to your boy.

286
00:11:24,910 --> 00:11:26,770
不  我不愿这么做  因为我们
No, I don't want to do it, because we're on a path

287
00:11:26,770 --> 00:11:27,860
已经向着胜利前进了
to win this thing, 

288
00:11:27,860 --> 00:11:29,310
我之所以放任你诱导我去使坏
and I let you bait me into doing

289
00:11:29,310 --> 00:11:31,160
是因为我以为
what I already did because I thought you were

290
00:11:31,160 --> 00:11:32,980
你只是没有耐心
just a little impatient.

291
00:11:33,120 --> 00:11:35,740
现在我开始明白到底是怎么回事了
But now I'm starting to realize what it really is.

292
00:11:36,010 --> 00:11:37,120
到底怎么回事
What is that?

293
00:11:37,310 --> 00:11:38,870
现在是谁胡说八道
Who's full of shit now?

294
00:11:39,650 --> 00:11:41,520
跟瑞秋一点关系也没有
This has nothing to do with Rachel.

295
00:11:41,520 --> 00:11:43,550
你脑子还挺快
You got there pretty damn fast.

296
00:11:44,370 --> 00:11:47,640
我让你一击拿下迈克·罗斯
Hey, I asked you to put Mike Ross down with one punch.

297
00:11:47,640 --> 00:11:50,060
你说没问题  但没做到
You said you would, and you didn't.

298
00:11:50,250 --> 00:11:53,430
所以要么按我说的做  要么让我自己来
So either do what I'm asking, or I'll do it myself.

299
00:12:05,530 --> 00:12:07,010
你不能那么干  哈维
You can't do it, Harvey.

300
00:12:07,010 --> 00:12:08,330
我当然能
Yes, I can.

301
00:12:08,470 --> 00:12:09,650
反正洛根总会动手
Logan's gonna do it anyway.

302
00:12:09,660 --> 00:12:11,220
至少让我亲自来吧
At least this way it'll be me.

303
00:12:11,220 --> 00:12:12,690
你雇人去调查迈克和洛根雇人
What's the difference if you hire somebody

304
00:12:12,690 --> 00:12:14,710
有什么本质区别吗
to look into Mike or Logan does?

305
00:12:15,040 --> 00:12:17,140
你很清楚他们会发现他的秘密
You know damn well they're gonna uncover his secret.

306
00:12:17,140 --> 00:12:18,800
我不清楚  你也一样
I don't know that, and you don't either.

307
00:12:18,800 --> 00:12:21,430
-我清楚  -没人发现过他的秘密
- Yeah, I do. - No one's ever found it before.

308
00:12:21,430 --> 00:12:23,070
那是因为你隐瞒的人
Because you were hiding it from people

309
00:12:23,070 --> 00:12:25,930
没有查他老底  现在有人查了
who weren't looking for it, not from people who are.

310
00:12:25,930 --> 00:12:27,750
你想要我怎么做  唐娜
What do you want from me, Donna?

311
00:12:30,410 --> 00:12:32,620
我想让你说服迈克放弃
I want you to get Mike to give up.

312
00:12:32,650 --> 00:12:33,540
我不去劝他
Well, I'm not gonna do that,

313
00:12:33,540 --> 00:12:35,400
我知道他不会放弃的
because I know he's not gonna give up.

314
00:12:35,400 --> 00:12:37,500
-你怎么知道  -我就是知道
- How do you know that? - Because I know.

315
00:12:37,890 --> 00:12:39,300
他可是迈克
This is Mike we're talking about.

316
00:12:39,300 --> 00:12:40,900
换作其他人
If it were anyone other than Mike,

317
00:12:40,900 --> 00:12:43,370
明天我的文章就见报了
I'd have an article in the journal tomorrow.

318
00:12:43,370 --> 00:12:44,650
你跟洛根可不是这么说的
That's not what you told Logan.

319
00:12:44,650 --> 00:12:47,610
我对洛根说谎了  但不管用
Because I goddamn lied to Logan, and it didn't work.

320
00:12:47,620 --> 00:12:49,420
现在我得做我该做的
Now I'm gonna do what I have to do.

321
00:12:51,050 --> 00:12:53,200
你至少可以警告他
Well, the least you can do is warn him.

322
00:12:53,890 --> 00:12:55,030
他是我们的竞争对手
He's on the other side.

323
00:12:55,030 --> 00:12:56,170
我不会警告他
I'm not gonna warn him.

324
00:12:56,170 --> 00:12:57,740
事情不是这么办的
That's not how it works.

325
00:13:01,490 --> 00:13:02,770
也许你应该想一个
Well, maybe you should think of something

326
00:13:02,770 --> 00:13:05,100
不会毁了他一生的办法
that won't ruin his goddamn life.

327
00:13:14,590 --> 00:13:16,350
准备好办正事了吗
You ready to get down to business?

328
00:13:16,370 --> 00:13:17,820
-准备好了  -很好
- Yes, I am. - Good.

329
00:13:17,820 --> 00:13:20,340
我在想也许我们可以共进午餐  边吃边干活
I was thinking that maybe we could do all this over lunch.

330
00:13:20,340 --> 00:13:21,690
现在才十点半
It's 10:30.

331
00:13:21,690 --> 00:13:23,410
有很多事情需要讨论  杰西卡
There's a lot to discuss, Jessica.

332
00:13:23,410 --> 00:13:25,140
没什么好讨论的
No, there isn't.

333
00:13:25,250 --> 00:13:27,200
准备好资料就行
We need to bury them in paperwork.

334
00:13:27,200 --> 00:13:27,770
不
No, we don't.

335
00:13:27,780 --> 00:13:29,380
我们要想一个正当理由
We just need to come up with a legitimate reason

336
00:13:29,380 --> 00:13:30,590
解释布鲁克斯为什么会做那笔交易
why Brooks made that trade.

337
00:13:30,590 --> 00:13:31,950
没有正当理由
There is no legitimate reason.

338
00:13:31,960 --> 00:13:33,460
我没说有  杰西卡
I didn't say there needs to be one, Jessica.

339
00:13:33,460 --> 00:13:35,140
我说我们要找一个
I said we need to find one.

340
00:13:35,140 --> 00:13:37,600
你搞起辩护真是如鱼得水啊
You are taking to defense like a fish to water.

341
00:13:37,600 --> 00:13:38,900
你雇用我
Well, you didn't bring me in here

342
00:13:38,900 --> 00:13:41,740
又不只因为我天生丽质  不是吗
just for my genetically superior bone structure, did you?

343
00:13:41,740 --> 00:13:43,800
当然不是  那是我让他来的原因
Mm, no, that's what I brought him in for.

344
00:13:43,800 --> 00:13:46,490
抱歉我来晚了  我刚才在熟悉案子
Hey, sorry I'm late. I was just getting up to speed.

345
00:13:47,760 --> 00:13:49,180
你把路易找来了
You brought Louis in.

346
00:13:49,180 --> 00:13:50,170
是啊
Of course.

347
00:13:50,170 --> 00:13:51,770
多个人总是好的
Three heads are better than two,

348
00:13:51,770 --> 00:13:53,750
你有异议吗
unless you have an objection?

349
00:13:54,250 --> 00:13:55,200
当然没有
No.

350
00:13:55,200 --> 00:13:56,550
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?

351
00:13:56,570 --> 00:13:59,540
我从不拒绝3P  对吧  伙计
I would never turn down a threesome, right, buddy?

352
00:13:59,610 --> 00:14:00,800
我听到了哦
I hear you.

353
00:14:01,000 --> 00:14:04,380
很好  杰西卡和我
Good, because Jessica and I were just having

354
00:14:04,380 --> 00:14:06,590
就接下来的行动有一点小分歧
a little difference of opinion about what to do next.

355
00:14:06,590 --> 00:14:09,120
是的  我相信路易  我的雇员
Yes, and I'm sure Louis, the man that I hired,

356
00:14:09,120 --> 00:14:12,110
这个职业生涯全指望我的人
the man who owes his very career to me,

357
00:14:12,680 --> 00:14:13,860
会赞同我的看法
will see things my way.

358
00:14:13,860 --> 00:14:15,600
我可不想得罪任何人
Well, I don't want to step on anyone's toes.

359
00:14:15,600 --> 00:14:18,330
路易  你不会得罪任何人
No, Louis, you're not stepping on anyone's toes here,

360
00:14:18,330 --> 00:14:20,830
老实说  我觉得你是个优秀的律师
and to be fair, I think you're an amazing attorney

361
00:14:20,830 --> 00:14:22,620
不必指望任何人
who doesn't owe anyone anything.

362
00:14:22,790 --> 00:14:24,780
你经常锻炼吗
Ooh, do you work out?

363
00:14:25,260 --> 00:14:27,760
我试着健身来着
Oh, I-I try to stay fit.

364
00:14:28,070 --> 00:14:28,610
试着
Try?

365
00:14:29,180 --> 00:14:30,330
成效不错嘛
Mission accomplished.

366
00:14:31,080 --> 00:14:32,330
说正题行吗
Can we get to the point?

367
00:14:32,590 --> 00:14:33,680
路  路易
Lou? Louis?

368
00:14:34,210 --> 00:14:36,970
我和杰夫在此案的处理方法上有分歧
Jeff and I have two different approaches to this case.

369
00:14:36,970 --> 00:14:39,660
没错  致命一击还是让他们无聊至死
Exactly, go for the knockout punch or bore them to death.

370
00:14:39,660 --> 00:14:40,950
你这么一说
Oh, well, when you frame it that way--

371
00:14:40,950 --> 00:14:43,150
真不敢相信你居然在用你那套辩论队的老把戏
I can't believe you're using that old debate team trick.

372
00:14:43,150 --> 00:14:44,420
健壮得像农场小伙
Farm boy strong.

373
00:14:44,420 --> 00:14:45,560
你真的是那种范例
That's what you are.

374
00:14:46,210 --> 00:14:47,710
杰西卡  你说什么辩论队把戏
Jessica, what debate team trick?

375
00:14:47,710 --> 00:14:49,930
管我的方法叫"无聊至死"
Calling my approach "Bore them to death"

376
00:14:49,930 --> 00:14:51,330
管你的叫"致命一击"
and yours "A knockout punch."

377
00:14:51,330 --> 00:14:52,570
伙计  你按得真好
Man, you're really good at this.

378
00:14:52,570 --> 00:14:54,400
以前给人按过吗
Are you-- have you done this before?

379
00:14:54,400 --> 00:14:55,310
当然了
Sure have.

380
00:14:55,570 --> 00:14:57,780
杰西卡  你可以想当然地以为
Look, Jessica, you can make assumptions about how

381
00:14:57,780 --> 00:15:00,370
这个农场小伙会对你言听计从
this farm boy's gonna come down on this all you want to,

382
00:15:00,370 --> 00:15:04,200
但你我都清楚  他站在我这边
but I think we all pretty much know he's playing on my team.

383
00:15:05,880 --> 00:15:07,470
杰夫  你说得对
Jeff, you're right.

384
00:15:07,660 --> 00:15:09,410
你说得对  事实上
You are right, and in fact,

385
00:15:09,410 --> 00:15:12,050
我认为  既然你和路易
I think that, because you and Louis

386
00:15:12,050 --> 00:15:14,670
在此案上看法一致  你俩就一起干吧
see eye to eye on this case, that you should work together,

387
00:15:15,800 --> 00:15:16,850
我就不搀和了
and I should bow out.

388
00:15:16,850 --> 00:15:18,400
你真觉得这会困扰到我吗
You actually think that bothers me?

389
00:15:19,190 --> 00:15:22,700
这农场小伙全归我了  杰西
Because now I've this farm boy all to myself, Jess.

390
00:15:24,020 --> 00:15:25,170
就剩你和我了  牛仔
Just you and me, cowboy.

391
00:15:25,480 --> 00:15:26,780
{\an8}木偶剧《芝麻街》中的一对好朋友

392
00:15:25,480 --> 00:15:26,780
就像厄尼和伯特
It's like Ernie and Bert.

393
00:15:30,040 --> 00:15:31,350
杰夫·马龙爱上我了
Jeff Malone is in love with me.

394
00:15:31,820 --> 00:15:33,420
-什么  -我去跟他开会
- What? - I was just in a meeting with him,

395
00:15:33,420 --> 00:15:35,000
他开始拍我肩膀
and he started off by patting my shoulder.

396
00:15:35,660 --> 00:15:36,530
他是个运动型的  路易
He's a jock, Louis.

397
00:15:36,530 --> 00:15:37,720
他们都这样
That's just how they are.

398
00:15:37,720 --> 00:15:39,870
不  他还揉我的肩
No, he was then rubbing my shoulders.

399
00:15:39,870 --> 00:15:41,040
还摸了我的胳膊
Then he touched my arm.

400
00:15:41,040 --> 00:15:42,060
手到处乱放
He's all over me.

401
00:15:42,060 --> 00:15:43,120
你们开会到底要说什么
Wow. What was that meeting about?

402
00:15:43,120 --> 00:15:44,040
那不重要
It doesn't matter.

403
00:15:44,040 --> 00:15:46,540
唐娜  他用的词都是两层意思
Donna, his arguments are loaded with double meaning.

404
00:15:47,580 --> 00:15:49,830
证监会的案子谁会去提刑法典啊
Who invokes the Penal Code in an S.E.C. case?

405
00:15:52,170 --> 00:15:54,580
他还说了刑法典吗[和JJ发音相近]
He said "Penal"?

406
00:15:54,580 --> 00:15:55,360
说了三次
Three times.

407
00:15:55,360 --> 00:15:56,640
第三次我们本来在说
The third time, we were just talking about

408
00:15:56,640 --> 00:15:58,840
格拉斯-斯蒂格尔法案  倒没什么  但
the Glass-Steagall Act, which is purely civil, and it--

409
00:15:58,840 --> 00:16:00,510
该死的  非让我详细描述你才懂吗
God damn it, woman, do I have to draw you a map?

410
00:16:00,510 --> 00:16:01,510
不过想想也是
I mean, come to think of it,

411
00:16:01,750 --> 00:16:03,800
现在总有运动员出柜呢
athletes coming out is all the rage now.

412
00:16:03,800 --> 00:16:06,760
你猜他最喜欢的运动是什么  篮...球
And guess what his favorite sport is: Basket...Ball.

413
00:16:06,760 --> 00:16:08,250
天哪
Oh, my God.

414
00:16:09,020 --> 00:16:10,370
闭嘴吧
Shut the front door.

415
00:16:10,370 --> 00:16:11,570
我比较想把后门闭上
No, I want to shut the back door.

416
00:16:11,570 --> 00:16:12,640
路易
Okay, Louis,

417
00:16:13,120 --> 00:16:16,520
既然已经确信了他是同性恋
now that we've firmly established his gayness,

418
00:16:16,870 --> 00:16:17,950
他为什么会觉得你也是
why would he think you're gay?

419
00:16:17,950 --> 00:16:18,700
你可是
I mean, you're...

420
00:16:21,160 --> 00:16:22,400
直如利箭啊
straight as an arrow.

421
00:16:24,150 --> 00:16:25,170
我貌似跟他说过
I may have said that I eat cock 

422
00:16:25,170 --> 00:16:26,490
我每餐都把屌炖了吃
for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.

423
00:16:27,650 --> 00:16:28,340
什么
What?

424
00:16:28,340 --> 00:16:29,490
我不是那个意思  唐娜
It was a different kind of cock, Donna.

425
00:16:29,490 --> 00:16:33,040
路易  你想让我干什么
Okay, Louis, what exactly do you want from me?

426
00:16:33,250 --> 00:16:34,710
我想让你告诉我怎么做
I want you to tell me what I should do about it.

427
00:16:34,710 --> 00:16:36,880
我这就告诉你怎么做
I'm gonna tell you exactly what you're gonna do about it:

428
00:16:37,490 --> 00:16:38,250
什么都别做
Nothing.

429
00:16:38,250 --> 00:16:39,130
什么意思  什么都别做
What do you mean, "Nothing"?

430
00:16:39,130 --> 00:16:40,690
别对他有所回应啊
I mean don't give him anything back.

431
00:16:40,690 --> 00:16:42,580
他会明白的  就没事了
He'll get the message. It'll pass.

432
00:16:45,130 --> 00:16:47,630
唐娜  我觉得你低估了我有多性感
Donna, I don't think you understand the power of my sexuality.

433
00:16:50,840 --> 00:16:51,560
你干什么
What are you doing?

434
00:16:51,870 --> 00:16:54,230
给你的档案里加点东西
Oh, you know, it's just a little something for your file.

435
00:16:54,230 --> 00:16:55,220
我还有档案
I have a file?

436
00:16:56,450 --> 00:16:57,780
那是机密
That information is classified.

437
00:16:57,780 --> 00:16:59,700
-等等  为什么  -答案也在你档案里
- Wait, why? - It's in your file.

438
00:17:00,070 --> 00:17:00,640
该死
Oh, shit.

439
00:17:15,310 --> 00:17:16,440
哈维·斯佩克特
Harvey Specter.

440
00:17:17,380 --> 00:17:19,760
你不自在的话  我这有几块石头
If you'd be more comfortable, I have a couple rocks

441
00:17:19,760 --> 00:17:20,890
你可以躲下面爬出去
you could crawl out from under.

442
00:17:20,890 --> 00:17:23,980
大多数人都说给我找丛野草让我藏身
Most people would go with some tall weeds I could hide behind.

443
00:17:23,980 --> 00:17:25,710
大多数人觉得这些公事都不针对个人
Most people don't take these fights personally.

444
00:17:25,710 --> 00:17:27,770
-我不觉得  -我正是为此而来
- I do. - That's exactly why I'm here.

445
00:17:27,770 --> 00:17:28,530
什么意思
Meaning?

446
00:17:29,440 --> 00:17:31,680
我来跟你直来直去地谈谈
I came here to tell you something man-to-man,

447
00:17:31,680 --> 00:17:33,610
我知道公司对你意义重大
because I know what this company means to you.

448
00:17:33,610 --> 00:17:35,100
你要是知道这点
If you knew what this company meant to me,

449
00:17:35,100 --> 00:17:36,790
就不会来偷我的公司了
you wouldn't be trying to steal it.

450
00:17:38,030 --> 00:17:39,980
沃尔特  我知道你儿子是怎么死的
Walter, I know how your son died.

451
00:17:41,990 --> 00:17:43,520
给我滚出去
Get the hell out of my office.

452
00:17:44,090 --> 00:17:47,570
说完再走  迈克·罗斯是个毒贩子
Not before I tell you that Mike Ross was a drug dealer.

453
00:17:48,720 --> 00:17:52,250
你就胡扯吧  我要叫保安了
Bullshit he was, and I'm calling security,

454
00:17:52,250 --> 00:17:53,970
你不赶紧出去
and if you're not gone by the time they get here,

455
00:17:53,970 --> 00:17:56,480
到时他们的工作就是从我手里救你了
their job's going to be getting me off you.

456
00:17:56,480 --> 00:17:58,670
我这就走  不过你去问他
Fine, I'll go, but ask him.

457
00:17:59,130 --> 00:18:00,810
问问他是不是贩过毒
Ask him if he ever dealt drugs.

458
00:18:01,360 --> 00:18:04,530
问问他是不是拒绝过药检
Ask him if he ever refused to take a drug test.

459
00:18:05,120 --> 00:18:07,120
问问他上班时是不是嗑嗨过
Ask him if he was ever high at work.

460
00:18:07,120 --> 00:18:08,010
我已经让你滚了
I said, "Get out."

461
00:18:08,010 --> 00:18:11,060
再问问他  他来找我雇他的当天
And ask him if on the very day he came to me looking for a job

462
00:18:11,060 --> 00:18:13,850
是不是拎了一整箱的大麻
he had a briefcase filled with marijuana.

463
00:18:15,780 --> 00:18:20,390
你就这样吗  说要找我"直来直去"
This is how you do this, come here "Man-to-man"

464
00:18:20,390 --> 00:18:24,460
然后就借我儿子的死让我交出公司吗
and use my son's death to take my company from me?

465
00:18:25,890 --> 00:18:28,370
我告诉你  你就是一混蛋
Well, you are nothing but a piece of shit.

466
00:18:31,760 --> 00:18:33,480
没错  我的确混蛋
You're right. I am a piece of shit.

467
00:18:34,020 --> 00:18:36,530
但这不代表我说的都是假的
But that doesn't make what I'm telling you any less true.

468
00:18:49,250 --> 00:18:50,440
沃尔特  你来干什么
Walter, what are you doing here?

469
00:18:50,440 --> 00:18:52,320
我犹豫了
I'm having second thoughts.

470
00:18:53,380 --> 00:18:54,210
你是说收购吗
About the takeover.

471
00:18:54,210 --> 00:18:55,100
我是说你
About you.

472
00:18:57,190 --> 00:18:57,930
抱歉  我没听懂
I'm sorry. I don't understan--

473
00:18:57,930 --> 00:19:00,210
你参与过贩毒吗
Have you ever been involved in a drug deal?

474
00:19:04,500 --> 00:19:06,040
沃尔特  我可是在努力帮你保住公司
Walter, look, I'm trying to save your company here.

475
00:19:06,040 --> 00:19:07,930
而我要搞清楚  与我共事的是什么人
And I'm here to find out what kind of man I'm in business with,

476
00:19:07,930 --> 00:19:10,390
所以我再问一遍
so I'm going to ask you again.

477
00:19:10,680 --> 00:19:12,760
你参与过贩毒吗
Have you ever been involved in a drug deal?

478
00:19:21,940 --> 00:19:23,210
哈维跟你说什么了
What did Harvey tell you?

479
00:19:24,280 --> 00:19:25,920
看来他说的是事实
Looks like he told me the truth.

480
00:19:25,920 --> 00:19:27,290
事实是哈维打不过我们
The truth is that Harvey can't beat us, 

481
00:19:27,290 --> 00:19:28,380
就来挑拨离间
so he's trying to divide us,

482
00:19:28,380 --> 00:19:30,210
还用你儿子的故事逼你就范
and he's using your son to do it.

483
00:19:30,210 --> 00:19:32,500
你也利用我的回忆达成了合作
Just like you used his memory to make you my partner.

484
00:19:32,500 --> 00:19:34,110
我是要保住你毕生的事业
To save your life's work.

485
00:19:34,110 --> 00:19:36,680
又一个骗子的新鬼话
Another lie from another liar.

486
00:19:37,120 --> 00:19:38,520
你俩真是般配
You two deserve each other.

487
00:19:39,120 --> 00:19:39,790
我们到此为止
We're done.

488
00:19:49,810 --> 00:19:51,650
-迈克  你还好吗  -我不管你找谁
- Mike, are you okay? - I don't care who you find.

489
00:19:51,650 --> 00:19:52,650
我要你雇人
I want you to hire someone

490
00:19:52,650 --> 00:19:55,240
挖出洛根·桑德斯的所有丑闻
to get every piece of dirt there is on Logan Sanders.

491
00:19:55,240 --> 00:19:56,650
去做就好
Just do it.

492
00:19:56,650 --> 00:19:57,610
你要去哪
Where are you going?

493
00:19:57,610 --> 00:19:59,030
搞定其他事
To take care of something else.

494
00:20:05,300 --> 00:20:07,190
两件事  今天是波特生日
Couple things. It's Porter birthday.

495
00:20:07,190 --> 00:20:09,460
我订了他喜欢的怪异的布朗克斯西葫芦蛋糕
I got him that weird zucchini cake he likes from the Bronx.

496
00:20:09,460 --> 00:20:10,150
什么蛋糕
What cake?

497
00:20:10,150 --> 00:20:12,430
有人把斯塔特曼的椅子还回来了
Somebody returned Stutman's chair.

498
00:20:12,430 --> 00:20:13,200
它丢过吗
It was missing?

499
00:20:13,200 --> 00:20:16,200
厨房里"既往不咎"的便条起作用了
And the "No questions asked" memo in the kitchen worked.

500
00:20:16,200 --> 00:20:18,420
-它阻止了什么  -不重要
- What did it stop? - Mm, it's not important.

501
00:20:18,420 --> 00:20:19,850
这些事都不重要
None of these things are important.

502
00:20:19,850 --> 00:20:21,380
还有一件事
Oh, and one more thing.

503
00:20:21,990 --> 00:20:23,820
路易觉得马龙爱上他了
Louis thinks Malone is in love with him.

504
00:20:24,470 --> 00:20:25,470
你的小秘密很安全
Your secret's safe.

505
00:20:26,280 --> 00:20:27,100
不用谢了
And you're welcome.

506
00:20:33,110 --> 00:20:35,220
路易  有时间吗
Hey, Louis, do you have a minute?

507
00:20:35,220 --> 00:20:37,980
我就时间紧  现在超级超级忙
Well, it's about all I have, 'cause I'm super, super busy.

508
00:20:37,980 --> 00:20:39,410
我就是来看看
Yeah, well, listen, I just wanted to check in

509
00:20:39,410 --> 00:20:41,230
你有没有准备好熬通宵
and see if you're ready to pull an all-nighter.

510
00:20:41,230 --> 00:20:42,680
我调来了所有经纪人业务录音
I just got all the brokerage tapes in,

511
00:20:42,680 --> 00:20:44,750
我觉得咱们可以重过一遍
and I figure we could just grind it out.

512
00:20:45,040 --> 00:20:45,630
今晚吗
Tonight?

513
00:20:45,630 --> 00:20:47,950
今晚  除非你想现在
Tonight, unless you want to go right now

514
00:20:47,950 --> 00:20:49,170
立刻着手搞定
and just pound it out all at once.

515
00:20:49,170 --> 00:20:50,120
好了  够了
Okay, that's it.

516
00:20:50,120 --> 00:20:51,590
我是说  你会错意了
I mean, you have got this all wrong.

517
00:20:51,590 --> 00:20:56,820
杰夫  我喜欢你  但是作为朋友
Jeff, I like you...as a friend.

518
00:20:57,630 --> 00:20:58,920
是的  路易
Right, Louis.

519
00:20:58,920 --> 00:21:00,740
我也喜欢你
I like you too.

520
00:21:00,740 --> 00:21:02,520
我觉得我已经表达得很清楚了
I think I've made that perfectly clear.

521
00:21:02,520 --> 00:21:05,560
太清楚了  朋友  太清楚
Too clear, man, too clear.

522
00:21:05,560 --> 00:21:07,140
引诱的意图已经够明显了
I mean, enough with the come-ons, already.

523
00:21:07,410 --> 00:21:08,990
-什么  -我明白了
- What? - Yeah, I mean, I get it.

524
00:21:08,990 --> 00:21:10,780
如果咱俩都是同志
You know, we're a perfect match, you know,

525
00:21:10,780 --> 00:21:12,300
那就是天生一对  就像黑檀木和白象牙
if you go that way, ebony and ivory.

526
00:21:10,780 --> 00:21:12,300
{\an8}游戏《鬼泣》中但丁的双枪

527
00:21:12,300 --> 00:21:14,150
但我喜欢的是女人  所以...
But I play a different instrument, so...

528
00:21:15,240 --> 00:21:16,900
路易  不是
Oh, Louis, no--

529
00:21:16,900 --> 00:21:18,660
我  听着  只是
Look, I-- look, it's just that--

530
00:21:18,660 --> 00:21:20,810
我只是不希望
I just don't-- I don't want there to be,

531
00:21:21,230 --> 00:21:23,210
事情变得尴尬  特别是杰西卡
you know, just awkwardness, especially since Jessica

532
00:21:23,210 --> 00:21:25,190
退出以后  就只剩我和你了
just bowed out, and it's just me and you now.

533
00:21:25,720 --> 00:21:26,450
是啊
Right.

534
00:21:29,940 --> 00:21:33,440
既然你看穿我的想法了  路易
Well, now that you've seen right through me, Louis,

535
00:21:33,440 --> 00:21:37,320
我  我是很失望
I...I am disappointed.

536
00:21:38,680 --> 00:21:39,880
你没事吧
Are you gonna be okay?

537
00:21:39,880 --> 00:21:42,500
说实话  我现在觉得有些受伤
To be honest, I'm feeling a little raw right now.

538
00:21:42,500 --> 00:21:43,410
可恶
Oh, shit.

539
00:21:46,750 --> 00:21:47,880
对不起
I'm sorry.

540
00:21:47,880 --> 00:21:49,550
你最好告诉杰西卡
Maybe it's best if you just told Jessica

541
00:21:49,550 --> 00:21:51,240
还是需要她介入
that she needs to step back in.

542
00:21:51,240 --> 00:21:52,860
-没错  -没错
- Yes. - Yeah.

543
00:21:53,880 --> 00:21:56,000
没问题
Can do, yeah.

544
00:21:58,320 --> 00:21:58,940
起来
Get up.

545
00:21:59,830 --> 00:22:01,110
你是来找我打架的吗
You here to fight me?

546
00:22:01,110 --> 00:22:02,540
我是不是应该等你转过身
Oh, should I wait for you to turn your back?

547
00:22:02,540 --> 00:22:03,850
这好像更符合你的风格
That seems to be more your speed.

548
00:22:03,850 --> 00:22:06,060
抱歉  难道你指望我事先通知你
I'm sorry, were you expecting me to give you a call?

549
00:22:06,060 --> 00:22:08,110
不  我指望你会有点人性
No, I was expecting you to be a human being.

550
00:22:08,260 --> 00:22:10,740
照我来看  我已经仁至义尽了
From where I'm sitting, I was a goddamn saint.

551
00:22:10,740 --> 00:22:11,580
是吗  此话怎讲
Oh, yeah? How's that?

552
00:22:11,580 --> 00:22:13,860
如果我不这么做  洛根就会
If I didn't do what I did, Logan was gonna hire

553
00:22:13,860 --> 00:22:16,650
雇私家侦探把你的老底翻个遍
a private investigator to smear you up and down the block.

554
00:22:16,650 --> 00:22:18,780
-那又怎样  -你知道会怎样
- So what? - You know what.

555
00:22:18,780 --> 00:22:20,360
我朝你膝盖开了一枪
I shot you in the knees,

556
00:22:20,360 --> 00:22:22,470
他才不会朝你脑袋开枪
so he wouldn't shoot you in the face.

557
00:22:22,470 --> 00:22:23,920
-不用谢我  -你知道吗  哈维
- You're welcome. - You know what, Harvey?

558
00:22:23,920 --> 00:22:25,080
我要跳过谢你这一步
I'm gonna take pass on the thank-you

559
00:22:25,080 --> 00:22:26,810
直接跳到我叫你
and instead skip right to the part where I call you

560
00:22:26,810 --> 00:22:27,630
混蛋的那一步
a piece of shit.

561
00:22:27,630 --> 00:22:28,430
你知道吗
You know what?

562
00:22:28,430 --> 00:22:30,380
这话我已经听腻了
I'm getting a little tired of hearing that.

563
00:22:30,380 --> 00:22:32,340
你在餐馆威胁要提起
And what does that make you for threatening to bring

564
00:22:32,340 --> 00:22:33,940
刑事诉讼又好到哪里去了
criminal charges in that restaurant?

565
00:22:33,940 --> 00:22:35,550
你在餐馆的所作所为
You deserved criminal charges

566
00:22:35,550 --> 00:22:37,200
就应该被起诉
for what you were doing in that restaurant.

567
00:22:37,200 --> 00:22:39,640
7个月前我们对利兹的那个家伙这么做时
You didn't have a problem when we did it seven months ago

568
00:22:39,640 --> 00:22:40,660
你可没有意见
to the guy from Leeds.

569
00:22:40,660 --> 00:22:42,980
7个月前  你没有对别人诽谤我
Seven months ago, you weren't lying to somebody about me.

570
00:22:42,980 --> 00:22:44,880
我说的是实话  而且7个月前
I didn't lie, and seven months ago,

571
00:22:44,880 --> 00:22:46,550
你还在这里
you were goddamn here.

572
00:22:48,100 --> 00:22:49,460
所以这才是问题的关键
So that's what this is about.

573
00:22:50,810 --> 00:22:52,490
你不能容忍我离开了这里
You can't stand that I got out of here

574
00:22:52,490 --> 00:22:54,220
而且没有你我也很成功
and that I'm succeeding without you.

575
00:22:54,580 --> 00:22:55,540
没有我
Without me?

576
00:22:56,720 --> 00:22:58,060
我造就了你
I made you.

577
00:22:58,660 --> 00:23:00,140
没有我  你什么都不是
Without me, you're nothing.

578
00:23:00,140 --> 00:23:00,950
就是这点
Right there.

579
00:23:02,360 --> 00:23:05,070
你就是这样的人  所以我才离开
That's who you are, and that's why I left.

580
00:23:05,070 --> 00:23:06,970
扯淡  别赖我身上
Bullshit. Don't lay that on me.

581
00:23:06,970 --> 00:23:09,720
你离开是想满足你膨胀的自负
You left because you needed to feed that huge ego.

582
00:23:09,720 --> 00:23:12,220
自负  自负
Ego? Ego?

583
00:23:12,220 --> 00:23:13,600
你知道如果我待在这
If I stayed here, you know what would have been

584
00:23:13,600 --> 00:23:16,160
我的余生都要提心吊胆
hanging over my head for the rest of my life.

585
00:23:16,160 --> 00:23:18,220
所以我才让你
Which is why I told you to move somewhere

586
00:23:18,220 --> 00:23:19,910
搬到没人认识的地方去
nobody ever knew you.

587
00:23:19,910 --> 00:23:21,070
但你要留在这
But you stayed here,

588
00:23:21,070 --> 00:23:23,820
所以你的威胁根本还在
so that thing is still over your goddamn head,

589
00:23:23,820 --> 00:23:24,880
是我阻止了这一切
and I stopped it.

590
00:23:24,880 --> 00:23:27,410
我不管你以为你阻止了什么
I don't care what you think you stopped.

591
00:23:27,410 --> 00:23:28,730
你马上去找沃尔特·吉利斯
You're gonna go to Walter Gillis,

592
00:23:28,730 --> 00:23:30,490
把你惹下的乱子弥补好
and you're gonna make this thing right.

593
00:23:30,490 --> 00:23:31,570
这样就很好
It is right.

594
00:23:31,570 --> 00:23:33,170
结束了  你输了
It's over. You lost.

595
00:23:33,170 --> 00:23:34,200
什么都没结束
Nothing's over.

596
00:23:35,020 --> 00:23:36,870
今天你才是输家
And you're the one who lost something today.

597
00:23:37,200 --> 00:23:38,160
你什么意思
What are you talking about?

598
00:23:38,160 --> 00:23:39,790
你搞人身攻击  我也来
You went personal. I went personal.

599
00:23:40,890 --> 00:23:44,240
你父亲的唱片母带  在我手上
Your father's master tapes... I've got 'em.

600
00:23:47,310 --> 00:23:49,510
那些带子跟这笔交易毫无关联
Those tapes have nothing to do with this deal.

601
00:23:52,080 --> 00:23:52,950
现在有关了
They do now.

602
00:24:00,010 --> 00:24:00,560
哈维
Harvey...

603
00:24:03,590 --> 00:24:04,610
这是我造成的
I did this.

604
00:24:04,990 --> 00:24:06,480
-什么  -那些带子
- What? - The tapes.

605
00:24:06,480 --> 00:24:08,450
迈克是从我这里打听到的
Mike found out about them from me.

606
00:24:09,400 --> 00:24:11,150
我和他一起喝过咖啡  只是因为
I've been meeting him for coffee just because I wanted

607
00:24:11,150 --> 00:24:13,300
我想确认你们俩之间一切都好
to make sure that everything was okay between the two of you,

608
00:24:13,300 --> 00:24:17,060
我从没想过他会做这种事
and I never, ever thought that he would do something like this.

609
00:24:17,060 --> 00:24:19,480
非常  非常对不起
I'm so, so sorry.

610
00:24:19,480 --> 00:24:20,950
这不是你的错  唐娜
It's not your fault, Donna.

611
00:24:23,180 --> 00:24:24,910
-你打算怎么做  -什么都不做
- What are you gonna do? - Nothing.

612
00:24:24,910 --> 00:24:26,560
那些带子不会影响这桩交易
The tapes have nothing to do with this deal.

613
00:24:26,560 --> 00:24:28,700
如果我不这么想  我就完了
The second I believe they do, I'm done.

614
00:24:30,840 --> 00:24:32,450
来得正好
Ugh, perfect timing.

615
00:24:33,090 --> 00:24:34,120
你要我帮你拦住他吗
Do you want me to get rid of him?

616
00:24:34,120 --> 00:24:34,790
我会处理的
I'll handle it.

617
00:24:38,560 --> 00:24:40,780
"让迈克·罗斯一败涂地"这句话
What part of "Drag Mike Ross through the mud"

618
00:24:41,120 --> 00:24:42,200
你是哪里没听明白
did you not understand?

619
00:24:42,200 --> 00:24:44,160
我不懂你为什么像个有钱的
The part where you come off looking like a rich,

620
00:24:44,160 --> 00:24:45,580
斗气的蠢货一样
vindictive douche bag.

621
00:24:45,580 --> 00:24:47,060
这可轮不到你说
That's not your call to make.

622
00:24:47,060 --> 00:24:49,930
就凭你那几年收购经验吗
Based on your years of experience in takeovers?

623
00:24:49,930 --> 00:24:52,280
你在决定成人前  或许待在寄宿学校
Here's something they didn't teach you in snowboarding school

624
00:24:52,280 --> 00:24:53,420
或者什么地方
or wherever the hell you went

625
00:24:53,420 --> 00:24:55,250
那里大概没人教过你
before you decided to be a grown-up.

626
00:24:55,250 --> 00:24:57,530
可以私下解决的事
Never destroy anyone in public

627
00:24:57,530 --> 00:25:00,120
就永远别摆上台面毁别人
when you can accomplish the same result in private.

628
00:25:00,560 --> 00:25:01,270
所以呢
Meaning?

629
00:25:01,270 --> 00:25:03,340
我切断了迈克和尔特·吉利斯的联系
I severed Mike's ties with Walter Gillis.

630
00:25:03,340 --> 00:25:04,210
都结束了
It's over.

631
00:25:05,060 --> 00:25:06,800
你曾经和我说迈克·罗斯不是威胁
You know, you told me that Mike Ross wasn't a threat,

632
00:25:06,800 --> 00:25:08,630
然后他申请到临时禁令让我们束手束脚
and then he handcuffed us with a T.R.O.

633
00:25:08,630 --> 00:25:11,110
你也说过你一下就能把他掀翻在地
You said that you'd take him down with one blow,

634
00:25:11,110 --> 00:25:12,360
然后他又卷土重来了
and then he got back up.

635
00:25:12,360 --> 00:25:15,610
我在寄宿学校学到的一个道理
So here's something that I did learn in snowboarding school.

636
00:25:15,610 --> 00:25:18,450
就是有人在夸口的时候  我要看到证据
When someone talks shit, I demand proof.

637
00:25:18,450 --> 00:25:19,530
什么证据
Proof of what?

638
00:25:19,530 --> 00:25:22,020
洛根  我们赢了  你不必
Logan, we won. You don't need--

639
00:25:22,020 --> 00:25:23,100
不必什么
Need to what?

640
00:25:23,100 --> 00:25:26,040
不必表现得像个有钱的  斗气的蠢货吗
Come off like a rich, vindictive douche bag?

641
00:25:26,770 --> 00:25:28,870
我要他放弃竞标的证据
I want proof that he's giving up his bid,

642
00:25:28,870 --> 00:25:30,050
如果今天上午没拿到
and if I don't get it by the morning,

643
00:25:30,050 --> 00:25:31,660
我会找我的私家侦探
I'm gonna call my private investigators,

644
00:25:31,660 --> 00:25:33,230
做我一开始要做的事
and I'm gonna finish what I started.

645
00:25:46,450 --> 00:25:47,310
你要去哪
Where are you going?

646
00:25:47,780 --> 00:25:48,780
你觉得呢
Where do you think I'm going?

647
00:25:48,780 --> 00:25:50,980
去找迈克签放弃竞标的协议书
To get Mike to sign an agreement to give up his bid.

648
00:25:50,980 --> 00:25:51,900
不行
You can't.

649
00:25:52,330 --> 00:25:53,170
为什么
Why not?

650
00:25:53,170 --> 00:25:54,180
因为你说得对
Because you were right.

651
00:25:54,180 --> 00:25:55,540
他不会听你的
He's never gonna listen to you.

652
00:25:56,260 --> 00:25:58,590
唐娜  我知道唱片带的事你不好受  但是
Donna, I know you're feeling bad about the tapes, but--

653
00:25:58,590 --> 00:26:00,020
和那个无关
That has nothing to do with it.

654
00:26:00,020 --> 00:26:01,210
那你是想说什么
Then what are you saying?

655
00:26:01,210 --> 00:26:03,270
我很内疚我告诉了他
I feel guilty that I told him,

656
00:26:03,270 --> 00:26:05,310
但他的所作所为是因为你
but what he did, that's on you.

657
00:26:06,330 --> 00:26:07,720
他之所以不会听你的
And the reason he's not gonna listen to you

658
00:26:07,720 --> 00:26:09,510
是因为你表现得像个混蛋
is because you acted like an asshole.

659
00:26:09,510 --> 00:26:10,590
你说什么
Excuse me?

660
00:26:10,590 --> 00:26:12,070
他来这里想要个解释
He came in here wanting an explanation

661
00:26:12,070 --> 00:26:14,120
问你为什么要做这种事
for why you did what you did,

662
00:26:14,120 --> 00:26:15,930
而你火上浇油
and you threw gas on the fire.

663
00:26:15,930 --> 00:26:17,800
我给了他解释
I gave him an explanation.

664
00:26:18,210 --> 00:26:20,880
是啊  你告诉他他什么都不是
Yeah, you told him he was nothing.

665
00:26:22,070 --> 00:26:22,880
你记得吗
You know what?

666
00:26:23,020 --> 00:26:23,930
半小时前
About a half an hour ago,

667
00:26:23,940 --> 00:26:25,630
你还告诉我这都是你的错
you told me this was all your fault.

668
00:26:25,630 --> 00:26:28,060
半小时前我在反省自己的行为
A half an hour ago, I was thinking about what I did.

669
00:26:28,380 --> 00:26:30,380
没在考虑你对他说的话
I wasn't thinking about what you said to him.

670
00:26:30,380 --> 00:26:31,910
这跟我对他说了什么无关
It doesn't matter what I said to him.

671
00:26:31,910 --> 00:26:33,340
我救了他
I saved him.

672
00:26:35,020 --> 00:26:38,040
哈维  你说过要不是迈克
Harvey, you said before if it had been anybody

673
00:26:38,040 --> 00:26:39,900
换作其他人  你就会连眼都不眨地
other than Mike, you would have done what Logan wanted

674
00:26:39,900 --> 00:26:41,720
按洛根说的做
without blinking an eye.

675
00:26:41,720 --> 00:26:44,130
如果有其他人像迈克一样
Well, if anybody other than Mike had walked in here

676
00:26:44,130 --> 00:26:45,240
走进来
the way he did,

677
00:26:47,010 --> 00:26:49,420
你会表现出一点同情心的
you would have shown him the tiniest bit of compassion.

678
00:26:49,420 --> 00:26:51,690
他进来之前就把唱片母带买走了
He bought those tapes before he ever walked in here.

679
00:26:51,690 --> 00:26:54,300
他并没有先跟你提母带的事情
Those tapes were not the first thing that he told you about,

680
00:26:55,610 --> 00:26:57,350
但他倒挑明了那会是最后一击
but he made damn sure they were the last.

681
00:26:57,350 --> 00:26:59,650
所以你阻止我就是为了喊我混蛋吗
So you just flagged me down to call me an asshole?

682
00:26:59,650 --> 00:27:00,810
不  我阻止你是想告诉你
No, I flagged you down to tell you

683
00:27:00,810 --> 00:27:02,150
他不会听你的话
that he's not gonna listen to you,

684
00:27:03,030 --> 00:27:04,440
但或许会听其他人的话
but he might listen to somebody else.

685
00:27:09,810 --> 00:27:11,150
路易斯刚刚告诉我
Just heard from Louis.

686
00:27:11,150 --> 00:27:12,360
他得了肠胃炎
He has the stomach flu,

687
00:27:12,530 --> 00:27:14,100
所以今晚我来替他
so I'm gonna have to step in tonight.

688
00:27:14,260 --> 00:27:16,280
这真是太糟了
Oh, that's too bad.

689
00:27:16,740 --> 00:27:17,990
这跟他觉得
This wouldn't have anything to do with him 

690
00:27:17,990 --> 00:27:19,990
你爱上他了无关吧
thinking you're in love with him, would it?

691
00:27:20,300 --> 00:27:21,440
不知道
No idea.

692
00:27:21,440 --> 00:27:22,720
想吃寿司吗
Feel like Sushi?

693
00:27:22,820 --> 00:27:24,930
杰夫  你想耍什么花招都行
Jeff, you can play all the games that you want,

694
00:27:24,930 --> 00:27:27,270
但通宵整理证据
but an all-night review of the evidence

695
00:27:27,270 --> 00:27:29,310
是在浪费我的时间
is a waste of my time.

696
00:27:29,310 --> 00:27:31,020
不如你叫几个初级律师帮你
So why don't you get a couple of associates?

697
00:27:31,020 --> 00:27:32,670
我们明早再见
And I will see you in the morning.

698
00:27:33,600 --> 00:27:36,980
听着  你不想待在这里也没关系
Listen, if you don't want to be here, that's fine.

699
00:27:37,720 --> 00:27:39,140
但我会自己做完
But I am gonna do this by myself,

700
00:27:39,140 --> 00:27:41,350
我不会让初级律师帮我做的
because I don't have associates do my work.

701
00:27:41,350 --> 00:27:43,170
为什么
And why is that?

702
00:27:43,510 --> 00:27:44,900
你真的想知道
Do you really want to know why?

703
00:27:48,320 --> 00:27:50,490
达尔顿·福斯特是个骗子
Dalton Foster was a con man

704
00:27:50,490 --> 00:27:52,470
不知他用什么法子
who somehow convinced

705
00:27:52,470 --> 00:27:55,570
骗得人们签字转让自己的保险
terminally ill people to sign over their insurance policies.

706
00:27:55,570 --> 00:27:57,800
总之  他是我的第一个大案子
Anyway, he was my first big case,

707
00:27:57,800 --> 00:28:00,380
所以我决定找些人帮我
so I decided that I would get some help

708
00:28:00,380 --> 00:28:03,490
像今晚一样整理证据
going through the evidence, just like this.

709
00:28:05,090 --> 00:28:06,680
结果反是帮了倒忙
The help screwed up.

710
00:28:07,430 --> 00:28:09,220
达尔顿·福斯特溜掉了
Dalton Foster walked.

711
00:28:09,560 --> 00:28:12,480
六个月后  他又故技重施
Six months later, he pulled the exact same scam.

712
00:28:12,480 --> 00:28:13,950
但那次问题是
Only this time, the problem was,

713
00:28:13,950 --> 00:28:17,240
他一个将死的客户奇迹般活过来了
one of his dying clients had a miraculous recovery.

714
00:28:18,050 --> 00:28:22,670
一天  达尔顿·福斯特走到她背后
So one day, Dalton came up from behind her...

715
00:28:23,960 --> 00:28:26,910
用一根铝棒把她打死了
And he beat her to death with an aluminum bat.

716
00:28:28,860 --> 00:28:31,060
所以我高兴你在这里吗  杰西卡
So am I glad you're here, Jessica?

717
00:28:31,240 --> 00:28:32,580
当然
Yes.

718
00:28:32,580 --> 00:28:35,660
我利用了路易斯吗  利用了
Did I take advantage of Louis? Absolutely.

719
00:28:35,930 --> 00:28:38,410
或许我是玩了花招让我俩在一起
I may play games to get us together,

720
00:28:38,950 --> 00:28:41,500
但我对案子是认真的
but I never play games with a case.

721
00:28:42,800 --> 00:28:44,090
从来不玩花招
Never.

722
00:28:51,640 --> 00:28:52,930
你有时间吗
You have a minute?

723
00:28:54,030 --> 00:28:55,290
肯定出大事了
This must be serious.

724
00:28:55,290 --> 00:28:56,070
为什么
Why is that?

725
00:28:56,070 --> 00:28:58,160
因为通常你都直接给我下命令
Because you usually just tell me what to do.

726
00:28:58,160 --> 00:28:59,200
记得你说过
Remember when you said

727
00:28:59,200 --> 00:29:01,150
如果我希望你给迈克传递信息
if I want you to deliver a message to Mike,

728
00:29:01,150 --> 00:29:02,860
就该直接跟你说
I should come to you directly?

729
00:29:05,310 --> 00:29:07,020
你想让我劝他放弃
You want me to get him to give up.

730
00:29:07,020 --> 00:29:08,920
如果迈克今晚不放弃
If Mike doesn't give up tonight,

731
00:29:08,920 --> 00:29:10,880
洛根会雇人彻头彻尾地
Logan is gonna hire someone to dig up

732
00:29:10,880 --> 00:29:12,800
调查他的身世背景
everything they can on him.

733
00:29:13,840 --> 00:29:15,540
所以你才去找了吉利斯
That's why you went to Gillis.

734
00:29:16,470 --> 00:29:18,100
你别无选择
You had no choice.

735
00:29:18,600 --> 00:29:20,280
但迈克不这么看
That's not the way Mike saw it.

736
00:29:20,780 --> 00:29:23,530
你那么做之前可以先来找我的
You know, you could have come to me before you did that.

737
00:29:24,150 --> 00:29:25,960
我现在不是来了吗
I'm coming to you now.

738
00:29:27,970 --> 00:29:28,980
这份工作怎么算钱
How do I bill it?

739
00:29:28,980 --> 00:29:30,600
平常怎么算就那么算
The same way we bill everything.

740
00:29:30,600 --> 00:29:32,650
算两倍时间好了
Say it took twice as long as it did.

741
00:29:43,910 --> 00:29:45,880
好  我收回
Okay, I take it back.

742
00:29:45,880 --> 00:29:47,260
我的策略
My strategy?

743
00:29:47,260 --> 00:29:49,440
我的策略不是"致命一击"
My strategy isn't "Knockout punch."

744
00:29:49,440 --> 00:29:51,610
应该叫做"大海捞针"
We should've called it "Needle in a haystack."

745
00:29:51,610 --> 00:29:53,040
要崩溃了吗
Getting frustrated?

746
00:29:53,040 --> 00:29:56,250
这家伙  这家伙真是话多
This guy? This guy does not shut up.

747
00:29:56,250 --> 00:29:57,660
我现在知道他有支气管炎
I now know about his bronchitis,

748
00:29:57,660 --> 00:29:59,410
他对干洗剂过敏
his problems with his dry cleaner,

749
00:29:59,410 --> 00:30:01,570
但都不能解释为何
but absolutely no explanation whatsoever

750
00:30:01,570 --> 00:30:03,070
他会现金不足
about why he cashed out.

751
00:30:03,070 --> 00:30:05,010
你是说除了被起诉  他还可能卷入了
Oh, you mean besides being tipped that he invested

752
00:30:05,010 --> 00:30:06,680
庞氏骗局
in a giant Ponzi scheme.

753
00:30:06,680 --> 00:30:07,940
等等
Wait.

754
00:30:08,570 --> 00:30:09,330
什么
What?

755
00:30:09,330 --> 00:30:11,390
他和一个分析师的电话
It's a call with an analyst predicting a downturn

756
00:30:11,390 --> 00:30:14,190
预测下个季度的小盘股票下跌
in small-cap stocks in the next quarter.

757
00:30:14,770 --> 00:30:16,030
你听
Listen.

758
00:30:25,590 --> 00:30:28,090
庞氏的资金就是来自小盘股票
The Ponzi fund was made up of small-cap stocks.

759
00:30:28,090 --> 00:30:31,130
这个理由可以解释他为何会现金不足
That's a legit reason for him to have cashed out.

760
00:30:32,550 --> 00:30:35,150
这恰恰是我们需要用来撤销指控的关键
Exactly what we need to get the charges dropped.

761
00:30:36,200 --> 00:30:40,520
这种电话也恰恰是初级律师最可能忽略的
And exactly the kind of call a junior attorney might have missed.

762
00:30:43,370 --> 00:30:45,490
现在你明白我们为什么得一起研究这个了吧
So do you see why we needed to do this together?

763
00:30:45,490 --> 00:30:47,620
是  我明白了
Yes, I see.

764
00:30:57,590 --> 00:30:58,970
怎么了
What is it?

765
00:31:04,470 --> 00:31:07,520
我身上背负的责任
I have responsibilities

766
00:31:07,520 --> 00:31:10,120
你是不会想去理解的
that you just don't want to understand.

767
00:31:10,440 --> 00:31:12,820
我确实不想
No, I don't.

768
00:31:12,940 --> 00:31:16,770
我是纽约唯一一个
I am the only woman partner

769
00:31:16,770 --> 00:31:19,140
身居如此高位的女性合伙人
at this level in the city.

770
00:31:19,620 --> 00:31:22,050
如果有流言传出去说我雇了一个
If word got out that I hired a partner

771
00:31:22,050 --> 00:31:23,480
正在跟我恋爱的合伙人
that I was in a relationship with--

772
00:31:23,480 --> 00:31:25,190
怎么  你会被取消律师资格吗
What, you'd be disbarred?

773
00:31:25,580 --> 00:31:27,370
你觉得我在开玩笑
You think this is a joke.

774
00:31:29,980 --> 00:31:32,010
我觉得你只是在找借口
I think you're making excuses

775
00:31:32,010 --> 00:31:33,850
阻止我进入你的生活
for keeping me out of your life,

776
00:31:33,850 --> 00:31:35,330
杰西卡  而且我是实话实说
Jessica, and I'm calling you on it.

777
00:31:35,330 --> 00:31:37,420
那又是什么意思
Oh, what the hell is that supposed to mean?

778
00:31:37,580 --> 00:31:40,440
意思就是  我向你保证
It means that I'm making you a promise, all right,

779
00:31:40,470 --> 00:31:42,870
没有人  没有人会发现我们的关系
that no one--no one will ever find out about us,

780
00:31:42,870 --> 00:31:46,060
所以如果那是你真正的顾虑
so if that's what you're really afraid of,

781
00:31:46,160 --> 00:31:48,350
如果那是让你退缩的原因
if that's what's truly holding you back,

782
00:31:48,350 --> 00:31:50,620
那问题就不复存在了
then it is off the table.

783
00:31:56,570 --> 00:31:57,980
抱歉
I'm sorry.

784
00:32:15,730 --> 00:32:18,190
我知道我们说过
Hey, so I know we said

785
00:32:18,190 --> 00:32:19,690
不再讨论那笔交易
we're not supposed to talk about the deal--

786
00:32:19,690 --> 00:32:21,120
你为什么骗我
Why did you lie to me?

787
00:32:26,040 --> 00:32:27,500
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

788
00:32:31,770 --> 00:32:33,220
我问起你和洛根的事时
When I asked you about you and Logan,

789
00:32:33,220 --> 00:32:34,920
你说是你提出分手的
you said that you ended it.

790
00:32:37,650 --> 00:32:40,660
但在这份证词上  你发誓说是他提出的
According to this, you swore it was him.

791
00:32:45,090 --> 00:32:47,710
这是他离婚时我的证词
This is my deposition from his divorce.

792
00:32:53,350 --> 00:32:54,800
你看了这个吗  为什么...
You read this? Why--why would--

793
00:32:54,800 --> 00:32:56,960
他查了我  我查了他
He looked into me. I looked into him.

794
00:32:58,780 --> 00:32:59,910
这是在查我
This is looking into me.

795
00:32:59,910 --> 00:33:01,750
你还没有回答我的问题
You still haven't answered the question.

796
00:33:01,930 --> 00:33:03,840
迈克  我告诉你的都是真的
Mike, I told you the truth.

797
00:33:04,350 --> 00:33:08,250
洛根想挽回他和他妻子之间的关系
Logan was trying to patch things up with his wife,

798
00:33:08,250 --> 00:33:10,890
所以他请求我证明他说的故事  我答应了
and he asked me to back his story, so I did.

799
00:33:10,890 --> 00:33:12,250
你为了他撒谎了
You lied for him.

800
00:33:15,980 --> 00:33:17,650
原来你曾经那么爱他
You loved him that much.

801
00:33:19,190 --> 00:33:20,190
我告诉过你  我爱过他
I told you that I loved him.

802
00:33:20,190 --> 00:33:21,960
是  可你没有告诉我这件事
Yeah, but you didn't tell me that.

803
00:33:24,110 --> 00:33:25,660
我在这里坐了一整晚
And I've been sitting here all night

804
00:33:25,660 --> 00:33:27,570
一直在想为什么你不...
wondering why you wouldn't...

805
00:33:30,520 --> 00:33:32,410
为什么你不把这件事告诉我
Why wouldn't you tell me that?

806
00:33:40,540 --> 00:33:42,080
我现在就告诉你
I'm gonna tell you now.

807
00:33:44,880 --> 00:33:46,340
我们有过一段婚外情
We had an affair.

808
00:33:48,750 --> 00:33:53,790
我们相爱了  他想娶我
We fell in love, and he wanted to marry me,

809
00:33:53,790 --> 00:33:55,260
我拒绝了
and I said no,

810
00:33:57,590 --> 00:34:01,670
三个月后  他改变心意了
and then three months later, he had a change of heart,

811
00:34:01,980 --> 00:34:03,250
离婚进行到一半时
and he wanted to get back with his wife

812
00:34:03,250 --> 00:34:05,550
他想和他妻子重修旧好  所以他求我帮他
during his divorce proceedings, so he asked me to help him,

813
00:34:05,550 --> 00:34:07,000
我就帮了
and I did.

814
00:34:10,260 --> 00:34:13,480
可是当他想娶我时  我拒绝了
But when he wanted to marry me, I said no,

815
00:34:13,480 --> 00:34:16,800
因为他不是那个我想与之白头偕老的人
because he wasn't the man I want to spend my life with.

816
00:34:18,770 --> 00:34:20,100
你才是
You are.

817
00:34:34,610 --> 00:34:35,990
我爱你
I love you.

818
00:34:36,460 --> 00:34:37,870
我也爱你
I love you too.

819
00:34:54,430 --> 00:34:55,930
惊喜
Surprise.

820
00:34:56,250 --> 00:34:56,950
-怎么了  -你得离开
- What? What? - You have to go.

821
00:34:56,950 --> 00:34:58,130
-你说什么  -她在这儿
- What are you talking about? - She's here.

822
00:34:58,130 --> 00:35:01,590
洛根  门外有人吗
Logan, is there somebody at the door?

823
00:35:01,810 --> 00:35:03,080
她只是...
Just...

824
00:35:03,530 --> 00:35:06,400
我...我是皮尔逊-哈德曼的
I am, um... I'm from Pearson Hardman,

825
00:35:06,400 --> 00:35:09,970
我有几份文件要给你丈夫
and I--I had a few files to bring your husband.

826
00:35:11,420 --> 00:35:12,680
文件呢
Where are they?

827
00:35:14,740 --> 00:35:16,280
就...就在这儿
They're--they're right here.

828
00:35:21,450 --> 00:35:22,710
出去
Get out.

829
00:35:23,020 --> 00:35:24,550
艾莉森  怎么了
Allison, what the hell?

830
00:35:24,550 --> 00:35:26,020
现在是早上7点30
It is 7:30 in the morning.

831
00:35:26,020 --> 00:35:27,320
你当我是傻子吗
You think I'm an idiot?

832
00:35:27,320 --> 00:35:28,300
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

833
00:35:28,300 --> 00:35:29,730
我知道就是她
I know that that's her.

834
00:35:29,730 --> 00:35:31,230
天哪  我都说了我没有...
God, I told you I'm not--

835
00:35:31,230 --> 00:35:33,140
别再骗我了
Stop lying to me.

836
00:35:33,140 --> 00:35:35,290
至少像个男人一样承认  那就是她
At least be a man and admit that that's her.

837
00:35:35,290 --> 00:35:36,780
我根本不认识那个女人  好吗
I don't even know that girl, okay?

838
00:35:36,780 --> 00:35:38,390
而且你觉得即使我要搞外遇
And you think that if I was having an affair

839
00:35:38,390 --> 00:35:41,980
我会和我父亲律所的律师助理搞吗
that I would have it with a paralegal from my father's firm?

840
00:35:57,770 --> 00:35:59,030
瑞秋
Rachel.

841
00:35:59,620 --> 00:36:01,770
我希望你能停止对迈克进行个人攻击
I want you to stop the personal attacks on Mike.

842
00:36:01,770 --> 00:36:03,370
我知道那听上去很糟  不过...
I know. It sounds terrible, but--

843
00:36:03,370 --> 00:36:04,540
游戏就是这么玩的
And it's how the game is played.

844
00:36:04,540 --> 00:36:05,690
我不在乎
I don't care.

845
00:36:05,690 --> 00:36:07,350
我要你停手
I want you to stop.

846
00:36:08,970 --> 00:36:11,780
我们能进来谈吗
Look, can we talk about this inside, please?

847
00:36:18,610 --> 00:36:19,470
我明白你...
I understand that you--

848
00:36:19,470 --> 00:36:22,550
不  听着  你说你已经改头换面了
No, look, you say you're a changed man,

849
00:36:22,550 --> 00:36:26,200
可你现在所做的事  并没有变好
but what you're doing now, it's not a change for the better.

850
00:36:26,200 --> 00:36:27,570
而是变得更糟了
It's for the worse.

851
00:36:27,570 --> 00:36:29,430
你告诉我说这没问题的
You told me this wasn't gonna be a problem.

852
00:36:29,430 --> 00:36:34,400
而你曾站在这里跟我说过
And you stood right here and told me

853
00:36:34,400 --> 00:36:36,460
你不爱你的妻子
that you didn't love your wife.

854
00:36:36,850 --> 00:36:38,540
但是三个月后
And then three months later,

855
00:36:38,540 --> 00:36:42,690
你求我替你撒谎来让她回心转意
you asked me to lie for you, so you could get her back.

856
00:36:42,690 --> 00:36:44,760
-瑞秋  -我要你停手
- Rachel-- - You don't have to stop this

857
00:36:44,760 --> 00:36:47,030
不是因为你已经改过自新
because you're some changed man.

858
00:36:48,020 --> 00:36:51,360
我要你停手  洛根  因为你欠我的
You have to stop this, Logan, because you owe me.

859
00:36:56,940 --> 00:36:58,210
好的
Okay.

860
00:37:00,250 --> 00:37:01,520
那就好
Okay.

861
00:37:08,880 --> 00:37:10,150
路易
Louis.

862
00:37:10,220 --> 00:37:12,550
我昨晚熬夜了  今天还没顾上喝咖啡
Listen, I was up late, I haven't had my coffee,

863
00:37:12,550 --> 00:37:16,410
不管什么事  能不能一个小时后再说
so can we talk about whatever this is in, like, an hour?

864
00:37:16,410 --> 00:37:17,720
不用太长时间
I'll be quick.

865
00:37:18,510 --> 00:37:20,240
我今早碰见了你的对头
I ran into your enemy this morning.

866
00:37:20,240 --> 00:37:21,880
还记得亚当·格里夫斯吗
You remember Adam Grieves?

867
00:37:22,780 --> 00:37:25,300
他让我转告你
He asked me to tell you that you guys

868
00:37:25,300 --> 00:37:26,800
你们周三还照常打球
are still on for ball on Wednesday.

869
00:37:26,800 --> 00:37:27,520
听我说  路易
Listen, Louis--

870
00:37:27,520 --> 00:37:29,490
你和我说的一切都是扯淡
Everything you told me, it was bullshit.

871
00:37:30,200 --> 00:37:32,150
你不是想和我上床
You're not trying to get into my pants.

872
00:37:33,340 --> 00:37:35,050
你是想和杰西卡上床
You're trying to get into Jessica's.

873
00:37:36,480 --> 00:37:38,160
你觉得你可以靠色相往上爬
You thought you could move your way up the ladder,

874
00:37:38,160 --> 00:37:40,980
所以你就利用我的友谊去拍她的马屁
and you used my friendship to cozy up to her.

875
00:37:40,980 --> 00:37:42,570
路易  不是这样的
Louis, that's just not true.

876
00:37:42,570 --> 00:37:44,110
那是什么
Well, then, what is it?

877
00:37:45,440 --> 00:37:48,790
你为什么撒谎让我退出这个案子
Why did you lie to me to get me off this case?

878
00:37:55,310 --> 00:37:59,050
我有漏了什么吗  杰夫
Tell me what I'm missing here, Jeff.

879
00:38:04,100 --> 00:38:05,540
就知道我是对的
That's what I thought.

880
00:38:05,540 --> 00:38:06,750
路易  别这样
Louis, please--

881
00:38:06,750 --> 00:38:10,810
我就这么一次放下戒心
For once I let my guard down and believed that someone

882
00:38:10,810 --> 00:38:13,820
相信有人会没有私心真的喜欢我
genuinely liked me without a hidden agenda.

883
00:38:16,930 --> 00:38:19,180
我再也不会犯这样的错误了
I will not make that mistake again.

884
00:38:33,490 --> 00:38:35,170
我来见迈克·罗斯
I'm here to see Mike Ross.

885
00:38:36,950 --> 00:38:38,400
你在这里干什么
What the hell are you doing here?

886
00:38:39,220 --> 00:38:40,580
我来见你
I came to see you.

887
00:38:41,730 --> 00:38:42,990
我还要开会
I have a meeting.

888
00:38:43,720 --> 00:38:45,760
我是来道歉的
I came to apologize.

889
00:38:47,550 --> 00:38:48,850
为了什么
For what?

890
00:38:49,460 --> 00:38:50,890
为我想要不光彩的赢
For trying to win dirty.

891
00:38:52,010 --> 00:38:55,550
我不能改变我已经做的事  但我会停手
I can't undo what I've already done, but I can stop doing it.

892
00:38:56,150 --> 00:38:57,770
我不想靠那种手段取胜
I don't want to win that way.

893
00:39:00,400 --> 00:39:04,220
这都是些拿来欺骗公众的话
That sounds like something your publicist would tell Forbes.

894
00:39:05,860 --> 00:39:07,820
还是说说你来此的真正原因吧
Why don't you tell me why you're really here?

895
00:39:09,120 --> 00:39:10,530
你想听真话
You want the truth?

896
00:39:13,030 --> 00:39:14,670
我不想伤害瑞秋
I don't want to hurt Rachel.

897
00:39:38,000 --> 00:39:39,260
沃尔特
Walter.

898
00:39:40,790 --> 00:39:42,350
我和你没什么好说的
I have nothing to say to you.

899
00:39:42,350 --> 00:39:43,900
沃尔特  求你了
Walter, please.

900
00:39:45,140 --> 00:39:46,630
给你半分钟时间
You have 30 seconds.

901
00:39:46,630 --> 00:39:49,710
好的  听着  我明白
Okay, look, I get it.

902
00:39:50,170 --> 00:39:51,580
我努力想告诉你事情有更多隐情
I tried to tell you there's more to the story.

903
00:39:51,580 --> 00:39:52,340
你之前不想听
You didn't want to hear it then,

904
00:39:52,340 --> 00:39:53,980
现在也还是不想听
and you don't want to hear it now.

905
00:39:53,980 --> 00:39:56,300
但你需要知道这个
But you need to hear this.

906
00:39:56,590 --> 00:39:58,130
不管你喜不喜欢我
Whether you like me or not,

907
00:39:58,130 --> 00:39:59,640
我是唯一支持你的人
I am the only one in your corner,

908
00:39:59,640 --> 00:40:00,970
你心里明白
and you know it.

909
00:40:02,470 --> 00:40:06,790
我创建这家公司的时候只有自己可以相信
I started this company with no one to trust but myself.

910
00:40:07,070 --> 00:40:08,820
如果我离开的时候也是这样
That's how I go out,

911
00:40:09,110 --> 00:40:10,720
那就这样吧  我们结束了
so be it. We're done.

912
00:40:10,760 --> 00:40:11,660
我很遗憾听你这样说
Well, I'm sorry to hear that,

913
00:40:11,660 --> 00:40:13,700
因为无论如何还是会支持你
because I'm gonna be in your corner anyway.

914
00:40:14,630 --> 00:40:17,080
我刚刚又买了你的公司2%的股份
I just bought another 2% of your stock,

915
00:40:17,500 --> 00:40:19,020
也就是说不管你参不参与
which means I'm saving your company

916
00:40:19,020 --> 00:40:22,180
我都要救你的公司
with or without you.

917
00:40:24,610 --> 00:40:27,440
时间到了  我再也不想看见你
Time's up. I don't want to see you again.

918
00:40:48,850 --> 00:40:50,620
杰夫  现在已经很晚了
Jeff, it's late.

919
00:40:50,620 --> 00:40:52,100
我不是来说我们之间的事
It's not about us.

920
00:40:55,580 --> 00:40:56,660
是伍德尔
Woodall.

921
00:40:56,660 --> 00:40:57,980
开战了
It started.

922
00:40:58,830 --> 00:41:00,130
多少
How many?

923
00:41:00,350 --> 00:41:02,910
七名客户  七张传票
Seven clients, seven subpoenas,

924
00:41:02,910 --> 00:41:04,500
明天都会到
all coming tomorrow.

925
00:41:08,290 --> 00:41:10,670
该是你体现价值的时候了
It's time for you to start earning your money.

926
00:41:28,180 --> 00:41:29,730
你给我买礼物了吗
You get me a present?

927
00:41:30,940 --> 00:41:32,290
是迈克给的
It's from Mike.

928
00:41:35,960 --> 00:41:37,550
这是我爸爸的唱片母带
It's my dad's tapes.

929
00:41:38,200 --> 00:41:39,780
他说它们是你的了
He said they're yours.

930
00:41:40,900 --> 00:41:42,390
你说服他让步了
You got him to back down.

931
00:41:42,560 --> 00:41:45,470
没有  但是我说服洛根让步了
No, but I got Logan to back off.

932
00:41:47,520 --> 00:41:48,970
你怎么做到的
How'd you manage that?

933
00:41:50,380 --> 00:41:52,210
那是我和客户之间的事
It's between me and my client.

934
00:41:55,750 --> 00:41:58,040
你知道你可以先来找我的
You know, you could have come to me first.

935
00:41:59,010 --> 00:42:00,740
我现在不是来了吗
I'm coming to you now.

