1
00:00:00,170 --> 00:00:01,400
《訴訟雙雄》前情提要

2
00:00:01,480 --> 00:00:03,050
艾娃·海辛頓  你被捕了
Ava Hessington, you're under arrest.

3
00:00:03,050 --> 00:00:04,400
蓄意謀殺
Conspiracy to commit murder.

4
00:00:04,400 --> 00:00:06,150
如果你想要拍合伙人的馬屁
If you're looking to ride Some partner's coattails,

5
00:00:06,150 --> 00:00:07,640
那還請你另尋他人
you're gonna have to look somewhere else.

6
00:00:07,880 --> 00:00:10,070
史蒂芬·亨特利  資深合伙人  倫敦分公司
Stephen Huntley, senior partner, London office.

7
00:00:10,190 --> 00:00:12,400
我想讓你找出這家伙的目的
I want you to find out what the hell that guy's up to.

8
00:00:13,290 --> 00:00:14,850
我知道你跟愛德華的協議
I know about your deal with Edward.

9
00:00:14,850 --> 00:00:16,800
這件事我不需要你來當我保姆
I don't need you baby-sitting me on this case.

10
00:00:16,800 --> 00:00:18,850
托尼·揚諾普洛斯拿到了那盤錄像
Tony Gianopolous got a hold of that video.

11
00:00:18,850 --> 00:00:20,280
我覺得他在試圖控制你們的公司
I think he's trying to take over the company.

12
00:00:20,380 --> 00:00:22,620
你讓我接受這個協議
You told me to take this deal.

13
00:00:22,620 --> 00:00:24,350
我照做了  看看我現在哪兒
I did, and now here I am.

14
00:00:24,500 --> 00:00:26,060
我不知道有這些謀殺
I didn't know about these murders.

15
00:00:26,060 --> 00:00:28,380
你或許不相信  事實上我也一無所知
What you don't seem to believe is neither did I.

16
00:00:28,710 --> 00:00:30,040
你再也不是傻瓜了  路易
You're not the fool anymore, Louis.

17
00:00:30,040 --> 00:00:31,230
邁克·羅斯才是
Mike Ross is.

18
00:00:31,870 --> 00:00:32,840
而且潑出去的水我也收不回來了
And I can't take it back.

19
00:00:32,850 --> 00:00:34,970
你在這公司里已經沒有未來了
Your future at this firm is over.

20
00:00:34,970 --> 00:00:36,670
這是所有關于托尼·揚諾普洛斯的資料
This is everything I have on Tony Gianopolous.

21
00:00:36,920 --> 00:00:38,090
歡迎加入利特團隊
Welcome to Team Litt.

22
00:00:39,340 --> 00:00:41,750
我們剛承認了在為一名謀殺犯辯護
We just admitted to each other that we're defending a murderer.

23
00:00:42,110 --> 00:00:44,070
不像個值得慶祝的事
It doesn't really seem like cause for celebration.

24
00:00:44,080 --> 00:00:45,130
不是慶祝
It's not a celebration.

25
00:00:45,140 --> 00:00:46,160
我跟達比說好
I made a deal with Darby

26
00:00:46,170 --> 00:00:47,970
要從杰西卡手里接下事務所
to take over the firm from Jessica.

27
00:00:48,050 --> 00:00:51,590
人人影視
YYeTs.com

28
00:00:48,050 --> 00:00:51,590
原創翻譯  中文字幕

29
00:00:48,050 --> 00:00:51,590
■

30
00:00:48,050 --> 00:00:51,590
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com

31
00:00:51,560 --> 00:00:55,500
翻譯：愛卿遛小鳥 圈圈 噎死青春 某豚 妄想的絨布熊

32
00:00:55,560 --> 00:01:01,500
翻譯：Reginamoon 宅女之后 士也瓜 珞小娘 阿囧 咕嘰

33
00:01:01,560 --> 00:01:05,500
校對：油炸電風扇  賀天天

34
00:01:05,560 --> 00:01:10,500
時間軸：sinagujia  憑陵新月

35
00:01:10,560 --> 00:01:15,560
后期：阿丟丟     總監：swears

36
00:01:22,890 --> 00:01:24,240
海辛頓石油奪權戰況升溫

37
00:01:29,600 --> 00:01:30,840
-聽說了嗎  -聽說了
- You heard? - I heard.

38
00:01:30,970 --> 00:01:33,440
-48小時后就要投票了  -她不會輸的
- Vote's in 48 hours. - She's not losing that vote.

39
00:01:33,530 --> 00:01:35,620
-我處理我的事  -我處理我的
- I'm getting my shit. - I got my shit.

40
00:01:35,620 --> 00:01:37,370
-會議室見  -五分鐘后到
- Conference room. - Five minutes.

41
00:01:42,720 --> 00:01:43,620
她在這里干什么
What is she doing here?

42
00:01:43,620 --> 00:01:44,890
她是我的新任律師助理
She's my new associate.

43
00:01:45,140 --> 00:01:46,700
所以你才做了那個視頻
So that's why you made the video.

44
00:01:46,740 --> 00:01:48,560
她讓你覺得她真誠待你
You seem upset that she led you to believe

45
00:01:48,560 --> 00:01:49,620
結果卻背叛了你
that she was trying to befriend you

46
00:01:49,620 --> 00:01:51,290
你好像挺生氣的
when it turned out she was gonna betray you.

47
00:01:51,550 --> 00:01:53,300
-路易  -有意見嗎
- Louis. - You got a problem with that?

48
00:01:53,300 --> 00:01:54,510
沒  沒意見
No. No problem.

49
00:01:54,510 --> 00:01:56,020
只要你干爹在這就行
Not as long as your daddy's here.

50
00:01:56,090 --> 00:01:57,740
我還要再跟你談一次話嗎
Do I have to have another talk with you?

51
00:01:57,740 --> 00:01:59,380
-他跟你談過話嗎  -是的
- He had a talk with you? - Yes.

52
00:01:59,520 --> 00:02:01,550
但我覺得沒必要找你保護我
But I didn't feel the need to run to you to protect me.

53
00:02:01,550 --> 00:02:03,130
誰叫你是備胎呢
Second choice never does.

54
00:02:03,140 --> 00:02:04,200
沒想到這會議室里
I can't believe it's up to me

55
00:02:04,200 --> 00:02:05,460
思想成熟的人只有我一個
to be the adult in the room.

56
00:02:05,460 --> 00:02:07,450
也許該談正事了吧
Maybe it's time we get down to business.

57
00:02:07,450 --> 00:02:09,070
好  第一件正事就是
Good, because the first order of business

58
00:02:09,070 --> 00:02:11,490
談談艾娃作完證供之后怎么辦
is discussing what to do following Ava's statement.

59
00:02:11,500 --> 00:02:12,760
她不會作證供的
She's not making a statement.

60
00:02:12,770 --> 00:02:14,380
-她會的  -要是艾娃作證供了
- Yes, she is. - Ava makes a statement,

61
00:02:14,380 --> 00:02:15,480
卡梅隆一定會緊追不放
Cameron's gonna be all over it.

62
00:02:15,480 --> 00:02:17,190
現在問題不在卡梅隆·丹尼斯
Cameron Dennis isn't the problem right now.

63
00:02:17,190 --> 00:02:19,860
問題在于艾娃·海辛頓是個不可靠的總裁
The problem is Ava Hessington isn't a credible CEO.

64
00:02:19,860 --> 00:02:22,450
問題在于她因被控謀殺而受審
The problem is she's on trial for murder.

65
00:02:22,450 --> 00:02:24,450
大眾都認為她有罪
And public perception says that she's as guilty

66
00:02:24,450 --> 00:02:26,530
就跟偷了面包的冉·阿讓一樣
as Jean Valjean with a loaf of bread in his pants.

67
00:02:24,450 --> 00:02:26,530
冉·阿讓  《悲慘世界》主角  因偷取面包被判處十九年苦役

68
00:02:26,530 --> 00:02:28,120
以防你還不清楚目前的形勢
And in case you are not up on current events,

69
00:02:28,120 --> 00:02:30,710
兩天后就要投票決定公司歸誰了
we're facing a vote for control of her company in two days.

70
00:02:30,710 --> 00:02:32,940
迫于威脅去作證供會顯得她很絕望
Talking under threat makes her look desperate.

71
00:02:32,940 --> 00:02:35,540
但不作證供會顯得她有罪或不夠稱職
And not talking makes her look either guilty or incompetent.

72
00:02:35,540 --> 00:02:36,820
我們得讓華爾街的人看看
We need to send the message to Wall Street

73
00:02:36,830 --> 00:02:38,790
她執掌大權  沒什么要隱瞞的
that she's in control and she's got nothing to hide.

74
00:02:38,790 --> 00:02:40,010
開這個會是為了
This is a meeting about

75
00:02:40,010 --> 00:02:43,480
在不危及謀殺辯護的前提下保住艾娃的公司
how to keep Ava's company without endangering her murder defense.

76
00:02:43,480 --> 00:02:45,200
你有沒有想過  她既然如此冷血
Did it ever occur to you that, if she's cold enough

77
00:02:45,200 --> 00:02:47,100
能殺了反對石油管道的人
to kill off opposition to her pipeline,

78
00:02:47,100 --> 00:02:49,140
就也能在媒體面前撒謊
she's cold enough to pull off lying to the press?

79
00:02:49,690 --> 00:02:52,750
大家心知肚明是她殺了人  對吧
I mean, we all know she did this, right?

80
00:02:56,780 --> 00:02:58,370
這個問題沒有商量的余地
This isn't open for discussion.

81
00:02:58,550 --> 00:02:59,770
她什么都不會說的
She's not saying a word.

82
00:03:00,110 --> 00:03:01,410
恐怕太遲了
I'm afraid it's too late.

83
00:03:01,920 --> 00:03:03,110
你干了什么
What did you do?

84
00:03:03,120 --> 00:03:04,670
她已經在去接受采訪的路上了
She's on her way to an interview right now.

85
00:03:04,670 --> 00:03:05,640
報刊雜志會刊登出來
It'll run in the journal,

86
00:03:05,640 --> 00:03:06,700
到時候就能一舉擊潰
and then it will blow Gianopolous

87
00:03:06,700 --> 00:03:08,770
揚諾普洛斯的狗屁收購企圖
and his bullshit takeover attempt out of the water.

88
00:03:14,910 --> 00:03:16,950
-我是康納利  -康納利先生  很抱歉
- Connelly. - Mr. Connelly, I do apologize,

89
00:03:16,950 --> 00:03:19,460
恐怕得換個地方進行采訪了
but I'm afraid we have to change the location of our interview.

90
00:03:19,460 --> 00:03:21,750
-你哪位  -我是海辛頓女士的助理
- Who is this? - Miss Hessington's assistant.

91
00:03:21,750 --> 00:03:23,590
我今早才跟她助理談過...
Well, I spoke to her assistant this morning--

92
00:03:23,590 --> 00:03:26,230
是的  麗貝卡負責海辛頓女士的日程安排
Yes, Rebecca handles Miss Hessington's schedule.

93
00:03:26,230 --> 00:03:27,700
我負責她的日常生活
I handle her life.

94
00:03:28,490 --> 00:03:29,910
怎么  那我就得滿城跑
What, so I'm supposed to traipse all over town

95
00:03:29,910 --> 00:03:31,040
來迎合她的喜好嗎
because of what she'd prefer?

96
00:03:31,040 --> 00:03:33,620
-不是喜好  是堅持  -堅持
- Not prefer. Insist. - Insist?

97
00:03:33,620 --> 00:03:35,800
我給她一次機會聽聽她的說法
I'm giving her a forum to tell her side of the story.

98
00:03:35,800 --> 00:03:38,590
是一次獨家采訪機會  而原本并非如此
An exclusive forum which needn't be the case.

99
00:03:38,590 --> 00:03:40,150
別弄錯了  康納利先生
Now make no mistake, Mr. Connelly,

100
00:03:40,150 --> 00:03:42,260
是海辛頓女士幫了你一個忙
Miss Hessington is the one doing the favor here.

101
00:03:42,260 --> 00:03:43,630
如果你想跟她談談的話
So, if you'd like to speak with her,

102
00:03:43,630 --> 00:03:46,400
我的司機很愿意送你去見她
my driver will be more than happy to take you to her.

103
00:03:46,690 --> 00:03:49,320
或者你想打給麗貝卡
Or if you would prefer to call Rebecca,

104
00:03:49,330 --> 00:03:51,740
我肯定她可以另約時間的
I'm sure she'll be able to set something up for you.

105
00:03:51,740 --> 00:03:54,560
明年十二月份怎么樣
Sometime say next December.

106
00:04:09,480 --> 00:04:10,710
點吧
Go ahead and order.

107
00:04:11,290 --> 00:04:12,660
康納利會晚到一些
Connelly's running a little late.

108
00:04:12,770 --> 00:04:13,750
他到這里
He should get here

109
00:04:13,760 --> 00:04:15,620
應該會在我勸完你不要參加采訪十分鐘之后
at ten past "You're not giving an interview."

110
00:04:15,810 --> 00:04:17,590
我沒想瞞著你
I wasn't trying to keep this from you.

111
00:04:17,600 --> 00:04:19,940
你也沒把備忘錄抄送給我一份
You didn't exactly CC me on the memo.

112
00:04:20,060 --> 00:04:21,910
好吧  你想聽實話嗎
Very well. You want the truth?

113
00:04:22,950 --> 00:04:25,940
我不喜歡三緘其口默不作聲
I don't particularly appreciate being muzzled.

114
00:04:25,940 --> 00:04:27,890
等幫你免除下半輩子牢獄之災的時候
I suggest you don't think of it as muzzled so much

115
00:04:27,890 --> 00:04:30,020
你就不會不喜歡了吧
as keeping you out of jail for the rest of your life.

116
00:04:30,050 --> 00:04:32,820
那你讓我怎么做  哈維
And what'll you have me do, Harvey, hmm?

117
00:04:32,820 --> 00:04:34,460
去圣巴茨島躲一周嗎
Take a week in St. Barts?

118
00:04:34,580 --> 00:04:36,050
絕對不可能
Because that is not going to happen.

119
00:04:36,050 --> 00:04:37,170
我知道這是不可能的
I know that's not going to happen.

120
00:04:37,170 --> 00:04:38,560
你涉嫌謀殺呢
You're on trial for murder.

121
00:04:38,600 --> 00:04:40,830
正因此  我們家族的公司
And because of that a tender offer's being made

122
00:04:40,830 --> 00:04:42,770
要被別公司競標收購
on a company with my family name.

123
00:04:43,510 --> 00:04:45,820
都到這個地步了  我竟然還沒有
And with all that going on, the fact that I haven't made

124
00:04:45,820 --> 00:04:48,240
發表聲明為自己辯護  真是扯淡
a statement defending myself is bullshit.

125
00:04:48,240 --> 00:04:49,950
不是扯淡  是聰明的表現
It's not bullshit. It's smart.

126
00:04:49,950 --> 00:04:51,270
你當然會這么想了
Of course you see it that way.

127
00:04:51,870 --> 00:04:53,350
你認為我是有罪的
You think I'm guilty.

128
00:04:53,360 --> 00:04:55,770
我已經跟你說過了  我怎么想無所謂
I've told you before it doesn't matter what I think.

129
00:04:55,770 --> 00:04:57,600
但如果你以為自己說自己是清白的
But if you think saying you're innocent

130
00:04:57,600 --> 00:04:59,670
就能讓大家相信你  是不可能的
is gonna make people believe you, it won't.

131
00:04:59,780 --> 00:05:01,550
你知道什么人說自己是清白的嗎
Because you know who says they're innocent?

132
00:05:02,080 --> 00:05:03,110
所有人
Everybody.

133
00:05:03,210 --> 00:05:06,040
每一天  我一言不發
Every day I keep my mouth shut,

134
00:05:06,040 --> 00:05:07,790
我們的股價就會暴跌
our stock takes a dive,

135
00:05:07,790 --> 00:05:09,810
這讓我很被動
and that makes me vulnerable.

136
00:05:09,840 --> 00:05:10,610
我知道
I get it.

137
00:05:10,610 --> 00:05:11,730
你想讓全世界相信
You want to convince the world

138
00:05:11,730 --> 00:05:13,490
你和那些謀殺案無關
you're not responsible for these murders

139
00:05:13,490 --> 00:05:15,330
好繼續控制自己的大石油公司
so you can keep control of your big oil company.

140
00:05:15,330 --> 00:05:16,520
我沒這么說
That is not what I said.

141
00:05:16,520 --> 00:05:19,170
但是卡梅隆·丹尼斯會讓事情聽起來如此
Well, that's how Cameron Dennis is gonna make it sound.

142
00:05:19,610 --> 00:05:22,510
艾娃  這次審判事關你的生死
Ava, you're on trial for your life.

143
00:05:22,510 --> 00:05:24,390
公司就是我的生命
This company is my life.

144
00:05:24,390 --> 00:05:26,490
事情表面看上去正會如此
And that's exactly what it's gonna look like--

145
00:05:26,550 --> 00:05:29,310
貪婪的石油巨頭用沾滿鮮血的雙手
A greedy oil exec clinging to her money factory

146
00:05:29,310 --> 00:05:31,040
死死抓住血汗工廠不放
with her blood-stained hands.

147
00:05:31,530 --> 00:05:32,530
好吧
Very well.

148
00:05:32,650 --> 00:05:33,850
我明白你的意思了
You've made your point.

149
00:05:34,980 --> 00:05:39,140
現在你最好想辦法讓我脫離所有困境
Now I suggest you find a way to get me out of both situations

150
00:05:39,140 --> 00:05:41,410
我是不會把自己的公司
'cause I am not losing control of my company

151
00:05:41,500 --> 00:05:42,850
拱手讓給托尼·揚諾普洛斯的
to Tony Gianopolous.

152
00:06:24,430 --> 00:06:25,510
新裙子呦
New dress?

153
00:06:25,570 --> 00:06:28,000
我能說什么呢   好馬配好鞍
What can I say, it deserved me.

154
00:06:28,150 --> 00:06:29,370
是什么重要場合
What's the occasion?

155
00:06:29,480 --> 00:06:31,560
女孩看起來光彩四射需要理由嗎
Does a girl need a reason to look spectacular?

156
00:06:32,470 --> 00:06:33,820
給我加糖
Sugar me.

157
00:06:33,920 --> 00:06:35,390
在你們互相甜蜜之前
Um, before anyone sugars anyone,

158
00:06:35,400 --> 00:06:37,200
如果你們在約會的話
if you two are dating,

159
00:06:37,200 --> 00:06:39,970
需要知道  我們公司在這方面
you need to know that we have A very strict policy

160
00:06:40,400 --> 00:06:41,500
有非常嚴格的規定
in favor of that.

161
00:06:41,590 --> 00:06:43,900
我們也有非常嚴格的規定
And we have a very strict policy

162
00:06:44,270 --> 00:06:46,140
自己的糖  自己做主
to keep our sugar to ourselves.

163
00:06:46,140 --> 00:06:47,300
那太遺憾了
Oh, that's a pity.

164
00:06:49,310 --> 00:06:52,370
今天早上我還想吃點甜的
I'm partial to a little sweetness in the morning.

165
00:06:53,590 --> 00:06:56,040
那我推薦52號大街上的面包房
Well, then I would recommend the bakery on 52nd.

166
00:06:56,050 --> 00:06:56,980
能賞光跟我一起去嗎
You care to join me?

167
00:06:57,180 --> 00:06:59,280
我不想否認我很想跟你一起去
I hate to deny you the pleasure of my company.

168
00:06:59,590 --> 00:07:01,270
我看我還是算了
I think I can manage without it.

169
00:07:01,910 --> 00:07:03,310
鑒于你來自于不同的國家
Since you're from a different country,

170
00:07:03,310 --> 00:07:04,160
我給你翻譯下
I'll translate:

171
00:07:04,170 --> 00:07:06,290
她是覺得你太娘了  親愛的
She finds you a bit douchey, love.

172
00:07:07,420 --> 00:07:08,410
是我的損失
My loss.

173
00:07:13,380 --> 00:07:14,370
失陪
Ladies.

174
00:07:17,000 --> 00:07:19,900
這個男人真是個問題啊
Oh, that man is trouble.

175
00:07:20,860 --> 00:07:22,380
沒事  我能應付的了
It's okay. I can handle it.

176
00:07:22,420 --> 00:07:23,210
不用  沒關系的
Oh, no, it's okay.

177
00:07:23,210 --> 00:07:24,190
我不需要你的幫助
I don't need you to.

178
00:07:25,050 --> 00:07:27,120
等等  咱們在說什么呢
Wait. What are we talking about?

179
00:07:27,720 --> 00:07:28,940
他喜歡我啊
The fact that he's into me.

180
00:07:29,100 --> 00:07:30,560
你神游去了嗎  他喜歡的是我
Were you here? He's into me.

181
00:07:30,790 --> 00:07:32,640
那為什么他的目光都在我身上
Then why was I the one getting all the stares?

182
00:07:33,580 --> 00:07:35,820
難道你沒聽說過  追求第二美女
Haven't you ever heard, "Go after the second prettiest

183
00:07:35,820 --> 00:07:37,100
以吸引第一美女嗎
to get the prettiest's attention"?

184
00:07:37,260 --> 00:07:38,690
從沒聽說過
No, I've never heard that.

185
00:07:38,690 --> 00:07:40,090
就是這個樣子
Well, it's a thing.

186
00:07:41,660 --> 00:07:43,070
你是說我只是第二美女嗎
Are you saying I'm the second prettiest?

187
00:07:43,650 --> 00:07:46,320
對他來說而已
I'm saying you are to him.

188
00:07:48,620 --> 00:07:50,820
這件裙子
Oh, the dress.

189
00:07:50,870 --> 00:07:52,180
-他約你了  -上周
- He asked you out? - Last week.

190
00:07:52,180 --> 00:07:53,130
-然后你  -我沒同意
- And? - I passed.

191
00:07:53,140 --> 00:07:54,680
-為什么  -我為什么要同意跟他出去
- Why? - Why should I go out with him?

192
00:07:54,680 --> 00:07:55,970
就因為他性感有魅力嗎
Just because he's charming and hot?

193
00:07:55,970 --> 00:07:58,130
-還詼諧幽默有風度  -還有頭銜
- And witty and british. - And has a title.

194
00:07:58,130 --> 00:07:59,250
-真的嗎  -假的
- He does? - No.

195
00:07:59,250 --> 00:07:59,940
但即使他有
But even if he did,

196
00:07:59,940 --> 00:08:01,060
我也不會因為這個跟他出去的
that wouldn't be a reason.

197
00:08:01,060 --> 00:08:01,770
我說過了  小瑞
I told you, Rach,

198
00:08:01,770 --> 00:08:04,390
-公事私事分開談  -公事
- I don't mix business with pleasure. - Business?

199
00:08:04,700 --> 00:08:06,410
他只待六個禮拜
He's only here for six weeks.

200
00:08:06,700 --> 00:08:08,830
還是倫敦分公司的人
And he is based out of London.

201
00:08:08,850 --> 00:08:10,750
基本上是別家公司的人了
It's practically a different company.

202
00:08:10,750 --> 00:08:12,400
還是兩個不同國家
And it's definitely a different country.

203
00:08:12,400 --> 00:08:14,060
-考慮一下  -不要
- So you'll consider it? - Nope.

204
00:08:19,300 --> 00:08:20,790
艾娃·海辛頓怎么樣了
What's going on with Ava Hessington?

205
00:08:20,890 --> 00:08:23,000
我說服了她不要接受采訪
I convinced her not to give an interview.

206
00:08:23,370 --> 00:08:24,820
她原先怎么會覺得
How'd she get it in her head it'd be a good idea

207
00:08:24,820 --> 00:08:26,170
-這是個好主意  -路易
- in the first place? - Louis.

208
00:08:26,180 --> 00:08:27,920
路易知不知道她被控謀殺
Is he aware she's up for murder?

209
00:08:27,920 --> 00:08:29,980
他知不知道大部分人是不會在辦公室
Is he aware that most people don't line their offices

210
00:08:29,980 --> 00:08:32,230
-掛滿自己照片的  -顯然不知道
- with pictures of themselves? - Evidently not.

211
00:08:32,260 --> 00:08:34,270
知道他還掛著死掉寵物貓的照片嗎
You know he's still got one of his dead cat?

212
00:08:34,270 --> 00:08:35,920
就別挖苦那只貓了  哈維
Harvey, leave the cat alone.

213
00:08:36,550 --> 00:08:38,120
真是只傻貓
Stupid cat.

214
00:08:39,280 --> 00:08:41,120
你怎么敢干涉我的案子
How dare you sabotage my case?

215
00:08:41,160 --> 00:08:42,610
我屁也沒干涉
I didn't sabotage shit.

216
00:08:42,610 --> 00:08:44,320
你背著我偷偷安排了采訪
You set that thing up behind my back

217
00:08:44,320 --> 00:08:45,480
直到你覺得為時已晚
and you didn't tell me about it.

218
00:08:45,480 --> 00:08:46,780
才告訴我實情
until you thought it was too late.

219
00:08:46,780 --> 00:08:48,040
是啊  因為我知道一旦收購企圖
Yeah, because I knew the minute things heated up

220
00:08:48,040 --> 00:08:50,180
吸引世人注意  你就會要回我的案子
on the takeover attempt, you'd want to take my case back.

221
00:08:50,180 --> 00:08:51,710
要回你的案子
Take your case back?

222
00:08:51,780 --> 00:08:54,100
我不知道你對法律了解多少
I don't know how familiar you are with the game of law,

223
00:08:54,100 --> 00:08:56,410
但是謀殺案比收購案重要多了
but murder trumps takeover.

224
00:08:56,420 --> 00:08:58,300
-別一副居高臨下的  -路易
- You condescending piece of Sh-- - Louis.

225
00:08:58,610 --> 00:08:59,570
哈維說得對
Harvey's right.

226
00:09:00,000 --> 00:09:01,400
艾娃受謀殺指控時
The woman can't make public statements

227
00:09:01,400 --> 00:09:03,580
-是不能發表公開聲明的  -必殺
- while she's on trial for murder. - Trump.

228
00:09:03,580 --> 00:09:04,610
如果她什么也不說
Well, if she's gonna keep her mouth shut,

229
00:09:04,610 --> 00:09:05,630
那她就得主動讓位
then she's gonna have to step down

230
00:09:05,630 --> 00:09:07,930
-否則我們就輸定投票了  -讓她讓位
- or we're gonna lose this vote. - Asking her to step down

231
00:09:07,930 --> 00:09:09,530
就好比讓她砍掉自己的手臂
would be asking her to cut off her arm.

232
00:09:09,530 --> 00:09:10,890
如果不這么做  哈維
If we don't cut off her arm, Harvey,

233
00:09:10,890 --> 00:09:11,860
整個人都會死掉
We're gonna lose the patient.

234
00:09:11,870 --> 00:09:13,750
她是我的客戶  我不會允許這事發生的
She's my client. I'm not gonna let that happen.

235
00:09:13,750 --> 00:09:15,320
艾娃·海辛頓不是我的客戶
Ava Hessington is not my client.

236
00:09:15,320 --> 00:09:16,970
海辛頓石油才是
Hessington Oil is.

237
00:09:16,970 --> 00:09:19,990
他們每年能付我們一千四百萬
And they generate $14 million a year in billables.

238
00:09:19,990 --> 00:09:21,090
你沒在聽嗎
Have you not been listening?

239
00:09:21,090 --> 00:09:23,180
艾娃·海辛頓就是海辛頓石油
Ava hessington is Hessington Oil.

240
00:09:23,190 --> 00:09:24,200
不會太久了
Not for long.

241
00:09:24,500 --> 00:09:26,160
-你說什么  -路易說的沒錯
- Excuse me? - Louis is right.

242
00:09:27,140 --> 00:09:28,720
如果她現在讓位
If she steps down now,

243
00:09:28,720 --> 00:09:31,140
我們還可以贏得投票  保住這個客戶
we can still win the vote and keep them as a client.

244
00:09:31,140 --> 00:09:32,510
誰來說服她呢
Well, who's gonna convince her to do that?

245
00:09:32,510 --> 00:09:33,800
不用說服她
We don't have to convince her.

246
00:09:33,820 --> 00:09:34,660
直接找董事會的人就行
We can just go to the board.

247
00:09:34,660 --> 00:09:36,210
-不用告訴她  -好像你會這樣
- We don't even have to tell her. - Like hell you will

248
00:09:36,210 --> 00:09:37,560
好像我會放任不管
and like hell I won't.

249
00:09:37,600 --> 00:09:39,300
哈維  必須這么做
Harvey, this needs to happen.

250
00:09:39,300 --> 00:09:41,510
-我不會這么做的  -這是我的決定
- No, I won't do it. - This is my call.

251
00:09:43,570 --> 00:09:44,740
我恐怕不是你能決定的
I'm afraid it isn't.

252
00:09:47,080 --> 00:09:48,070
你說什么
Excuse me?

253
00:09:48,840 --> 00:09:51,730
我們都知道是誰給我指派的這個案子
You and I both know who assigned me to this case,

254
00:09:52,330 --> 00:09:53,440
并不是你
and it wasn't you.

255
00:09:53,920 --> 00:09:55,910
是你選擇合并公司的那個男人
It was the man you chose to merge with.

256
00:09:56,110 --> 00:09:59,930
他擁有我們事務所51%的股份
The same man who has a 51% share of our law firm.

257
00:09:59,930 --> 00:10:02,280
除非你能撤銷這次合并
So unless you're gonna undo that,

258
00:10:02,870 --> 00:10:04,330
你就好好忍著吧
you're gonna live with this.

259
00:10:06,890 --> 00:10:07,830
她生氣嗎
Was she pissed?

260
00:10:08,380 --> 00:10:09,570
肯定得生氣
I bet she was pissed.

261
00:10:09,570 --> 00:10:10,770
不過應該沒你生氣
Not as pissed as you're gonna be.

262
00:10:10,870 --> 00:10:12,150
你什么意思
What are you talking about?

263
00:10:12,490 --> 00:10:14,500
明后兩天你要和卡特里娜共事
You're on Katrina duty for the next two days.

264
00:10:14,500 --> 00:10:16,300
什么  我寧愿去看公共廁所呢
What? I'd rather be on latrine duty.

265
00:10:16,300 --> 00:10:18,460
-你沒得選  -好吧  我要擅離職守了
- it's not an option. - Okay, then I'm going AWOL.

266
00:10:18,510 --> 00:10:21,040
讓我幫你理一理  阿甘
Well, let me connect the dots for you, Forrest Gump.

267
00:10:21,490 --> 00:10:23,780
雖然杰西卡在策略上妥協了
Even though Jessica gave in on the strategy,

268
00:10:23,820 --> 00:10:26,240
但是路易表明他愿意犧牲艾娃
Louis made it clear he's willing to sacrifice Ava,

269
00:10:26,240 --> 00:10:27,940
別指望他能規規矩矩行事
and you don't trust him to play by the rules.

270
00:10:28,410 --> 00:10:30,990
所以你要和她一起工作
Which is why you're gonna work side by side with her

271
00:10:30,990 --> 00:10:32,570
找出方法殺出困境
to figure a way out of this jam.

272
00:10:32,590 --> 00:10:35,450
同時保證她和路易不會背后給一刀
And at the same time make sure she and Louis don't shaft us.

273
00:10:35,450 --> 00:10:36,800
挺聰明嗎  阿甘
Not bad, Forrest.

274
00:10:36,800 --> 00:10:40,040
阿甘軍中好友  兩人約定要做鮮蝦生意

275
00:10:36,800 --> 00:10:38,600
如果我是阿甘  你就是巴布
Okay, if I'm Forrest, then you're Bubba.

276
00:10:38,600 --> 00:10:40,130
-賣蝦啊  -哈維
- Shrimpin' bidness. - Harvey...

277
00:10:41,260 --> 00:10:42,650
如果艾娃丟掉了公司
If Ava loses her company,

278
00:10:42,650 --> 00:10:44,680
達比還會支持你成為執行合伙人嗎
will Darby still back you as managing partner?

279
00:10:44,680 --> 00:10:46,850
我沒問  但我肯定絕對不會
I didn't ask, but I sure as hell wouldn't.

280
00:10:54,430 --> 00:10:55,440
什么事  路易
What is it, Louis?

281
00:10:55,910 --> 00:10:58,650
我想感謝你之前支持我
I just wanted to thank you for backing me earlier.

282
00:10:58,750 --> 00:11:00,620
我支持你是因為你的策略是最優的
I had your back because you had the best strategy.

283
00:11:00,620 --> 00:11:01,730
仍然對我很重要
It still means a lot to me.

284
00:11:01,740 --> 00:11:03,190
我不知道哈維怎敢告訴你
And, you know, I don't know where Harvey gets off

285
00:11:03,190 --> 00:11:04,360
如何管理事務
telling you how to run things.

286
00:11:04,550 --> 00:11:06,280
沒事了  路易  我無所謂了
It's over, Louis. I'm moving on.

287
00:11:06,980 --> 00:11:07,950
沒必要無所謂
It doesn't have to be.

288
00:11:10,420 --> 00:11:12,020
你到底想說什么
What exactly are you proposing?

289
00:11:18,740 --> 00:11:20,610
讓我做你的黑天鵝
Allow me to be your black swan.

290
00:11:21,360 --> 00:11:23,220
你的職位妨礙你做的事
Let me do the things that your position precludes you

291
00:11:23,220 --> 00:11:24,150
我來做
from doing,

292
00:11:24,150 --> 00:11:27,770
比如不光彩的選擇  暗箱操作
the dark choices, the distasteful wet work.

293
00:11:27,880 --> 00:11:30,280
你是說  用堿液溶解尸體嗎
You mean like using lye to dissolve a human body?

294
00:11:30,280 --> 00:11:33,480
我是說  用謊言趕走一個討厭的執行總裁
I mean using lies to dislodge a pesky CEO.

295
00:11:33,480 --> 00:11:34,950
已經有人告訴我們不可以這么做了
Well, we've been told that's not an option.

296
00:11:34,960 --> 00:11:36,950
也許你不可以  但按我們剛達成的共識
Not for you, maybe, but as we just agreed,

297
00:11:37,040 --> 00:11:38,290
這是對董事會的正確選擇
it's the right option for the board.

298
00:11:38,460 --> 00:11:40,970
而哈維和他的廢柴主人
And Harvey and his master Lord Poppycock

299
00:11:40,970 --> 00:11:41,970
不用知道
don't have to know.

300
00:11:42,770 --> 00:11:45,300
路易  我真心欣賞你的提議  但
Louis, I appreciate your offer, I do, but--

301
00:11:45,710 --> 00:11:48,880
就這一次你站在我這邊  而不是他
But the one time you take my side over his,

302
00:11:48,880 --> 00:11:50,100
還不想為之盡力
you're not willing to fight for it.

303
00:11:50,110 --> 00:11:51,360
我是想努力
I'm willing to fight.

304
00:11:51,360 --> 00:11:53,040
只是不想背著達比干
I just won't do it behind Darby's back.

305
00:11:53,160 --> 00:11:55,050
我發誓  絕對不會查到你身上
Look, I swear it'll never come back to you.

306
00:11:55,770 --> 00:11:58,080
我的意思不是害怕被抓個正著
I didn't say I was afraid to get caught.

307
00:11:58,430 --> 00:12:00,240
我是說  我不想用那種方式來辦
I said I don't want to operate that way.

308
00:12:01,090 --> 00:12:02,250
失陪了
Now if you'll excuse me.

309
00:12:02,250 --> 00:12:04,150
需不需要我提醒你  你讓我背著哈維
Need I remind you you had me go behind Harvey's back

310
00:12:04,150 --> 00:12:05,720
和麥肯諾汽車公司做同樣的事
to do the same thing with McKernon Motors?

311
00:12:05,720 --> 00:12:07,170
兩者不一樣
That was not the same.

312
00:12:07,620 --> 00:12:08,530
我懂了
I get it.

313
00:12:09,420 --> 00:12:10,620
你當時權力在握
You were in charge then.

314
00:12:12,020 --> 00:12:13,290
現在不是了
You're not in charge anymore.

315
00:12:25,350 --> 00:12:26,380
都卡住了嗎
All jamed up?

316
00:12:26,740 --> 00:12:27,900
恐怕是
I'm afraid so.

317
00:12:28,370 --> 00:12:29,860
稍微耍點小手段就行
You just need to coax it a little.

318
00:12:30,170 --> 00:12:31,510
是嗎  那要怎么做
Oh, and how does one do that?

319
00:12:31,510 --> 00:12:32,730
摸一下就好了
Oh, it's all in the touch.

320
00:12:32,730 --> 00:12:34,070
我除了溫柔  還是溫柔
Well, I've been nothing but gentle.

321
00:12:34,760 --> 00:12:36,040
該溫柔的時候溫柔
There's a time to be gentle,

322
00:12:36,120 --> 00:12:37,650
該強硬的時候強硬
And there's a time to be firm.

323
00:12:40,360 --> 00:12:42,200
你該看看我是怎么對付傳真機的
You should see how I handle the fax.

324
00:12:43,880 --> 00:12:44,950
可以想象
I can imagine.

325
00:12:46,140 --> 00:12:47,810
要知道  事實上從你的能力來看
You know, in fact, given your skills,

326
00:12:47,810 --> 00:12:49,630
我覺得你大概是解決我短期需求的
I think you'd probably be the ideal person

327
00:12:49,630 --> 00:12:52,000
理想人選
to handle my short-term needs.

328
00:12:52,590 --> 00:12:54,450
我在美國這邊資源有限
See, I'm in the States on a limited basis,

329
00:12:54,450 --> 00:12:57,600
沒人能幫我減輕工作量
and I've got nobody to help me with my workload.

330
00:12:58,130 --> 00:12:59,110
我知道
I get it.

331
00:12:59,280 --> 00:13:01,080
你被迫事必躬親
You're forced to do everything yourself.

332
00:13:02,080 --> 00:13:03,420
太讓人精疲力竭了
It's getting exhausting.

333
00:13:04,170 --> 00:13:06,850
你需要找人幫你緩解壓力
And you need someone to help relieve the pressure.

334
00:13:08,460 --> 00:13:10,130
自然而然  我想到了你
Naturally, I thought of you.

335
00:13:10,350 --> 00:13:11,380
不是瑞秋嗎
Not Rachel?

336
00:13:11,400 --> 00:13:12,750
我覺得你知道答案
I think you know the answer to that.

337
00:13:13,190 --> 00:13:14,350
我當時知道
I knew it then.

338
00:13:14,580 --> 00:13:15,660
我知道你知道
I know you did.

339
00:13:16,640 --> 00:13:18,970
就是我在紐約的時候
It'll be a brief, casual arrangement

340
00:13:18,970 --> 00:13:19,910
為我做簡單輕松的安排
whilst I'm in New York.

341
00:13:19,910 --> 00:13:21,560
我的時間也只允許做這么多了
I wouldn't have time for anything more.

342
00:13:22,740 --> 00:13:23,860
那我們達成協議嘍
Then we have an agreement?

343
00:13:24,620 --> 00:13:25,670
我不知道
I don't know.

344
00:13:26,730 --> 00:13:27,920
你會是什么樣的老板呢
What kind of boss would you be?

345
00:13:27,920 --> 00:13:29,030
苛刻的
Demanding.

346
00:13:30,020 --> 00:13:32,310
-但很慷慨  -慷慨很好
- But very generous. - Generous is good.

347
00:13:32,570 --> 00:13:35,850
就像丹尼爾·戴·劉易斯演的麥克白
As is Daniel Day-Lewis doing Macbeth.

348
00:13:37,480 --> 00:13:38,930
你確實明白  這個協議
You do realize that this arrangement

349
00:13:38,930 --> 00:13:40,510
不會有任何文秘工作吧
would involve no secretarial work?

350
00:13:40,560 --> 00:13:42,110
有的話我才失望呢
I'd be disappointed if it did.

351
00:13:49,600 --> 00:13:52,200
-卡特里娜·班尼特  -聽您調遣
- Katrina Bennett. - At your service.

352
00:13:52,280 --> 00:13:53,590
老天  我喜歡這個聲音
God, I love the sound of that.

353
00:13:53,590 --> 00:13:54,670
你下令  我行動
Your wish is my command.

354
00:13:54,740 --> 00:13:55,590
我要你...
My wish is for you--

355
00:13:55,590 --> 00:13:57,300
和邁克·羅斯一起努力干活
To work hand in glove with Mike Ross

356
00:13:57,300 --> 00:13:58,670
打敗托尼·揚諾普洛斯
on getting rid of Tony Gianopolous,

357
00:13:58,670 --> 00:13:59,760
留意著他們在干什么
keep an eye on what they're doing

358
00:13:59,760 --> 00:14:01,430
同時別讓他們太明白
while at the same time limit their understanding

359
00:14:01,430 --> 00:14:02,250
我們在做什么  
of what we're doing.

360
00:14:02,260 --> 00:14:03,180
你是怎么都知道的
How do you know all that?

361
00:14:03,180 --> 00:14:04,270
-這是我的工作  -稍等片刻
- It's my job. - Wait a minute.

362
00:14:04,270 --> 00:14:05,420
我原以為你受不了邁克·羅斯
I thought you can't stand Mike Ross.

363
00:14:05,420 --> 00:14:06,750
突然之間你迫不及待想和他共事嗎
All of a sudden you're willing to work with him?

364
00:14:07,080 --> 00:14:07,970
這是我的工作  
It's my job.

365
00:14:07,970 --> 00:14:09,150
如果我讓你在下雨的冬夜
If I ask you to murder someone

366
00:14:09,150 --> 00:14:10,910
殺個人  你會作何反應呢
n a rainy winter's eve, how would you respond?

367
00:14:11,340 --> 00:14:13,010
用槍還是刀呢
You want a gun or a knife?

368
00:14:14,860 --> 00:14:16,510
如果你不那么迷人  我就會愛上你了
If you were less attractive, I'd love you.

369
00:14:17,260 --> 00:14:18,320
我知道
I know.

370
00:14:20,310 --> 00:14:23,280
路易  我們為什么不直接踢了艾娃·海辛頓
Louis, why aren't we just kicking Ava Hessington out?

371
00:14:23,280 --> 00:14:24,960
她還來不及搞清楚狀況就會滾蛋了
She'd be gone before she even knew what hit her.

372
00:14:25,470 --> 00:14:26,540
如果哈維有你一半的頭腦
If Harvey had half your brains,

373
00:14:26,540 --> 00:14:27,830
我們就會這么干了
that's exactly what we'd be doing.

374
00:14:28,200 --> 00:14:30,410
但他沒有  而且盡管我不想承認
But he doesn't, and as much as I hate to admit it,

375
00:14:30,410 --> 00:14:31,970
這個事情得由他做決策
he's in charge of this decision.

376
00:14:32,030 --> 00:14:33,410
他又不掌管這個公司
He's not in charge of this firm.

377
00:14:34,000 --> 00:14:35,880
去找杰西卡  她會同意你的
Go to Jessica, she'll agree with you,

378
00:14:35,880 --> 00:14:37,940
你得到了許可  哈維還來不及搞清狀況
you'll get the credit, and Harvey will be

379
00:14:37,940 --> 00:14:40,130
就滾出海辛頓石油的案子了
off Hessington Oil before he even knows what hit him.

380
00:14:40,310 --> 00:14:43,160
卡特里娜  盡管我很認同你的提議
Katrina, as much as I appreciate your suggestion,

381
00:14:43,570 --> 00:14:45,850
但我拒絕搞兩面派
I refuse to operate in a duplicitous manner.

382
00:14:48,080 --> 00:14:50,650
那我會想個法子打敗托尼·揚諾普洛斯
Then I'll find us a way to get rid of Tony Gianopolous anyway.

383
00:14:57,530 --> 00:14:59,100
我可能得讓你看我得到的東西
I might have to let you look at what I've got,

384
00:14:59,100 --> 00:15:00,540
但沒讓你碰
but I don't have to let you touch it.

385
00:15:01,570 --> 00:15:02,540
碰嗎
Touch it?

386
00:15:03,210 --> 00:15:04,950
這房間簡直是災難
This room is a disaster.

387
00:15:04,950 --> 00:15:06,560
這屋子很好
This room is fine.

388
00:15:06,690 --> 00:15:10,250
每樣東西的內容和位置我都一清二楚
I know where everything is and what everything is.

389
00:15:12,710 --> 00:15:14,050
你到底在忙什么
What are you even doing?

390
00:15:14,330 --> 00:15:16,050
找揚諾普洛斯的把柄
Finding dirt on Gianopolous.

391
00:15:16,520 --> 00:15:17,200
你在和這世上
You're dealing with one

392
00:15:17,200 --> 00:15:19,470
最精明的企業狙擊手之一打交道
of the most sophisticated raiders in the world.

393
00:15:19,470 --> 00:15:20,940
他不會留下任何蛛絲馬跡的
He's not leaving a trail for you to follow.

394
00:15:20,940 --> 00:15:22,510
是嗎  那你有什么高見嗎
Oh, yeah? And what's your strategy?

395
00:15:22,790 --> 00:15:25,540
錄他的聲音  做一段讓他難堪的視頻嗎
You gonna record him and make an embarrassing video?

396
00:15:25,540 --> 00:15:28,450
不  和他耍點小花招
No. Gonna play a little game.

397
00:15:29,870 --> 00:15:30,890
壟斷
Monopoly?

398
00:15:31,420 --> 00:15:32,830
你以為我沒想過嗎
You don't think I started with that?

399
00:15:32,900 --> 00:15:34,640
在石油行業根本沒辦法走壟斷這條路
There's no way to have a monopoly in the oil business.

400
00:15:34,640 --> 00:15:36,390
太大了
It's too goddamn big.

401
00:15:36,490 --> 00:15:38,130
就算你走得通  這些是揚諾普洛斯
And even if you could, these are all the companies

402
00:15:38,130 --> 00:15:39,980
擁有的公司
that Gianopolous owns in any way,

403
00:15:39,990 --> 00:15:42,590
這些是石油行業的大企業
and these are the biggest companies in the oil industry.

404
00:15:42,590 --> 00:15:44,470
根本沒法把它們聯系起來
There's no way to connect the dots.

405
00:15:45,860 --> 00:15:48,330
那你是想一條路走到黑
Well, do you want to go down the same road

406
00:15:48,340 --> 00:15:49,270
和我再戰一場
and have another fight

407
00:15:49,270 --> 00:15:50,440
還是嘗試另辟蹊徑呢
or do you want to try to figure out a way--

408
00:15:50,440 --> 00:15:53,110
-我去  -怎么了
- Shit. - What?

409
00:15:55,700 --> 00:15:57,060
我們一直都想錯了
We've been looking in the wrong place.

410
00:16:05,760 --> 00:16:07,000
我去
Shit.

411
00:16:10,160 --> 00:16:11,380
我去
Shit.

412
00:16:16,110 --> 00:16:17,600
我勒個去
Shity shit.

413
00:16:19,160 --> 00:16:21,600
我...去
Shit.

414
00:16:22,490 --> 00:16:23,680
你也看出來了
You're into the wire?

415
00:16:29,730 --> 00:16:31,650
-我去  -我去
- Shit. - Shit.

416
00:16:42,280 --> 00:16:43,520
杰西卡
Jessica.

417
00:16:43,710 --> 00:16:46,770
真巧啊  在多倫多還能碰到你
What a lovely coincidence running into you in Toronto.

418
00:16:46,960 --> 00:16:48,380
這可不是什么巧合
This is not a coincidence.

419
00:16:48,380 --> 00:16:49,820
好吧  但我仍舊希望碰到你是件好事
Well, I hope it's still going to be lovely.

420
00:16:50,500 --> 00:16:53,060
我想讓你明確地告訴哈維
I need you to make it perfectly clear to Harvey

421
00:16:53,060 --> 00:16:54,550
他在海辛頓石油
that he has no say

422
00:16:54,550 --> 00:16:56,570
收購一案中不再有發言權
in the Hessington Oil takeover battle.

423
00:16:56,570 --> 00:16:57,820
我為什么要這么做呢
And why would I do that?

424
00:16:57,820 --> 00:16:59,140
因為他正在犯一個巨大的錯誤
Because he's making a huge mistake

425
00:16:59,140 --> 00:17:00,680
并且打著你的名義
and using your name to do it.

426
00:17:00,680 --> 00:17:01,350
我沒猜錯的話
And let me guess,

427
00:17:01,350 --> 00:17:03,430
你希望艾娃主動退出管理層
you'd like her to remove herself from management.

428
00:17:04,360 --> 00:17:05,600
她可以主動退出
She can do it herself,

429
00:17:05,680 --> 00:17:07,440
或者我來幫她退出
or I can do it for her.

430
00:17:07,440 --> 00:17:09,920
但不管怎樣  在官司打完之前
But either way she's got to go

431
00:17:09,920 --> 00:17:11,170
她都得先離開
until this trial is over.

432
00:17:11,170 --> 00:17:12,880
我恐怕不這么認為
I'm afraid I don't see it that way.

433
00:17:13,200 --> 00:17:14,410
那你錯了
Well, you're wrong.

434
00:17:14,990 --> 00:17:16,380
你越界了
And you're overstepping.

435
00:17:17,560 --> 00:17:18,780
聽我說
Listen to me.

436
00:17:19,830 --> 00:17:22,890
如果我們不出手介入的話
She stands to lose control of this company permanently

437
00:17:22,890 --> 00:17:24,010
她會永遠失去她的公司的
if we don't do something.

438
00:17:24,010 --> 00:17:25,420
那就做點什么
Then do something.

439
00:17:25,470 --> 00:17:28,560
我在做  但你卻對我束手束腳
I'm trying, but you're cutting off my legs

440
00:17:28,560 --> 00:17:30,750
只因為你與她父親的交情
because of a bond you had with her father.

441
00:17:30,750 --> 00:17:33,670
不  因為我把情義看得比錢重
No, because I value relationships over money.

442
00:17:33,810 --> 00:17:36,020
我更在乎我們合并的協議
Well, I value the terms of our merger.

443
00:17:36,400 --> 00:17:39,050
海辛頓石油是你最大的賣點之一
And Hessington Oil was one of your biggest selling points.

444
00:17:39,050 --> 00:17:40,860
哈維·斯佩克特也是你的賣點
And Harvey Specter one of yours.

445
00:17:40,860 --> 00:17:43,170
我不會眼睜睜地看著這場官司打輸
I'm not going to stand for losing this takeover.

446
00:17:43,170 --> 00:17:46,620
那就別光看不做  但是艾娃絕不能離開
Then don't. But Ava isn't going anywhere.

447
00:17:47,390 --> 00:17:48,730
還有一點
One more thing.

448
00:17:48,920 --> 00:17:51,190
與其花公司的錢
Instead of spending firm money to fly

449
00:17:51,200 --> 00:17:53,120
飛到別的國家來質疑我的判斷
to another country to question my judgment,

450
00:17:53,120 --> 00:17:54,730
不如先打個電話給我
feel free to call first.

451
00:17:55,020 --> 00:17:57,480
我很樂意在電話里給你同樣的答復
I'll be happy to give you the same answer over the phone.

452
00:18:02,870 --> 00:18:03,850
這主意太棒了
This is brilliant.

453
00:18:04,480 --> 00:18:05,690
我們找到聯系了
We've got the connection.

454
00:18:05,690 --> 00:18:07,290
現在只需要想辦法阻止就行了
We just need to figure out how to stop it.

455
00:18:08,130 --> 00:18:09,220
我已經想到了
I already have.

456
00:18:09,750 --> 00:18:12,210
做得好  卡特里娜  你挖到好東西了
This is great work, Katrina. You struck oil.

457
00:18:13,620 --> 00:18:15,000
這其實是邁克的注意
It was actually Mike's idea.

458
00:18:15,050 --> 00:18:16,470
你為什么要歸功于他
Why do you want to give him credit?

459
00:18:17,370 --> 00:18:18,470
因為如果我不說  你不會聽我
Because if I don't, you won't listen

460
00:18:18,470 --> 00:18:20,330
要你帶著他一起去
when I say you should take him with you.

461
00:18:20,330 --> 00:18:21,490
我誰也不帶著
I'm not taking anyone with me.

462
00:18:21,490 --> 00:18:23,380
這是你讓他看到你
It's an opportunity for him to see you

463
00:18:23,380 --> 00:18:26,420
把一個傳奇人物打得落花流水的好機會
beat the shit out of a living legend.

464
00:18:28,880 --> 00:18:30,650
托尼·揚諾普洛斯被打得落花流水
Tony Gianopolous gets blown out of the water,

465
00:18:30,650 --> 00:18:31,810
邁克被我折服
and Mike gets blown away.

466
00:18:32,040 --> 00:18:33,560
杰西卡全看在眼里
And Jessica hears about it all.

467
00:18:33,840 --> 00:18:35,520
我會向哈維提議的
I'm gonna suggest this to Harvey.

468
00:18:35,680 --> 00:18:37,520
就說這是你的主意好了
Feel free to tell him it was all your idea.

469
00:18:37,880 --> 00:18:38,930
你別介意
Don't mind if I do.

470
00:18:39,500 --> 00:18:41,030
說曹操曹操到
Oh, perfect timing.

471
00:18:41,030 --> 00:18:42,430
哈維  我正好有事找你
Harvey, I was just gonna run something by you.

472
00:18:42,430 --> 00:18:43,560
我沒時間  路易
I don't have time, Louis.

473
00:18:43,560 --> 00:18:45,250
我手頭上有個兇殺案
I'm working on a murder case.

474
00:18:45,250 --> 00:18:46,580
我只是路過通知你
I just dropped by to inform you

475
00:18:46,580 --> 00:18:48,740
邁克要和你一起去找揚諾普洛斯
Mike's coming with you to see Gianopolous.

476
00:18:50,210 --> 00:18:51,370
做夢吧他
Like hell he is.

477
00:18:51,370 --> 00:18:53,100
-什么  -我誰也不帶著
- Excuse me? - I'm not taking anyone.

478
00:18:53,830 --> 00:18:55,320
-路易  -別發號施令
- Louis-- - And don't Louis me.

479
00:18:55,390 --> 00:18:57,190
這是我的案子  從我拿到這案子開始
This is my case, and you've been sticking your nose in it

480
00:18:57,190 --> 00:18:59,810
-你一直在插手攪合  -插手攪合
- ever since I got it.  - Sticking my nose in?

481
00:18:59,810 --> 00:19:00,800
你能拿這案子
You only have this case

482
00:19:00,800 --> 00:19:02,510
全都是因為我夠慷慨把它給你
'cause I was kind enough to give it to you.

483
00:19:02,650 --> 00:19:03,610
你把這個案子給我
You only gave it to me

484
00:19:03,610 --> 00:19:05,700
是因為你沒發現你得為
because you hadn't realized that you were responsible for

485
00:19:05,700 --> 00:19:08,450
讓對艾娃的指控從賄賂變成謀殺負責
turning Ava's bribery charges into murder charges.

486
00:19:08,630 --> 00:19:09,860
你不用再管這個案子了
You're off this case.

487
00:19:09,860 --> 00:19:11,690
盡管這么做  打電話給艾娃
Go ahead. Call Ava.

488
00:19:12,190 --> 00:19:13,650
告訴她你把注意力從她的謀殺官司
Tell her that you're diverting your attention

489
00:19:13,650 --> 00:19:15,700
轉移到解決這件事上來了
from her murder trial to work on this.

490
00:19:17,380 --> 00:19:18,620
是吧  你不想這么做
Yup. Didn't think so.

491
00:19:18,670 --> 00:19:19,570
滾出我的辦公室
Get out of my office

492
00:19:19,570 --> 00:19:21,390
我要準備開會了
because I got a meeting to prepare for.

493
00:19:26,480 --> 00:19:27,570
他剛剛怎么了
What just happened to him?

494
00:19:28,390 --> 00:19:30,160
-他被"利"擊了  -顯而易見
- He got "Litt" up. - Damn straight.

495
00:19:33,250 --> 00:19:34,260
你看見這個了嗎
Have you seen this?

496
00:19:34,260 --> 00:19:36,420
這是今天《華爾街日報》上的文章
It's an article in today Wall Street Journal

497
00:19:36,420 --> 00:19:38,200
把我寫得像貪婪的企業家
painting me as the picture of corporate greed.

498
00:19:38,210 --> 00:19:40,650
我之前就告訴過你了  假如你開口了
As I told you before, if you speak out--

499
00:19:40,660 --> 00:19:42,570
我就有機會拯救我的公司了
I have the chance to save my company.

500
00:19:42,570 --> 00:19:44,470
路易·利特正在想辦法解決這事
Louis litt is doing that right now.

501
00:19:44,490 --> 00:19:45,330
這不是重點
That is not the point.

502
00:19:45,330 --> 00:19:46,510
這就是重點
That is the point.

503
00:19:46,510 --> 00:19:47,870
我們還是可以拯救你的公司
We can still save your company,

504
00:19:47,870 --> 00:19:50,260
而你也不用危及你的謀殺官司
and you won't have to hurt yourself at your murder trial.

505
00:19:50,260 --> 00:19:52,950
不  重點是我想在我的謀殺庭審上發言
No, the point is I want to speak at my murder trial.

506
00:19:52,950 --> 00:19:54,250
這樣很不明智
That's not wise.

507
00:19:54,420 --> 00:19:56,940
你在這些年里參加過幾次謀殺庭審
And how many murder trials have you conducted in your many years?

508
00:19:56,940 --> 00:19:57,740
艾娃
Ava.

509
00:19:57,740 --> 00:19:58,880
保持沉默是毀滅性的
Silence is damning.

510
00:19:58,880 --> 00:20:01,540
看看這篇文章  我已經被認為有罪了
Look at this article. I'm already guilty.

511
00:20:01,540 --> 00:20:02,750
如果你上證人席
If you take this stand,

512
00:20:02,750 --> 00:20:04,880
卡梅隆·丹尼斯會把你撕成碎片的
Cameron Dennis is gonna rip you to shreds.

513
00:20:04,880 --> 00:20:06,270
我不是來征求意見的
This is not up for discussion.

514
00:20:06,270 --> 00:20:07,810
我要在庭審上發言
I will have my say.

515
00:20:07,930 --> 00:20:09,720
那我會讓你看看自己會落到哪般田地
Then I'm gonna show you what you're in for.

516
00:20:09,790 --> 00:20:11,900
如果你不準備這樣做  就太不稱職了
Well, you wouldn't be doing your job if you didn't.

517
00:20:18,820 --> 00:20:19,930
請坐  利特先生
Have a seat, Mr. Litt.

518
00:20:20,520 --> 00:20:21,670
我等下就過去
I'll be with you in a minute.

519
00:20:22,030 --> 00:20:23,030
你等下就過來
You'll be with me?

520
00:20:23,100 --> 00:20:26,190
是的  就像我剛剛說的  等一下就好
Yes. As I said. In a minute.

521
00:20:27,080 --> 00:20:28,640
你知道我本應問問你是誰
Well, you know, I'd ask you who you are,

522
00:20:28,640 --> 00:20:29,790
但事實是
but the truth is

523
00:20:29,790 --> 00:20:33,350
我  我他媽不在乎
I, uh...I don't really give a shit.

524
00:20:33,580 --> 00:20:35,150
托尼·揚諾普洛斯到底在哪
Where the hell's Tony Gianopolous?

525
00:20:35,230 --> 00:20:37,500
揚諾普洛斯先生在樓上
Mr. Gianopolous is upstairs.

526
00:20:37,500 --> 00:20:39,740
要想上樓  你得穿過那些門
To get upstairs, you have to get through those doors.

527
00:20:39,740 --> 00:20:42,060
要想穿過那些門  你得經過我同意
And to get through those doors you have to get through me.

528
00:20:43,250 --> 00:20:44,740
而我不會讓你過去的
And you're not getting through me.

529
00:20:46,740 --> 00:20:50,710
說不定我有鑰匙
Well, perhaps I have the key.

530
00:20:54,690 --> 00:20:57,140
這是我們一個分公司的資產負債表
This is the balance sheet from one of our subsidiaries.

531
00:20:57,140 --> 00:20:58,020
這什么用也沒有
This is nothing.

532
00:20:58,260 --> 00:20:59,690
對不起我忘了
Sorry, forgot.

533
00:20:59,690 --> 00:21:00,820
這是套密碼鎖
It's a combination lock.

534
00:21:02,210 --> 00:21:05,080
這些展示了揚諾普洛斯公司的總資產
This represents the totality of Gianopolous limited holdings.

535
00:21:05,280 --> 00:21:06,940
你們控制了40%的
You control 40% of

536
00:21:06,940 --> 00:21:09,590
美國廣播電臺  谷物生產  州際貨運
the U.S. Radio Stations, corn production, interstate trucking,

537
00:21:09,590 --> 00:21:10,970
而這些只是冰山一角
and that's just the tip of the iceberg.

538
00:21:10,970 --> 00:21:12,740
看起來我選了個好雇主
Looks like I picked the right employer.

539
00:21:12,750 --> 00:21:15,110
有一個問題  海辛頓石油擁有的這么多產業
One problem: Hessington Oil owns enough of those industries

540
00:21:15,110 --> 00:21:16,930
足夠讓聯邦貿易委員會來找你麻煩
to get you in trouble with the FTC.

541
00:21:19,000 --> 00:21:20,750
是的  覺得我們發現不了嗎
Yeah. Think we wouldn't find that?

542
00:21:20,920 --> 00:21:22,390
你以為我們不知道
You think we wouldn't?

543
00:21:22,470 --> 00:21:23,760
這些文件已經過期了
These folders are out of date.

544
00:21:23,760 --> 00:21:25,370
我們已經撤資了
We've already divested.

545
00:21:25,370 --> 00:21:29,320
轉投這個  這個  還有這個
Into this, this, and this.

546
00:21:29,320 --> 00:21:33,080
那又怎樣  海辛頓在那些領域里沒資產
So what? Hessington doesn't have holdings in those areas.

547
00:21:33,120 --> 00:21:34,400
他們現在有了
They do now.

548
00:21:34,970 --> 00:21:35,980
假如你不放過他們
And if you don't leave 'em alone,

549
00:21:35,980 --> 00:21:37,920
你就甩不掉我聯邦貿易委員會的朋友了
you're gonna be tied up with my friend from the FTC

550
00:21:37,920 --> 00:21:40,010
直到天長地久
until kingdom goddamn come.

551
00:21:40,870 --> 00:21:42,230
明白了嗎
Got that, Spank?

552
00:21:43,700 --> 00:21:45,330
這樣說來  揚諾普洛斯先生
Then it's a good thing Mr. Gianopolous

553
00:21:45,340 --> 00:21:46,820
在和他朋友共進晚餐時
arranged an exception for us

554
00:21:46,820 --> 00:21:48,460
為我們破一下例是好事了
over dinner with his friend,

555
00:21:48,460 --> 00:21:51,170
他的朋友是聯邦貿易委員會會長
the commissioner of the FTC.

556
00:21:53,550 --> 00:21:54,180
那樣不
That's not--

557
00:21:54,180 --> 00:21:55,030
合法
Legal?

558
00:21:55,040 --> 00:21:57,120
是合法的  只要我們不聲張
Yes, it is. As long as we disclose it,

559
00:21:57,130 --> 00:21:58,910
而我們通常很低調
which we always do.

560
00:21:58,910 --> 00:22:01,690
你以為你是第一個試圖打敗我們的律師
You think you're the first lawyer to try to outsmart us?

561
00:22:01,690 --> 00:22:02,720
我們可不是律師
We're not lawyers.

562
00:22:02,720 --> 00:22:03,650
我們是投資銀行家
We're investment bankers.

563
00:22:03,650 --> 00:22:04,880
我們打電話叫你們幫忙處理文書工作
We call you for the paperwork.

564
00:22:04,880 --> 00:22:06,140
我們沒上哈佛
We didn't go to Harvard.

565
00:22:06,140 --> 00:22:07,270
我們去的是沃頓商學院
We went to Wharton,

566
00:22:07,270 --> 00:22:09,700
我們早就預料到你們的動作了
and we saw you coming a mile away.

567
00:22:10,940 --> 00:22:12,000
被打擊了吧
Spank.

568
00:22:12,920 --> 00:22:15,880
順便說下  揚諾普洛斯先生現在在摩納哥
Oh, by the way, Mr. Gianopolous is in Monaco.

569
00:22:15,920 --> 00:22:18,250
克里斯蒂娜帶你出去的時候可以證實
Christina will validate you on the way out.

570
00:22:22,530 --> 00:22:23,870
總算要收拾一下了
Finally cleaning up?

571
00:22:26,230 --> 00:22:27,970
不能永遠待在這兒嘛
Can't stay here forever.

572
00:22:29,280 --> 00:22:31,070
你和艾娃談得怎樣
How'd your meeting with Ava go?

573
00:22:31,180 --> 00:22:33,310
她想在自己的庭審上作證
She wants to testify at her own trial.

574
00:22:33,720 --> 00:22:34,430
開什么玩笑
Are you kidding?

575
00:22:34,430 --> 00:22:36,680
是啊我也覺得  我們正在解決這件事
Yeah, I know. We're working on it.

576
00:22:37,080 --> 00:22:38,290
我以為你和路易在一起
Thought you'd be with Louis.

577
00:22:38,290 --> 00:22:40,640
他自己一個人去見揚諾普洛斯了
He went to go see Gianopolous by himself.

578
00:22:41,700 --> 00:22:42,770
希望他能成功
I hope it works.

579
00:22:43,960 --> 00:22:45,240
我們的計劃周全
We have a good plan.

580
00:22:46,880 --> 00:22:48,300
不管怎樣
For what it's worth,

581
00:22:49,210 --> 00:22:51,740
我跟路易說  讓他帶上你
I suggested Louis take you with him.

582
00:22:54,680 --> 00:22:55,820
臥槽
Shit.

583
00:22:56,850 --> 00:22:58,380
就像西爾會說
As Sil would say,

584
00:22:58,540 --> 00:23:00,460
就在我以為我會出局時
"Just when I thought I was out,

585
00:23:00,540 --> 00:23:02,110
他們又把我拉回來
they pull me back in."

586
00:23:02,120 --> 00:23:04,210
你也看《黑道家族》啊
Okay, so you watch The Sopranos too?

587
00:23:04,210 --> 00:23:05,520
誰不是先看《黑道家族》
Nobody watches The Wire

588
00:23:05,520 --> 00:23:07,470
再看《火線》
without starting with The Sopranos.

589
00:23:10,380 --> 00:23:13,750
你  你真的和路易說帶上我嗎
You--did you really suggest that to louis?

590
00:23:14,420 --> 00:23:17,370
這是你想出來的  是你的功勞
It was your idea. You deserve the credit.

591
00:23:21,700 --> 00:23:22,930
握手言和吧
Truce?

592
00:23:24,090 --> 00:23:25,350
沒問題
Truce.

593
00:23:28,080 --> 00:23:29,760
臥槽
Shit.

594
00:23:33,290 --> 00:23:36,010
你是想從外賣員那多拿點毛豆嗎
You trying to score some extra edamame from the delivery guy?

595
00:23:36,010 --> 00:23:39,500
算了吧  他每次都多給我毛豆
Please, Yuki always brings me extra edamame.

596
00:23:39,500 --> 00:23:41,600
那你是為了誰盛裝打扮
Well, then who's the touch-up for?

597
00:23:43,030 --> 00:23:47,230
你居然能在辦公室里就大變身
And did you do a costume change without leaving the office?

598
00:23:47,230 --> 00:23:49,990
我有一個人的電話
I have a number that calls a guy...

599
00:23:50,360 --> 00:23:51,820
-那人知道我的尺寸  -我要那個號碼
- who knows my size. - I need that number.

600
00:23:51,820 --> 00:23:53,740
不能給你
I can't give you that number.

601
00:23:54,170 --> 00:23:57,850
天啊  你要跟史蒂芬去約會
Oh, my god. You have a date with Stephen.

602
00:23:57,850 --> 00:23:59,580
也不是約會
It's not really a date.

603
00:23:59,580 --> 00:24:03,010
更像是...一個協議
It's more...of an arrangement.

604
00:24:03,010 --> 00:24:04,450
協議嗎
An arrangement?

605
00:24:04,490 --> 00:24:06,880
他有些短期需求  問我能不能趁他還沒走
He has some short-term needs, asked if I could help him out

606
00:24:06,880 --> 00:24:08,780
幫他個忙  省略一千字
while he's in town, blah blah blah,

607
00:24:08,780 --> 00:24:09,980
我跟他約了八點見面
I'm meeting him at 8:00.

608
00:24:09,980 --> 00:24:11,520
省略一千字
Blah blah blah?

609
00:24:11,530 --> 00:24:13,650
省略了什么
What's blah blah blah?

610
00:24:13,650 --> 00:24:15,430
你懂的  就是...
Oh, you know, it's just...

611
00:24:16,090 --> 00:24:17,830
這個  那個  另一個
this, that, and the other thing.

612
00:24:17,830 --> 00:24:20,650
那他知道省略一千字里邊包括了
And does he know that blah blah blah constitutes

613
00:24:20,650 --> 00:24:21,850
這個  那個  另一個嗎
this, that, and the other thing?

614
00:24:21,850 --> 00:24:25,350
瑞秋  史蒂芬跟我的交流方式很巧妙
Rachel. Stephen and I communicate a little more subtly--

615
00:24:25,350 --> 00:24:27,770
暗示語  雙關語
suggestive banter, double entendres.

616
00:24:28,210 --> 00:24:29,590
我們都心知肚明協議的內容
We both know what we agreed to.

617
00:24:29,590 --> 00:24:32,340
聽起來像是你倆要來一段瘋狂的熱戀
It sounds to me like you agreed to a hot and steamy affair.

618
00:24:32,340 --> 00:24:34,490
我不屑解釋  解釋便是掩飾
I'm not gonna even dignify that with a response.

619
00:24:34,490 --> 00:24:36,630
天啊  你倆是決定開始熱戀嗎
Oh, my god, did you agree to a hot and steamy affair?

620
00:24:37,230 --> 00:24:38,520
我不知道
I have no idea.

621
00:24:43,870 --> 00:24:45,140
路易  有事嗎
Louis, what can I do for you?

622
00:24:45,140 --> 00:24:46,320
我想退出這件案子
I want off this case.

623
00:24:46,320 --> 00:24:47,740
看來你讓揚諾普洛斯出局了
I take it you struck out with Gianopolous?

624
00:24:47,740 --> 00:24:48,610
我沒讓他三振出局[棒球術語]
I didn't strike out.

625
00:24:48,610 --> 00:24:50,790
我只是變了個魔術
What I did was almost pull a rabbit out of a hat.

626
00:24:50,790 --> 00:24:52,670
但實際上  我們的唯一妙招
But the truth is the one good move we had

627
00:24:52,670 --> 00:24:54,060
已經不起作用了
has been taken away from us,

628
00:24:54,060 --> 00:24:55,440
我不會傻站著認輸
And I'm not gonna be left holding the bag

629
00:24:55,440 --> 00:24:57,490
都是因為哈維不讓我出招
because Harvey chose to handcuff me.

630
00:24:57,490 --> 00:24:59,540
路易  我不會讓你放棄這件案子
Louis, I'm not taking you off this case.

631
00:25:01,830 --> 00:25:03,810
不過  我會讓你出招
But I am taking the handcuffs off.

632
00:25:05,500 --> 00:25:09,080
等下  你意思是你同意
Wait, are you saying that I have your blessing

633
00:25:09,080 --> 00:25:12,900
讓我說服董事會開除艾娃·海辛頓
to go to the board and convince them to ditch Ava Hessington?

634
00:25:13,010 --> 00:25:14,510
我什么也沒說
I'm not saying anything.

635
00:25:16,180 --> 00:25:17,410
明白了
Got it.

636
00:25:17,830 --> 00:25:19,090
偷偷干
Wet work.

637
00:25:20,140 --> 00:25:22,020
這次對話從沒發生過
This conversation never happened.

638
00:25:25,630 --> 00:25:26,720
怎么了
What is it?

639
00:25:27,070 --> 00:25:27,990
你跟哈維說過這話嗎
Have you ever said to Harvey,

640
00:25:28,000 --> 00:25:29,230
"這次對話從沒發生過"
"This conversation never happened"?

641
00:25:29,230 --> 00:25:30,950
-路易  -拜托告訴我你沒說過
- Louis. - Please tell me you never have.

642
00:25:30,950 --> 00:25:32,730
如果我說過  會告訴你嗎
Would I tell you if I had?

643
00:25:33,550 --> 00:25:34,620
我就當你沒說過
I'll take that as a no.

644
00:25:34,620 --> 00:25:36,140
晚安  路易
Good night, Louis.

645
00:25:36,940 --> 00:25:38,270
黑天鵝
Black swan.

646
00:25:46,590 --> 00:25:49,030
周三  晚上6點52分
Wednesday, 6:52 P.M.,

647
00:25:49,170 --> 00:25:50,340
發生了
It happened.

648
00:26:08,180 --> 00:26:09,930
你沒有心臟病發吧
You aren't having a heart attack, are you?

649
00:26:09,930 --> 00:26:11,520
那會毀了你的美好夜晚嗎
Would that put a crimp in your evening?

650
00:26:11,520 --> 00:26:13,170
我可以把你的票高價賣掉
Well, I guess I could scalp your ticket,

651
00:26:13,170 --> 00:26:15,470
畢竟這是本季度最火的戲劇
seeing as it is the hottest of the season.

652
00:26:15,480 --> 00:26:18,390
我都快要賣了脾臟才買到票
You know, I practically had to sell my spleen for them.

653
00:26:18,390 --> 00:26:20,530
這就有趣了  聽說這票是你的客戶給的
That's funny. I heard you got them from a client.

654
00:26:20,700 --> 00:26:22,660
那你有聽說我把脾臟賣給他了嗎
Did you also hear that I traded him my spleen?

655
00:26:22,660 --> 00:26:24,340
我不管你是賣脾還是賣肺
I don't care if it cost you a lung.

656
00:26:24,350 --> 00:26:27,300
丹尼爾·戴·劉易斯穿蘇格蘭短褶裙  值了
Daniel Day-lewis in a kilt? Worth it.

657
00:26:27,300 --> 00:26:29,500
真高興聽你這樣說
I'm really glad to hear that.

658
00:26:29,610 --> 00:26:30,910
當然啦
Of course you are.

659
00:26:30,910 --> 00:26:32,800
你知道我多喜歡戲劇啊
You found out how much I love the theater.

660
00:26:33,020 --> 00:26:35,170
你該不會以為  我安排這些
You don't think the reason that I arranged all of this

661
00:26:35,170 --> 00:26:37,360
是因為我調查過你吧
is because I looked into you?

662
00:26:38,140 --> 00:26:39,390
你沒調查我嗎
Didn't you?

663
00:26:39,700 --> 00:26:40,880
我的確調查過你
Sure I did.

664
00:26:41,360 --> 00:26:42,750
我喜愛戲劇
You know, I'm actually to theater

665
00:26:42,750 --> 00:26:44,250
猶如哈維喜愛運動
what Harvey is to sport.

666
00:26:44,250 --> 00:26:45,490
你才不喜歡戲劇呢
You don't give a sh-- about theater.

667
00:26:45,500 --> 00:26:46,860
你熱愛運動
You love sports.

668
00:26:47,790 --> 00:26:49,670
-比較喜歡橄欖球  -騙誰呢
- Rugby mostly. - Nice try.

669
00:26:49,670 --> 00:26:51,160
我盡力而為
We do what we can.

670
00:26:51,160 --> 00:26:52,270
但是看完戲
But we are going for dinner

671
00:26:52,270 --> 00:26:54,190
我們將和丹尼爾·戴·劉易斯共進晚餐
with Daniel Day-Lewis after the show.

672
00:26:54,250 --> 00:26:55,460
你開玩笑吧
You're kidding.

673
00:26:55,680 --> 00:26:57,160
我也許對戲劇不感興趣
I may be indifferent to the theater,

674
00:26:57,160 --> 00:26:59,260
但我懂做事的門路
but I know how to get things done.

675
00:26:59,490 --> 00:27:00,780
你果然厲害
You are good.

676
00:27:01,030 --> 00:27:03,180
我們第一次碰面時我就說了
I told you that on the first day we met.

677
00:27:03,540 --> 00:27:04,860
我不只是厲害
I'm better than good.

678
00:27:06,430 --> 00:27:08,400
晚餐是幾點
What time is dinner?

679
00:27:08,610 --> 00:27:09,920
十點半
10:30.

680
00:27:10,160 --> 00:27:11,690
那我們得趕快走了
Then we better get going.

681
00:27:12,650 --> 00:27:14,470
表演還有二十分鐘才開始呢
Oh, the show doesn't start for another 20 minutes.

682
00:27:14,470 --> 00:27:15,890
我們不去看表演了
We aren't going to the show.

683
00:27:22,120 --> 00:27:23,380
出租車
Taxi!

684
00:27:25,160 --> 00:27:27,170
這真的有必要嗎
Is that really necessary?

685
00:27:27,170 --> 00:27:28,250
你將會宣誓作證
You will be in the deposition.

686
00:27:28,250 --> 00:27:29,730
我才不管是不是取證
I don't care about the deposition.

687
00:27:29,740 --> 00:27:30,950
哈維
Harvey.

688
00:27:30,950 --> 00:27:31,880
你想知道你會面臨什么
You want to know how you come across,

689
00:27:31,880 --> 00:27:33,250
那你就得自己親眼去看看
you have to see how you come across.

690
00:27:33,250 --> 00:27:34,900
現在回答我問題
Now answer my question.

691
00:27:34,900 --> 00:27:37,210
你有沒有賄賂外國政府
Did you bribe a foreign government?

692
00:27:38,030 --> 00:27:39,670
海辛頓女士  你為何遲疑
Why are you hesitating, Miss Hessington?

693
00:27:39,670 --> 00:27:40,390
有什么不可告人的嗎
Something to hide?

694
00:27:40,390 --> 00:27:41,620
哈維想說的是
Look, I think what Harvey's trying to say-

695
00:27:41,620 --> 00:27:42,590
你一旦遲疑
You hesitate,

696
00:27:42,590 --> 00:27:43,970
他們就會懷疑你
they won't trust you.

697
00:27:43,970 --> 00:27:45,320
你的賄賂罪不會對你造成影響
Your bribery isn't in question.

698
00:27:45,320 --> 00:27:47,010
卡梅隆會將你的認罪納入證據
Cameron is gonna enter that plea into evidence.

699
00:27:47,010 --> 00:27:48,300
你只要承認繼續作證就好了
You have to own it and move on.

700
00:27:48,300 --> 00:27:49,900
同時我建議你承認得真切些
And I suggest you do it more believably,

701
00:27:49,900 --> 00:27:51,690
因為當你面對
because when you're up there

702
00:27:51,690 --> 00:27:54,370
底下十二位裁決者時
staring down the barrel of 12 executioners,

703
00:27:54,370 --> 00:27:56,190
你不允許有任何遲疑
There's no changing your mind.

704
00:27:56,190 --> 00:27:58,360
你以為我不知道你是想嚇唬我
You think I don't know you're trying to rattle me?

705
00:27:58,360 --> 00:28:00,700
嚇唬你  我只是告訴你事實
Rattle you? I'm just giving you the facts.

706
00:28:00,700 --> 00:28:02,620
卡梅隆才會真的把你嚇倒
Cameron's gonna rattle you.

707
00:28:02,880 --> 00:28:04,330
而且他會得手的
And it's gonna work,

708
00:28:04,330 --> 00:28:06,210
因為你我都知道  這就是你干的
because you and I both know you did this.

709
00:28:06,210 --> 00:28:08,140
-你好大的膽子  -我說什么了
- How dare you! - How dare I what?

710
00:28:08,140 --> 00:28:09,770
是你想去作證的
This is your idea.

711
00:28:09,770 --> 00:28:11,460
那就快問我問題
Then ask me a goddamn question.

712
00:28:11,460 --> 00:28:12,690
你賄賂了那個政府
You bribed that government.

713
00:28:12,690 --> 00:28:14,850
什么人會相信
What's to stop anyone with a pulse

714
00:28:14,850 --> 00:28:17,370
這些賄款被用來殺人了
from believing you knew that money was payment

715
00:28:17,370 --> 00:28:18,580
而你卻渾然不知
for killing those people?

716
00:28:18,580 --> 00:28:20,870
對于我而言  生命遠比錢重要
Because life is more important to me than money.

717
00:28:20,870 --> 00:28:23,370
那一開始你為什么賄賂他們
Then why the hell did you pay that bribe in the first place?

718
00:28:23,370 --> 00:28:25,020
因為這是那兒的潛規則
Because that's how it works over there.

719
00:28:25,020 --> 00:28:26,870
殺人也是那兒的潛規則
Murder is also how it works over there.

720
00:28:26,870 --> 00:28:28,640
你殺的人  你自己清楚
You did it. You know it.

721
00:28:28,640 --> 00:28:30,430
所以你無法說服任何人
And you're not convincing anyone.

722
00:28:32,360 --> 00:28:33,540
很好
Very good.

723
00:28:34,120 --> 00:28:36,050
終于問到點子上了
Finally we get to it.

724
00:28:37,750 --> 00:28:39,480
如果你回去看看資料
If you check your records,

725
00:28:39,490 --> 00:28:42,120
你會發現之所以我們競標贏了
You'd know the reason we won that bid is

726
00:28:42,120 --> 00:28:44,880
我們是唯一的公司親自到現場
that we were the only company who took it upon ourselves

727
00:28:44,880 --> 00:28:46,100
和民眾交流
to go to the people.

728
00:28:46,100 --> 00:28:48,670
因為你要親自瞧瞧到底什么擋你們道了
Because you needed to see what your obstacle was.

729
00:28:48,670 --> 00:28:50,170
擋我們的道
My obstacle?

730
00:28:51,240 --> 00:28:54,340
我們比其他公司多付整整一億
We paid $100 million more than anyone else

731
00:28:54,340 --> 00:28:58,510
就是說好  這些錢將被用來安置和補償
on the condition that the money be used to relocate any family

732
00:28:58,510 --> 00:29:02,810
所有在我們輸油管五十英里以內的人們
who lost anything within 50 miles of that pipeline--

733
00:29:03,630 --> 00:29:07,640
工作  家園  土地  牲畜
Job, home, land, livestock.

734
00:29:07,650 --> 00:29:08,900
損失什么補什么
Anything.

735
00:29:09,940 --> 00:29:12,030
那兒所發生的慘案令我作嘔
What happened over there sickens me.

736
00:29:12,960 --> 00:29:14,990
我為此天天失眠
I lose sleep over it every night.

737
00:29:17,390 --> 00:29:19,370
一旦這場噩夢完結了
And as soon as I am out of this nightmare,

738
00:29:19,380 --> 00:29:22,290
我就將關閉這整個項目
I am going to shut down the entire project--

739
00:29:22,590 --> 00:29:25,060
輸油管  油田  所有的一切
The pipeline, the oil fields, all of it.

740
00:29:27,510 --> 00:29:30,010
剛剛所說的應該足以讓兩位
So I've had just about enough of you two wondering

741
00:29:30,010 --> 00:29:32,790
重新審視我到底是不是有罪了
whether I'm guilty of these murders or not.

742
00:29:33,830 --> 00:29:36,360
對你來說  這次演習夠好了嗎
Is that a good enough trial run for you?

743
00:29:46,020 --> 00:29:47,500
我的天
Holy shit.

744
00:29:48,370 --> 00:29:49,780
不是她干的
She didn't do it.

745
00:29:51,770 --> 00:29:53,560
我知道你對企圖奪權一事
I understand you have a strategy

746
00:29:53,560 --> 00:29:55,590
已有了對策
to defeat the takeover attempt.

747
00:29:55,590 --> 00:29:57,570
沒錯  但這取決于
I do. But it involves a conversation

748
00:29:57,570 --> 00:29:59,790
你多重視艾娃·海辛頓了
about how essential you find Ava Hessington.

749
00:29:59,790 --> 00:30:01,910
如果扳倒托尼·揚諾普洛斯唯一方法
If the only way to beat Tony Gianopolous

750
00:30:01,910 --> 00:30:03,230
是犧牲她
is to get rid of her,

751
00:30:03,230 --> 00:30:04,840
那我想我們別無選擇
then I don't think we have a choice.

752
00:30:04,840 --> 00:30:07,010
如果你需要一個說服其他董事的理由
If you need cover for the other board members,

753
00:30:07,010 --> 00:30:09,460
那告訴他們這是皮爾遜-達比律所的建議
then you can just tell them that Pearson Darby recommended that.

754
00:30:09,460 --> 00:30:10,730
那我將向他們建議
And I'll recommend to them

755
00:30:10,730 --> 00:30:13,260
我們繼續與皮爾遜-達比合作
that we retain Pearson Darby.

756
00:30:13,270 --> 00:30:14,550
看來我們達成一致了
So we have a deal.

757
00:30:26,650 --> 00:30:28,040
你怎么了
What's the matter with you?

758
00:30:31,440 --> 00:30:33,630
我們剛剛對艾娃·海辛頓取證了
We just deposed Ava Hessington.

759
00:30:34,690 --> 00:30:36,230
你對你自己的客戶取證
You deposed your own client?

760
00:30:36,310 --> 00:30:37,410
模擬取證
Practice.

761
00:30:38,220 --> 00:30:40,390
你沒有成功讓她打消這念頭嗎
You couldn't convince her not to testify?

762
00:30:41,980 --> 00:30:43,420
不  不是這個原因
No, not that.

763
00:30:44,540 --> 00:30:46,810
她說服了我們  也許她應該那么做
She convinced us that maybe she should.

764
00:30:47,990 --> 00:30:51,180
那樣的話只可能有一個理由
Well, there would be only one reason to even consider that.

765
00:30:51,180 --> 00:30:52,560
不是她干的
She didn't do it.

766
00:30:53,950 --> 00:30:55,120
不可能
No way.

767
00:30:55,120 --> 00:30:57,880
我知道  你說過如果她能無情到殺人
I know. You said, if she's cold enough to do it,

768
00:30:57,880 --> 00:30:59,740
她就能無情地為這件事說謊
she'd be cold enough to lie about it.

769
00:30:59,740 --> 00:31:04,000
但這個女人將要失去她的權力  她的公司
But this woman is about to lose her title, her company,

770
00:31:04,350 --> 00:31:05,610
她的全部生活
her whole life...

771
00:31:08,030 --> 00:31:10,360
而且我知道她在說實話
And I know that she is telling the truth.

772
00:31:15,430 --> 00:31:16,920
你不需要相信我
You don't have to believe me.

773
00:31:18,310 --> 00:31:19,750
你自己看吧
Take a look for yourself.

774
00:31:25,740 --> 00:31:27,330
情況怎么樣
What happened?

775
00:31:27,500 --> 00:31:29,930
-他同意了  -她要出局了
- He agreed. - She's out.

776
00:31:30,060 --> 00:31:32,180
明天的投標報價投票之前就會結束
It'll be done tomorrow before the tender offer vote.

777
00:31:32,190 --> 00:31:34,090
那我們還有時間
Then we still have time.

778
00:31:34,090 --> 00:31:35,130
你在說什么
What are you talking about?

779
00:31:35,130 --> 00:31:36,520
她是無辜的
She's innocent.

780
00:31:37,680 --> 00:31:38,920
什么
What?

781
00:31:40,330 --> 00:31:41,680
看看這個
Take a look at this.

782
00:31:46,970 --> 00:31:48,830
我知道我們該做什么了
I figured out what we're gonna do.

783
00:31:48,950 --> 00:31:50,110
那是什么
And what is that?

784
00:31:50,230 --> 00:31:51,760
我們一開始就該做的事情
What we should have done in the first place.

785
00:31:51,760 --> 00:31:53,620
我們要讓她跟董事會談談
We're gonna let her talk to the board.

786
00:31:53,920 --> 00:31:55,790
并在明天的會議中搶占先機
And preempt tomorrow's meeting with one of our own.

787
00:31:55,800 --> 00:31:57,500
如果她能讓我們相信她是無辜的
If she can convince us she's innocent,

788
00:31:57,500 --> 00:31:59,280
她也能說服他們讓她繼續掌權
she can convince them to keep her in charge

789
00:31:59,280 --> 00:32:01,510
-并且投票反對接管  -雙贏
- and vote against the takeover. - Win-win.

790
00:32:01,510 --> 00:32:03,990
-讓路易斯去做這事兒  -路易斯嗎
- Have Louis set it up. - Whoa, whoa, whoa. Louis?

791
00:32:03,990 --> 00:32:05,610
對  他會樂意的
Yeah. He'll love it.

792
00:32:05,610 --> 00:32:08,130
讓她講話  最早就是他的主意
Letting her talk is what he wanted her to do in the first place.

793
00:32:08,130 --> 00:32:09,550
完成任務
Get it done.

794
00:32:19,970 --> 00:32:21,740
路易斯  你還在這兒干嘛
Louis, what are you still doing here?

795
00:32:21,930 --> 00:32:23,310
你已經工作一天了
You put in a long day.

796
00:32:23,310 --> 00:32:25,340
你做得很好  現在回家去吧
You did a great job. Now go home.

797
00:32:25,880 --> 00:32:27,020
我不能
I can't.

798
00:32:27,340 --> 00:32:28,440
為什么
Why not?

799
00:32:29,320 --> 00:32:30,710
不是她干的
She didn't do it.

800
00:32:32,160 --> 00:32:33,420
什么  不是誰干的
Who didn't do what?

801
00:32:35,000 --> 00:32:37,620
艾娃·海辛頓跟那些謀殺沒有任何關系
Ava Hessington had nothing to do with those murders.

802
00:32:39,590 --> 00:32:41,100
你怎么會這樣
How do you like that?

803
00:32:44,310 --> 00:32:45,600
明天早上見
I'll see you in the morning.

804
00:32:45,620 --> 00:32:46,880
杰西卡
Jessica.

805
00:32:48,260 --> 00:32:50,060
我是認真的  她是無辜的
I'm serious. She's innocent.

806
00:32:51,810 --> 00:32:53,770
那跟我今晚回家有什么關系
And what does that have to do with me going home tonight?

807
00:32:53,780 --> 00:32:55,470
有很大的關系
It has everything to do with it.

808
00:32:56,270 --> 00:32:58,050
哈維同意讓她跟董事會談話
Harvey agreed to let her talk to the board.

809
00:32:58,050 --> 00:32:59,180
那就是我想要的
That's all I ever wanted.

810
00:32:59,180 --> 00:33:02,060
路易斯  如果他們明早不把她趕走
Louis, if they don't oust her tomorrow morning,

811
00:33:02,110 --> 00:33:04,950
他們就會輸掉明天下午的收購投票
They will lose that takeover vote tomorrow afternoon.

812
00:33:04,960 --> 00:33:06,830
不管怎樣她都得離開
She will be pushed out either way.

813
00:33:06,830 --> 00:33:08,140
可至少我不用對
Well, at least I won't be responsible

814
00:33:08,140 --> 00:33:09,920
奪走一個無辜女人的公司負責
for taking away an innocent woman's company.

815
00:33:09,920 --> 00:33:12,110
你不用為這事兒負責
You're not responsible for it.

816
00:33:12,180 --> 00:33:14,190
這是一次敵意收購
This is a hostile takeover.

817
00:33:14,190 --> 00:33:15,140
他們明天就來了
They're coming tomorrow,

818
00:33:15,140 --> 00:33:17,910
而市場才不在乎她是不是無辜的
and the market doesn't care whether she's innocent or not.

819
00:33:17,920 --> 00:33:19,180
哈維會認為是我干的
Harvey's gonna think it was me.

820
00:33:19,180 --> 00:33:20,690
確實是你
It was you.

821
00:33:20,690 --> 00:33:22,590
而且他之前就應該想到了
And he would have thought that before.

822
00:33:23,850 --> 00:33:25,780
請不要阻止我
Please do not stop me

823
00:33:25,780 --> 00:33:27,360
再去找董事會
from going back to that board.

824
00:33:27,360 --> 00:33:30,090
路易斯  是你自愿來做這件事的
Louis, you offered to do this.

825
00:33:30,090 --> 00:33:31,510
你不是為了哈維
You're not doing this to Harvey.

826
00:33:31,510 --> 00:33:33,520
你是為了你的客戶
You're doing this for your client,

827
00:33:33,520 --> 00:33:34,620
海辛頓石油
Hessington Oil.

828
00:33:34,620 --> 00:33:36,870
艾娃·海辛頓就是海辛頓石油
Ava Hessington is Hessington Oil.

829
00:33:36,870 --> 00:33:38,110
不再是了
Not anymore.

830
00:33:38,120 --> 00:33:38,790
杰西卡
Jessica.

831
00:33:38,790 --> 00:33:40,210
夠了
Enough.

832
00:33:40,620 --> 00:33:42,330
這次對話確實發生過
This conversation did happen,

833
00:33:42,670 --> 00:33:43,940
而且已經結束了
and it's over.

834
00:33:57,890 --> 00:33:59,670
你在那兒站了多久了
How long have you been standing there?

835
00:33:59,900 --> 00:34:02,470
足夠了解如果如果這事兒解決不了
Long enough to know that if this law thing doesn't work out,

836
00:34:02,470 --> 00:34:04,330
你將有一個糟糕的周五
you'd make a lousy boy Friday.

837
00:34:05,280 --> 00:34:07,870
我想讓你幫忙  但我不想占你便宜
I'd ask you to help, but I wouldn't want to take advantage.

838
00:34:07,880 --> 00:34:11,090
我會答應幫你  但不想被你占便宜
And I'd say yes, but I don't want to be taken advantage of.

839
00:34:11,420 --> 00:34:13,290
盡管我看得很開心
Though I am happy to watch.

840
00:34:13,740 --> 00:34:15,820
我對你來說就是砧板上的一塊肉  對吧
I'm nothing but a piece of meat to you, aren't I?

841
00:34:15,820 --> 00:34:17,560
安靜  復印工
Quiet, copy boy.

842
00:34:20,190 --> 00:34:21,690
明晚同一時間嗎
Same time tomorrow night?

843
00:34:21,690 --> 00:34:22,890
當然
Absolutely.

844
00:34:30,260 --> 00:34:31,530
真有意思
Interesting.

845
00:34:33,830 --> 00:34:35,870
如果你覺得復印室有意思的話
If you find copy rooms interesting,

846
00:34:35,870 --> 00:34:37,390
你該多出去走走
You need to get out more.

847
00:34:37,390 --> 00:34:38,900
我說的不是復印室
Oh, I'm not talking about the copy room.

848
00:34:38,900 --> 00:34:40,640
我說的是你和史蒂芬
I'm talking about you and Stephen

849
00:34:40,640 --> 00:34:41,560
還有你步伐中蕩漾的春心
and the spring in your steps.

850
00:34:41,560 --> 00:34:42,420
如果不是我了解你的話
If I didn't know any better,

851
00:34:42,420 --> 00:34:44,220
我會說你和他滾床單了
I'd say You were sleeping with him.

852
00:34:44,670 --> 00:34:47,380
天吶  你跟他睡了  不是嗎
Oh, my god, you slept with him, didn't you?

853
00:34:47,380 --> 00:34:48,570
沒有
No.

854
00:34:49,220 --> 00:34:50,420
感覺怎么樣
How was it?

855
00:34:50,420 --> 00:34:53,620
只能說  我太厲害了
Suffice it to say, I was awesome.

856
00:34:53,950 --> 00:34:55,570
等等  你真正想問的
Oh, wait, sorry, you probably wanted to know

857
00:34:55,570 --> 00:34:56,220
是他吧
about him, didn't you?

858
00:34:56,220 --> 00:34:57,450
說到點上了  沒錯
That was the point of the question, yes.

859
00:34:57,450 --> 00:34:58,190
嗯
Eh.

860
00:34:58,190 --> 00:34:59,510
-真的嗎  -想都別想
- Really? - God, no.

861
00:34:59,510 --> 00:35:00,870
-他可能就是我的白馬王子  -不會吧
- I may have met my match. - Oh, my God.

862
00:35:00,870 --> 00:35:02,290
-那兼職工作呢  -進行中
- And the arrangement? - Ongoing.

863
00:35:02,290 --> 00:35:03,570
那你告訴哈維了嗎
Well, did you tell Harvey?

864
00:35:03,570 --> 00:35:04,360
我勒個去
Oh, my god.

865
00:35:04,360 --> 00:35:05,340
怎么了
What?

866
00:35:05,340 --> 00:35:06,820
我都把哈維忘了
I never thought about Harvey.

867
00:35:07,150 --> 00:35:08,940
我可是唐娜啊  怎么會沒想到呢
I'm Donna. How could I have not thought of that?

868
00:35:08,940 --> 00:35:10,260
因為你沒用你的大腦思考
Because you weren't thinking with your brain.

869
00:35:10,260 --> 00:35:11,220
說得好
Good one.

870
00:35:11,230 --> 00:35:12,100
你在用...
You were thinking with your--

871
00:35:12,100 --> 00:35:13,050
我懂我懂
Yeah, I got it.

872
00:35:13,050 --> 00:35:14,270
那你打算怎么做
So what are you gonna do?

873
00:35:15,640 --> 00:35:17,530
他一回來我就和他說
I'm gonna tell him as soon as he gets back.

874
00:35:26,510 --> 00:35:27,260
一切都準備好了嗎
Have everything we need?

875
00:35:27,260 --> 00:35:27,880
都準備好了
Everything.

876
00:35:27,890 --> 00:35:28,800
路易去哪了
Where's louis?

877
00:35:28,800 --> 00:35:29,720
他會在那里等我們
He's gonna meet us over there.

878
00:35:29,720 --> 00:35:31,090
我們應該一起去的
We should all be going together.

879
00:35:31,090 --> 00:35:33,430
不過至少艾娃還算準時
Well, at least Ava's here on time.

880
00:35:35,420 --> 00:35:37,100
你干了些什么
What the hell did you do?

881
00:35:37,100 --> 00:35:38,090
你在說什么啊
What are you talking about?

882
00:35:38,090 --> 00:35:40,280
我剛剛被自己公司投票表決踢出來了
I just got voted out of my own company.

883
00:35:40,280 --> 00:35:41,410
等等  收購投票表決不是應該
Wait, the vote on the takeover

884
00:35:41,410 --> 00:35:42,780
在今天中午才開始的嗎
isn't supposed to be till this afternoon.

885
00:35:42,780 --> 00:35:44,480
在那之前他們進行了另一個投票
Well, they had a different one before that,

886
00:35:44,480 --> 00:35:45,810
我出局了
and I'm out.

887
00:35:45,840 --> 00:35:48,110
我想知道你是不是早就知道這件事
And what I want to know is, did you know?

888
00:35:48,120 --> 00:35:49,590
艾娃  我沒有背著你做任何事
Ava, I didn't go behind your back.

889
00:35:49,590 --> 00:35:51,720
也許你的確沒做啥背叛我的事
Well, you may not have gone behind my back,

890
00:35:51,720 --> 00:35:53,730
但如果早先你讓我發表公開聲明的話
but this never would have happened if you'd let me

891
00:35:53,730 --> 00:35:55,540
我也不會落得如此下場
speak publicly in the first place.

892
00:35:55,540 --> 00:35:58,500
艾娃  我相信你是清白的
Look, Ava, my believing in your innocence

893
00:35:58,500 --> 00:36:00,890
但我仍然不會希望你接受記者采訪
wouldn't change my mind about you talking to a reporter.

894
00:36:00,890 --> 00:36:02,420
那你今天又要我來說些什么
Then why were you going to let me speak today?

895
00:36:02,420 --> 00:36:04,080
因為接受記者采訪
Because an interview isn't the same thing

896
00:36:04,080 --> 00:36:06,270
和自己公司里的關門會議不是一回事
as a closed-door meeting within your own company.

897
00:36:06,270 --> 00:36:07,800
但他們已經開過了關門會議
Well, they had a closed-door meeting,

898
00:36:07,800 --> 00:36:10,360
而唯一的受益者就是你
and the only person who benefited from that was you.

899
00:36:10,360 --> 00:36:11,310
怎么說
How's that?

900
00:36:11,310 --> 00:36:13,590
我出局了  但你沒有
I may be out, but you're not.

901
00:36:13,840 --> 00:36:16,720
皮爾遜-達比依舊被雇用作
Pearson Darby has been conveniently retained

902
00:36:16,720 --> 00:36:19,340
海辛頓石油的法律顧問
as Hessington Oil's legal counsel.

903
00:36:22,210 --> 00:36:23,780
你覺得我會不知道這是你干的嗎
You think I don't know this was you?

904
00:36:23,780 --> 00:36:25,690
我才不在乎你知不知道
I don't care whether you know it was me or not.

905
00:36:25,690 --> 00:36:26,500
我堅信這么做是正確的
I stand by what I did,

906
00:36:26,500 --> 00:36:27,560
即使有下次我還會這么做
and I'd do it again.

907
00:36:27,560 --> 00:36:28,490
就因為我倆的私人恩怨
You mean selling Ava out

908
00:36:28,490 --> 00:36:30,490
你就出賣了艾娃
because of your personal issues with me?

909
00:36:30,490 --> 00:36:33,150
這跟私人恩怨沒關  而且跟你也沒關
This isn't personal, and it's not about you.

910
00:36:33,150 --> 00:36:35,140
一派胡言  自從達比把這案子交給我
Bullshit. Ever since Darby handed me

911
00:36:35,140 --> 00:36:37,080
而沒給你  你就一直很不爽
this case and not you, you've been pissed.

912
00:36:37,080 --> 00:36:40,230
我不爽是因為我倆在計劃上的分歧
I wasn't pissed until we had a disagreement on strategy,

913
00:36:40,240 --> 00:36:42,780
而且你還借用他的名字把我擋在門外
and you invoked his name to cut me out.

914
00:36:43,190 --> 00:36:44,240
我懂了
I get it.

915
00:36:44,240 --> 00:36:46,150
我沒說錯  這就是私人恩怨
I wasn't wrong about it being personal.

916
00:36:46,150 --> 00:36:47,640
不過猜錯了讓你不爽的對象
I was wrong about which person.

917
00:36:47,640 --> 00:36:48,740
你根本就不是生我的氣
You're not pissed at me.

918
00:36:48,740 --> 00:36:51,310
你是懊惱自己被耍了
You're pissed at yourself for getting played.

919
00:36:52,080 --> 00:36:53,240
你剛對我說了啥
What did you just say to me?

920
00:36:53,240 --> 00:36:54,130
沒聽錯
You heard me.

921
00:36:54,130 --> 00:36:55,330
你那時腦子短路了吧
Fools rush in,

922
00:36:55,330 --> 00:36:58,830
竟然在一開始給了他51%的股份
and you're the one who gave him the 51% in the first place.

923
00:37:00,850 --> 00:37:04,100
我和愛德華合并公司為的是公司的未來
I merged with Edward for the sake of this firm,

924
00:37:04,100 --> 00:37:06,370
這跟我對艾娃的所作所為是一樣的
just like what I did today with Ava.

925
00:37:06,810 --> 00:37:10,310
在這間房里宣泄自己私人情緒的是你才對
And the only one in this room taking things personally is you.

926
00:37:10,460 --> 00:37:11,780
接著騙自己吧
Tell yourself whatever you want,

927
00:37:11,780 --> 00:37:13,600
我知道這件事和達比有關
but don't tell me it doesn't have to do with Darby

928
00:37:13,600 --> 00:37:14,940
這就是私人恩怨
and don't tell me it isn't personal,

929
00:37:14,940 --> 00:37:17,540
因為你受不了一輩子當二把手
because you can't stand being number two.

930
00:37:23,030 --> 00:37:23,900
哈維  有時間嗎
Harvey, do you have a minute?

931
00:37:23,900 --> 00:37:24,790
沒時間
No, I don't.

932
00:37:24,790 --> 00:37:26,790
現在給我撥通愛德華·達比的電話
I need Edward Darby on the phone right now.

933
00:37:26,790 --> 00:37:28,480
還有  你今早去哪了
By the way, where were you this morning?

934
00:37:28,480 --> 00:37:29,800
你說啥  我今早在這啊
What are you talking about? I was here.

935
00:37:29,800 --> 00:37:31,010
但你沒在自己的位置上
You weren't here.

936
00:37:31,620 --> 00:37:32,880
我在復印室
I was in the copy room.

937
00:37:32,880 --> 00:37:35,020
你跑去復印室干嘛
Well, what the hell were you doing in the copy room?

938
00:37:35,450 --> 00:37:38,140
我要去幫史蒂芬處理點事
I was finishing up a couple things for Stephen.

939
00:37:38,140 --> 00:37:39,640
你在為史蒂芬干活
You're working for Stephen?

940
00:37:39,820 --> 00:37:42,530
-只是復印些東西  -你為我工作
- I made some copies. - You work for me.

941
00:37:44,080 --> 00:37:45,160
真抱歉
Sorry.

942
00:37:45,410 --> 00:37:46,580
下不為例
It was a one-time thing.

943
00:37:46,580 --> 00:37:48,560
既然你還沒幫我給達比打電話
Well, since you haven't gotten Darby for me yet,

944
00:37:48,560 --> 00:37:49,630
你想說些啥
what do you want?

945
00:37:50,210 --> 00:37:51,780
不是什么大事  可以等等再說
Nothing. It can wait.

946
00:38:08,920 --> 00:38:10,060
有什么事
What do you want?

947
00:38:11,500 --> 00:38:13,910
我想跟你說我很享受和你一起工作
I want to tell you that I enjoyed working with you.

948
00:38:14,730 --> 00:38:16,650
我原本以為我也會這么說
I thought I was gonna be able to say the same.

949
00:38:18,630 --> 00:38:20,600
有件事告訴你  我勸了路易  
If it means anything to you, I told Louis

950
00:38:20,600 --> 00:38:22,310
讓他別再把艾娃踢出去
to stop the plan to get rid of Ava.

951
00:38:22,320 --> 00:38:24,300
你知道他不會停手的  對嗎
Did you know he wasn't going to?

952
00:38:24,790 --> 00:38:25,810
沒錯
No.

953
00:38:26,480 --> 00:38:28,920
但事實是  即使這樣
But the truth is, even if I did,

954
00:38:28,920 --> 00:38:31,270
我也不會做任何阻攔他的事
I wouldn't have done anything to stop it.

955
00:38:31,680 --> 00:38:33,490
那我是不是就該因此相信你呢
Is that supposed to make me believe you?

956
00:38:34,880 --> 00:38:36,650
我只是想讓你了解我
It's supposed to make you understand me.

957
00:38:40,610 --> 00:38:41,970
你對他很忠心
You're loyal to him.

958
00:38:42,370 --> 00:38:43,820
因為我是他的部下
I'm committed to him.

959
00:38:45,600 --> 00:38:46,900
晚安  卡特里娜
Good night, Katrina.

960
00:38:48,150 --> 00:38:49,240
晚安 
Good night.

961
00:39:01,510 --> 00:39:02,760
她有什么事
What did she want?

962
00:39:03,730 --> 00:39:04,800
沒什么
Nothing.

963
00:39:06,240 --> 00:39:08,270
就說跟我合作挺愉快的
Tell me she enjoyed working with me.

964
00:39:09,580 --> 00:39:10,700
那你呢
Did you?

965
00:39:11,030 --> 00:39:12,030
我怎么
Did I what?

966
00:39:12,030 --> 00:39:13,440
你也覺得跟她合作很愉快吧
Did you enjoy working with her?

967
00:39:13,440 --> 00:39:16,030
總是看見你倆
I mean, I just kept seeing you guys

968
00:39:16,030 --> 00:39:18,190
在一起工作
working together all the time,

969
00:39:18,190 --> 00:39:20,520
就跟黏在一起似的
and you just seemed to be bonding away.

970
00:39:20,520 --> 00:39:21,500
吃醋了嗎
Are you jealous?

971
00:39:21,510 --> 00:39:22,630
這不好笑
It's not funny.

972
00:39:22,630 --> 00:39:24,700
我不是因為覺得好笑才笑
I'm not smiling because it's funny.

973
00:39:25,210 --> 00:39:27,200
而是因為覺得這樣很貼心
I'm smiling because it's sweet.

974
00:39:27,210 --> 00:39:28,300
你和珍妮那次我真的吃醋了
You didn't think it was sweet

975
00:39:28,300 --> 00:39:29,390
你可沒覺得貼心
when I was jealous of you and Jenny.

976
00:39:29,390 --> 00:39:30,900
那時候咱倆不是還沒在一起嗎
You and I weren't together then,

977
00:39:30,900 --> 00:39:32,480
可現在不一樣了
but we are now.

978
00:39:32,480 --> 00:39:33,560
是啊
Right.

979
00:39:34,920 --> 00:39:37,330
所以我現在才更覺得鬧心了
Which is why it bothers me more now.

980
00:39:37,670 --> 00:39:38,820
瑞秋...
Rachel...

981
00:39:40,200 --> 00:39:42,250
我把我的秘密告訴了你
I trusted you with my secret,

982
00:39:42,550 --> 00:39:43,990
由此你便掌控著我的人生
my life.

983
00:39:44,840 --> 00:39:46,600
我都這樣信任你了  難道你不知道
If I trusted you with that, don't you know that

984
00:39:46,600 --> 00:39:47,930
我的意思...
that means I...

985
00:39:51,560 --> 00:39:52,640
是...
That I...

986
00:39:55,910 --> 00:39:57,260
你想說什么
What are you-- what are you trying to say?

987
00:39:57,260 --> 00:39:58,970
你知道我想說什么
You know what I'm trying to say.

988
00:39:59,960 --> 00:40:02,140
現在不要說  我不想在這里聽
Don't say it now. I don't want to hear it here.

989
00:40:02,140 --> 00:40:04,810
這里嗎 能做的我們在這里都做過了
Here? Where we've done pretty much everything else?

990
00:40:04,810 --> 00:40:06,360
-邁克  我  -我愛你
- Mike, I-- - I love you.

991
00:40:08,220 --> 00:40:09,490
我愛你
I love you.

992
00:40:10,440 --> 00:40:12,210
我不想把這話憋心里了
I don't want to keep it in anymore.

993
00:40:17,170 --> 00:40:18,700
我也愛你
I love you too.

994
00:40:18,700 --> 00:40:22,010
現在我也不管有誰知道了
And in this moment I don't care who knows.

995
00:40:46,940 --> 00:40:48,020
你的所作所為
What you did amounts

996
00:40:48,020 --> 00:40:50,190
完全忤逆了我的意思
to nothing short of insubordination.

997
00:40:50,190 --> 00:40:52,480
你大老遠飛過來就是為了告訴我這句話嗎
Did you fly all the way from another country to tell me that?

998
00:40:52,480 --> 00:40:53,480
打個電話就行了嘛
You could have just called.

999
00:40:53,480 --> 00:40:55,070
我的意思很明確
I gave you a very clear directive,

1000
00:40:55,070 --> 00:40:56,040
可你卻一點也不合作
and you defied me.

1001
00:40:56,040 --> 00:40:56,960
你要來跟我理論一番嗎
Do you want to get into it?

1002
00:40:56,960 --> 00:40:58,280
樂意至極
I most certainly do.

1003
00:40:58,280 --> 00:40:59,640
當我同意跟你合并
When I agreed to merge with you,

1004
00:40:59,640 --> 00:41:01,460
就知道是51比49的控股
I knew it was 51-49,

1005
00:41:01,460 --> 00:41:03,660
但我想你不會因為比我多出這2%
But I didn't think you would lord your 2%

1006
00:41:03,660 --> 00:41:05,060
強行命令我
over me like a hammer.

1007
00:41:05,060 --> 00:41:07,510
我當初購買你的股權
And when I agreed to acquire you,

1008
00:41:07,520 --> 00:41:08,700
也沒覺得有這個必要
I didn't think I'd have to.

1009
00:41:08,700 --> 00:41:10,040
你的意思是后悔這次合并了嗎
Are you saying you regret this merger?

1010
00:41:10,040 --> 00:41:11,840
我是說我得多留意
I'm saying perhaps I should have paid more attention

1011
00:41:11,850 --> 00:41:12,860
危險信號
to the red flags,

1012
00:41:12,860 --> 00:41:15,340
比如掩藏前任合伙人挪用公款
such as covering up the embezzlement of a former partner.

1013
00:41:15,340 --> 00:41:17,830
這件事可是讓你抓住了把柄
Something you were more than willing to use to make the deal.

1014
00:41:17,830 --> 00:41:19,460
你背著我搞鬼
You went behind my back.

1015
00:41:19,460 --> 00:41:21,430
你就用這個案子刁難我
And you stuck me with this case

1016
00:41:21,440 --> 00:41:24,150
還讓我冒著損失一大筆錢的危險
and then risked losing me a huge amount of money.

1017
00:41:24,150 --> 00:41:27,220
我把案子給哈維之前
I gave Harvey this case after already handing you

1018
00:41:27,220 --> 00:41:28,660
就給了你一大筆錢
a huge amount of money.

1019
00:41:28,660 --> 00:41:31,630
大洋這邊  由我做主
I am in charge on this side of the ocean.

1020
00:41:31,630 --> 00:41:33,730
因為我給了你這個權力
Because I allow it to be that way.

1021
00:41:33,730 --> 00:41:35,460
又繞回來了
And there it is again.

1022
00:41:35,600 --> 00:41:37,200
51比49
51-49.

1023
00:41:37,770 --> 00:41:40,880
之前我一直以為哈維是那匹
Until now I believed that Harvey was the wild horse

1024
00:41:40,880 --> 00:41:43,320
無法馴服的野馬  但現在看來可能是你
that couldn't be tamed, but perhaps it is you.

1025
00:41:43,990 --> 00:41:45,500
哈維說的對
I think maybe Harvey was right.

1026
00:41:45,500 --> 00:41:46,700
的確是私人恩怨
It is personal.

1027
00:41:46,700 --> 00:41:48,140
但不是我造成的
But I didn't make it that way.

1028
00:41:48,140 --> 00:41:50,140
都是你  是你讓你對艾娃的個人情感
You did, when you allowed your feelings

1029
00:41:50,140 --> 00:41:52,050
影響了你的判斷
for Ava to cloud your judgment.

1030
00:41:52,050 --> 00:41:55,200
既然你說到這個  我之前的合伙人
And as you pointed out, I had a partner once

1031
00:41:55,210 --> 00:41:57,900
就是按照個人的狗屁情感辦事
who made decisions based on his personal shit,

1032
00:41:57,900 --> 00:42:00,640
我是不會再讓歷史重演的
and I will not allow that to happen again.

1033
00:42:00,850 --> 00:42:02,770
不管控股權如何分配
And 51-49 or not,

1034
00:42:02,770 --> 00:42:05,750
我剛在我這邊的賬本上加了一千四百萬
I just took 14 million and put it on my side of the ledger,

1035
00:42:05,750 --> 00:42:08,840
所以愛德華  麻煩你走的時候把燈關了
so do me a favor, Edward, and turn off the lights on your way out.

