1
00:07:26,270 --> 00:07:29,520
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:07:26,270 --> 00:07:29,520
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:07:26,270 --> 00:07:29,520
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:07:26,270 --> 00:07:29,520
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:07:26,270 --> 00:07:29,520
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:07:29,520 --> 00:07:34,680
{\an8}翻译：草草  爱卿溜小鸟  王大可  feilixiaozi  某豚  CS小明漫画家

7
00:07:34,680 --> 00:07:39,780
{\an8}翻译：杳杳  elf.CiciXT  猫咪赐我速死  鱼小姐啦  香茗小焙  小饭

8
00:07:39,780 --> 00:07:44,900
{\an8}校对：油炸电风扇  潇湘月影  贺天天

9
00:07:44,900 --> 00:07:50,130
{\an8}时间轴：今   猫   凭陵新月     

10
00:07:50,130 --> 00:07:55,420
{\an8}后期：加森       总监&精校：某羽

11
00:07:52,130 --> 00:07:54,290
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

12
00:07:52,130 --> 00:07:54,290
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第一集

13
00:00:01,010 --> 00:00:02,920
{\an2}{\pos(192,265)}《诉讼双雄》前情提要

14
00:00:02,470 --> 00:00:04,340
我手里的名单上有
I have a list here of the signing bonuses

15
00:00:04,340 --> 00:00:07,210
这里三个初级律师签约时许诺的奖金
of the top three associates who have come into this firm.

16
00:00:07,210 --> 00:00:10,480
预支的奖金加上我的薪水就够我的学费了
The advance, plus my salary, will cover my tuition.

17
00:00:10,480 --> 00:00:11,680
那些钱加起来也不够
Those numbers don't add up.

18
00:00:11,680 --> 00:00:14,030
有些初级律师和正式律师一样工作
Some of the associates work as lawyers,

19
00:00:14,080 --> 00:00:15,780
我也可以
and I can do the same.

20
00:00:15,860 --> 00:00:17,000
这是一封录用函
It's an offer letter.

21
00:00:17,000 --> 00:00:18,370
我们是投资银行家
We're investment bankers.

22
00:00:18,370 --> 00:00:20,230
我们的工作比你们的厉害多了
Our job blows yours out of the water.

23
00:00:20,230 --> 00:00:21,790
哈维  斯特芬妮·利斯顿刚刚给我打了电话
Harvey, Stephanie Liston just called me.

24
00:00:21,790 --> 00:00:24,260
她说迈克刚刚被带去问话
She said they just brought Mike in for questioning.

25
00:00:24,260 --> 00:00:27,280
你这个无良律师  我会时刻盯着你的
You're a dirty lawyer, and now you're on my radar.

26
00:00:27,280 --> 00:00:30,010
我受够了把我在乎的人置于危险境地
I'm tired of putting the people I care about in jeopardy.

27
00:00:30,030 --> 00:00:32,420
我下午给乔纳森·西德威尔打电话了
I called Jonathan Sidwell this afternoon.

28
00:00:32,730 --> 00:00:33,750
我接受那份工作了
I took the job.

29
00:00:33,750 --> 00:00:35,910
迈克·罗斯从没上过法学院
Mike Ross never went to law school.

30
00:00:36,280 --> 00:00:38,480
我知道  但我还是雇了他
I knew it, and I hired him anyway.

31
00:00:40,180 --> 00:00:42,020
我还是不能留下来  哈维
I still can't stay, Harvey.

32
00:00:42,110 --> 00:00:43,510
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

33
00:00:44,200 --> 00:00:45,730
允许我走吧
Give me permission to go.

34
00:01:20,210 --> 00:01:21,980
你是要去上班还是上学
Going to work or school?

35
00:01:22,720 --> 00:01:24,020
都去
Both.

36
00:01:25,610 --> 00:01:27,690
有时间再跟我缠绵一会儿吗
Think you have time for some of this?

37
00:01:28,370 --> 00:01:32,360
如果你把你的豪车借给我  就可以考虑
Maybe if you will loan me your limo.

38
00:01:35,270 --> 00:01:37,120
这绝对好商量
I'm sure we can work something out.

39
00:01:39,580 --> 00:01:42,110
{\an8}周四晚九点  卡萨布兰卡  现代启示录

40
00:02:13,810 --> 00:02:15,220
我以为你刚才在穿衣服
Thought you were getting dressed.

41
00:02:15,220 --> 00:02:17,010
是穿了
I did get dressed.

42
00:02:17,250 --> 00:02:18,970
然后又脱了
Then you got undressed.

43
00:02:19,480 --> 00:02:21,310
感觉有点热
I got a little hot.

44
00:02:22,940 --> 00:02:24,160
没错
Yes.

45
00:02:24,160 --> 00:02:25,480
是热
You did.

46
00:02:36,960 --> 00:02:39,740
说起来  这儿是有点热
Come to think of it, it is getting a little warm in here.

47
00:03:07,210 --> 00:03:08,490
吉利斯先生
Mr. Gillis.

48
00:03:08,490 --> 00:03:10,240
我是迈克·罗斯  认识你很高兴
Mike Ross. Nice to meet you.

49
00:03:10,280 --> 00:03:11,850
你要知道我同意见你
You should know I'm only doing this

50
00:03:11,850 --> 00:03:13,720
仅仅是出于对乔纳森·西德威尔的礼貌
as a courtesy to Jonathan Sidwell.

51
00:03:13,720 --> 00:03:16,590
但我现在就告诉你  不行
But I'll tell you right now, the answer is no.

52
00:03:16,590 --> 00:03:18,700
-很好  -什么意思
- Good. - Why good?

53
00:03:18,700 --> 00:03:21,660
经历了拒绝的同意才更有意义
Because a yes is always so much better when it starts as a no.

54
00:03:21,660 --> 00:03:23,100
你很有自信
You're a confident young man,

55
00:03:23,100 --> 00:03:25,690
但我清楚我的配送中心的价值
but I know what my distribution centers are worth.

56
00:03:25,690 --> 00:03:27,510
那是对你的价值
You know what they're worth to you.

57
00:03:27,840 --> 00:03:29,490
这是对我的价值
This is what they're worth to me.

58
00:03:34,150 --> 00:03:36,270
价格比我想的高
This is bigger than I expected.

59
00:03:36,700 --> 00:03:38,120
这话我听过
I've heard that before.

60
00:03:38,120 --> 00:03:39,900
行了  别打哈哈了
Okay, fun time's over.

61
00:03:39,900 --> 00:03:41,760
我不想卖给
I'm not interested in selling to someone

62
00:03:41,760 --> 00:03:43,220
我不熟悉的陌生人
who I don't know where they're coming from.

63
00:03:43,220 --> 00:03:45,030
那我来介绍下自己吧
Let me tell you where I'm coming from.

64
00:03:45,320 --> 00:03:46,750
我总是会做好功课
I do my homework.

65
00:03:47,020 --> 00:03:49,350
这些中心简直是在昭告那些虎视眈眈的人
These centers are a beacon to every predator out there

66
00:03:49,350 --> 00:03:50,350
你根本没为
that you haven't laid the groundwork 

67
00:03:50,350 --> 00:03:52,360
退出DVD界打好基础
to get out of the DVD business.

68
00:03:52,360 --> 00:03:55,090
听起来你是想吓唬我
Sounds to me like where you're coming from is trying to scare me.

69
00:03:55,090 --> 00:03:56,540
不  我不是想吓唬你
No, no, I'm not trying to scare you.

70
00:03:56,540 --> 00:03:57,990
是想帮助你
I'm trying to help you.

71
00:03:59,860 --> 00:04:02,560
很多人都在觊觎  你很清楚
They're circling, and you know it.

72
00:04:02,650 --> 00:04:04,160
你不卖给我
You don't do this,

73
00:04:04,180 --> 00:04:05,570
就等于是邀请别人
you might as well send out an invitation

74
00:04:05,570 --> 00:04:07,760
来恶意收购
asking for a hostile takeover.

75
00:04:08,820 --> 00:04:10,530
这个数字不可能是真的
This number can't be real.

76
00:04:10,530 --> 00:04:12,030
-是真的  -那你打算
- It is. - Then what the hell

77
00:04:12,030 --> 00:04:13,700
拿我的配送中心做什么
are you gonna do with my distribution centers?

78
00:04:13,700 --> 00:04:16,560
我很乐意在买下后5秒后告诉你
I'll be happy to tell you that five seconds after I buy them.

79
00:04:18,840 --> 00:04:21,060
沃尔特  我知道你想保全你的手下
Walter, I know you want your people to be okay,

80
00:04:21,060 --> 00:04:22,640
我保证  他们会没事的
and I give you my word they will be.

81
00:04:22,640 --> 00:04:26,070
但这些中心  已经成了累赘
But these centers... have become a headache.

82
00:04:26,070 --> 00:04:28,910
那些掠食者找上门来时  你需要现金
And you need cash for when those predators come knocking.

83
00:04:28,910 --> 00:04:31,700
让他们来纠缠吧  我一概挡在外面
Let them knock. I'm not answering the door.

84
00:04:31,700 --> 00:04:33,420
不  你不懂
No, you're not hearing me.

85
00:04:33,800 --> 00:04:35,500
如果你筹的钱不够
If you don't raise enough money, 

86
00:04:35,650 --> 00:04:38,440
他们无论如何都会进来
they're coming in whether you answer that door or not.

87
00:04:42,050 --> 00:04:43,840
提议有效期为一小时
The offer's good for another hour.

88
00:04:51,930 --> 00:04:54,490
你不是我的那个打发胶的犯罪同伙
You are not my hair-gelled partner in crime.

89
00:04:54,720 --> 00:04:56,970
我九年级之后就没用过发胶
I haven't used hair gel since ninth grade.

90
00:04:57,200 --> 00:04:59,740
我当时头发太卷了
I was trying to avoid the frizzy look.

91
00:05:00,070 --> 00:05:01,410
他在哪
Where is he?

92
00:05:01,700 --> 00:05:04,120
唐娜说他今天在外面有个晨会
Donna said that he had a morning meeting outside of the office.

93
00:05:04,120 --> 00:05:05,190
唐娜人呢
And where is Donna?

94
00:05:05,190 --> 00:05:06,450
这儿呢
Right here.

95
00:05:06,500 --> 00:05:08,560
我喜欢在别人需要时准点出现
I prefer to appear at the exact moment I'm needed.

96
00:05:08,560 --> 00:05:09,900
可惜哈维没这个概念
I wish I could say the same for Harvey.

97
00:05:09,900 --> 00:05:11,670
-哈维有个很...  -省省吧
- Oh, well, Harvey has a very-- - Save it.

98
00:05:11,670 --> 00:05:12,840
她虽然嫩
She may have been born yesterday,

99
00:05:12,840 --> 00:05:16,110
但我知道"晨会"的真正意思
but I know that morning meeting doesn't mean "morning meeting."

100
00:05:16,110 --> 00:05:17,070
大家都知道
Everyone knows that.

101
00:05:17,070 --> 00:05:18,900
但我不能直说
It's just not my place to say it.

102
00:05:18,900 --> 00:05:20,200
我也不能
Not mine either.

103
00:05:20,200 --> 00:05:21,680
他昨天也这样
He did it yesterday too.

104
00:05:21,740 --> 00:05:23,550
等他来了
When he resurfaces,

105
00:05:23,550 --> 00:05:25,800
告诉他斯佩克特  皮尔逊想见他
tell Specter Pearson wants to see him.

106
00:05:29,450 --> 00:05:31,240
我高中时用摩丝
I used mousse in high school.

107
00:05:31,240 --> 00:05:33,350
-当时是90年代嘛  -年龄对不上吧
- It was the 90s. - Was it?

108
00:05:33,350 --> 00:05:34,710
听到了哦
I heard that.

109
00:05:45,300 --> 00:05:48,560
{\an8}西德威尔投资集团

110
00:05:52,310 --> 00:05:53,840
给我带午餐了吗
Did you bring me lunch?

111
00:05:54,040 --> 00:05:55,460
陈氏王朝
Chen Dynasty.

112
00:05:56,150 --> 00:05:57,150
里面有几个蛋卷
How many egg rolls are in here?

113
00:05:57,150 --> 00:05:58,940
-两个  -你跟吉利斯达成协议了
- Two. - You closed Gillis.

114
00:05:58,940 --> 00:06:00,600
不  我绝杀了吉利斯
No, I killed Gillis.

115
00:06:00,600 --> 00:06:03,470
但愿你跟他们说了捞面里别放蘑菇
Well, I hope you told them no mushrooms in the lo mein.

116
00:06:03,470 --> 00:06:05,790
-你又没跟我说过  -我以为没必要说呢
- You never told me that. - I didn't think I had to.

117
00:06:05,790 --> 00:06:07,760
不该是由你来照顾我的吗
Aren't you supposed to be the one taking care of me?

118
00:06:07,760 --> 00:06:09,690
我的捞面里有蘑菇
Ugh, how am I supposed to do that

119
00:06:09,690 --> 00:06:11,640
我还怎么照顾你
when there are mushrooms in my lo mein?

120
00:06:11,640 --> 00:06:13,400
再说一次我为什么要留你在身边
Why do I keep you around again?

121
00:06:13,400 --> 00:06:15,030
弗莱德曼科技公司的交易备忘
Deal memo on Friedman Technologies,

122
00:06:15,030 --> 00:06:16,620
斯蒂尔曼签名的约定书
engagement letter signed by Stillman,

123
00:06:16,620 --> 00:06:19,360
还有今晚你跟瑞秋一起去看的
and, oh, two front-row tickets to daft punk

124
00:06:19,360 --> 00:06:20,980
傻朋克演唱会前排票
for you and Rachel tonight.

125
00:06:21,100 --> 00:06:23,430
但我为什么要留你在身边
But why do I keep you around?

126
00:06:24,320 --> 00:06:26,230
迈克  西德威尔在里面等你
Mike, Sidwell's in there waiting for you.

127
00:06:26,230 --> 00:06:28,780
小心点  他心情不太好
Be careful, okay? He's not in a good mood.

128
00:06:28,780 --> 00:06:30,380
没事的  知道为什么吗
It's okay. You know why?

129
00:06:30,380 --> 00:06:32,200
因为我拿下了吉利斯
'cause I killed it with Gillis.

130
00:06:32,450 --> 00:06:33,630
-艾米  -干什么
- Hey, Amy. - Yeah?

131
00:06:33,630 --> 00:06:35,170
吃蘑菇吧  对你有好处
Eat the mushrooms. They're good for you.

132
00:06:35,170 --> 00:06:36,630
去你的
Screw you.

133
00:06:37,370 --> 00:06:39,640
-早上好  -你上哪去了
- Morning. - Where have you been?

134
00:06:39,640 --> 00:06:41,150
就是让沃尔特·吉利斯把他所有的
Oh, you know, just getting Walter Gillis

135
00:06:41,150 --> 00:06:43,310
配送中心都卖给我们而已
to sell us all of his distribution centers.

136
00:06:45,990 --> 00:06:48,030
-你干什么呢  -看着像干什么呢
- What the hell are you doing? - What's it look like I'm doing?

137
00:06:48,030 --> 00:06:50,420
我在告诉你  我们不是修道院
I'm sending a message. We're not a convent.

138
00:06:50,420 --> 00:06:51,800
我们这行是要赚钱的
We're in business to make money.

139
00:06:51,800 --> 00:06:53,280
这笔生意赚钱了啊
And this deal does that.

140
00:06:53,280 --> 00:06:55,210
你这么做是为了让那些人继续工作
You did this deal to retain those people's jobs.

141
00:06:55,210 --> 00:06:58,060
-盈利了30%  -我们做对冲基金的
- And to make us 30%. - We're a hedge fund.

142
00:06:58,060 --> 00:06:59,410
做不到50%
If we don't make 50%,

143
00:06:59,410 --> 00:07:01,530
还不如买分时公寓  然后听天由命呢
we might as well buy time-shares and hope for the best.

144
00:07:01,530 --> 00:07:03,690
扯淡呢  这笔生意很好
That's bullshit. This deal is solid.

145
00:07:03,690 --> 00:07:05,880
不  扯淡的是你来这里三个月了
No, what's bullshit is you've been here for three months.

146
00:07:05,880 --> 00:07:08,230
你所做的都只是安打而已  我需要全垒打
All you've done is hit singles, and I need a goddamn home run.

147
00:07:08,230 --> 00:07:09,910
-乔纳森  听我说  -我不想听
- Jonathan, listen. - I don't want to hear it.

148
00:07:10,500 --> 00:07:12,450
我要你给点力
I want you to get your head out of your ass.

149
00:07:12,450 --> 00:07:13,950
别再挽救别人的工作了
Stop trying to save people's jobs,

150
00:07:13,950 --> 00:07:15,960
好好赚点大钱吧
and start making us some real money.

151
00:07:16,960 --> 00:07:18,680
不然就回去做律师
Or go back to being a lawyer.

152
00:08:04,380 --> 00:08:05,920
听说你要见我
I heard you wanted to see me.

153
00:08:06,120 --> 00:08:07,770
那是三小时前的事了
That was three hours ago.

154
00:08:07,770 --> 00:08:09,560
要是你知道我三小时前在做什么
If you knew what I was doing three hours ago,

155
00:08:09,560 --> 00:08:11,180
应该就不会想见我了
I don't think you would've wanted to see me.

156
00:08:11,180 --> 00:08:12,930
我知道你三小时前在做什么
I know what you were doing three hours ago.

157
00:08:12,930 --> 00:08:14,930
那你应该一起来的
Well, then, you should have come on over.

158
00:08:17,040 --> 00:08:18,090
也许你也应该
Maybe you should try having

159
00:08:18,090 --> 00:08:20,110
开开晨会
some morning meetings yourself.

160
00:08:20,180 --> 00:08:22,300
我的早晨怎么过不用你操心
Don't you worry about my mornings.

161
00:08:22,370 --> 00:08:25,130
你要操心的是洛根·桑德斯
What you need to worry about is Logan Sanders.

162
00:08:25,130 --> 00:08:26,340
怎么
What?

163
00:08:26,340 --> 00:08:29,010
他把他爸哪家子公司搞破产了
He drive one of his father's subsidiaries into bankruptcy?

164
00:08:29,010 --> 00:08:31,470
恰恰相反  他重新做人了
The opposite. Boy got his shit together.

165
00:08:31,540 --> 00:08:34,100
麦克斯要退休了  洛根会掌权
Max is retiring, and Logan's taking over.

166
00:08:34,100 --> 00:08:35,800
我猜猜  他想见一面
Let me guess. He wants a meeting.

167
00:08:35,800 --> 00:08:36,980
已经说定了
He's got one.

168
00:08:36,980 --> 00:08:39,220
明早十点跟你见
With you, tomorrow morning, 10:00 a.m.

169
00:08:39,220 --> 00:08:41,470
很好  往后延一周
Great. Push it a week.

170
00:08:41,470 --> 00:08:43,500
哈维  这孩子自认为是头年轻的雄狮
Harvey, this kid considers himself a young lion.

171
00:08:43,500 --> 00:08:44,500
他要立威
He's gonna want to make his mark,

172
00:08:44,500 --> 00:08:46,310
最简单的方法就是
and the easiest way for him to do that

173
00:08:46,310 --> 00:08:47,950
换律师
is to change lawyers.

174
00:08:47,950 --> 00:08:49,990
也许吧  但雄狮可不会想要
Maybe, but the last thing a lion wants

175
00:08:49,990 --> 00:08:53,190
晚餐被盛在银盘子里递给他
is to have his dinner handed to him on a silver platter.

176
00:08:53,190 --> 00:08:54,870
你要让他捕猎
You're gonna give him a hunt.

177
00:08:55,340 --> 00:08:57,550
你全靠自己想到的吗
Did you think of that all on your own?

178
00:08:57,550 --> 00:08:58,350
我现在犀利非常
I'm extra sharp.

179
00:08:58,350 --> 00:08:59,830
一早上都没干活
I haven't worked a minute all morning.

180
00:08:59,830 --> 00:09:01,920
搞笑吧  我因为做爱搞得迟到了
See, that's funny, 'cause I was late from all the sex.

181
00:09:01,920 --> 00:09:03,490
赶紧滚出我的办公室
Get the hell out of my office.

182
00:09:14,360 --> 00:09:16,300
看看是谁来了哟
Look what the cat dragged in.

183
00:09:16,300 --> 00:09:18,650
-还穿了个马甲  -来了
- And you're wearing a vest. - Here it comes.

184
00:09:18,650 --> 00:09:20,920
-什么来了  -祝词
- Here what comes? - Mazel tov.

185
00:09:21,340 --> 00:09:23,490
今天是你的大日子  恭喜
Congratulations on your special day.

186
00:09:23,490 --> 00:09:25,120
-这个梗不错  -哈维  别说他了
- That's a good one. - Harvey, leave him alone.

187
00:09:25,120 --> 00:09:26,260
他看着比你帅
He looks better than you do.

188
00:09:26,260 --> 00:09:28,170
-谢谢  唐娜  -不客气
- Thank you, Donna. - You're welcome.

189
00:09:28,340 --> 00:09:30,020
花生先生来过电话
Oh, and Mr. Peanut called,

190
00:09:28,340 --> 00:09:30,020
{\an8}花生先生  某坚果品牌卡通人物  形象为一个花生带着高礼帽

191
00:09:30,020 --> 00:09:31,720
说他很愿意把礼帽借给你
and he said he'd be happy to lend you his top hat.

192
00:09:31,720 --> 00:09:34,440
-你们两个说完了吗  -我能说一整天
- Are you two finished? - I could go all day.

193
00:09:34,440 --> 00:09:35,950
我以为马甲已经够惨了
I think the vest has had enough.

194
00:09:35,950 --> 00:09:36,830
是啊
Yeah.

195
00:09:36,830 --> 00:09:39,130
所以你大老远跑来就是为了告诉我
So you come all the way down here just to let me know

196
00:09:39,130 --> 00:09:40,680
关于沃尔特·吉利斯你说对了
that you were right about Walter Gillis?

197
00:09:40,680 --> 00:09:42,280
我大老远跑来是为了告诉你
I came all the way over here to tell you

198
00:09:42,280 --> 00:09:44,220
我在儿童泳池游够了
I am done playing in the kiddie pool.

199
00:09:44,220 --> 00:09:46,130
-继续说  -我要去抓大鱼
- I'm listening. - I'm going after a whale.

200
00:09:46,130 --> 00:09:47,950
我想我恋爱了  我们开战吧
I think I'm in love. Let's go to war.

201
00:09:47,950 --> 00:09:49,250
问题就在这里
That's the thing.

202
00:09:50,040 --> 00:09:51,540
我们不会开战的
We're not going to war.

203
00:09:52,060 --> 00:09:54,940
迈克  不管是谁一旦发现
Mike, the second whoever it is finds out

204
00:09:54,940 --> 00:09:56,560
你持有他们公司5%的股份
that you've got 5% of their company,

205
00:09:56,560 --> 00:09:57,850
不管你愿不愿意  我们都会陷入战争
We're going to war whether you like it or not.

206
00:09:57,850 --> 00:10:00,870
他们不会发现  因为我没收到5%
They're not gonna find that out because I don't own 5%.

207
00:10:00,870 --> 00:10:03,430
需要我给你科普一下流程吗
Do I need to give you a tutorial on the procedure?

208
00:10:03,430 --> 00:10:04,610
你要以购买股份为开端
You start by buying shares.

209
00:10:04,610 --> 00:10:06,300
我知道流程是怎样的  哈维
I know what the procedure is, Harvey.

210
00:10:06,300 --> 00:10:07,550
那你到底买了多少股份
Well, how many shares have you bought?

211
00:10:07,550 --> 00:10:09,180
-一分没有  -"我知道流程"
- None. - This phrase,

212
00:10:09,180 --> 00:10:10,540
这句话的意思
"I know what the procedure is,"

213
00:10:10,540 --> 00:10:12,090
可能并不是你想的那样
I don't think it means what you think it means.

214
00:10:12,090 --> 00:10:15,380
哈维  对你来说也许不可思议
Well, as inconceivable as it might be to you, Harvey,

215
00:10:15,380 --> 00:10:17,270
但我不打算进行恶意收购
I'm actually not going in hostile.

216
00:10:17,270 --> 00:10:18,120
什么意思
What are you talking about?

217
00:10:18,120 --> 00:10:19,590
我的意思是接近某人
I'm talking about approaching someone

218
00:10:19,590 --> 00:10:21,710
然后收购公司 让它存活下来
to buy their company in order to keep it alive,

219
00:10:21,710 --> 00:10:23,090
而不把它分拆出售
instead of selling it for parts.

220
00:10:23,090 --> 00:10:25,360
你是要给别人拥抱和彩虹啊
You're offering someone hugs and rainbows.

221
00:10:25,360 --> 00:10:27,700
我要给别人一个存活的机会
I'm offering someone the chance to survive

222
00:10:27,700 --> 00:10:29,600
也相信并支持他们会放手一搏
and banking that they'll take that chance

223
00:10:29,600 --> 00:10:30,990
而不是就这么放弃
rather than give up.

224
00:10:31,630 --> 00:10:33,320
但你没有钱对吧
You don't have the money, do you?

225
00:10:33,320 --> 00:10:34,260
是的  没有
No, I don't.

226
00:10:34,260 --> 00:10:36,410
但就算我有钱  也不会用
But even if I did, I wouldn't use it.

227
00:10:37,130 --> 00:10:38,670
每个没有钱的人
Well, welcome to what every person

228
00:10:38,670 --> 00:10:40,600
都曾经这么说过
who doesn't have money has ever said.

229
00:10:40,600 --> 00:10:42,280
我懂了
Oh, I get it.

230
00:10:42,330 --> 00:10:44,550
你以为这还是那种可以嘲笑我想法的会面
You think this is the meeting where you make fun of my idea.

231
00:10:44,550 --> 00:10:45,580
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no, no.

232
00:10:45,580 --> 00:10:47,000
这是一次你发现  无论你是否喜欢
This is the meeting where you realize

233
00:10:47,000 --> 00:10:49,960
我的想法都会成为现实的会面
that my idea is happening whether you like it or not.

234
00:10:51,620 --> 00:10:52,730
那种会面有什么意思
Where's the fun in that meeting?

235
00:10:52,730 --> 00:10:54,000
意思
Oh, the fun?

236
00:10:54,110 --> 00:10:57,070
全在谈判桌的我这侧
It's all right over here on this side of the table.

237
00:10:57,690 --> 00:10:59,220
我会给你点时间
Hey, I'll give you a chance 

238
00:10:59,220 --> 00:11:00,530
适应新的现实
to get acquainted with the new reality.

239
00:11:00,530 --> 00:11:01,420
我在办公室等着
I'll be in my office.

240
00:11:01,420 --> 00:11:03,320
今天之前给我答复
Get back to me by the end of the day.

241
00:11:03,630 --> 00:11:04,880
天哪
Wow.

242
00:11:04,880 --> 00:11:07,600
看来我们的小宝贝长大成人了
Looks like our baby boy's all growns up.

243
00:11:08,020 --> 00:11:10,230
亲爱的  你们这里可以提供免费停车吗
Hey, tell me, sweetheart, you guys validate parking?

244
00:11:10,230 --> 00:11:11,550
是的  当然了
Oh, yeah, sure thing.

245
00:11:11,550 --> 00:11:14,010
拿这个就可以
I've got it right here.

246
00:11:14,010 --> 00:11:15,670
可以用几个小时
And how many hours is that good for?

247
00:11:15,670 --> 00:11:17,760
有所谓吗  反正都会在账单上找回来
What's it matter? We're just gonna charge it back to you anyway.

248
00:11:17,760 --> 00:11:19,620
你知道吗  我的秘书比你年轻
You know my secretary is, like, so much younger

249
00:11:19,620 --> 00:11:21,620
身材好  还幽默
and fitter and funnier than you.

250
00:11:21,620 --> 00:11:23,060
你滚吧
Start running.

251
00:11:25,260 --> 00:11:26,850
他刚说了身材比我好吗
Did he say "Fitter"?

252
00:11:29,690 --> 00:11:30,610
你有什么发现
What did you find out?

253
00:11:30,610 --> 00:11:32,630
-伍德尔卷土重来了  -我也是  时间
- Woodall's resurfacing. - Me too. When?

254
00:11:32,630 --> 00:11:34,350
-下周  -我也是  地点
- Next week. - Me too. Where?

255
00:11:34,350 --> 00:11:36,100
-证监会  -我也是  职位
- S.E.C. - Me too. Title?

256
00:11:36,100 --> 00:11:38,450
-主管  -总监
- Supervisor. - Director.

257
00:11:38,450 --> 00:11:39,400
我也是  我那么说只是在确认
Me too. I just threw that in

258
00:11:39,400 --> 00:11:40,910
你不是在附和我
to make sure you weren't yes-man-ing me.

259
00:11:41,100 --> 00:11:41,920
继续说
Talk to me.

260
00:11:41,920 --> 00:11:44,450
我查到了伍德尔派来追查我们的人的名字
I found out the name of the man Woodall's sending after us.

261
00:11:44,450 --> 00:11:46,340
杰夫·马龙
Jeff Malone.

262
00:11:48,290 --> 00:11:50,070
杰夫·马龙是个野兽
Jeff Malone is a beast.

263
00:11:50,160 --> 00:11:53,500
打败野兽的唯一办法就是找个更大的野兽
Well, the only way to beat a beast is with a bigger beast.

264
00:11:54,070 --> 00:11:55,770
我要在别人之前开始着手处理
I need to get in there before everyone else

265
00:11:55,770 --> 00:11:57,790
让哈维和杰西卡知道我有远见寻找问题
and let Harvey and Jessica know that I had the foresight

266
00:11:57,790 --> 00:11:59,660
有头脑发现问题
to look for it, the cunning to find it,

267
00:11:59,660 --> 00:12:01,350
而且还有勇气去解决问题
and the balls to stop it.

268
00:12:01,350 --> 00:12:02,670
然后你搞定马龙
Then you take on Malone.

269
00:12:02,670 --> 00:12:04,370
下一站  冠名合伙人
Next stop: name partner.

270
00:12:04,370 --> 00:12:07,060
-皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特  -好了
- Pearson Specter Litt. - Okay, you know what?

271
00:12:07,060 --> 00:12:09,590
事成之后再高兴不迟
Just let's not count our chickens before they hatch.

272
00:12:10,750 --> 00:12:12,370
但再说一遍让我乐乐
But just for shits and giggles, say it one more time.

273
00:12:12,370 --> 00:12:13,660
省略斯佩克特
Leave out Specter.

274
00:12:13,660 --> 00:12:16,790
唐娜  我拿到了保罗·波特的年度重组方案
Donna, I got Paul Porter's annual restructuring proposal.

275
00:12:16,790 --> 00:12:19,440
你能把它归到"关我屁事"那档里吗
Can you file it under "I don't give a shit"?

276
00:12:19,650 --> 00:12:21,790
迈克怎么办  要不我让瑞秋
What about Mike? You want me to have Rachel

277
00:12:21,790 --> 00:12:23,010
给他弄个盛大演出吗
prepare a dog and pony show for him?

278
00:12:23,010 --> 00:12:24,840
-不需要  -为什么
- That won't be necessary. - Why not?

279
00:12:24,840 --> 00:12:26,680
哈维  我得跟你谈谈
Harvey, I need to talk to you right now

280
00:12:26,680 --> 00:12:27,980
是件很重要的事
about something very important.

281
00:12:27,980 --> 00:12:29,470
哈维  为什么不需要
Harvey, why won't it be necessary?

282
00:12:29,470 --> 00:12:31,640
想跟姑娘约会可不能死缠烂打
'Cause you don't beg the girl to go out with you.

283
00:12:31,640 --> 00:12:32,540
得按兵不动
You wait.

284
00:12:32,540 --> 00:12:34,100
-她自会送上门  -那都算不上...
- She'll call. - That's not even--

285
00:12:34,100 --> 00:12:37,120
先等一下  要是她们不联系你呢
Excuse me. Hold on a second. Um, what if they don't call?

286
00:12:37,700 --> 00:12:39,050
永远都会联系的
They always call.

287
00:12:39,050 --> 00:12:40,580
那是你  其他人呢
Well, what about people who aren't you?

288
00:12:40,580 --> 00:12:42,790
-你是说你自己吗  -当然了
- You mean you? - Yeah, of course I do.

289
00:12:43,040 --> 00:12:44,830
不联系你就不联系了呗
If they don't call, then they don't call.

290
00:12:44,830 --> 00:12:46,680
但要是让她们看出了你的绝望
But once they smell your desperation,

291
00:12:46,680 --> 00:12:47,740
你的男性尊严就没了
they won't respect you,

292
00:12:47,740 --> 00:12:49,430
你就再无崛起之日了
and you'll never get what you want anyway.

293
00:12:49,430 --> 00:12:51,680
你不是要跟我谈什么吗
I'm sorry, did you want to talk to me about something?

294
00:12:52,230 --> 00:12:53,520
不着急
It can wait.

295
00:12:54,390 --> 00:12:55,370
对了
Come to think of it,

296
00:12:55,370 --> 00:12:57,130
等瑞秋从学校回来
tell Rachel when she's back from school

297
00:12:57,130 --> 00:12:59,050
告诉她今天不用上班了
she can have the rest of the day off.

298
00:13:03,910 --> 00:13:05,180
哈维
Harvey.

299
00:13:05,410 --> 00:13:08,450
要是你这么干  不如再给迈克发封电报
You do that, you might as well send Mike a telegram that says,

300
00:13:08,450 --> 00:13:10,410
告诉他"我根本没把你的想法放在心上"
"I'm not putting any thought into your idea."

301
00:13:10,410 --> 00:13:11,890
是啊  也行
Yeah, might as well.

302
00:13:12,760 --> 00:13:14,790
你确定要这么玩吗
Okay, are you sure that's how you want to play this?

303
00:13:14,790 --> 00:13:16,320
我不是都回答过了吗
Didn't I just answer that?

304
00:13:16,610 --> 00:13:19,890
但这可不是迈克联不联系你这么简单
You did, but this isn't about whether or not Mike calls back.

305
00:13:19,890 --> 00:13:22,070
而是你不让迈克做主
This is about you not letting Mike call the shots.

306
00:13:22,070 --> 00:13:23,520
要是让他做主  他绝对
I let him call the shots, all he's gonna do

307
00:13:23,520 --> 00:13:25,220
-会搬起石头砸自己的脚  -也许
- is shoot himself in the foot. - Maybe.

308
00:13:25,220 --> 00:13:26,950
但如果对方不是迈克
But if this was anybody other than Mike,

309
00:13:26,950 --> 00:13:28,150
你不可能这么反常
You wouldn't be acting like this.

310
00:13:28,150 --> 00:13:30,210
胡说  托尼·扬诺普洛斯都没法摆布我
Bullshit. I don't let Tony Gianopolous push me around.

311
00:13:30,210 --> 00:13:31,110
别说迈克·罗斯了
You think I'm gonna let Mike Ross?

312
00:13:31,110 --> 00:13:33,340
你当然不会受托尼摆布
No, of course you don't let Tony push you around,

313
00:13:33,340 --> 00:13:35,760
但我从没见你嘲笑过他的主意
but I've never seen you mock one of his ideas.

314
00:13:35,760 --> 00:13:37,770
那是因为他的点子没那么荒唐
Yeah, because his ideas aren't ridiculous.

315
00:13:37,770 --> 00:13:39,680
这是迈克第一个重大决策
This is Mike's first big idea.

316
00:13:39,680 --> 00:13:42,050
我跟你说过了  他这个决策蠢爆了
And I just told you, his first big idea sucks.

317
00:13:42,050 --> 00:13:44,630
要是你利用瑞秋来传达这个消息
And if you use Rachel to deliver that message,

318
00:13:44,630 --> 00:13:45,920
结局肯定不好看
this is gonna end badly.

319
00:13:45,920 --> 00:13:47,130
谢了  老妈  但我还是
Okay, thanks, mom, but I think

320
00:13:47,130 --> 00:13:48,670
要继续玩下去
I'm gonna keep playing ball in the house.

321
00:13:48,670 --> 00:13:51,170
你可以像个不想听话的孩子一样
Okay, act like a child who doesn't want to be told

322
00:13:51,170 --> 00:13:52,650
但迈克是个客户
what to do, but Mike's a client,

323
00:13:52,650 --> 00:13:54,140
你得把他当成客户来对待
and you need to start treating him like one.

324
00:13:54,140 --> 00:13:56,060
唐娜  下次我需要了解
Donna, the next time I need help figuring out

325
00:13:56,060 --> 00:13:58,060
如何对待客户的时候  会通知你的
how to treat a client, I'll let you know.

326
00:13:58,820 --> 00:14:00,240
好  很好
Okay, great.

327
00:14:11,770 --> 00:14:13,460
哈维  有事吗
Harvey, what can I do for you?

328
00:14:13,460 --> 00:14:15,570
有个叫杰夫·马龙的人在会议室
There's a Jeff Malone waiting in the conference room

329
00:14:15,570 --> 00:14:16,570
等着见我们俩
wanting to see both of us.

330
00:14:16,570 --> 00:14:18,060
你认识他吗
Any idea who he is?

331
00:14:18,390 --> 00:14:21,270
见过  他是证监会的牛人
I've run into him before. He's a hotshot at the S.E.C.

332
00:14:21,270 --> 00:14:23,520
-你觉得他想干什么  -我们去问问吧
- What do you think he wants? - Let's go find out.

333
00:14:27,520 --> 00:14:28,800
皮尔逊女士
Ms. Pearson.

334
00:14:29,090 --> 00:14:30,620
你一定是哈维·斯佩克特了
You must be Harvey Specter.

335
00:14:30,620 --> 00:14:32,620
-我是杰夫·马龙  -这我知道
- I'm Jeff Malone. - I know who you are.

336
00:14:32,620 --> 00:14:34,500
我想知道的是你来干什么
My question is, why are you here?

337
00:14:34,580 --> 00:14:36,830
-敌意满满啊  -你负责调查
- You seem hostile. - You investigate

338
00:14:36,830 --> 00:14:39,590
公开上市公司  我们可不是
publicly traded companies. We're not publicly traded.

339
00:14:39,590 --> 00:14:41,290
没错  可你们的客户是
No, but your clients are.

340
00:14:41,290 --> 00:14:43,400
所以他才会有疑问  我们才会有敌意
Hence his question and our hostility.

341
00:14:43,400 --> 00:14:45,340
-我们  -晚餐被不速之客打扰时
- Our? - We tend to stick together

342
00:14:45,340 --> 00:14:47,500
我们一向团结一致
when an uninvited guest interrupts our dinner.

343
00:14:47,500 --> 00:14:49,890
我没带酒来  但我希望在离开时
Well, I didn't bring any wine, but when I go,

344
00:14:49,890 --> 00:14:51,470
你们会为我的到来感到高兴
I hope you'll be happy that I dropped by.

345
00:14:51,470 --> 00:14:52,950
这可不好说
Yeah, I doubt that.

346
00:14:52,950 --> 00:14:56,210
那就快告诉我们是哪个客户把你招来
So why don't you tell us which client you're here for

347
00:14:56,210 --> 00:14:57,790
说完就走吧
and be on your way?

348
00:14:57,910 --> 00:14:59,280
所有
All of them.

349
00:15:00,240 --> 00:15:03,530
什么时候证监会开始通过盯上客户
Since when does the S.E.C. go around intimidating law firms

350
00:15:03,530 --> 00:15:04,990
来威胁律所了
by going after their clients?

351
00:15:04,990 --> 00:15:06,130
现在还没有  但等下周
They don't, but they will

352
00:15:06,130 --> 00:15:08,410
埃里克·伍德尔上任就会了
when Eric Woodall starts there next week.

353
00:15:08,650 --> 00:15:11,170
做了那些事还盯上我们的客户
He comes at our clients after what he did,

354
00:15:11,170 --> 00:15:14,140
这次他就不是被解雇  而是进监狱了
This time, he won't get fired, he'll end up in jail.

355
00:15:14,360 --> 00:15:16,720
但来的不会是伍德尔
Except it won't be Woodall who's coming.

356
00:15:16,720 --> 00:15:19,320
-而是他  -对
- It'll be him. - Exactly.

357
00:15:20,070 --> 00:15:22,700
虽然我接下来的任务指派措辞含糊
Listen, I'm gonna be getting a vaguely worded assignment

358
00:15:22,700 --> 00:15:23,900
但任务安排非常明确
with a not-so-vague agenda

359
00:15:23,900 --> 00:15:27,290
尽证监会全力查清你们客户的资产
of getting up your clients' asses with the full power of the S.E.C.

360
00:15:27,290 --> 00:15:28,970
当他们询问原因
And when they ask why--

361
00:15:29,230 --> 00:15:30,770
他们总会询问原因的
And they always ask why--

362
00:15:30,770 --> 00:15:32,060
我很可能会告诉他们
I'm gonna be expected to tell them

363
00:15:32,060 --> 00:15:34,330
因为他们是你们律所的客户
that it's because they're clients of your firm.

364
00:15:34,330 --> 00:15:35,510
你为什么要告诉我们这些
Why are you telling us this?

365
00:15:35,510 --> 00:15:37,510
因为他不想为伍德尔干活
Because he doesn't want to work for Woodall.

366
00:15:37,780 --> 00:15:39,240
他想来这儿
He wants to work here.

367
00:15:40,480 --> 00:15:42,910
我一直听说你能力了得
I've always heard how good you were.

368
00:15:43,850 --> 00:15:45,290
很高兴今天亲自证实了
It's nice to see it's true.

369
00:15:46,910 --> 00:15:48,020
无论如何  事情是这样
Anyway, here's the thing.

370
00:15:48,770 --> 00:15:51,540
我真的当烦了公务员
I'm really tired of being a public servant,

371
00:15:51,540 --> 00:15:52,860
更重要的是
and more importantly,

372
00:15:52,860 --> 00:15:55,590
我一直觉得那个埃里克·伍德尔
I've always thought that Eric Woodall was a...

373
00:15:56,310 --> 00:15:57,750
妈的  我就直说了吧
oh, shit, I'll just go ahead and say it.

374
00:15:57,750 --> 00:15:58,620
他是个混球
He's a dick.

375
00:15:59,110 --> 00:16:00,940
我们总算有一点能达成共识
Finally, something we can agree on.

376
00:16:00,940 --> 00:16:03,020
我觉得我们唯一还没达成共识的  哈维
Seems to me the only thing left for us to agree on, Harvey,

377
00:16:03,020 --> 00:16:04,500
就是我的起薪
is my starting salary.

378
00:16:05,680 --> 00:16:06,670
开玩笑而已
I'm just kidding.

379
00:16:07,030 --> 00:16:09,720
我确信所有新加入的高级合伙人薪酬都一样
I'm sure all your new senior partners get paid the same.

380
00:16:10,120 --> 00:16:12,940
准备规划新办公室的装修计划前
Before you start picking out floor patterns for your new office,

381
00:16:13,260 --> 00:16:15,200
我想和我的合伙人先讨论讨论
I'd like to discuss this with my partner first.

382
00:16:15,200 --> 00:16:16,580
我拭目以待
I'd expect nothing less.

383
00:16:18,050 --> 00:16:20,260
还有一件事
Oh, uh, just one more thing.

384
00:16:20,870 --> 00:16:23,840
我还没正式接到任务  所以没什么冲突
I haven't been formally given this assignment yet, so I have no conflict.

385
00:16:24,030 --> 00:16:25,200
但等一周后任务下达
But in one more week I will,

386
00:16:25,200 --> 00:16:26,640
这边的提议就作废了
which means this offer will be gone.

387
00:16:26,640 --> 00:16:27,640
你在威胁我吗
Is that a threat?

388
00:16:27,640 --> 00:16:30,590
我从不威胁未来的合作伙伴  杰西卡
I would never threaten someone that I want to be in business with, Jessica.

389
00:16:31,070 --> 00:16:31,950
这只是个事实
It's just the truth.

390
00:16:38,110 --> 00:16:38,940
我喜欢他
I like him.

391
00:16:41,850 --> 00:16:44,690
-和哈维聊得怎样  -没聊
- How did it go with Harvey? - It didn't.

392
00:16:47,340 --> 00:16:49,280
"没聊"是什么意思
What do you mean "It didn't"?

393
00:16:50,100 --> 00:16:52,440
只有你能对付杰夫·马龙
You're the only man here who can take on Jeff Malone.

394
00:16:52,440 --> 00:16:54,540
-他怎么可能想不到呢  -我没提
- How could he not see that? - I didn't bring it up.

395
00:16:55,160 --> 00:16:57,580
路易  凛冬将至
Louis, winter is coming.

396
00:16:57,580 --> 00:16:59,420
我知道  我就是守夜人
I know, and I'm the night's watch.

397
00:16:59,420 --> 00:17:01,240
但眼下我们得有耐心
But right now we need to be patient.

398
00:17:02,740 --> 00:17:06,830
-耐心从不是你的强项  -今天是
- Patience is not your strong suit. - Well, today it is.

399
00:17:07,240 --> 00:17:08,750
因为我一直坚守一个信条
Because if there's one thing that I've always known,

400
00:17:08,750 --> 00:17:10,860
绝不主动联系靓妞
it's that you do not call the pretty girl.

401
00:17:10,860 --> 00:17:12,310
等她们联系你
You wait for her to call you.

402
00:17:13,590 --> 00:17:16,320
-路易  我在和别人约会  -替你高兴
- Louis, I'm seeing someone. - I'm happy for you,

403
00:17:16,320 --> 00:17:18,030
虽然不知道你为什么现在说
though I have no idea why you're saying that right now.

404
00:17:18,030 --> 00:17:19,020
卡特里娜  相信我
Katrina, trust me.

405
00:17:19,020 --> 00:17:21,220
他们很快就会发现杰夫·马龙的事
They're gonna find out about Jeff Malone soon enough

406
00:17:21,660 --> 00:17:22,680
因为他会主动找上门
'cause he's gonna come calling.

407
00:17:23,020 --> 00:17:25,470
一旦他来了  他们就会来找我
And when he does, they're gonna come right over to me.

408
00:17:25,470 --> 00:17:27,580
你喜欢他随便你  我不会雇他的
Like him all you want. I'm not hiring him.

409
00:17:27,580 --> 00:17:29,220
-为什么不  -你说为什么
- Why not? - Why do you think?

410
00:17:29,220 --> 00:17:32,250
因为你不喜欢被枪指着做决定
Because you don't like making decisions staring down the barrel of a shotgun.

411
00:17:32,250 --> 00:17:34,010
这就是杰西卡·皮尔森  真是幸会了啊
Jessica pearson. Nice to meet you.

412
00:17:34,320 --> 00:17:37,550
杰西卡  这人主动提议和我们并肩作战
Jessica, the man walked in here and offered to fight for us.

413
00:17:37,550 --> 00:17:39,160
如果不选他  还能选谁
If it's not him, who's it gonna be?

414
00:17:39,160 --> 00:17:41,050
隔壁办公室那货
The guy in the office next door.

415
00:17:42,150 --> 00:17:42,860
路易吗
Louis?

416
00:17:43,510 --> 00:17:46,190
哈维  路易对美国证监会了如指掌
Harvey, Louis knows everything there is to know about the S.E.C.

417
00:17:46,190 --> 00:17:48,180
他厉害得很  你知道的
He's damn good, and you know it.

418
00:17:48,180 --> 00:17:50,190
这人不仅厉害得很  还心狠手辣
This guy isn't damn good. He's a killer.

419
00:17:50,190 --> 00:17:52,270
他是个检察官  我们要找能辩护的
And he's a prosecutor. We need a defender.

420
00:17:52,270 --> 00:17:53,740
如果把我逼到死胡同
If I'm in a dark alley,

421
00:17:53,740 --> 00:17:56,740
我认为心狠手辣比能辩护重要得多
I'd take the killer over the defender seven days a week.

422
00:17:56,740 --> 00:17:58,940
埃里克·伍德尔要把我们逼进死胡同
And Eric Woodall's gonna put us in a dark alley.

423
00:17:58,940 --> 00:18:00,870
路易的实力我们都清楚
Louis is a known quantity.

424
00:18:00,870 --> 00:18:03,100
而现在杰夫·马龙最大的卖点
And right now Jeff Malone's biggest selling point

425
00:18:03,100 --> 00:18:04,810
就是告诉我们伍德尔要对付我们了
is telling us that Woodall is coming.

426
00:18:05,130 --> 00:18:06,450
路易却没说
Louis sure as hell didn't,

427
00:18:06,450 --> 00:18:08,050
他要么什么都不知道
which means he either didn't know

428
00:18:08,050 --> 00:18:09,450
要么没胆量来见你
or he wasn't man enough to come in here

429
00:18:09,450 --> 00:18:11,080
亲自挑起担子
and take the job for himself.

430
00:18:12,190 --> 00:18:14,020
哈维  你知道我为什么不愿意
Harvey, do you know why I don't like

431
00:18:14,020 --> 00:18:16,280
被逼迫做决定吗
being strong-armed into decisions?

432
00:18:16,810 --> 00:18:19,190
因为我无法信任逼迫我的人
Because I'll never be able to trust the person who did it.

433
00:18:19,610 --> 00:18:21,590
那就想办法找个同样优秀的人选
Then figure out a way to get someone as good.

434
00:18:21,590 --> 00:18:24,110
否则就妥协让步  雇佣这家伙
Or hire this guy and come to terms with it.

435
00:18:24,110 --> 00:18:26,750
因为如果路易跟马龙狭路相逢
Because if it's Louis against Malone in a street fight,

436
00:18:26,750 --> 00:18:28,300
我赌马龙赢
I'm picking that dude.

437
00:18:37,070 --> 00:18:38,110
谢谢
Oh, thank you.

438
00:18:39,150 --> 00:18:41,440
你跟神秘的哈维·斯佩克特的会面怎么样
Hey, how'd your meeting go with the mysterious Harvey Specter?

439
00:18:41,440 --> 00:18:43,450
做混蛋是不能提高神秘度的
Being a dick doesn't make him mysterious.

440
00:18:43,450 --> 00:18:45,480
照这么说  你就坦荡得跟白纸一样了
Well, then I guess you're an open book.

441
00:18:45,480 --> 00:18:47,870
我本来想送你蠢朋克乐队的票
You know, I was gonna give you those Daft Punk tickets,

442
00:18:47,870 --> 00:18:49,790
既然你这么说  我要送给艾德娜了
but now after that, I think I'll give them to Edna.

443
00:18:49,790 --> 00:18:52,700
蠢朋克成立的时候  艾德娜都六十三岁了
Okay, first of all, Edna was 63 when Daft Punk was born.

444
00:18:53,110 --> 00:18:54,310
真的  皮肤那么好
Really? With that skin?

445
00:18:54,310 --> 00:18:55,670
知道吗  我费了很大力气才拿到票
You know what, I worked hard to get you those things.

446
00:18:55,670 --> 00:18:56,550
你为什么不去
Why aren't you going?

447
00:18:56,550 --> 00:18:57,820
我跟哈维摊牌了
I dropped the hammer on Harvey,

448
00:18:57,820 --> 00:18:59,930
这意味着瑞秋要熬夜加班了
which means Rachel's gonna be working all night.

449
00:19:00,190 --> 00:19:01,790
你怎么来了
Hey, what are you doing here?

450
00:19:03,070 --> 00:19:04,550
我在哥大上课时接到了唐娜的信息
Donna texted me when I was at Columbia...

451
00:19:05,280 --> 00:19:07,830
告诉我哈维让我放半天假
and told me that Harvey gave me the rest of the day off

452
00:19:07,830 --> 00:19:09,690
因为我工作做得太好了
because I'm kicking ass.

453
00:19:09,910 --> 00:19:11,490
他让你放半天假
He's giving you the rest of the day off?

454
00:19:11,490 --> 00:19:12,520
所以我想
Mm-hmm, so I figured

455
00:19:12,520 --> 00:19:15,050
音乐会之前  咱们可以共进晚餐庆祝一下
we could celebrate over dinner before the concert.

456
00:19:17,150 --> 00:19:19,760
怎么  他从不给你放假  你嫉妒了
What, are you jealous 'cause he never did that for you?

457
00:19:20,130 --> 00:19:21,610
没有  好极了
Um, no. That's great.

458
00:19:21,610 --> 00:19:23,640
你选餐厅  我去找你
You pick a place. I'll meet you there.

459
00:19:23,640 --> 00:19:26,070
我得先安排一下明天的会议
I got to set up some meetings for tomorrow first.

460
00:19:26,070 --> 00:19:27,610
雏鹰餐厅怎么样
What about The Little Owl?

461
00:19:27,610 --> 00:19:28,790
-可以  -好
- Yeah. - Okay.

462
00:19:40,110 --> 00:19:41,170
迈克  你怎么来了
Mike, what are you doing here?

463
00:19:41,950 --> 00:19:44,860
你给我传递了信息  所以我也来表个态
You delivered a message, so now I'm delivering one.

464
00:19:47,970 --> 00:19:50,090
皮尔逊-斯佩克特正式进入审查
Pearson Specter is formally in review.

465
00:19:50,960 --> 00:19:52,230
你说什么
What did you just say to me?

466
00:19:52,930 --> 00:19:55,370
你想接手我的案子  就得自己争取
You want my business, you're gonna have to earn it.

467
00:19:55,370 --> 00:19:57,850
-我已经争取到了  -靠给我的计划捣乱吗
- I have earned it. - By sh---ing on my plan?

468
00:19:57,850 --> 00:19:58,850
你没有什么计划
You don't have a plan.

469
00:19:58,850 --> 00:20:00,010
你这是要撞南墙的
You're running into a wall.

470
00:20:00,010 --> 00:20:01,680
我可不想跟你一起撞南墙
It's not my job to crash into it with you.

471
00:20:01,680 --> 00:20:02,820
撞南墙
Crash into it?

472
00:20:02,820 --> 00:20:04,270
你甚至都没问过我在追查谁
You didn't even ask me who I'm going after.

473
00:20:04,270 --> 00:20:06,000
没这个必要  因为无关紧要
I didn't have to because it doesn't matter.

474
00:20:06,000 --> 00:20:07,980
-你说啊  是谁  -吉利斯工业
- But go ahead. Who is it? - Gillis Industries.

475
00:20:07,980 --> 00:20:10,200
那可不是大鱼  那是怪兽
That's not a whale. That's a monster.

476
00:20:10,200 --> 00:20:11,960
沃尔特·吉利斯那样的人
A man like Walter Gillis

477
00:20:11,960 --> 00:20:13,560
才不会听你的这样
isn't gonna listen to a guy like you

478
00:20:13,560 --> 00:20:16,370
要用阳光彩虹来挽救他的人的话
offering to save him with sunshine and rainbows.

479
00:20:16,370 --> 00:20:17,660
我说服他把配送中心卖给我之前
That's exactly what you said to me

480
00:20:17,660 --> 00:20:19,800
你也说过同样的话
before I got him to sell me his distribution centers.

481
00:20:19,800 --> 00:20:21,740
恭喜你  他允许你帮他遛狗了
Congratulations. You got to walk his dog.

482
00:20:21,740 --> 00:20:23,700
但那不意味着你能娶他的女儿
That doesn't mean he's gonna let you marry his daughter.

483
00:20:23,700 --> 00:20:26,620
听着  你想做我的伙伴
Listen to me. You want to be my guy?

484
00:20:26,620 --> 00:20:28,350
就别再告诉我  为什么我不能做什么事
You stop telling me why I can't do this,

485
00:20:28,350 --> 00:20:30,080
而要帮我想做成的办法
and you start figuring out how I can.

486
00:20:30,080 --> 00:20:31,470
我已经告诉你怎么做了
I already told you how you can.

487
00:20:31,470 --> 00:20:33,880
你弄到钱  开始买入股份
You get some money, start buying some shares,

488
00:20:33,880 --> 00:20:35,260
带着筹码入场
and you walk in there with a club

489
00:20:35,260 --> 00:20:37,100
该出手就出手
and the balls to use it if you have to.

490
00:20:37,100 --> 00:20:38,900
哈维  我告诉你我的计划要实施
Harvey, when I told you my plan's happening

491
00:20:38,900 --> 00:20:40,480
那不管你喜欢与否  它都要实施
whether you like it or not, I meant it.

492
00:20:40,480 --> 00:20:42,090
我明天要面试几家律所
I'm interviewing law firms tomorrow.

493
00:20:42,090 --> 00:20:44,280
你最好态度手段放软点
You show up with a better attitude and another move,

494
00:20:44,280 --> 00:20:45,780
否则就失去我这个客户了
or you just lost a client.

495
00:20:52,210 --> 00:20:53,520
想聊聊吗
So you wanna talk about it?

496
00:20:55,180 --> 00:20:56,270
聊什么
Talk about what?

497
00:20:56,830 --> 00:20:59,870
聊你和哈维之间到底怎么回事
About whatever's going on with you and Harvey.

498
00:21:02,700 --> 00:21:05,130
为什么大家都拿我当小孩呢
Why does everybody think that I was born yesterday?

499
00:21:05,540 --> 00:21:07,430
我就说了他放我半天假
I tell you that he gives me the rest of the day off work,

500
00:21:07,430 --> 00:21:08,770
你就消失到晚餐时
you vanish until dinner,

501
00:21:08,770 --> 00:21:10,190
而且一整晚都在怄气
and then you're pissed off for the rest of the night,

502
00:21:10,190 --> 00:21:12,540
不用高手都看出你们之间有不愉快
so it doesn't take a rocket scientist.

503
00:21:12,540 --> 00:21:13,530
可不是吗
Clearly.

504
00:21:15,180 --> 00:21:16,900
我是说  我爱你
I meant "I love you."

505
00:21:17,360 --> 00:21:18,760
挽回得不错
Mm-hmm, nice recovery.

506
00:21:18,760 --> 00:21:20,470
但你还没回答我的问题
Doesn't get you out of answering my question.

507
00:21:20,470 --> 00:21:21,430
你真想知道吗
You really want to know?

508
00:21:21,930 --> 00:21:22,560
那我告诉你
I'll tell you.

509
00:21:23,200 --> 00:21:25,000
哈维是迈克尔·乔丹
Harvey was Michael Jordan.

510
00:21:26,130 --> 00:21:27,430
现在是勒布朗的时代了
Now it's Lebron's time,

511
00:21:27,440 --> 00:21:28,740
但他不能接受这点
and he can't take it.

512
00:21:29,950 --> 00:21:31,930
这指责可挺严重的
That's a pretty big accusation to make.

513
00:21:31,930 --> 00:21:33,850
你不了解事情的全部经过
Well, there's more to the story than you know.

514
00:21:33,850 --> 00:21:36,210
-怎么了  -算了吧
- What? - Right, so come on.

515
00:21:36,210 --> 00:21:38,070
我说过我不想破坏你们的关系
I said I didn't want to get between you two.

516
00:21:38,910 --> 00:21:39,680
怎么了
What?

517
00:21:42,860 --> 00:21:45,400
这么说吧  你的出色表现
Let's just say that you kicking ass for him

518
00:21:45,400 --> 00:21:47,630
并不是你得到休假的原因
isn't the reason you got the day off.

519
00:21:54,160 --> 00:21:55,390
我以为你今天要去法学院上课呢
I thought you had law school today.

520
00:21:55,390 --> 00:21:56,690
解决完这件事之后去
I do right after this.

521
00:21:58,890 --> 00:21:59,730
他告诉你了
He told you.

522
00:22:00,450 --> 00:22:01,400
你觉得他不会吗
Did you think he wouldn't?

523
00:22:02,490 --> 00:22:04,160
如果你想传信息给迈克
Look, if you want to send a message to mike,

524
00:22:04,160 --> 00:22:04,970
尽管传
go right ahead.

525
00:22:04,970 --> 00:22:06,540
如果你希望我给他传递信息
If you want me to send a message to mike,

526
00:22:06,540 --> 00:22:08,090
告诉我时间地点就好  但是
tell me when and where, but...

527
00:22:09,200 --> 00:22:11,580
请不要再这样利用我
Please don't ever use me like that again.

528
00:22:12,730 --> 00:22:13,580
你说得对
You're right.

529
00:22:15,740 --> 00:22:16,580
我什么
I'm what now?

530
00:22:18,100 --> 00:22:20,050
我不应该那样做  对不起
I shouldn't have done that. I'm sorry.

531
00:22:20,050 --> 00:22:21,780
今天是愚人节吗
Is it April Fools' Day?

532
00:22:21,780 --> 00:22:23,300
不  但以后不要再说
No, but don't ever let it be said

533
00:22:23,300 --> 00:22:24,450
我不懂承认错误了
that I can't admit when I'm wrong.

534
00:22:24,450 --> 00:22:25,830
我不会再说了
Then I will stop saying that.

535
00:22:26,310 --> 00:22:27,200
你今天不是有课吗
Didn't you say you have class today?

536
00:22:27,200 --> 00:22:27,840
我这就走
I'm on my way.

537
00:22:30,550 --> 00:22:31,470
那是怎么一回事
What was that all about?

538
00:22:31,470 --> 00:22:33,120
就是些行政事务
Just some administrative stuff.

539
00:22:33,120 --> 00:22:35,700
行政事务  你和瑞秋
Administrative stuff. You and rachel.

540
00:22:36,230 --> 00:22:37,070
我不想谈论这件事
I don't want to talk about it.

541
00:22:37,070 --> 00:22:39,000
你是指我说的话都应验了
You mean how I said would happen happened

542
00:22:39,000 --> 00:22:40,900
现在你意识到我是对的了吗
and now you realize I was right the whole time?

543
00:22:40,900 --> 00:22:42,330
没人喜欢幸灾乐祸的人  唐娜
No one likes a gloater, Donna.

544
00:22:42,330 --> 00:22:42,940
那我估计
Well, then I guess

545
00:22:42,940 --> 00:22:44,550
哈维·斯佩克特的幸灾乐祸大学
the Harvey Specter university of gloating

546
00:22:44,550 --> 00:22:46,020
要关门大吉了
is gonna have to shut down.

547
00:22:46,020 --> 00:22:48,310
我周末还可以做演讲
I can still give lectures on the weekend.

548
00:22:49,990 --> 00:22:50,920
你要听我说出来吗
You want to hear it?

549
00:22:52,130 --> 00:22:53,170
你是对的
You were right.

550
00:22:54,730 --> 00:22:55,590
给雷打电话
Call Ray.

551
00:22:56,000 --> 00:22:57,940
我要让迈克知道我是他的律师
I'm gonna go let Mike know I'm his lawyer.

552
00:22:58,310 --> 00:23:00,540
你要推迟我们的见面吗
You're gonna push a meeting with me?

553
00:23:01,740 --> 00:23:04,870
哈维  洛根·桑德斯来找你了
Harvey, Logan Sanders is here to see you.

554
00:23:05,370 --> 00:23:07,120
首先  我不喜欢
First of all, I don't appreciate

555
00:23:07,120 --> 00:23:09,310
你带着这种态度冲到我办公室
You stomping into my office with an attitude.

556
00:23:09,310 --> 00:23:10,790
是吗  我还不喜欢被人怠慢呢
Yeah, well, I don't appreciate being put off,

557
00:23:10,790 --> 00:23:12,630
特别是在我知道你从未推延过
especially when I know that you never pushed a meeting

558
00:23:12,630 --> 00:23:13,500
和我父亲的会面后
with my father.

559
00:23:13,500 --> 00:23:16,220
你父亲从不找杰西卡安排跟我会面
Your father never went to Jessica to set a meeting with me.

560
00:23:16,220 --> 00:23:19,010
那下次我直接打给你的时候
Then I assume that next time I call you directly,

561
00:23:19,290 --> 00:23:20,430
你会接我电话咯
you'll pick up the phone.

562
00:23:20,430 --> 00:23:24,580
洛根  我来告诉你关于我的一些基本常识
Logan, let me give the ABCs of me.

563
00:23:25,020 --> 00:23:27,340
我不接受会面  我安排会面
I don't take meetings. I set them.

564
00:23:27,340 --> 00:23:30,120
我的尊重不是要求来的  是争取来的
And my respect isn't demanded. It's earned.

565
00:23:30,780 --> 00:23:32,700
这才两点  第三点呢
That's only two things. What's "C"?

566
00:23:32,700 --> 00:23:35,230
第三点是留给证明了自己知道前两点的人的
"C" is for people who show me they know "A" and "B."

567
00:23:35,960 --> 00:23:38,130
既然我们在引用《甜心先生》的台词
Well, since we're quoting Jerry Maguire,

568
00:23:38,130 --> 00:23:39,950
我只希望你能让我看到钞票
all I want is for you to show me the money.

569
00:23:40,660 --> 00:23:43,410
你刚才迈出了赢得我尊重的第一步
You just took step number one towards earning my respect.

570
00:23:43,410 --> 00:23:45,530
-我喜欢你这一点  -很好
- And I dig that about you. - Great.

571
00:23:45,880 --> 00:23:48,220
我们现在能讨论正事了吗
Would it be too much trouble for me to discuss my business now?

572
00:23:49,300 --> 00:23:50,950
我本来还想聊《赤色风暴》的
Well, I was gonna move on to Crimson Tide,

573
00:23:50,950 --> 00:23:52,070
但谈公事也行
But, yeah, go ahead.

574
00:23:52,070 --> 00:23:52,990
说吧
Knock yourself out.

575
00:23:53,750 --> 00:23:55,890
你听说过温沃德家族吗
You ever hear of a family called the Winwards?

576
00:23:55,890 --> 00:23:57,760
没有  我应该知道吗
No. Should I?

577
00:23:58,260 --> 00:24:01,410
1950年  他们市值几十亿美元
In 1950, they were worth the equivalent of a billion dollars.

578
00:24:01,410 --> 00:24:04,790
到1988年  他家有个人只有几家干洗店了
By 1988, one of them owned a couple of dry cleaners.

579
00:24:04,790 --> 00:24:06,430
之所以会这样  不是因为他们挥霍无度
And it didn't happen because they squandered it.

580
00:24:06,430 --> 00:24:08,690
而是因为他们像恐龙一样过时了
It happened because they stayed a dinosaur.

581
00:24:08,690 --> 00:24:10,170
你不想成为恐龙
You don't want to become a dinosaur.

582
00:24:10,170 --> 00:24:11,410
是的
No.

583
00:24:11,410 --> 00:24:14,690
我倾向于认为我是鲨鱼
I like to think of myself as a shark.

584
00:24:14,690 --> 00:24:16,540
要么前进要么死亡
Keep moving forward or die.

585
00:24:16,540 --> 00:24:18,420
你想进行恶意收购
You're talking hostile takeover.

586
00:24:18,420 --> 00:24:20,250
不然你以为我为什么会在这儿
You think I'd be here if I wasn't?

587
00:24:20,250 --> 00:24:22,910
你刚刚迈出了赢得我尊重的第二步
You just took step number two towards earning my respect.

588
00:24:22,910 --> 00:24:24,080
哪家公司
What's the company?

589
00:24:24,080 --> 00:24:27,370
吉利斯工业  我已经有4.9%的股份了
Gillis Industries, and I already own 4.9%.

590
00:24:27,370 --> 00:24:29,780
洛根  我们必须结束这次谈话了
Logan, we have to end this conversation right now.

591
00:24:29,780 --> 00:24:30,430
什么意思
What are you talking about?

592
00:24:30,430 --> 00:24:31,820
我以为我刚赢得了你的尊重呢
I thought I just earned your respect.

593
00:24:31,820 --> 00:24:33,340
的确  但我们有冲突
You did, but we have a conflict.

594
00:24:33,340 --> 00:24:34,710
什么意思
What do you mean, you have a conflict?

595
00:24:34,710 --> 00:24:36,140
我们有利益冲突
I mean we have a conflict.

596
00:24:36,140 --> 00:24:38,940
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do about it?

597
00:24:38,940 --> 00:24:40,440
我现在就去解决
I'm gonna go and resolve it.

598
00:24:40,440 --> 00:24:43,410
那你最好快点  因为我这事我做定了
Well, you better do it fast, because I am in on this.

599
00:24:43,410 --> 00:24:45,670
你我要么为敌  要么为友
and that means you're either with me or against me.

600
00:24:45,670 --> 00:24:48,570
这还算上我十亿美元的生意
That includes all $1 billion of my business.

601
00:24:59,590 --> 00:25:00,750
要李子泥吗
Hey. Prunie?

602
00:25:01,990 --> 00:25:03,940
-那是什么  -李子奶昔
- What is that? - It's a prune smoothie.

603
00:25:03,940 --> 00:25:05,370
我自己发明的
I invented it myself.

604
00:25:05,370 --> 00:25:06,380
下次吧
Rain check.

605
00:25:08,190 --> 00:25:10,890
路易  猜猜昨天谁
Louis, guess who stopped by yesterday

606
00:25:10,890 --> 00:25:13,350
突然来见杰西卡和哈维了
for an impromptu meeting with Jessica and Harvey.

607
00:25:13,350 --> 00:25:15,040
是不是迪克·切尼[布什的副总统]
Please tell me it was Dick Cheney.

608
00:25:15,040 --> 00:25:16,840
你为什么盼着迪克·切尼来
Why would you want it to be Dick Cheney?

609
00:25:16,840 --> 00:25:18,610
为啥不盼着他来
Why wouldn't I want it to be Iron Dick?

610
00:25:18,950 --> 00:25:20,600
老天  我知道你说的是谁了
Holy sh--, I think I know who you were talking about.

611
00:25:20,600 --> 00:25:21,720
我想也是
I think you do too.

612
00:25:22,620 --> 00:25:23,960
是不是某个证监会的混蛋
Is it a certain S.E.C. beast

613
00:25:23,960 --> 00:25:26,710
名字正好跟史密夫·史马龙押韵
whose name happens to rhyme with Schmeff Schmalone?

614
00:25:26,710 --> 00:25:29,180
是史密斯  也的确押韵
Schmess it is, and Schmess it does.

615
00:25:29,180 --> 00:25:30,500
我真蠢
Well, schmuck me.

616
00:25:30,500 --> 00:25:32,260
路易  我们有麻烦了
Louis, we have a problem.

617
00:25:32,890 --> 00:25:34,560
什么麻烦  好像我不知道一样
What's the problem? As if I didn't know.

618
00:25:37,980 --> 00:25:40,820
我刚见了洛根·桑德斯
I just got out of a meeting with Logan Sanders.

619
00:25:41,930 --> 00:25:43,080
洛根·桑德斯
Logan Sanders?

620
00:25:43,980 --> 00:25:46,100
-你不是要和我说...  -说什么
- This isn't about... - About what?

621
00:25:46,950 --> 00:25:48,410
那个...  没什么
The--n-never mind.

622
00:25:48,410 --> 00:25:49,240
怎么了
What's the problem?

623
00:25:49,240 --> 00:25:50,620
迈克先前跟我谈到的公司
He wants to go after the same company

624
00:25:50,620 --> 00:25:52,080
他也想收购
that Mike pitched me first.

625
00:25:52,080 --> 00:25:53,880
这有什么问题  迈克先跟你说的
So what's the problem? Mike brought it to you first.

626
00:25:53,880 --> 00:25:54,950
你有义务坚持帮他
You're obligated to stick with him.

627
00:25:54,950 --> 00:25:58,410
问题是迈克正式把我们列为待审律所了
The problem is Mike formally put us in review.

628
00:25:58,410 --> 00:26:00,870
老天  所以你才来找我
Holy sh--. That's why you're coming to me.

629
00:26:01,080 --> 00:26:02,200
你要失去迈克了
You're gonna lose Mike,

630
00:26:02,200 --> 00:26:04,170
你想知道怎么才能不丢这个客户
And you want to know if there's any way around it?

631
00:26:04,170 --> 00:26:06,060
-有办法吗  -没有  哈维
- Is there? - No, Harvey.

632
00:26:06,480 --> 00:26:08,870
抱歉  但你不能代表迈克了
I'm sorry, but you're gonna have to drop Mike.

633
00:26:21,900 --> 00:26:23,500
-哈维怎么了  -没什么
- What happened with harvey? - Nothing.

634
00:26:23,500 --> 00:26:25,040
他跟迈克有点情况
He had an emergency with Mike.

635
00:26:26,270 --> 00:26:29,980
好吧  但你不觉得现在该站出来了吗
Fine, but don't you think now is the time to act for yourself?

636
00:26:29,980 --> 00:26:32,270
不  原计划很好  就照那个来
No, we have a good plan, and we're sticking to it.

637
00:26:32,270 --> 00:26:34,330
他们在为马龙的事发愁  他们愁得越久
They're stewing on Malone, and the more they stew--

638
00:26:34,330 --> 00:26:36,190
我们筹码越多
the more leverage we have.

639
00:26:36,920 --> 00:26:38,130
冠名合伙人
Name partner.

640
00:26:38,730 --> 00:26:41,060
就像我说的  得有耐心
And as I've said, all we need to do is be patient.

641
00:26:42,030 --> 00:26:45,130
也许你能静下心等
Well, patience may be one of your virtues,

642
00:26:45,980 --> 00:26:47,590
但我不行
but it is not one of mine.

643
00:26:51,380 --> 00:26:53,550
{\an8}皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特
路易·利特
高级合伙人

644
00:26:54,020 --> 00:26:54,840
我不想给你带来厄运
I didn't want to jinx it.

645
00:26:54,840 --> 00:26:55,680
没有
You didn't.

646
00:27:04,910 --> 00:27:07,050
卡特里娜  这是别人为我做的
Katrina, this is one of the sweetest things

647
00:27:07,050 --> 00:27:08,360
最贴心的事之一了
anyone's ever done for me.

648
00:27:08,780 --> 00:27:11,590
我希望你别浪费了实现这一切的机会
I want to make sure you don't waste your opportunity to get this.

649
00:27:13,420 --> 00:27:14,380
我保证不会的
I promise I won't.

650
00:27:25,780 --> 00:27:27,320
你来干什么
What are you doing here?

651
00:27:27,320 --> 00:27:28,610
不该让别人看到我们在一起
We shouldn't be seen together.

652
00:27:28,610 --> 00:27:30,640
你能大摇大摆地走进我办公的地方
You had no problem walking into my place of business.

653
00:27:30,640 --> 00:27:32,460
为什么我不能来你的办公室
Why should I have a problem walking into yours?

654
00:27:32,460 --> 00:27:34,780
除非你来这儿是要通知我被录用了
Because unless you're here to tell me that I have the job,

655
00:27:34,780 --> 00:27:37,140
否则你会让我现在的饭碗不保
then you're putting my position here in jeopardy.

656
00:27:37,440 --> 00:27:38,230
那你觉得我发现
How do you think I felt

657
00:27:38,230 --> 00:27:40,150
跟我上床的男的跑来我的会议室
when I found the man that I'm sleeping with

658
00:27:40,150 --> 00:27:41,790
是什么感觉
standing in my conference room?

659
00:27:42,820 --> 00:27:44,390
杰西卡  你能小点声吗
Jessica, will you please lower your voice?

660
00:27:44,390 --> 00:27:45,380
不仅如此
Not only that, but you stood there

661
00:27:45,380 --> 00:27:46,750
你还站那儿一脸坏笑
with a sh---eating grin on your face

662
00:27:46,750 --> 00:27:49,280
想要逼迫我雇佣你
and tried to strong-arm me into giving you a job.

663
00:27:49,700 --> 00:27:51,630
你现在是不是跟我一样有兴致了
Are you as turned on as I am right now?

664
00:27:52,510 --> 00:27:53,540
一点都不好笑
You're not funny.

665
00:27:55,030 --> 00:27:56,890
你怎么不先找我商量
Why didn't you come to me first with this?

666
00:27:56,890 --> 00:27:59,150
要是我先找你商量
Because if I had come to you with this first,

667
00:27:59,150 --> 00:28:01,460
你一定以为我是要利用我们的关系
you would have thought I was trading on our relationship.

668
00:28:01,460 --> 00:28:02,760
-你不是吗  -不是
- Aren't you? - No.

669
00:28:03,390 --> 00:28:04,370
如果我们没在一起
And if we weren't together,

670
00:28:04,370 --> 00:28:05,870
我肯定会直接找你们两位
I would have gone to both of you, all right?

671
00:28:05,870 --> 00:28:07,430
所以我就直接去找你们两个了
So I went to both of you.

672
00:28:07,430 --> 00:28:09,350
事情也许的确办得差强人意
Now it may not have been perfect, but...

673
00:28:10,030 --> 00:28:11,900
但也没什么万无一失的办法
there was no perfect way of doing it,

674
00:28:11,900 --> 00:28:13,160
除非我不去做
unless I hadn't done it.

675
00:28:13,160 --> 00:28:14,520
我觉得这个办法挺完美的
Now that sounds pretty perfect to me.

676
00:28:14,520 --> 00:28:15,610
你到底在怕什么
What are you so afraid of?

677
00:28:15,610 --> 00:28:17,220
还要我画幅画跟你解释吗
Do I have to draw you a picture?

678
00:28:17,400 --> 00:28:18,580
有句老话说得好
I'm not the one that made up the saying

679
00:28:18,580 --> 00:28:19,700
"吃饭的地方别拉屎"[工作的地方别恋爱]
"You don't shit where you eat."

680
00:28:19,700 --> 00:28:22,550
我在你的画里是屎还是饭
Am I the shit or the food in this little painting of yours?

681
00:28:22,550 --> 00:28:23,810
因为如果我们只是一时之欢
Because if we're just a fling,

682
00:28:23,810 --> 00:28:24,810
我是否与你共事
then what difference does it make

683
00:28:24,810 --> 00:28:26,540
又有什么关系呢
whether I work with you or not?

684
00:28:26,950 --> 00:28:28,530
我没说我们是一时之欢
I didn't say we're just a fling.

685
00:28:28,530 --> 00:28:30,830
那如果我们之间有机会
Then if there really is a chance for us,

686
00:28:30,830 --> 00:28:31,810
为什么不两者兼得呢
then why not go for both?

687
00:28:31,810 --> 00:28:34,720
因为我曾见过当合伙人关系破裂
Because I've seen what happens when things go south

688
00:28:34,730 --> 00:28:36,070
会发生什么事
between partners,

689
00:28:36,340 --> 00:28:38,510
而我不愿将我的事业置于险境
and I'm not willing to put my business in jeopardy.

690
00:28:38,510 --> 00:28:39,480
你的事业
Your business.

691
00:28:39,480 --> 00:28:42,200
对  我的事业
Yes, my business.

692
00:28:42,480 --> 00:28:45,430
我曾不屈不饶守护下来的事业
The one that I have fought tooth and nail to keep together,

693
00:28:45,430 --> 00:28:49,050
你却拿把猎枪溜达进来
the same business that you strolled into with a shotgun

694
00:28:49,300 --> 00:28:52,010
说  嫁给我  不然我就开始扫射
and said, "Marry me, or I'll start shooting."

695
00:28:54,020 --> 00:28:55,590
杰丝  如果你希望我
Jess, if you want me to apologize

696
00:28:55,590 --> 00:28:57,710
为我要求的方式道歉  那我道歉
for the way that I asked, then I will.

697
00:28:57,830 --> 00:29:00,410
但我只会要求我想要的东西
But I don't ask for things that I don't want.

698
00:29:00,410 --> 00:29:02,790
而我想要的就是在皮尔逊-斯佩克特工作
And what I want is to work at Pearson Specter

699
00:29:02,790 --> 00:29:04,020
而且和你在一起
and to keep seeing you.

700
00:29:05,300 --> 00:29:07,610
这两者不能兼得
Those two things are not both gonna happen.

701
00:29:10,310 --> 00:29:11,380
那么我想你必须决定
Then I guess you have to decide

702
00:29:11,380 --> 00:29:12,880
什么对你更重要了
what's more important to you--

703
00:29:14,110 --> 00:29:17,450
是我们的感情  还是你的事业
what we have or what you have.

704
00:29:24,640 --> 00:29:25,350
迈克
Hey, Mike.

705
00:29:25,350 --> 00:29:26,760
还有一个人想见你
There's another prospect here to see you,

706
00:29:26,770 --> 00:29:28,490
但他迟到了  而且领带太粗了
but he's late, and his tie's too fat.

707
00:29:28,490 --> 00:29:29,310
我要让他进来吗
Should I let him in?

708
00:29:29,310 --> 00:29:30,910
你教她说这些废话的吗
You tell her to say all that garbage?

709
00:29:30,910 --> 00:29:32,520
不必他教  粗领带男
He didn't need to, Johnnie Fat Tie.

710
00:29:32,520 --> 00:29:34,610
我想我还有时间见最后一个人
Yeah, I guess I have time for one more meeting.

711
00:29:34,610 --> 00:29:36,230
-迈克  我们得谈谈  -不过抱歉  先生
- Mike, I need to talk to you. - Although, I'm sorry, sir.

712
00:29:36,230 --> 00:29:38,140
你错过甜点了  我可以帮你叫点
You've missed the pastries. I can call you some up.

713
00:29:38,140 --> 00:29:39,420
听我说
Listen to me.

714
00:29:39,990 --> 00:29:41,940
我来这里是因为我本想告诉你
I came down here because I wanted to tell you

715
00:29:41,940 --> 00:29:43,630
如果你想赢得这场战斗
if you want to run through this wall,

716
00:29:43,630 --> 00:29:45,220
我准备好和你并肩作战了
I'm ready to run through it with you.

717
00:29:45,220 --> 00:29:45,940
很好
Good.

718
00:29:45,950 --> 00:29:47,020
但我不能
But I can't.

719
00:29:48,860 --> 00:29:49,390
什么
What?

720
00:29:49,390 --> 00:29:50,550
我只能告诉你
What I can do is tell you

721
00:29:50,550 --> 00:29:52,360
我准备好和你一起赢得另一场战斗了
I'm ready to run through another one.

722
00:29:52,360 --> 00:29:53,410
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?

723
00:29:53,410 --> 00:29:55,440
-我们有利益冲突  -扯淡
- We have a conflict. - Bullshit.

724
00:29:56,110 --> 00:29:57,950
-是谁  -这不是扯淡
- Who is it? - It's not bullshit.

725
00:29:57,950 --> 00:29:58,650
那到底是谁
Then who is it?

726
00:29:58,650 --> 00:29:59,610
你知道我不能说
You know I can't tell you that.

727
00:29:59,610 --> 00:30:01,460
不  我只知道昨天你才说
No, what I know is that it's very convenient

728
00:30:01,470 --> 00:30:02,710
我的主意不够好
that you suddenly have a conflict

729
00:30:02,710 --> 00:30:05,240
现在就突然有了利益冲突  真够巧的
the day after you tell me that my idea isn't good enough.

730
00:30:05,250 --> 00:30:06,630
我不觉得有什么巧
I don't find it convenient at all,

731
00:30:06,630 --> 00:30:07,760
但你把我们列入审查
but you put us in review,

732
00:30:07,760 --> 00:30:09,110
所以我现在必须和别的客户合作了
and now I have to go with the other client.

733
00:30:09,110 --> 00:30:11,700
我把你们列入审查是因为你拒绝入伙
I put you in review because you refused to get on board.

734
00:30:11,700 --> 00:30:12,570
而我刚刚和你说了
And I just told you,

735
00:30:12,570 --> 00:30:14,340
我想与你一起赢得另一场战斗
I want to run through another wall with you,

736
00:30:14,340 --> 00:30:16,680
如果你放弃  我们还可以合作
and we still can if you drop this.

737
00:30:18,070 --> 00:30:19,790
为什么我要是让步的那一个
And why should I be the one to drop it?

738
00:30:19,820 --> 00:30:22,540
因为他们不会让步  而我必须与他们共进退
Because they're not going to, and I have to stick with them.

739
00:30:22,540 --> 00:30:24,150
而且我告诉你  你不会赢
And I'm telling you, you're gonna lose.

740
00:30:24,150 --> 00:30:25,200
为什么  就因为你站在那边了吗
What, because you're on the other side?

741
00:30:25,200 --> 00:30:26,570
因为他们的方案更好
Because their plan is better.

742
00:30:26,570 --> 00:30:27,680
狗嘴里吐不出象牙
Says the professional bullshitter

743
00:30:27,690 --> 00:30:30,890
你满嘴屁话就是想说服我退出
who has a brand-new vested interest in me bowing out.

744
00:30:31,280 --> 00:30:32,560
我就当我刚才什么都没听到
I'm gonna let that go.

745
00:30:32,560 --> 00:30:33,830
而如果你不放弃
But if you don't let this go,

746
00:30:33,830 --> 00:30:36,680
事情结束之前我不能当你们的律师
I can't represent you on anything until it's over.

747
00:30:39,270 --> 00:30:40,600
那我们不用再说了
Then I guess we're done here.

748
00:31:00,400 --> 00:31:01,370
你会做饭
You cook?

749
00:31:02,570 --> 00:31:04,430
你回家在厨房见到这些
You come home to this in your kitchen,

750
00:31:04,430 --> 00:31:06,220
就只问这个吗
and that's what you're going to ask me?

751
00:31:06,780 --> 00:31:07,780
好吧  我本想问你
Well, I was gonna ask you

752
00:31:07,780 --> 00:31:09,050
你怎么进到我公寓的
how the hell you got into my apartment,

753
00:31:09,050 --> 00:31:10,750
但我知道你不会告诉我
but I knew you weren't gonna tell me.

754
00:31:11,810 --> 00:31:13,360
你记得你说过
Do you remember when you told me

755
00:31:13,360 --> 00:31:16,150
我也应该考虑找人开开晨会吗
I should think about taking some morning meetings?

756
00:31:19,340 --> 00:31:21,700
我承认我曾经想过这事
I can't say that it's never crossed my mind,

757
00:31:21,700 --> 00:31:23,030
但你真觉得这是个好主意...
but you really think it's a good idea--

758
00:31:23,040 --> 00:31:24,330
杰夫·马龙
Jeff Malone.

759
00:31:24,920 --> 00:31:26,230
他不是我的菜
Well, he's not my type.

760
00:31:27,540 --> 00:31:28,260
你不是开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.

761
00:31:28,260 --> 00:31:29,430
你昨天怎么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?

762
00:31:29,430 --> 00:31:31,110
因为我昨天还不打算雇他
Because I wasn't gonna hire him yesterday,

763
00:31:31,110 --> 00:31:32,740
所以不关你的事
so it was none of your business.

764
00:31:33,220 --> 00:31:35,970
可今天我可能会  所以得告诉你
But today I might, so now it is.

765
00:31:35,970 --> 00:31:38,470
你想知道我的想法
And you want to know how I feel about it.

766
00:31:38,470 --> 00:31:39,690
你是我的合伙人嘛
You're my partner.

767
00:31:39,710 --> 00:31:41,730
我已经告诉过你我的想法了
Well, I already told you how I feel about hiring him.

768
00:31:41,730 --> 00:31:43,060
你和他的关系不会改变我的想法
This doesn't change that.

769
00:31:43,310 --> 00:31:44,240
那就好
Good to know.

770
00:31:46,580 --> 00:31:48,880
看来你还有别的顾虑
Seems like something else is on your mind.

771
00:31:50,630 --> 00:31:52,680
他不只想一起工作
He doesn't just want to work together.

772
00:31:53,640 --> 00:31:55,560
还想继续和我交往
He wants us to keep seeing each other.

773
00:31:55,590 --> 00:31:57,570
而你不想冒失去的危险得到
And you don't want to risk the one to have the other.

774
00:31:57,570 --> 00:31:59,540
对  我不想
No. I don't.

775
00:32:00,400 --> 00:32:01,560
这事我有经验
I've been there.

776
00:32:02,310 --> 00:32:03,360
我知道
I know.

777
00:32:04,010 --> 00:32:06,910
那你就得想清楚哪个更重要
Then you need to figure out which is more important.

778
00:32:08,920 --> 00:32:10,100
我觉得我心里有数
I guess I do.

779
00:32:14,960 --> 00:32:16,890
这么说你们俩已经...
So you two have, um...

780
00:32:18,350 --> 00:32:19,680
对
Yes.

781
00:32:21,210 --> 00:32:23,360
他看过你没穿衣服的样子
So he's seen you naked?

782
00:32:23,550 --> 00:32:25,760
这是必须的
That's usually how these things work.

783
00:32:30,370 --> 00:32:32,420
你在想像我没穿衣服的样子吗
Are you picturing me naked right now?

784
00:32:35,000 --> 00:32:35,900
或许吧
Maybe.

785
00:32:37,820 --> 00:32:38,690
是的
Yes.

786
00:32:39,210 --> 00:32:40,480
去洗手
Go wash your hands.

787
00:32:45,370 --> 00:32:47,740
别在卫生间待太久
Don't spend too much time in that bathroom.

788
00:32:48,690 --> 00:32:49,660
让我把这事理一理
Let me get this straight.

789
00:32:49,670 --> 00:32:51,260
你带着杀手锏来找我
You come to me with a killer idea,

790
00:32:51,260 --> 00:32:52,870
但突然间又不想干了
and all of a sudden you don't want to do it anymore

791
00:32:52,870 --> 00:32:54,260
而原因只是失去了好基友吗
'cause you lost your bff?

792
00:32:54,260 --> 00:32:57,050
我不想这么做是因为那不再是杀手锏了
I don't want to do it because it's not a killer idea anymore.

793
00:32:57,050 --> 00:32:59,300
-为什么  -因为哈维有利益冲突
- Why the hell not? - Because Harvey has a conflict,

794
00:32:59,310 --> 00:33:01,280
说明有其他人加入了战局
which means somebody already has a dog in the fight.

795
00:33:01,280 --> 00:33:02,750
-谁在乎啊  -我在乎
- Who gives a shit? - I do.

796
00:33:02,750 --> 00:33:04,930
因为不管那人是谁都已经开始收购股票了
'Cause whoever it is is already buying shares.

797
00:33:05,790 --> 00:33:07,570
你来这儿不是要投降
You didn't come in here to give up.

798
00:33:07,570 --> 00:33:08,640
你来是找我要钱的
You came in here to get my money.

799
00:33:08,650 --> 00:33:09,580
你说得没错
You're damn right I did.

800
00:33:09,580 --> 00:33:11,700
我给了你钱  就处于弱势了
I give you my money, now I have downside.

801
00:33:11,700 --> 00:33:13,030
乔纳森  听着
Jonathan, look.

802
00:33:13,700 --> 00:33:15,340
你说你想要个全垒打
You said you wanted a home run.

803
00:33:15,960 --> 00:33:17,120
那就得拿出你的支票簿
You gotta pull out your checkbook,

804
00:33:17,120 --> 00:33:18,430
否则我无法大获全胜
'cause I can't compete without it.

805
00:33:18,430 --> 00:33:20,410
-你昨天还可以啊  -今天形势不同了
- You could yesterday. - Now it's today.

806
00:33:20,410 --> 00:33:21,720
你还是要去那儿
And you're still going in there

807
00:33:21,720 --> 00:33:22,790
打扮成西装革履的银行家
another banker in a suit,

808
00:33:22,790 --> 00:33:24,750
期盼他能平白无故地信任你
hoping he'll trust you based on nothing.

809
00:33:25,920 --> 00:33:27,350
不会是平白无故的
I've got more than nothing.

810
00:33:29,660 --> 00:33:30,940
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?

811
00:33:31,950 --> 00:33:32,910
相信我
Trust me.

812
00:33:33,790 --> 00:33:35,040
我做足了功课
I did my homework.

813
00:33:36,990 --> 00:33:38,000
那就开球吧
Batter up.

814
00:33:44,230 --> 00:33:45,200
你来这儿做什么
What are you doing here?

815
00:33:45,380 --> 00:33:47,270
我说过在达成协议五秒钟后  我会告诉你
I said I'd tell you what we were gonna do with your centers

816
00:33:47,270 --> 00:33:48,940
我们的配送中心处理方案
five seconds after we closed.

817
00:33:49,650 --> 00:33:51,090
我们什么时候达成了协议
When did we close?

818
00:33:51,380 --> 00:33:52,800
大约三秒前
About three seconds ago.

819
00:33:53,390 --> 00:33:55,010
那咱们得抓紧点
I guess we better hurry.

820
00:33:58,100 --> 00:34:00,400
你们打算怎么安排我的员工
All right, what's going to happen to my employees?

821
00:34:00,440 --> 00:34:02,000
我们打算把你的配送中心
We're going to sell your distribution centers

822
00:34:02,000 --> 00:34:03,820
卖给一家医药公司
to a pharmaceutical company

823
00:34:04,380 --> 00:34:06,000
功能不变
as distribution centers.

824
00:34:06,000 --> 00:34:07,210
他们仍会雇用你的员工
They use your workers.

825
00:34:07,220 --> 00:34:10,310
他们可以立刻上手  双赢
They hit the ground running. Win-win.

826
00:34:10,310 --> 00:34:11,690
你的确信守承诺
You're a man of your word.

827
00:34:13,870 --> 00:34:16,490
但你过来另有原因
But that's not why you're here.

828
00:34:17,770 --> 00:34:19,110
没错
No, it isn't.

829
00:34:20,330 --> 00:34:22,360
我不想卖掉我的事业
I'm not interested in selling my business.

830
00:34:22,370 --> 00:34:23,990
我知道  因为我了解
I know that, because I know 

831
00:34:24,000 --> 00:34:26,430
为何你倾入了所有心血打造这家公司
why you've thrown your whole life into this company

832
00:34:26,430 --> 00:34:29,090
以及为何你最初选择进入电影业
and why you chose the movie business in the first place.

833
00:34:29,420 --> 00:34:30,500
你想说什么
What's your point?

834
00:34:31,570 --> 00:34:32,490
菲利普
Phillip.

835
00:34:34,110 --> 00:34:35,020
你儿子
Your son.

836
00:34:36,440 --> 00:34:38,370
你们喜欢一起看电影
You loved watching movies together.

837
00:34:39,170 --> 00:34:40,470
所以你才创办了这家公司
That's why you started this company

838
00:34:40,470 --> 00:34:42,330
而且不管给你多少钱
and why you won't let go of what it's become

839
00:34:42,330 --> 00:34:43,970
你都不会放弃它
for any amount of money.

840
00:34:44,630 --> 00:34:45,650
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?

841
00:34:46,570 --> 00:34:47,670
我告诉过你
I told you.

842
00:34:48,250 --> 00:34:49,520
我总会做好功课
I do my homework.

843
00:34:53,700 --> 00:34:54,630
你失去了他
You lost him,

844
00:34:55,560 --> 00:34:56,510
你需要排解悲伤
and you needed an outlet,

845
00:34:56,510 --> 00:35:00,320
所以这家公司对你就意味着
and that's what this company is to you now--

846
00:35:01,280 --> 00:35:02,150
你的家人
your family.

847
00:35:02,150 --> 00:35:04,150
我说过了  我不会卖的
I told you, I'm not selling.

848
00:35:04,150 --> 00:35:05,990
而我也告诉过你  不管你是否愿意
And I told you, they're coming after you

849
00:35:05,990 --> 00:35:07,640
他们都会揪着你不放
whether you like it or not.

850
00:35:08,230 --> 00:35:09,900
而我和他们的不同之处
And the difference between me and them

851
00:35:09,900 --> 00:35:11,530
在于他们想要把你的公司拆散
is they want to tear your company apart,

852
00:35:11,530 --> 00:35:13,050
而我想让它保持完整
and I want to keep it together.

853
00:35:13,050 --> 00:35:15,140
你没有足够的资源这么做
You don't have the resources to do that.

854
00:35:15,520 --> 00:35:16,390
不
Yes.

855
00:35:17,590 --> 00:35:18,400
我有
I do.

856
00:35:20,890 --> 00:35:22,860
从一小时前  我开始投资你的公司
As of an hour ago, I started investing.

857
00:35:22,870 --> 00:35:26,440
过了这一周  我会拥有4.9%的股份
So by this time next week, I will own 4.9%.

858
00:35:27,760 --> 00:35:29,250
我本没必要告诉你这些
I didn't have to tell you that.

859
00:35:29,250 --> 00:35:31,190
所以我就应该信任你吗
And that's supposed to make me trust you?

860
00:35:36,340 --> 00:35:39,020
我11岁的时候失去了双亲
I lost both of my parents when I was 11 years old,

861
00:35:40,850 --> 00:35:44,880
所以我明白需要亲人的感觉
so I know a little something about needing family.

862
00:35:45,440 --> 00:35:46,330
沃尔特
Walter...

863
00:35:48,220 --> 00:35:49,850
我不能保证我们会赢
I can't guarantee you we'll win,

864
00:35:51,390 --> 00:35:54,510
但我能保证我永远不会出卖你
but I can guarantee you that I will never sell you out.

865
00:35:58,380 --> 00:35:59,700
好的  我加入
All right, I'm in.

866
00:36:06,830 --> 00:36:08,390
听着  赞恩  我希望那份文件
Listen, Zane, I want that goddamn filing

867
00:36:08,390 --> 00:36:09,740
立刻出现在我桌子上
on my desk nine seconds ago,

868
00:36:09,740 --> 00:36:11,610
否则你就卷铺盖回家吧
or you can forget You ever worked here.

869
00:36:11,690 --> 00:36:12,730
现在恕我失陪
Now excuse me.

870
00:36:12,760 --> 00:36:14,520
我得去找某人的茬了
I've got to go be a dick to someone.

871
00:36:14,720 --> 00:36:15,540
坐下
Sit down.

872
00:36:18,990 --> 00:36:20,690
是要说你和迈克的事吗
Is this about you and Mike?

873
00:36:21,080 --> 00:36:23,370
听我说  这会是一场血战
listen to me-- this is gonna be a street fight,

874
00:36:23,370 --> 00:36:25,930
而只有一方会撑到最后
and there's only gonna be one man standing when it's over.

875
00:36:25,930 --> 00:36:27,490
所以我只问你这一次
So I'm only gonna ask you this once.

876
00:36:27,490 --> 00:36:28,530
你不需要问了
You don't need to.

877
00:36:28,790 --> 00:36:31,160
我不想退出  我想加入
I don't want out. I want in.

878
00:36:31,290 --> 00:36:33,200
我之前说你可以派我去警告迈克
And when I said, "You want me to send a message to Mike?"

879
00:36:33,200 --> 00:36:34,390
我是真心的
I meant it.

880
00:36:34,930 --> 00:36:36,400
我只是想问你愿不愿意
I was just gonna ask if you were comfortable

881
00:36:36,400 --> 00:36:37,950
每天早晨帮我买咖啡
getting me coffee in the mornings.

882
00:36:38,800 --> 00:36:40,010
我是认真的
I'm serious.

883
00:36:40,110 --> 00:36:42,210
和我爸爸对阵的时候我没有退缩
I didn't back down from a fight with my dad,

884
00:36:42,210 --> 00:36:44,740
那么和迈克对阵的时候我也不会
and I'm not going to back down from one with Mike.

885
00:36:45,390 --> 00:36:46,370
很好
Good.

886
00:36:47,140 --> 00:36:49,680
现在我真的要去买咖啡了
Now, I actually am gonna get coffee.

887
00:36:49,680 --> 00:36:51,050
太好了  一份糖  加一点奶油
Great. One sugar, a splash of cream,

888
00:36:51,050 --> 00:36:52,620
多放些榛果糖浆
and don't skimp on the hazelnut.

889
00:36:54,290 --> 00:36:56,120
太得寸进尺了吗
Too soon.

890
00:36:56,130 --> 00:36:58,160
与其在这里得寸进尺
Instead of failing to be charming,

891
00:36:58,160 --> 00:36:59,930
你不如赶紧去干点有用的
why don't you do something useful 

892
00:36:59,930 --> 00:37:02,940
为洛根·桑德斯起草一份投标报价书
and get moving on drawing up a tender offer for Logan Sanders?

893
00:37:02,940 --> 00:37:04,980
洛根  你是想说麦克斯·桑德斯吧
Logan? No, you mean Max Sanders.

894
00:37:04,980 --> 00:37:06,940
我总忘记你现在是半工半学
I keep forgetting that you're in law school half the time.

895
00:37:06,940 --> 00:37:08,290
麦克斯退休了
Max is retired.

896
00:37:08,460 --> 00:37:09,910
现在是洛根大展身手的时候了
It's Logan's show now.

897
00:37:16,930 --> 00:37:17,940
你想见我
You wanted to see me?

898
00:37:18,530 --> 00:37:20,420
我们得加快行动速度
We need to move up our timeline.

899
00:37:20,680 --> 00:37:22,470
我已经在尽快购买股份了
Well, I'm buying shares as fast as I can.

900
00:37:22,470 --> 00:37:24,120
我是指投标报价书
I'm talking about a tender offer.

901
00:37:24,490 --> 00:37:25,670
我们的计划是震慑住对方
The plan is shock and awe.

902
00:37:25,670 --> 00:37:26,600
如果我们匆忙拿出投标报价书
If we rush a tender offer,

903
00:37:26,600 --> 00:37:27,390
就没有足够的筹码
we won't have enough leverage

904
00:37:27,390 --> 00:37:28,600
迫使股东们投票给我们
to force people to vote with us.

905
00:37:28,600 --> 00:37:29,690
如果我们是唯一的买家
It's fine to have shock and awe

906
00:37:29,690 --> 00:37:30,860
震慑策略就完全没问题
when you're the only one in the game,

907
00:37:30,860 --> 00:37:32,290
但是沃尔特·吉利斯知道了我们要出手
but Walter Gillis knows we're coming,

908
00:37:32,290 --> 00:37:34,040
还找到了一个同盟
and he got himself an ally.

909
00:37:35,170 --> 00:37:36,290
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?

910
00:37:37,030 --> 00:37:38,000
我就是知道
Because I do.

911
00:37:38,790 --> 00:37:40,160
引起你利益冲突的人  是谁
Your conflict-- who is it?

912
00:37:40,160 --> 00:37:42,770
-我不能说  -你什么时候能说
- I can't talk about it. - Well, when the hell can you?

913
00:37:42,770 --> 00:37:44,070
一个小时后
In another hour.

914
00:37:50,000 --> 00:37:51,100
你帮我准备好了吗
You have it for me?

915
00:37:51,720 --> 00:37:54,310
哈维  你知道你现在想退出还来得及
Harvey, you know you can still get out of this if you want to.

916
00:37:54,320 --> 00:37:56,290
如果你告诉迈克不要签  他就不会签的
Mike's not gonna sign that thing if you tell him not to.

917
00:37:56,290 --> 00:37:57,630
已经太晚了
It's too late for that.

918
00:37:57,860 --> 00:37:59,110
我的天
Oh, my god.

919
00:37:59,110 --> 00:38:00,940
我正好要找你
Hey, just the woman I wanted to see.

920
00:38:00,940 --> 00:38:02,290
唐娜  你有哈德曼
Donna, would you happen to have the measurements

921
00:38:02,290 --> 00:38:03,170
旧办公室的尺寸吗
to Hardman's old office?

922
00:38:03,170 --> 00:38:04,400
路易  让开
Louis, get out of my way.

923
00:38:04,400 --> 00:38:06,510
这是怎么了  唐娜
Whoa. What's going on, Donna?

924
00:38:06,800 --> 00:38:07,780
怎么了
What's going on?

925
00:38:09,080 --> 00:38:10,530
哈维跟你说什么
That bullshit Harvey told you

926
00:38:10,530 --> 00:38:12,290
等女孩先联系
about waiting for the girl to call,

927
00:38:12,510 --> 00:38:13,610
都是瞎扯的
it's bullshit.

928
00:38:14,090 --> 00:38:15,740
他确实等了  结果现在太迟了
He waited, and now it's too late.

929
00:38:23,890 --> 00:38:25,490
计划有变  把你所有事情都取消
Change of plans. Cancel anything you have.

930
00:38:25,500 --> 00:38:26,890
-我们要在这里待一晚上  -为什么
- We're staying here all night. - What for?

931
00:38:26,890 --> 00:38:27,600
证监会要来了
The S.E.C.'s coming,

932
00:38:27,600 --> 00:38:29,570
杰西卡要找个人跟他们斗
Jessica's hiring one person to fight 'em,

933
00:38:29,570 --> 00:38:30,520
我们明天的第一件事
and first thing tomorrow,

934
00:38:30,520 --> 00:38:32,320
就是要说服她应该找我
we need to convince her that person's me.

935
00:38:36,150 --> 00:38:38,100
我看到你手上的电影光碟了
I see you have the movies.

936
00:38:40,680 --> 00:38:41,940
我猜那意味着你已经决定了
I guess that means you've decided

937
00:38:41,940 --> 00:38:44,090
我们之间的关系
which relationship you want us to have.

938
00:38:44,820 --> 00:38:45,790
确实
I have.

939
00:38:47,320 --> 00:38:48,890
但可能不是你想的那种
But it's not what you might think.

940
00:38:53,580 --> 00:38:55,400
如果你还想要那份工作
If you still want the job,

941
00:38:56,240 --> 00:38:57,530
那就从明天开始
it starts tomorrow.

942
00:39:01,070 --> 00:39:01,960
我想要
I do.

943
00:39:04,020 --> 00:39:06,110
那今晚就是我们的最后一晚
Then tonight is our last night.

944
00:39:07,580 --> 00:39:09,960
那就瞧瞧四小时后你还是不是这样想
We'll see if you still think that in four hours.

945
00:39:10,690 --> 00:39:12,110
你想搞三次吗
Oh, you want to go three times?

946
00:39:12,110 --> 00:39:13,990
我还包括了一部电影的时间呢
Oh, I was including one of the movies.

947
00:39:14,640 --> 00:39:16,600
-不是吧  -不是
- No. - No.

948
00:39:36,680 --> 00:39:38,510
你终于有自己的办公室了
Finally got yourself an office.

949
00:39:39,070 --> 00:39:41,910
也许你忘了  我之前也有一间办公室
Maybe you forgot, but I had an office before.

950
00:39:41,910 --> 00:39:43,260
我只是还回去了
I just gave it back.

951
00:39:43,570 --> 00:39:46,260
我记得  为表忠诚
I remember, as a show of loyalty.

952
00:39:46,270 --> 00:39:49,750
是啊  此一时彼一时
Yeah, well, that was then. This is now.

953
00:39:53,580 --> 00:39:55,030
你想说什么  哈维
What you got there, Harvey?

954
00:39:55,740 --> 00:39:57,220
你以为你跟沃尔特·吉利斯见面
You think you could meet with Walter Gillis

955
00:39:57,230 --> 00:39:58,250
不会被我发现吗
and I wouldn't find out?

956
00:39:58,250 --> 00:39:59,720
不  我知道你会发现的
No, I knew you'd find out.

957
00:40:00,180 --> 00:40:01,390
我只是不在乎
I just didn't care.

958
00:40:03,330 --> 00:40:05,490
那也许你也不介意签这个
Then maybe you won't mind signing this.

959
00:40:06,480 --> 00:40:07,520
让我猜猜
Let me guess.

960
00:40:08,280 --> 00:40:10,500
你想让我签字  放弃你因为
You want me to waive the conflict that you still have

961
00:40:10,500 --> 00:40:12,310
听了我全部计划而依然存在的利益冲突
after hearing my plan first.

962
00:40:13,150 --> 00:40:15,890
我不是来这里看你这狗屁办公室的
I sure didn't come here to see your shitty office.

963
00:40:17,610 --> 00:40:18,520
既然你有求于我
Aren't you supposed to be nice

964
00:40:18,520 --> 00:40:20,560
难道不应该对我友好一点吗
to the person you need something from?

965
00:40:20,580 --> 00:40:23,230
你签不签他们都会追着不放的
They're still coming whether you sign it or not.

966
00:40:24,370 --> 00:40:28,430
但如果我不签  他们不会跟你一起来
If I don't sign it, they won't be coming with you.

967
00:40:28,640 --> 00:40:29,570
确实
True.

968
00:40:30,080 --> 00:40:32,710
当然  如果你不签
Of course, if you don't sign it,

969
00:40:33,230 --> 00:40:36,210
可能会让某些人说你怕我
it may cause some people to say you're afraid of me.

970
00:40:36,570 --> 00:40:38,770
我说的"某些人"是指我
And by "Some people," I mean me.

971
00:40:39,570 --> 00:40:41,610
当然了  如果我仅仅因为你那样说就签了
Of course, if I sign it just because you said that,

972
00:40:41,610 --> 00:40:44,390
那可能会让某些人说你成功让我上钩了
then it might cause some people to say you baited me.

973
00:40:45,100 --> 00:40:47,810
但我一去见沃尔特·吉利斯
But I knew you were coming

974
00:40:47,810 --> 00:40:50,060
我就知道你会来
the second I went to see Walter Gillis.

975
00:40:50,070 --> 00:40:51,070
所以...
So...

976
00:40:52,280 --> 00:40:54,200
我先替你签了一份
I went ahead and signed one for you.

977
00:40:56,190 --> 00:40:58,180
-看来我们是开战了  -是的
- I guess it's on. - I guess it is.

978
00:40:59,870 --> 00:41:01,880
你觉得我们要制定些基本规则吗
You think we need to lay out some ground rules?

979
00:41:02,000 --> 00:41:04,230
决斗还需要规则吗
Rules? In a knife fight?

980
00:41:05,020 --> 00:41:07,490
是不是得有人喊  一二三  开始
I guess somebody ought to yell, "One, two, three, go."

981
00:41:07,850 --> 00:41:09,270
一二三  开始
One, two, three, go.

982
00:41:12,950 --> 00:41:14,180
通常有人得到新办公室时
You know, usually when someone gets a new office,

983
00:41:14,180 --> 00:41:16,210
应该给他带点礼物  对吗
you're supposed to bring them something, right?

984
00:41:17,220 --> 00:41:19,400
比如兰花什么的
Like an orchid or something?

985
00:41:21,380 --> 00:41:22,250
没有吗
No?

986
00:41:23,380 --> 00:41:24,340
什么都没有吗
Nothing?

987
00:41:34,500 --> 00:41:36,140
你签了弃权书  对吗
You signed the waiver, didn't you?

988
00:41:36,290 --> 00:41:37,440
你知道我签了
You know I did.

989
00:41:38,140 --> 00:41:39,700
不能向哈维妥协
Not gonna back down from Harvey.

990
00:41:40,620 --> 00:41:44,920
我猜你已经让吉利斯支持你的方案了吧
And I suppose you got Gillis on board with your plan?

991
00:41:44,950 --> 00:41:47,630
如果没有  我就没必要签弃权书了
I wouldn't have needed to sign the waiver if I didn't.

992
00:41:51,120 --> 00:41:53,040
会没事的
Hey, it's gonna be okay.

993
00:41:53,770 --> 00:41:55,060
我跟哈维之间的事情
This thing between me and Harvey--

994
00:41:55,060 --> 00:41:56,570
没必要影响到我们
It doesn't have to affect us.

995
00:41:57,050 --> 00:41:58,110
我们不会受影响的
We won't let it.

996
00:42:00,770 --> 00:42:02,800
我到今天才知道洛根·桑德斯
I didn't know that Logan Sanders

997
00:42:02,800 --> 00:42:05,290
已经接管了他父亲的公司
took over his father's company until today.

998
00:42:05,510 --> 00:42:07,140
那跟什么事情有关系吗
What does that have to do with anything?

999
00:42:07,240 --> 00:42:09,530
-他是哈维的客户  -是啊  怎么了
- He's Harvey's client. - Yeah, so?

1000
00:42:12,860 --> 00:42:15,180
你记得我告诉过你  我...
Do you remember when I told you that I...

1001
00:42:17,080 --> 00:42:19,200
我曾经跟一个有妇之夫偷情吗
that I once had an affair with a married man?

1002
00:42:20,090 --> 00:42:21,160
就是他
It was him.

