1
00:00:10,950 --> 00:00:12,180
唐娜
Donna...

2
00:00:13,890 --> 00:00:15,220
唐娜
Donna.

3
00:00:15,230 --> 00:00:16,910
我们共事这么久
You know, in all the years that we worked together,

4
00:00:16,910 --> 00:00:18,720
你总共才到过我家两次
you've been over to my place exactly twice,

5
00:00:18,720 --> 00:00:20,100
一次是那次可怕的晚宴  还有
the god-awful dinner party and...

6
00:00:20,100 --> 00:00:21,100
某一次
the other time.

7
00:00:21,100 --> 00:00:22,330
我才离职三周
I have been gone three weeks,

8
00:00:22,340 --> 00:00:24,570
你就数次拜访  想怎样
and you've been here that many times. What?

9
00:00:24,570 --> 00:00:26,010
那次晚宴我玩得很开心
I had a good time at that dinner party.

10
00:00:26,010 --> 00:00:28,140
我的天  你真是会转移话题啊
Oh, my God, it is just like you to make a joke.

11
00:00:28,140 --> 00:00:29,990
另外那次你也别再提了
And ignore the other time.

12
00:00:32,930 --> 00:00:34,790
我来给你送奖金的
I brought you your bonus.

13
00:00:38,320 --> 00:00:39,820
真的吗  你以为
Really? You thought that

14
00:00:39,820 --> 00:00:41,420
开张支票打发我  一切就没事了吗
would make it all better, handing me a check?

15
00:00:41,420 --> 00:00:42,960
我知道你很生气
Look, I know that you're pissed.

16
00:00:42,960 --> 00:00:44,430
-竟然被你发现了  -唐娜
- Oh, what gave it away? - Donna...

17
00:00:44,430 --> 00:00:47,100
你不得已才在庭上愤然而起  对不对
You just had to jump in there at the trial, didn't you?

18
00:00:47,100 --> 00:00:49,230
你不得已才为我抗争
You just had to fight my battles for me.

19
00:00:49,230 --> 00:00:51,210
是  我这么做是因为上次来找你
Yeah, I did that because, the last time I saw you,

20
00:00:51,220 --> 00:00:52,830
你还因为我没有为你抗争而生气
you were pissed that I didn't fight for you.

21
00:00:52,830 --> 00:00:54,890
恭喜  哈维  你做的这一切
Well, congratulations, Harvey. All you managed to do

22
00:00:54,890 --> 00:00:56,680
搞得好像我真的爱你
has made it look like I love you.

23
00:00:57,500 --> 00:00:58,890
我的上帝
Oh, Jesus Christ.

24
00:00:58,890 --> 00:01:00,880
我的天  你确实这么想
Oh, my God, you think I do.

25
00:01:03,530 --> 00:01:06,520
我还真没见过你这么自以为是的人
I have actually never met such a self-important--

26
00:01:06,520 --> 00:01:09,100
唐娜  关于那次  你曾对我说过
Donna, about that time, you once told me--

27
00:01:09,100 --> 00:01:10,860
我才不在乎以前跟你说了什么
I don't care what I once told you!

28
00:01:10,860 --> 00:01:12,360
路易问的又不是那些
That wasn't what Louis was asking.

29
00:01:12,360 --> 00:01:13,850
他问我是否爱你
He was asking if I love you.

30
00:01:13,850 --> 00:01:15,120
而你却没回答
And you wouldn't answer.

31
00:01:15,120 --> 00:01:16,760
因为他逼我只用“是”或“否”去回答
Because he was forcing a yes or no answer

32
00:01:16,760 --> 00:01:18,790
一个复杂的问题
to a complicated question.

33
00:01:19,840 --> 00:01:24,050
我没有爱上你  哈维
I am not in love with you, Harvey.

34
00:01:24,350 --> 00:01:26,760
我爱你  就像爱哥哥
I love you like a brother

35
00:01:26,760 --> 00:01:28,280
或者是表哥那样
or a cousin, somebody that

36
00:01:28,280 --> 00:01:30,630
会非常非常期盼在圣诞节相聚
you really, really look forward to seeing at Christmas,

37
00:01:30,630 --> 00:01:33,010
再非常非常高兴地送走他
and then you're really, really glad to see leave.

38
00:01:33,010 --> 00:01:34,580
对你我而言
And as far as you and I are concerned,

39
00:01:34,580 --> 00:01:36,140
圣诞节过完了
Christmas is over.

40
00:01:36,160 --> 00:01:37,800
我来这儿不仅仅是想给你送支票
I didn't just come here to give you a check.

41
00:01:37,800 --> 00:01:39,350
我想让你复职
I came here to get you back.

42
00:01:39,350 --> 00:01:40,580
怎么  卡梅伦做得不好吗
What, Cameron not working out?

43
00:01:40,580 --> 00:01:42,610
我听说那死小子重建了我的归档系统
I heard that little shit redid my entire filing system.

44
00:01:42,610 --> 00:01:45,430
卡梅伦做得挺好  是我需要你
Cameron's fine. Look, I need you.

45
00:01:45,430 --> 00:01:48,390
-需要  -需要
- Need? - Need.

46
00:01:48,390 --> 00:01:50,420
-那杰西卡呢  -她不干涉此事了
- Well, what about Jessica? - Already signed off.

47
00:01:50,420 --> 00:01:51,380
你怎么让她不干涉的
How did you get her to do that?

48
00:01:51,380 --> 00:01:55,000
我告诉她  没有你  我也不再是我
Because I told her I can't be me without you.

49
00:01:57,240 --> 00:01:59,840
-不  你没这么说  -我想这么说的
- No, you didn't. - Well, I thought it.

50
00:02:00,310 --> 00:02:01,880
而且不说她也明白
And she knows it.

51
00:02:01,880 --> 00:02:03,770
行  要我回去得答应我两个条件
Okay, I will come back on two conditions.

52
00:02:03,770 --> 00:02:07,430
一是给姐换张数目大点的支票
One is you replace that check with a bigger one.

53
00:02:07,910 --> 00:02:09,440
另外一个呢
And the other?

54
00:02:16,950 --> 00:02:18,360
哈罗德
Harold...

55
00:02:18,640 --> 00:02:20,680
-在看黄片吗  -没有
- Is that porn? - No.

56
00:02:21,140 --> 00:02:23,900
好吧  没错  可不是出于猥琐的目的
Well, yes, but that's not what I'm using it for.

57
00:02:23,910 --> 00:02:25,650
我敢打包票
Okay, I'm about 150% sure

58
00:02:25,650 --> 00:02:27,880
我会后悔这么问你  但
that I'm gonna regret this, but...

59
00:02:28,430 --> 00:02:29,580
你为什么要看
What are you using it for?

60
00:02:29,580 --> 00:02:31,310
我看的是上面的纹身
I'm looking at tattoos.

61
00:02:31,310 --> 00:02:33,380
跟你说了  我要纹一个作为第一次
I told you, it's what I'm getting with my first--

62
00:02:33,380 --> 00:02:35,770
发奖金喽  孩子们
Bonus time, boys and girls.

63
00:02:36,210 --> 00:02:39,220
给多了  给太多了
Too much. Way too much.

64
00:02:39,220 --> 00:02:43,060
再乘以个零  还是发太多了
Oof, multiply this by zero, and it's still way too much.

65
00:02:43,470 --> 00:02:45,790
奥尼尔  拉辛
O'Neil, Racine,

66
00:02:45,790 --> 00:02:48,850
赛巴蒂尼  没有罗斯的
Sabbatini... no Ross.

67
00:02:48,850 --> 00:02:50,420
-真有趣  路易  -我没开玩笑
- Very funny, Louis. - I'm not kidding.

68
00:02:50,420 --> 00:02:52,280
看来你是真的没奖金哟
It looks like you came up empty.

69
00:02:59,560 --> 00:03:01,680
撤销梭利斯起诉的动议准备好了吗
You have the file for the Solis motion to dismiss?

70
00:03:01,690 --> 00:03:04,240
都在这儿了  主要引用也已标出
Yep, all set. Main citations are tabbed.

71
00:03:04,240 --> 00:03:07,610
好  走吧  我很忙
Good. Go. I'm busy.

72
00:03:08,680 --> 00:03:10,240
好吧  我只是…
Okay, I was just, um...

73
00:03:10,240 --> 00:03:12,580
你知道吗  之前  你…
You know, before, um...you--

74
00:03:12,580 --> 00:03:14,380
你抽风了吗
Are you having a stroke?

75
00:03:15,000 --> 00:03:16,770
-什么事  -我的奖金
- What? - My bonus.

76
00:03:16,770 --> 00:03:17,720
路易那里没有
Louis didn't have it.

77
00:03:17,720 --> 00:03:20,100
至少他是这么说的
Well, at least, he said that he didn't have it,

78
00:03:20,100 --> 00:03:21,650
所以我想可能你
so I thought that maybe you, uh...

79
00:03:21,650 --> 00:03:23,930
可能杰西卡觉得不该发奖金给你
Maybe Jessica thinks you don't deserve one.

80
00:03:23,930 --> 00:03:26,440
你懂的  因为  你不是律师
You know, because... You're not a lawyer.

81
00:03:26,440 --> 00:03:29,450
好吧  她说的没错  那我觉得
Right, right. No, that's true, so I guess

82
00:03:29,450 --> 00:03:30,670
这些文件也没什么用了
these won't be doing you any good.

83
00:03:30,670 --> 00:03:32,540
那只是杰西卡的想法
Jessica thinks you're not a lawyer.

84
00:03:32,540 --> 00:03:35,650
我可不那么想
I don't think that.

85
00:03:43,080 --> 00:03:45,080
莫妮卡·伊顿那事你办得不错
Your Monica Eton performance worked.

86
00:03:45,080 --> 00:03:47,870
劝服了卡森  加洛和福格蒂
You switched Carson, Gallo, and Fogerty.

87
00:03:47,870 --> 00:03:49,780
等等  所以你给我这么多
Wait, is that why you're giving me so much?

88
00:03:49,790 --> 00:03:51,620
没错  我们现在领先一票
Yes. We're up one.

89
00:03:51,620 --> 00:03:52,920
这话最好还是别说的太早
You might want to hold onto it for a bit.

90
00:03:52,920 --> 00:03:54,290
-为什么  -汉森
- Why? - Hanson.

91
00:03:54,300 --> 00:03:56,170
去司法部就职了
Took a job at the Justice Department.

92
00:03:56,170 --> 00:03:58,910
我们没优势了  现在平手
Our lead is gone. Now we're even.

93
00:04:00,370 --> 00:04:02,500
还有四天投票
Well, the vote's in four days.

94
00:04:02,500 --> 00:04:03,790
平手就是现任者胜
The tie goes to the incumbent.

95
00:04:04,470 --> 00:04:05,510
这么说我们稳操胜券
So we're good.

96
00:04:05,510 --> 00:04:07,310
-很可能  -很好
- Probably. - Nice.

97
00:04:09,060 --> 00:04:11,860
你知道刚提到的“话别说得太早”
Uh, you do realize that "Hold onto it for a bit" Thing,

98
00:04:11,860 --> 00:04:13,720
只是说说而已吧
that's just a figure of speech.

99
00:04:13,730 --> 00:04:15,750
好  我就  就这样啦
Yeah, okay, I'm just...That's it.

100
00:04:25,740 --> 00:04:27,240
你想见我
You wanted to see me?

101
00:04:27,280 --> 00:04:30,720
刚才看到你在给助理们发奖金
Saw you handing out bonuses to the associates earlier.

102
00:04:30,720 --> 00:04:33,170
他们应该都感激涕零吧
They must all be feeling grateful.

103
00:04:33,820 --> 00:04:35,030
公司的确很慷慨
The firm was quite generous.

104
00:04:35,030 --> 00:04:37,540
但应该奖励的不只是助理们
It's not just the associates who should be rewarded.

105
00:04:37,540 --> 00:04:39,290
就我而言嘛  工作上的成就感
Well, for me personally, it's the satisfaction

106
00:04:39,290 --> 00:04:41,050
就是我的动力
of the work that drives me.

107
00:04:41,050 --> 00:04:43,890
虽然奖金也确实让我更有干劲
Although the money does help keep score.

108
00:04:43,890 --> 00:04:44,870
你误会我的意思了
You misunderstand me.

109
00:04:44,870 --> 00:04:46,340
我不是要给你发钱  路易
I don't have a check for you, Louis.

110
00:04:46,340 --> 00:04:50,290
我还想让你给我写张支票呢
I was hoping you had one for me.

111
00:04:50,290 --> 00:04:51,470
抱歉  我不太明白
I'm sorry, I'm confused.

112
00:04:51,470 --> 00:04:52,140
杰西卡才负责
Jessica is the one

113
00:04:52,140 --> 00:04:55,250
合伙人的奖金发放
who handles the bonuses for the partners.

114
00:04:55,250 --> 00:04:57,280
我说的不是奖金支票
I'm not talking about a bonus check.

115
00:04:57,280 --> 00:05:00,440
是资深合伙人的入股金
I'm talking about a buy-in check for a senior partnership.

116
00:05:00,690 --> 00:05:02,990
作为开创合伙人  我有权每年
As founding partner, I'm entitled to name

117
00:05:02,990 --> 00:05:06,420
任命一位新的资深合伙人
one new senior partner a year.

118
00:05:07,680 --> 00:05:10,190
我打算任命你
I'm naming you.

119
00:05:16,330 --> 00:05:18,320
你要让  你要…
You're making-- you're--

120
00:05:19,380 --> 00:05:22,270
-任命我…  -没错
- You're making me... - Yes.

121
00:05:30,490 --> 00:05:32,460
我等不及要告知天下了
I can't wait to tell everybody.

122
00:05:32,730 --> 00:05:35,190
我爹娘  锡姆科夫拉比〔犹太教士〕
My mother, my father, Rabbi Shimkoff...

123
00:05:35,190 --> 00:05:36,590
是啊
Yes.

124
00:05:37,990 --> 00:05:41,780
天哪  想想哈维得知时的表情
Oh, my God, the look on Harvey's face!

125
00:05:41,860 --> 00:05:43,330
路易
Louis...

126
00:05:43,620 --> 00:05:45,830
现在就正式生效了
It's official as of this moment.

127
00:05:45,830 --> 00:05:47,880
但我想公开的宣布还是留到
But I think we should make the actual announcement

128
00:05:47,880 --> 00:05:49,780
下次资深合伙人会议吧
at the next senior partners meeting.

129
00:05:49,780 --> 00:05:50,940
没问题  会议还要
Sure, the meeting where

130
00:05:50,940 --> 00:05:53,070
票选出执行合伙人
the managing partner will be voted on.

131
00:05:53,130 --> 00:05:55,200
日程上是这么安排的
I believe that is on the agenda.

132
00:05:55,670 --> 00:05:59,410
最好当面宣布这件事  你觉得呢
Best to do these things face to face, don't you agree?

133
00:05:59,880 --> 00:06:01,410
这是我俩的秘密
It's our secret.

134
00:06:02,160 --> 00:06:04,150
明天与其他星期二无异
Tomorrow's just like any other Tuesday.

135
00:06:04,150 --> 00:06:05,600
正是如此
Exactly.

136
00:06:05,830 --> 00:06:09,280
祝贺你
Hey, congratulations.

137
00:06:11,020 --> 00:06:15,020
 ■

138
00:06:11,020 --> 00:06:15,020
 本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
 更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
 

139
00:06:15,020 --> 00:06:19,020
■

140
00:06:15,020 --> 00:06:19,020
翻译：鱼小姐啦  丢丢曳  妄想的绒布熊  妄想的绒布熊

141
00:06:19,020 --> 00:06:23,020
■

142
00:06:19,020 --> 00:06:23,020
翻译：鸟儿拖骨头姐来救火  月月

143
00:06:23,020 --> 00:06:27,020
■

144
00:06:23,020 --> 00:06:27,020
时间轴：迟迟  加森   校对：油炸电风扇  月月

145
00:06:27,020 --> 00:06:31,020
■

146
00:06:27,020 --> 00:06:31,020
特效&后期：小仓鼠   总监： 原地满血复活月

147
00:06:36,220 --> 00:06:38,390
第二季 第九集

148
00:06:36,220 --> 00:06:38,390
诉 讼 双 雄

149
00:06:36,220 --> 00:06:38,390
蓝光-1080P-SHORTBREHD版调轴风格微修：字幕雷哥

150
00:07:32,240 --> 00:07:33,250
滚开
Get out.

151
00:07:33,250 --> 00:07:35,150
把你的彩标归档系统也拿走
And take your color-coded filing system with you.

152
00:07:35,150 --> 00:07:36,800
那是个系统  我怎么
It's a system. How do I--

153
00:07:36,800 --> 00:07:39,580
我就是想为这一刻添加点戏剧色彩
I'm trying to give the moment some dramatic flair.

154
00:07:39,920 --> 00:07:41,900
天  他连这也毁了
Jeez, now he ruined that too.

155
00:07:41,900 --> 00:07:43,330
上帝
God.

156
00:07:45,000 --> 00:07:45,960
就这样吗
That's it?

157
00:07:45,960 --> 00:07:47,980
这也值得当做一个条件吗
That was worth making a whole condition?

158
00:07:47,980 --> 00:07:49,610
我从没炒过别人鱿鱼
I've never fired anyone before.

159
00:07:49,610 --> 00:07:51,240
你知道他只是一个流动临工吧
You know he's a floating temp, right?

160
00:07:51,240 --> 00:07:54,050
午饭后他可能就在别人的座位上了
I mean, he'll be on somebody else's desk by the end of lunch.

161
00:07:54,820 --> 00:07:57,310
每个人都要往我的兴头上泼冷水吗
Does everyone have to rain on my parade?

162
00:08:07,360 --> 00:08:09,310
首先  你们只需看一眼数据
First of all, you just have to look at the statistics.

163
00:08:09,310 --> 00:08:11,370
梭利斯这家伙过去几年
I mean, this guy Solis could barely crack

164
00:08:11,370 --> 00:08:13,350
每年还打不到20个本垒打
20 homers a season a few years ago.

165
00:08:13,350 --> 00:08:15,800
现在他一年就能有40个本垒打
And now he's banging out over 40 a year?

166
00:08:15,800 --> 00:08:19,300
这该如何解释呢  岁月赋予的智慧  
What's that supposed to be, the wisdom of age?

167
00:08:19,300 --> 00:08:21,280
想知道他是否嗑药  你们甚至还不用看
And you don't even have to look at what he's doing on the field

168
00:08:21,280 --> 00:08:22,780
他在练习场的表现
to wonder if this guy is juicing.

169
00:08:22,790 --> 00:08:24,260
只需看他一眼就够了
Just take a look at him.

170
00:08:24,260 --> 00:08:26,700
或许我不是科学家
Now, look, I might not be a scientist,

171
00:08:26,700 --> 00:08:29,150
但我还有点常识
but I do have common sense,

172
00:08:29,150 --> 00:08:31,860
常识告诉我这个人服了兴奋剂
and it says this guy is doping.

173
00:08:31,860 --> 00:08:36,550
可是  注意了  这只是一家之言
But hey, that's just one man's opinion.

174
00:08:36,990 --> 00:08:37,970
法官大人
Your honor,

175
00:08:37,970 --> 00:08:41,070
如果当个混球算犯罪
if being an asshole was a criminal offense,

176
00:08:41,540 --> 00:08:43,550
我会说  把兹林斯基先生关起来吧
I'd say lock Mr. Zielinski up.

177
00:08:43,550 --> 00:08:46,300
如果他们想说他是混球  尽管说
In fact, if they want to call him that, be my guest.

178
00:08:46,300 --> 00:08:49,660
但他们最好加上“一家之言”  像他这样
But they better use the word "Opinion", like he did.

179
00:08:49,660 --> 00:08:52,700
因为这就是我当事人的权利
Because unless I woke up this morning in Nazi Germany,

180
00:08:52,700 --> 00:08:54,790
除非美国也成纳粹德国了
that's my client's right.

181
00:08:54,900 --> 00:08:57,090
-纳粹德国  -打个比方
- Nazi Germany? - Making a point.

182
00:08:57,090 --> 00:08:58,080
是啊  说得好〔德语〕
Ja,gut one.

183
00:08:58,080 --> 00:09:00,160
法官大人  他当事人在节目上说
Your honor, his client blatantly declares

184
00:09:00,160 --> 00:09:02,930
他的诽谤只是一家之言
his rants are merely his opinions

185
00:09:02,930 --> 00:09:05,650
只是为了打法律的擦边球
for the sole purpose of skirting libel law.

186
00:09:05,650 --> 00:09:07,760
我上街开65迈  只是为了
I drive 65 for the sole purpose

187
00:09:07,760 --> 00:09:08,990
不被开罚单
of avoiding a speeding ticket.

188
00:09:08,990 --> 00:09:10,020
不能为了这个就说我有罪
Doesn't make me a criminal.

189
00:09:10,020 --> 00:09:13,880
但斯佩克特先生并没有恶意中伤其他司机
But Mr. Specter doesn't have malice against other drivers.

190
00:09:13,880 --> 00:09:15,260
-他手上有什么  -我不知道
- What does he have? - I don't know.

191
00:09:15,260 --> 00:09:17,140
法官大人  我们手里有一些
Your honor, we have a little recording

192
00:09:17,140 --> 00:09:18,650
兹林斯基先生的录影
of Mr. Zielinski of our own.

193
00:09:18,650 --> 00:09:20,980
这是当兹林斯基先生不知道
This is what Mr. Zielinski sounds like

194
00:09:20,980 --> 00:09:23,840
摄像机在拍摄时的言语
when he doesn't know the cameras are rolling.

195
00:09:24,990 --> 00:09:27,830
梭利斯  这家伙就是个大骗子
Solis? The guy is a goddamn fraud.

196
00:09:27,840 --> 00:09:29,180
他用兴奋剂  我心知肚明
He's juicing, I know it.

197
00:09:29,180 --> 00:09:32,050
我不在意他或者大联盟声称有什么证据
I don't care what evidence he or the league claim to have.

198
00:09:32,120 --> 00:09:34,430
只要我说话  就有人在听
When I say things, people listen,

199
00:09:34,430 --> 00:09:36,940
我要把这混蛋赶出联赛
and I'm gonna run his ass out of the game.

200
00:09:36,940 --> 00:09:37,760
法官大人
Your honor--

201
00:09:37,760 --> 00:09:40,070
省省吧  斯佩克特先生
Save it, Mr. Specter.

202
00:09:40,070 --> 00:09:41,940
本案进入庭审阶段
Case goes to trial.

203
00:09:45,510 --> 00:09:47,200
你真的只开65迈吗
You really only drive 65?

204
00:09:47,200 --> 00:09:48,660
在学校区域的时候
In a school zone.

205
00:09:48,660 --> 00:09:50,820
梭利斯不需要钱  你们想要什么
Solis doesn't need the money. What do you want?

206
00:09:50,820 --> 00:09:52,960
大联盟三年的不定期抽查
Three years' worth of random tests by the league

207
00:09:52,960 --> 00:09:55,860
外加我们为粉碎谣言进行的独立测试
plus independent tests we had run to quash the rumors.

208
00:09:55,860 --> 00:09:57,970
如你所见  我当事人是清白的
As you can see, my client is clean.

209
00:09:57,970 --> 00:09:59,420
兹林斯基没有这些东西
Zielinski doesn't have these.

210
00:09:59,420 --> 00:10:00,870
他有  我很清楚
Oh, he does, and I know it.

211
00:10:00,870 --> 00:10:02,360
因为我们曾把这些资料发给他
Because we sent them to him.

212
00:10:02,360 --> 00:10:05,110
但他故意不在节目上披露
But he chooses not to reveal them on his show.

213
00:10:05,110 --> 00:10:06,740
如果我让他在节目上公布这些测试结果
What if I get him to air these results

214
00:10:06,740 --> 00:10:08,620
外加你们那边的说法呢
plus your side of the story?

215
00:10:08,630 --> 00:10:09,960
太迟了
Too late for that.

216
00:10:09,960 --> 00:10:11,810
我们要你当事人道歉
We want an apology from your client.

217
00:10:11,810 --> 00:10:13,240
私下吗
In person?

218
00:10:13,920 --> 00:10:14,820
想得美
Nice try.

219
00:10:14,820 --> 00:10:16,760
我们要他公开收回言论
We want an on-air complete retraction,

220
00:10:16,760 --> 00:10:18,690
这没得商量
and that's non-negotiable.

221
00:10:27,480 --> 00:10:29,850
路易
Louis.

222
00:10:29,850 --> 00:10:31,020
你好  唐娜
Hi, Donna.

223
00:10:31,020 --> 00:10:33,080
-我听说你回来了  -是啊
- I heard you were back. - I am.

224
00:10:33,090 --> 00:10:36,190
对  看见了
Yeah, see that.

225
00:10:36,190 --> 00:10:38,040
这个  我…
Look, you know, I, um...

226
00:10:38,090 --> 00:10:39,480
我从来没想
I never-- I never wanted to--

227
00:10:39,480 --> 00:10:42,090
想过什么
To...what?

228
00:10:42,100 --> 00:10:44,260
我从没想那么做
I never wanted to do what I did.

229
00:10:45,950 --> 00:10:48,140
我不知道该怎么说
And I-I just don't have the words...

230
00:10:49,640 --> 00:10:51,100
想好再说
Find them.

231
00:10:54,970 --> 00:10:56,450
对不起
I'm sorry.

232
00:10:59,180 --> 00:11:03,540
真的真的对不起
I'm so, so sorry.

233
00:11:08,130 --> 00:11:10,340
那咱们就别再提那件事了
Then let us never speak of it again.

234
00:11:12,830 --> 00:11:14,380
你开玩笑的  对吗
Mm... you're kidding, right?

235
00:11:14,390 --> 00:11:15,760
你刚才是真心的吗
Did you mean what you just said?

236
00:11:15,760 --> 00:11:18,060
-不能再真了  -那就行了
-And more. - Then it's done.

237
00:11:18,060 --> 00:11:20,570
-才没有  -你听到我刚…
- No, it isn't. - Did you hear what I just--

238
00:11:20,650 --> 00:11:25,470
季票  林肯中心  每场都是第一排
Season pass, Lincoln Center, front row every show.

239
00:11:25,470 --> 00:11:26,350
-真的  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.

240
00:11:26,350 --> 00:11:28,190
-我要和你一起去吗  -当然不用
- Do I have to go with you? - Hell no.

241
00:11:28,190 --> 00:11:31,330
-谢谢你  路易  -不客气
- Thank you, Louis. - You are welcome.

242
00:11:32,480 --> 00:11:34,030
天啊  今天还能再好一点吗
God, could this day get any better?

243
00:11:34,030 --> 00:11:35,070
“再好一点”
"Any better"?

244
00:11:35,070 --> 00:11:36,360
之前有什么好事吗
What was so good about it before?

245
00:11:36,370 --> 00:11:37,800
-什么事  -有什么事
- Huh, what happened? - Something.

246
00:11:37,810 --> 00:11:40,050
没什么啊  我就不能为你回归而高兴吗
Nothing, no, can't I just be glad you're back?

247
00:11:40,050 --> 00:11:42,210
你嘴都咧到后脑勺了
You look like you have 80 teeth.

248
00:11:43,290 --> 00:11:46,540
-西装什么牌子  -布莱奥尼  怎么
- What kind of suit is that? - Brioni. Why?

249
00:11:44,540 --> 00:11:46,540
意大利定制西服品牌

250
00:11:46,540 --> 00:11:47,960
要死了
Oh, shit.

251
00:11:52,460 --> 00:11:53,400
欢迎回来  唐娜
Welcome back, Donna.

252
00:11:53,410 --> 00:11:55,340
谢谢  但我要和你说点事
Thank you, but there's something I need to tell you.

253
00:11:55,350 --> 00:11:57,900
-不用道歉了  -不是这事
- No need to apologize. - Uh, that's not what it is.

254
00:11:57,910 --> 00:11:59,060
你没加到薪
You're not getting a raise.

255
00:11:59,060 --> 00:12:01,550
丹尼尔刚升了路易做资深合伙人
Daniel just made Louis senior partner.

256
00:12:02,750 --> 00:12:04,150
你怎么知道
How do you know?

257
00:12:04,260 --> 00:12:06,660
四年前  诺玛告诉我路易有套西装
Four years ago, Norma told me that Louis had a suit

258
00:12:06,660 --> 00:12:09,070
准备在当上资深合伙人的那天穿
picked out for the day he made senior partner.

259
00:12:09,090 --> 00:12:11,280
-他现在穿着了  -贱人
- He is wearing it. - Son of a bitch.

260
00:12:11,280 --> 00:12:12,480
哈德曼又买到了一票
Hardman bought another vote.

261
00:12:12,480 --> 00:12:13,370
你准备怎么做
What are you gonna do about it?

262
00:12:13,370 --> 00:12:14,920
抢回来
Get it back.

263
00:12:16,020 --> 00:12:17,910
-唐娜  -怎么
- Donna... - Yes?

264
00:12:17,910 --> 00:12:19,580
西装看上去怎么样
How'd the suit look?

265
00:12:20,370 --> 00:12:21,790
过时了
Dated.

266
00:12:21,800 --> 00:12:22,800
谢谢
Thank you.

267
00:12:22,800 --> 00:12:25,090
难以置信  那混蛋害我们进退两难
Can't believe that asshole put us in this pickle.

268
00:12:25,090 --> 00:12:26,100
我以为你会欣赏他
I'd think you'd admire him.

269
00:12:26,100 --> 00:12:28,190
他为你爱的比赛正名了
He's cleaning up the game you love.

270
00:12:28,190 --> 00:12:30,770
他空口无凭  肆意指控
He's been throwing accusations around with no proof,

271
00:12:30,770 --> 00:12:32,460
我最近真是受够这些了
and I've had about enough of that lately.

272
00:12:32,470 --> 00:12:34,210
不管有没有证据  是个人都看见
Well, proof or no proof, anybody can see

273
00:12:34,210 --> 00:12:35,340
梭利斯用了兴奋剂
that Solis is juicing.

274
00:12:35,350 --> 00:12:37,020
测试可不是这么说的
That's not what those tests say.

275
00:12:37,030 --> 00:12:39,840
相信我  人们能想办法通过测试的
People can find ways to pass tests, trust me.

276
00:12:39,840 --> 00:12:41,530
迈克
Michael!

277
00:12:42,930 --> 00:12:46,380
奶奶  瑞秋  不会吧
Grammy? Rachel. Oh, no.

278
00:12:46,390 --> 00:12:47,280
哈维
Um, Harvey...

279
00:12:47,280 --> 00:12:48,790
这就是你著名的奶奶吗
This is your famous grandmother?

280
00:12:48,790 --> 00:12:51,840
你说的对  他很犀利
Oh, you were right. He is sharp.

281
00:12:52,500 --> 00:12:53,610
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?

282
00:12:53,610 --> 00:12:56,130
斯佩克特先生  见到你很高兴
Mr. Specter, pleasure to meet you.

283
00:12:56,140 --> 00:12:57,890
你孙子说了你很多好话
Your grandson says nice things about you.

284
00:12:57,890 --> 00:13:00,980
他可跟我说你相当难缠
Oh, he tells me you're quite the hardass.

285
00:13:00,980 --> 00:13:02,710
会变得难缠
Can be a hardass.

286
00:13:02,710 --> 00:13:05,080
他用的其实不是“难缠”这个词
"Hardass" isn't really the word he uses.

287
00:13:05,080 --> 00:13:08,040
-奶奶  -这利嘴还真是遗传的啊
- Okay, Grammy. - I see lip runs in the family.

288
00:13:08,040 --> 00:13:09,720
见到你很高兴
It's nice meeting you.

289
00:13:12,090 --> 00:13:13,610
你在这儿干什么
Yeah, um... what are you doing here?

290
00:13:13,610 --> 00:13:15,550
还有你为什么在瑞秋的办公室
And--and--and why are you in Rachel's office?

291
00:13:15,550 --> 00:13:17,820
我们在楼下大厅偶然遇到的
Oh, we bumped into each other downstairs in the lobby.

292
00:13:17,820 --> 00:13:19,400
我想找你吃饭的
I thought we could eat.

293
00:13:19,400 --> 00:13:22,020
是不是还给我带了星际大战的午餐盒
Might as well have brought it to me a Star Wars lunchbox.

294
00:13:22,020 --> 00:13:25,080
别和我贫  迈克  已经两个月了
Don't give me lip, Michael. It's been two months.

295
00:13:25,080 --> 00:13:27,580
我以为你会想知道我是不是还活着
I thought maybe you'd want to see I'm still alive.

296
00:13:27,580 --> 00:13:30,180
她说的没错  迈克
She's got a point, Michael.

297
00:13:30,190 --> 00:13:33,300
另外  我很想见见你同事
Plus I wanted to meet the people you work with.

298
00:13:33,300 --> 00:13:34,990
比如瑞秋
Like Rachel.

299
00:13:35,020 --> 00:13:37,110
她比你说的还可爱
She's even more lovely than you said.

300
00:13:37,110 --> 00:13:39,170
-“可爱”  -好了  我们走吧
- "Lovely"? - Okay, we're done here.

301
00:13:39,720 --> 00:13:40,360
再见  亲爱的
Bye, dear.

302
00:13:40,360 --> 00:13:42,070
-希望很快能再见到你  -我也是
- I hope to see you again soon. - Me too.

303
00:13:42,080 --> 00:13:44,550
见到您真的很高兴
It was lovely to meet you.

304
00:13:46,120 --> 00:13:49,270
你真的有必要告诉瑞秋我说她很辣吗
Okay, did you really have to tell Rachel that I said she was hot?

305
00:13:49,280 --> 00:13:52,590
好吧  让我见见那个叫哈罗德的小丑
Oh, fine, just let me meet that Harold clown,

306
00:13:52,590 --> 00:13:53,880
然后我就走
and I'll go.

307
00:14:01,280 --> 00:14:03,530
你早就计划好了  对吗
You planned this whole thing from the beginning, didn't you?

308
00:14:03,540 --> 00:14:04,730
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.

309
00:14:04,730 --> 00:14:07,100
你帮汉森在司法部找到工作
You got Hanson that job at Justice.

310
00:14:07,100 --> 00:14:08,010
是我们的损失
It was a loss for us,

311
00:14:08,010 --> 00:14:09,840
但司法部赚到了  不是吗
but a gain for Justice, don't you think?

312
00:14:09,840 --> 00:14:13,850
背着我让路易·利特当资深合伙人
And making Louis Litt a senior partner behind my back.

313
00:14:13,860 --> 00:14:16,220
这就是新一代丹尼尔·哈德曼
Is that all part of the new Daniel Hardman

314
00:14:16,220 --> 00:14:17,780
所谓的透明性吗
era of transparency?

315
00:14:17,780 --> 00:14:19,200
这在我权利范围内
It's within my rights

316
00:14:19,200 --> 00:14:21,530
依据的可是你写的章程
according to the bylaws you wrote.

317
00:14:21,530 --> 00:14:23,080
是啊
Ah, yes,

318
00:14:23,080 --> 00:14:26,920
收买他的投票花了你多少钱
and how much did buying his vote cost you?

319
00:14:26,920 --> 00:14:28,400
花了我多少钱
Cost me?

320
00:14:28,910 --> 00:14:31,490
他早就该被提拔了
It was earned years ago.

321
00:14:31,710 --> 00:14:34,920
你迟迟不提拔他就是一个完美的例子
And your failure to promote him is a perfect example

322
00:14:34,920 --> 00:14:37,530
证明你的判断力是如何危害到这个公司的
of how your judgment has harmed this firm.

323
00:14:37,530 --> 00:14:40,280
我的判断力和周到考虑
My judgment and my discretion

324
00:14:40,280 --> 00:14:42,570
是你五年前没有蹲监狱的
are the only reasons your ass didn't end up

325
00:14:42,570 --> 00:14:43,770
唯一原因
in jail five years ago.

326
00:14:43,770 --> 00:14:46,360
这不是考虑周到  这是为了一己私利
It wasn't discretion, it was self-interest.

327
00:14:46,360 --> 00:14:48,060
你把我赶走并独霸了这间公司
You ousted me and got the firm.

328
00:14:48,060 --> 00:14:52,890
-我救了你并得到了公司  -是的
- I saved you and got the firm. - You did.

329
00:14:52,890 --> 00:14:55,150
但五年前你没有从我手里偷走管理权
But you didn't steal the ball from me five years ago.

330
00:14:55,150 --> 00:14:56,710
我自己放弃的
I dropped it.

331
00:14:56,750 --> 00:15:01,140
你本来最多  而且应该做的只是我的副手
My lieutenant was all you were ever meant to be.

332
00:15:02,220 --> 00:15:04,280
我和你做个交易
I'm going to offer you a deal.

333
00:15:04,880 --> 00:15:07,750
带走波特  费德曼  盖拉格
Take Porter, Feldman, Gallagher...

334
00:15:07,760 --> 00:15:10,650
我会让你走  随便在哪儿另立门户
I'll let you walk away, set up shop wherever you like.

335
00:15:10,650 --> 00:15:12,830
我会忽略竞争冲突那条
I'll waive the non-compete.

336
00:15:13,500 --> 00:15:15,130
你票数不够
You don't have the votes.

337
00:15:15,130 --> 00:15:16,560
我把你赶走过一次
I put you out once.

338
00:15:16,560 --> 00:15:18,300
当我这次打败了你
When I beat you this time,

339
00:15:18,300 --> 00:15:20,850
你将声名狼藉
they're gonna have to peel you off the wall.

340
00:15:21,450 --> 00:15:22,460
真高兴能看到你
It's nice to see you

341
00:15:22,460 --> 00:15:24,720
也会为达成目的而不择手段
doing your own dirty work for a change.

342
00:15:24,720 --> 00:15:27,630
不幸的是  这次你没法让哈维
Unfortunately, this time, you can't have Harvey threaten

343
00:15:27,630 --> 00:15:30,380
以向我病危的妻子或幼女告状
to tell my dying wife or my teenage daughter

344
00:15:30,380 --> 00:15:32,400
说我行为失检  来威胁我
about my indiscretions.

345
00:15:34,320 --> 00:15:37,460
你根本不知道莎拉是谁  是不是
You didn't even know about Sarah, did you?

346
00:15:37,980 --> 00:15:39,560
我说什么他做什么
He did what I told him to do.

347
00:15:39,570 --> 00:15:40,960
并非如此
No.

348
00:15:41,680 --> 00:15:45,120
你甚至不能控制你自己的斗犬
You can't even control your own attack dog.

349
00:15:45,120 --> 00:15:46,240
给我听着
Well, get this.

350
00:15:46,240 --> 00:15:49,180
艾丽西娅死后我根本没想过要回来
I wasn't even planning on coming back after Alicia died.

351
00:15:49,180 --> 00:15:51,470
然后你派他来  我别无选择
Then you sent him, and I had no choice.

352
00:15:51,470 --> 00:15:52,880
胡说八道
Bullshit.

353
00:15:52,880 --> 00:15:54,160
你做自己想做的事
You do what you want to do.

354
00:15:54,160 --> 00:15:57,080
过去  将来  一贯如此
You always have, and you always will.

355
00:15:57,600 --> 00:16:01,130
过去的就让它过去吧
Well, water under the bridge.

356
00:16:01,130 --> 00:16:03,320
而现在  时过境迁
We are where we are.

357
00:16:05,080 --> 00:16:06,890
我倒是挺喜欢我现在的样子
And I like where I am.

358
00:16:06,890 --> 00:16:10,780
我们走着瞧  看是谁笑到最后
And we'll see who peels whom off the wall.

359
00:16:20,820 --> 00:16:22,380
听我说
Let me get this straight.

360
00:16:22,380 --> 00:16:24,780
你知道丹尼尔已经有所行动
You realized that Daniel was pulling a move,

361
00:16:24,780 --> 00:16:25,930
然后你迎头和他对质
and you confronted him?

362
00:16:25,930 --> 00:16:28,180
你和我说过多少次不要打草惊蛇
How many times have you told me not to poke the bear?

363
00:16:28,180 --> 00:16:29,740
我没有打草惊蛇
I didn't just poke.

364
00:16:29,740 --> 00:16:31,660
-我给了他一个提议  -然后他拒绝了
- I made him an offer. - Which he refused.

365
00:16:31,660 --> 00:16:33,340
现在他知道我们是要挖角路易了
And now he knows we're on to Louis.

366
00:16:33,340 --> 00:16:35,590
如果因为路易·利特害我丢了饭碗
If I lose this thing because of Louis Litt...

367
00:16:35,590 --> 00:16:37,160
你不会失败的
You're not losing.

368
00:16:37,160 --> 00:16:39,590
你手上有哈德曼没有的制胜奇招
You have a card to play that Hardman doesn't have.

369
00:16:39,590 --> 00:16:41,560
-不 不行  -你有的
- No, no - Yes.

370
00:16:41,560 --> 00:16:43,170
合伙人的奖金还没发呢
Partner bonuses haven't gone out yet.

371
00:16:43,180 --> 00:16:45,590
我不会用钱去收买人心
I'm not using the bonuses to buy people off.

372
00:16:45,590 --> 00:16:48,260
你也许会因为用公司的钱来弄权
You might be ethically against playing politics

373
00:16:48,260 --> 00:16:50,180
而良心不安  但是他才不会
with our firm's money, but he isn't.

374
00:16:50,180 --> 00:16:51,540
这和道不道德无关
This isn't about ethics.

375
00:16:51,540 --> 00:16:53,620
如果我给路易多加十万奖金
If I give Louis an extra $100,000,

376
00:16:53,620 --> 00:16:56,480
那加洛  克莱曼  里格该怎么办
How's that gonna play with Gallo, Klyman, Reeger?

377
00:16:56,480 --> 00:16:59,010
那就效仿丹尼尔  任命一个资深合伙人
Then do what Daniel did. Make another senior partner.

378
00:16:59,010 --> 00:17:02,840
每人每年只有一次机会  我任命了你
We get one each per year. I named you.

379
00:17:02,840 --> 00:17:05,120
去读一遍公司章程  好吗
Read the bylaws, will you?

380
00:17:05,360 --> 00:17:07,080
简直是开玩笑
You've got to be kidding me.

381
00:17:07,320 --> 00:17:10,040
路易要成为关键一票了
Louis is going to be the deciding vote.

382
00:17:11,420 --> 00:17:13,350
他最好投给我
And he better vote for me.

383
00:17:14,210 --> 00:17:15,740
-不  不  -必须这样
- No, no! - Yes.

384
00:17:15,740 --> 00:17:17,650
哈维  这是个绝佳机会
Harvey, this is your chance to prove

385
00:17:17,650 --> 00:17:19,300
证明你从保罗·波特一事中
you learned something from that mess

386
00:17:19,300 --> 00:17:20,400
吸取了教训
you made with Paul Porter.

387
00:17:20,410 --> 00:17:21,390
可我没什么能给路易的
I have nothing to offer him.

388
00:17:21,390 --> 00:17:23,870
哈维  你一直待他如禽兽一般
Harvey, you've treated that man like shit at every turn.

389
00:17:23,870 --> 00:17:25,900
你是他心头的一根刺
You are the thorn in his side.

390
00:17:25,900 --> 00:17:28,700
是时候去把这根刺拔出来了
It is time that you pull that thorn out.

391
00:17:38,660 --> 00:17:40,400
这是你的书面质询
Here are your interrogatories.

392
00:17:40,400 --> 00:17:42,580
-谢谢  -哦对了  迈克
- Thank you. - Oh, and remember, Michael,

393
00:17:42,580 --> 00:17:44,930
你必须做完作业才能看电视
you have to finish your homework before you can watch TV.

394
00:17:44,930 --> 00:17:46,840
就因为我奶奶给我买了午饭
Oh, right, because my grandmother brought me lunch,

395
00:17:46,850 --> 00:17:48,300
-把我弄得像个  - 小男孩
- that makes me... - A little boy.

396
00:17:48,300 --> 00:17:50,030
你觉得这真有趣  对吗
And this is really fun for you.

397
00:17:50,030 --> 00:17:51,850
真的挺有意思的
It really kind of is.

398
00:17:52,880 --> 00:17:54,490
你是在考虑搬家吗
Are you thinking about moving?

399
00:17:54,580 --> 00:17:56,750
不  事实上我在想
Uh, no, actually I was looking into getting

400
00:17:56,750 --> 00:17:59,650
在曼哈顿找个地方给我的午餐奶奶住
a place in Manhattan for my lunch lady.

401
00:17:59,650 --> 00:18:01,910
-你真的是在为她这么做吗  -我是在这么做
- You'd really do that for her? - I am doing it.

402
00:18:01,910 --> 00:18:04,770
这些与她对我的付出相比
It doesn't even come close to paying her back

403
00:18:04,770 --> 00:18:06,790
不过是九牛一毛
for everything she's done for me.

404
00:18:08,750 --> 00:18:10,360
这实在是
That's, um...

405
00:18:11,150 --> 00:18:13,100
这真让人感动  迈克
That's really amazing, Mike.

406
00:18:13,100 --> 00:18:14,330
你想知道什么才是令人感动的吗
You wanna know what's amazing?

407
00:18:14,330 --> 00:18:16,510
-什么  -这个地方
- What? - This place.

408
00:18:16,510 --> 00:18:18,420
就在这儿  来看看
Right here, check it out.

409
00:18:18,900 --> 00:18:21,280
-挺温馨的  不是吗  -第十大道开外
- It's pretty sweet, right? - Off 10th avenue.

410
00:18:21,280 --> 00:18:23,010
买这儿会附送防弹背心吗
Does it come with a bulletproof vest?

411
00:18:23,010 --> 00:18:25,370
好吧
Um...okay.

412
00:18:27,080 --> 00:18:28,180
看  这个怎么样
There, how about this one?

413
00:18:28,180 --> 00:18:30,430
-要爬六层楼  -风景美不胜收
- A six floor walk-up. - Great views.

414
00:18:30,440 --> 00:18:31,930
闪开
Move over.

415
00:18:33,840 --> 00:18:35,640
好吧
Okay.

416
00:18:39,540 --> 00:18:41,490
-等等  -怎么了
- Wait a minute. - Yeah?

417
00:18:41,510 --> 00:18:44,180
这是你计划好的  好让我来帮你  是不是
You set all this up, so I'd help, didn't you?

418
00:18:44,200 --> 00:18:45,220
我可能是个小男孩
Oh, I may be a little boy,

419
00:18:45,220 --> 00:18:47,140
可我不是那么蠢的小男孩
But I'm not a stupid little boy.

420
00:18:47,140 --> 00:18:49,510
你是个鬼鬼祟祟的小男孩
You're a sneaky little boy.

421
00:18:49,510 --> 00:18:50,690
给我看看别的
Show me how it goes.

422
00:18:53,480 --> 00:18:57,260
合伙人  资深合伙人  在我听来都一样
Partner, senior partner. It all sounds the same to me.

423
00:18:57,260 --> 00:18:59,290
不  妈  要我告诉你多少次
No, Mom, how many times do I have to tell you?

424
00:18:59,290 --> 00:19:02,030
资深合伙人是公司核心
Senior partner is the inner circle.

425
00:19:02,030 --> 00:19:04,930
这只会让你听上去像个老男人
It just makes you sound like an old man.

426
00:19:04,940 --> 00:19:05,780
闭嘴
Stop it.

427
00:19:05,780 --> 00:19:07,190
你这又是从哪儿看出来的  爸
And what would you know about it, Dad?

428
00:19:07,190 --> 00:19:09,370
孩子  你在掉头发了
Well, you are losing your hair.

429
00:19:09,370 --> 00:19:11,510
-这是我的发型  -不是发型的问题
- It's the cut. - It is not the cut.

430
00:19:11,510 --> 00:19:12,650
这就是发型
It's the cut!

431
00:19:12,650 --> 00:19:13,960
还有  爸  如果你不嫌麻烦
And by the way, dad, if you're not going to bother

432
00:19:13,960 --> 00:19:15,360
看看摄像头在哪里
to figure out where the camera is,

433
00:19:15,360 --> 00:19:17,040
或许你该穿上那该死的裤子
maybe you should put some freaking pants on.

434
00:19:17,040 --> 00:19:18,210
我知道摄像头在哪里
I know where the camera is.

435
00:19:18,210 --> 00:19:19,900
我不为我的身体感到羞愧
I'm not ashamed of my body.

436
00:19:19,900 --> 00:19:23,020
当你也这么觉得了  你才会有个太太
If you felt the same way, maybe there'd be a Mrs. Litt.

437
00:19:23,020 --> 00:19:26,540
路易  我想在闭眼前看到我的孙子孙女
Louie, I don't want to die before I see my grandchildren.

438
00:19:26,540 --> 00:19:27,760
妈  你已经有两个孙辈了
Mom, you have two grandchildren.

439
00:19:27,760 --> 00:19:30,170
那是埃斯特的孩子  不是你的
Esther's children are not Litts!

440
00:19:30,170 --> 00:19:31,360
那是你父母吗
Is that your mom and dad on there?

441
00:19:31,360 --> 00:19:32,460
先给我出去  哈维  我在视频
Get out, Harvey, I'm skyping.

442
00:19:32,460 --> 00:19:35,310
是哈维·斯佩克特吗  让我和他说两句
Is that Harvey Specter? Let me speak to him.

443
00:19:35,310 --> 00:19:38,320
是时候让我见见你的好朋…
It is about time I met your best fri...

444
00:19:38,980 --> 00:19:39,890
他们是你父母吗
Was that your mom and dad?

445
00:19:39,900 --> 00:19:41,440
什么事儿  不
What's up? No.

446
00:19:44,320 --> 00:19:45,770
这是什么
What's this?

447
00:19:45,810 --> 00:19:49,210
我裁缝的地址  唐娜说你要的
The address of my tailor. Donna said you asked for it.

448
00:19:49,920 --> 00:19:54,130
如果我真的去了会发生什么事情
And what would really happen to me if I show up at that address?

449
00:19:54,130 --> 00:19:57,280
你拿到套体面的西服  可以今晚穿
You get a nice suit, one that you could wear tonight

450
00:19:57,280 --> 00:19:59,160
我要带你出去吃饭
when I take you out to dinner.

451
00:20:01,250 --> 00:20:02,460
唐娜说的
Donna.

452
00:20:02,460 --> 00:20:04,060
当上资深合伙人了还守口如瓶
What's the fun of being senior partner

453
00:20:04,060 --> 00:20:05,310
这还有什么意思
if you have to keep it a secret?

454
00:20:05,310 --> 00:20:07,720
我干嘛要和你一起用餐
And why exactly should I dine with you?

455
00:20:07,730 --> 00:20:09,850
因为你等这一天很久了
Because you've been waiting a long time for this,

456
00:20:09,850 --> 00:20:11,980
并且我想祝贺你
and I want to congratulate you.

457
00:20:12,190 --> 00:20:15,240
你想要恭喜我成为你的同僚
You want to congratulate me on becoming your peer.

458
00:20:15,240 --> 00:20:16,250
-是的  -说出来
- Yes. - Say it.

459
00:20:16,250 --> 00:20:17,980
-你我是同僚  -你我是同僚
- I'm your peer. - You're my peer.

460
00:20:17,980 --> 00:20:19,710
-我们完全一样  -我们完全一样
- We're exactly the same. - We're exactly the same.

461
00:20:19,710 --> 00:20:20,940
如果两个女孩看见我们走在街上
If two girls saw us walking down the street,

462
00:20:20,940 --> 00:20:21,970
她们会说  看那儿有对双胞胎
they'd say, "Hey, those guys are twins.

463
00:20:21,970 --> 00:20:23,520
-一模一样  -约定作废
- Identical. - Okay, I'm cancelling.

464
00:20:23,520 --> 00:20:25,390
哦不  我去的  我去的
Okay, no, I'm in. I'm in.

465
00:20:25,800 --> 00:20:27,160
我真去的  几点
I'm in. What time?

466
00:20:27,160 --> 00:20:28,520
七点半
7:30.

467
00:20:28,520 --> 00:20:30,860
-你七点半会在那里吗  -好吧  八点
- Are you gonna be there at 7:30?  - OK, eight.

468
00:20:36,350 --> 00:20:38,190
唐娜对那女人说  我才不管你是谁
Donna tells the woman, "I don't care who you are,

469
00:20:38,190 --> 00:20:39,540
你别想动我的葡萄柚
you're not getting my grapefruit."

470
00:20:39,550 --> 00:20:41,100
-然后你做了什么  -我还能做什么
- Then what did you do? - What could I do?

471
00:20:41,100 --> 00:20:42,920
我给了她我的葡萄柚
I gave her my grapefruit.

472
00:20:43,590 --> 00:20:46,100
谢谢  这太棒了  哈维
Thank you. This is great, Harvey.

473
00:20:46,110 --> 00:20:47,640
我们就像一只手上的两根手指
We're like two fingers on the same hand.

474
00:20:47,640 --> 00:20:49,000
只要我是食指
As long as I'm the index.

475
00:20:49,000 --> 00:20:50,730
我认真的  这很不错  
I'm serious, this is nice, you know?

476
00:20:50,730 --> 00:20:53,020
同事  平等
Colleagues. Equals.

477
00:20:54,280 --> 00:20:55,320
朋友
Friends.

478
00:20:55,320 --> 00:20:57,760
作为你的朋友
Well, as a friend,

479
00:20:57,980 --> 00:20:59,680
我要给你看些东西
I want you to see something.

480
00:20:59,770 --> 00:21:01,140
你带了什么
What do you got?

481
00:21:02,770 --> 00:21:04,380
五年前  我请你帮忙
Five years ago, I asked you for help

482
00:21:04,380 --> 00:21:05,580
去调查另一家公司的账本
to look into another firm's books.

483
00:21:05,590 --> 00:21:08,210
事实上  是我们公司的账本
Well, they were our books.

484
00:21:11,060 --> 00:21:13,230
我帮你证明了哈德曼挪用公款
I helped you prove Hardman was embezzling.

485
00:21:13,240 --> 00:21:15,430
你还帮他找了个替死鬼
You also tried to set up a fall guy.

486
00:21:18,760 --> 00:21:19,680
就是我
Me.

487
00:21:19,970 --> 00:21:23,570
“一个蠢货”  我记得是你当时用的词
"A schmuck," I believe, was the term you used at the time.

488
00:21:23,570 --> 00:21:24,760
这是五年前的事情
This was five years ago,

489
00:21:24,760 --> 00:21:26,360
然后你现在才抽出空来告诉我吗
And you're just getting around to telling me now?

490
00:21:26,570 --> 00:21:27,460
我想知道你为什么这么做
I wonder why that is.

491
00:21:27,460 --> 00:21:29,440
我觉得你不应为此受伤害
I didn't see the need for you to be hurt.

492
00:21:29,720 --> 00:21:31,330
对极了  因为我是你的朋友
Right, 'cause I'm your friend.

493
00:21:31,610 --> 00:21:32,870
朋友告诉你真相
A friend tells you the truth,

494
00:21:33,130 --> 00:21:36,420
事实是  哈德曼利用你来掩藏他的罪行
And the truth is, Hardman used you to hide his embezzling,

495
00:21:36,430 --> 00:21:37,820
现在他又在利用你
and he's using you again.

496
00:21:38,050 --> 00:21:39,820
请问这和你现在做的
And how exactly is that different from

497
00:21:39,820 --> 00:21:40,850
有什么本质区别
what you're doing right now?

498
00:21:40,850 --> 00:21:42,150
你不能相信他
You can't trust him.

499
00:21:42,150 --> 00:21:43,290
但是我能相信你吗
But I can trust you?

500
00:21:43,590 --> 00:21:44,870
-当然可以  -得了吧
- Yes, you can. - Oh, please.

501
00:21:45,180 --> 00:21:47,380
我告诉杰西卡你那录音笔的事了吗
Did I tell jessica about your little dictaphone maneuver?

502
00:21:47,380 --> 00:21:48,520
不  你知道你做了什么吗
No, you know what you did?

503
00:21:48,520 --> 00:21:49,370
你凌驾于我之上
You lorded it over my head,

504
00:21:49,370 --> 00:21:51,170
说我欠你一个人情  然后现在你来收人情了
said that I'd owe you, and now you've come to collect.

505
00:21:51,170 --> 00:21:52,030
别浪费口舌了  快去吧
Well, you know what? Go ahead.

506
00:21:52,030 --> 00:21:53,720
去告诉妈妈  跟她告状
Run to Mommy. Tattle.

507
00:21:53,720 --> 00:21:55,150
这都是因为我的那一票吗
I mean, this was about my vote?

508
00:21:55,330 --> 00:21:56,720
如果我投给丹尼尔
If I do vote for Daniel,

509
00:21:56,720 --> 00:21:58,290
杰西卡又准备怎么办呢
what is Jessica gonna do about it?

510
00:22:10,610 --> 00:22:12,620
我找到这间背对莱克斯街的公寓
I found this one that faces away from Lex,

511
00:22:12,620 --> 00:22:13,820
这样她就听不到街上的噪音
so she won't get all the street noise,

512
00:22:13,820 --> 00:22:15,110
我还查过门卫了
and I checked into the doormen.

513
00:22:15,260 --> 00:22:17,760
劳尔在这里干了14年  金波干了17年
Raul's been here 14 years, and Jimbo 17.

514
00:22:18,010 --> 00:22:18,760
金波
Jimbo?

515
00:22:18,990 --> 00:22:20,260
我天生好人缘
People open up to me.

516
00:22:20,860 --> 00:22:22,710
你意下如何
So what do you think?

517
00:22:23,480 --> 00:22:25,000
我觉得…
I think...

518
00:22:26,450 --> 00:22:28,330
我告诉奶奶她今晚有新地方住
Grammy's gonna love it when I tell her

519
00:22:28,330 --> 00:22:29,850
她一定会很高兴的
she has a new place to live tonight.

520
00:22:30,750 --> 00:22:32,590
快来  你还没见过卧室呢
Come on, you haven't even seen the bedroom yet.

521
00:22:35,610 --> 00:22:37,490
-天哪  -我知道
- Holy shit. - I know.

522
00:22:37,490 --> 00:22:38,800
堪称完美  对吧
It's perfect, right?

523
00:22:38,800 --> 00:22:40,630
你只需在这里装上新窗帘
All you need are some new curtains right here.

524
00:22:40,640 --> 00:22:42,900
不  我首先要做的就是铺上美美的地毯
No, the first thing I would do is put down a nice rug.

525
00:22:43,050 --> 00:22:44,300
你要盖住硬木地板
You wanna cover the hardwood?

526
00:22:44,580 --> 00:22:46,440
-只是部分  -那就是小地毯
- Not all of it. - So you mean an area rug.

527
00:22:46,440 --> 00:22:51,010
不  是把地毯铺在部分硬木上
No, I mean, cover an area of the hardwood with a rug.

528
00:22:51,010 --> 00:22:53,080
可以接受  比如一块8x10的剑麻地毯
I can live with that. Like an 8x10 sisal.

529
00:22:53,080 --> 00:22:55,010
-什么麻  -米黄色  粗面的那种
- A whatsal? - The beige, scratchy kind.

530
00:22:55,010 --> 00:22:56,550
粗面的地毯简直是自相矛盾
A scratchy rug defeats its own purpose.

531
00:22:56,550 --> 00:22:58,080
我本来就没打算铺地毯
It wasn't my idea in the first place.

532
00:22:58,080 --> 00:22:59,560
好吧  至于床
Fair enough, but the bed--

533
00:23:00,000 --> 00:23:01,100
就放在这里
The bed goes here.

534
00:23:01,100 --> 00:23:02,880
天哪  你太不懂享受生活了
Oh, my God, you're such a guy.

535
00:23:02,880 --> 00:23:04,640
要是床不放在这里
If the bed doesn't go here,

536
00:23:04,640 --> 00:23:06,610
那这窗户岂不是糟蹋了
then what's the point of even having the window?

537
00:23:06,610 --> 00:23:08,400
反正窗帘也会遮挡住光线的
Yeah, but your curtains cover up the light anyway.

538
00:23:08,400 --> 00:23:09,080
不  那是遮帘
No, that would be shades,

539
00:23:09,080 --> 00:23:11,250
也绝不要用在这间房里
which this room will never, ever have.

540
00:23:11,250 --> 00:23:13,540
过来看看
Look, just come right here.

541
00:23:14,140 --> 00:23:15,380
明白吗
See what I mean?

542
00:23:18,630 --> 00:23:19,910
太美了
Beautiful.

543
00:23:26,510 --> 00:23:27,540
我该去和哈维碰面了
I should go meet Harvey.

544
00:23:27,540 --> 00:23:29,890
-这里太热了  -是啊
- It's really hot in here. - Yeah.

545
00:23:33,490 --> 00:23:34,790
姗姗来迟啊
Nice of you to make it.

546
00:23:35,030 --> 00:23:36,540
抱歉  我和瑞秋有点事
Sorry, I had this thing with Rachel.

547
00:23:36,540 --> 00:23:39,190
约会啊  可真难得
Oh, a date. Isn't that special?

548
00:23:39,410 --> 00:23:41,400
没有你昨晚的约会那么难得
Not as special as your date last night.

549
00:23:41,880 --> 00:23:43,380
路易怎么样  他穿了什么
So how is Louis? What did he wear?

550
00:23:43,580 --> 00:23:45,190
-得手了吗  -狠狠拒绝了我
- Did you get any? - Shut me down.

551
00:23:45,190 --> 00:23:45,990
什么
What?

552
00:23:46,700 --> 00:23:48,360
这下棘手了  我们怎么办
This is serious. What are we gonna do?

553
00:23:48,360 --> 00:23:49,940
不知道  不过我告诉你
I don't know, but I'll tell you one thing--

554
00:23:50,070 --> 00:23:51,660
我不接受拒绝
I'm not taking no for an answer.

555
00:23:51,910 --> 00:23:54,830
不可能  你们要我在节目里当众道歉
No way! You want me to apologize on the air?

556
00:23:55,070 --> 00:23:56,380
还不如扒了我的裤子
Why don't I just drop my pants

557
00:23:56,380 --> 00:23:59,000
-在我屁股上画个小丑  -等官司赢了吧
- and paint a clown on my ass? - Save that for sweeps.

558
00:23:59,000 --> 00:24:00,840
我有名誉有地位  斯佩克特先生
I have a reputation, Mr. Specter.

559
00:24:01,030 --> 00:24:03,900
顺便一提  我不喜欢你在庭上攻击我
And by the way, I don't appreciate you bashing it in court.

560
00:24:03,900 --> 00:24:05,880
我出庭是为了赢案子
Look, I went to court to win the case,

561
00:24:05,880 --> 00:24:07,220
不是保住你的名誉
not protect your reputation.

562
00:24:07,220 --> 00:24:09,500
事实证明你两件事一件都没做到
Yeah, well, turns out you didn't do either one.

563
00:24:09,690 --> 00:24:10,820
给你个建议
Here's a suggestion.

564
00:24:11,050 --> 00:24:13,230
下一次  你在大放厥词之前
Next time, make sure you're actually off the air

565
00:24:13,230 --> 00:24:14,680
先确定没人偷拍
before shooting your mouth off.

566
00:24:15,550 --> 00:24:16,900
我坚持自己说过的话
I stand by what I said.

567
00:24:17,110 --> 00:24:18,710
梭利斯在服用兴奋剂
Solis is doping.

568
00:24:18,710 --> 00:24:21,130
美国棒球右外野手
曾保持赛季最多全垒打纪录达37年

569
00:24:18,710 --> 00:24:21,130
罗杰·马里斯的名字后面有个星号
Roger Maris got an asterisk next to his name.

570
00:24:21,130 --> 00:24:23,720
这家伙也该在名字后面打个星号
This guy deserves an asterisk next to his name,

571
00:24:23,720 --> 00:24:25,210
而且我还要他滚出大联盟
and I want him out of the League.

572
00:24:25,210 --> 00:24:26,950
你又不是职棒大联盟执行长
You're not the Commissioner of Baseball.

573
00:24:26,950 --> 00:24:28,810
执行长绝没有我这样的收视率
Yeah, well, the commissioner could never get my ratings.

574
00:24:28,810 --> 00:24:30,350
-兹林斯基先生  -看见没
- Mr. Zielinski-- - See, finally,

575
00:24:30,350 --> 00:24:31,730
终于有人尊重我了
someone who treats me with respect.

576
00:24:31,730 --> 00:24:32,370
我们不能再声称
We can't claim

577
00:24:32,370 --> 00:24:34,090
你只是表达自我观点了
that you're just offering up opinions anymore.

578
00:24:34,090 --> 00:24:35,730
要是你不道歉的话  我们就得拿出
If you don't apologize, we have to show

579
00:24:35,730 --> 00:24:38,340
你指控梭利斯服用兴奋剂的事实依据
that you have a factual basis for accusing Solis of doping.

580
00:24:38,340 --> 00:24:40,130
-我当然有根据  -那就说出你的消息来源
- Of course I did. - Then give us your source.

581
00:24:40,130 --> 00:24:41,550
要是告诉了你们
What kind of career do you think

582
00:24:41,550 --> 00:24:42,690
我以后还怎么混啊
I'd have if I give that up?

583
00:24:42,890 --> 00:24:44,330
告诉你们  我会一无所有
I'll tell you what-- nonexistent.

584
00:24:44,330 --> 00:24:45,610
正如你的消息来源一样
Exactly like your source.

585
00:24:45,610 --> 00:24:47,020
-哈维  拜托  -够了
- Harvey, please, could-- - That's it.

586
00:24:47,020 --> 00:24:48,630
与其在我拒绝以后还烦着我
Instead of bugging me to give up my guy

587
00:24:48,630 --> 00:24:49,890
叫我告诉你们消息来源是谁
after I already told you no,

588
00:24:49,890 --> 00:24:52,760
不如做好自己的事  给我赢下这场官司
why don't you do your damn job and win this case?

589
00:24:57,180 --> 00:24:59,790
看来“红脸黑脸”没成功啊
Well, looks like good cop, bad cop didn't work.

590
00:24:59,790 --> 00:25:03,340
-事实上  我觉得成功了  -什么意思
- Actually it did...on me. - What are you talking about?

591
00:25:03,560 --> 00:25:05,720
要是他满嘴喷粪  还没有消息来源
If he's full of shit and has no source,

592
00:25:06,010 --> 00:25:08,510
他肯定知道这事在庭上站不住脚
he knows this eventually goes against him in court.

593
00:25:08,510 --> 00:25:09,960
我觉得梭利斯的确在服用兴奋剂
I think Solis is doping.

594
00:25:09,960 --> 00:25:11,310
你可算看透了
Welcome to the party.

595
00:25:11,930 --> 00:25:13,960
而且兹林斯基还是有点原则的
And Zielinski may have some integrity.

596
00:25:13,970 --> 00:25:15,660
你不是说他是个混蛋
I thought you said he was a dick.

597
00:25:16,270 --> 00:25:17,970
要是他真的是在保护自己的消息来源
If he's actually protecting his source,

598
00:25:18,170 --> 00:25:20,040
他就是个有原则的混蛋
he's a dick with a code.

599
00:25:20,240 --> 00:25:21,600
他的原则就是问题所在了
His code is our problem.

600
00:25:22,270 --> 00:25:24,020
要是我们找不到消息来源  就赢不了
If we can't find that source, we can't fix it.

601
00:25:24,200 --> 00:25:25,440
别再想消息来源了
Forget the source.

602
00:25:25,440 --> 00:25:27,930
我们得查清梭利斯是怎么通过兴奋剂测试的
We need to figure out how Solis passed those tests.

603
00:25:27,930 --> 00:25:29,020
我们要怎么查
How are we supposed to do that?

604
00:25:29,020 --> 00:25:30,500
不是我们  是你
Not us, you.

605
00:25:30,720 --> 00:25:32,820
我就是兹林斯基  而你是梭利斯
I'm like Zielinski, you're like Solis.

606
00:25:32,820 --> 00:25:34,290
-我是明星运动员  -你是骗子
- An all-star. - A cheater.

607
00:25:35,400 --> 00:25:36,900
你不会跟律师协会说
You're not gonna tell the bar association

608
00:25:36,900 --> 00:25:38,440
应该在我的名字后面加个星号的  是吧
that I deserve an asterisk, are you?

609
00:25:39,410 --> 00:25:40,660
你给我灵感了
You just gave me a good idea.

610
00:25:41,650 --> 00:25:44,080
最好不要涉及到你跟律师协会说
I hope it doesn't involve you telling the bar association

611
00:25:44,080 --> 00:25:45,280
应该在我的名字后面加个星号
that I deserve an asterisk.

612
00:25:52,750 --> 00:25:54,170
球棒
Oh, a bat.

613
00:25:54,170 --> 00:25:56,180
怎么  如果我不投杰西卡  你就打我吗
What, are you gonna hit me if I don't vote for Jessica?

614
00:25:56,380 --> 00:25:59,370
不  我只是想让你听完我的话再做决定
No, I just wanted you to hear a story before you decided.

615
00:26:01,790 --> 00:26:03,070
继续给哈德曼泼脏水
More dirt on Hardman.

616
00:26:03,560 --> 00:26:04,860
是关于罗杰·马里斯的
The story's about Roger Maris.

617
00:26:05,400 --> 00:26:06,810
怎么  他为哈德曼工作吗
Yeah, what, did he work for Hardman?

618
00:26:09,410 --> 00:26:11,150
他曾为洋基队效力
He used to play for the Yankees.

619
00:26:11,380 --> 00:26:13,470
他打破了贝比·鲁斯创造的本垒打纪录
He beat Babe Ruth's home run record

620
00:26:13,710 --> 00:26:16,470
-用的就是这球棒  -还有道具  真可爱
- with this bat. - You brought a prop. That's really cute.

621
00:26:16,650 --> 00:26:18,550
马里斯在一个较长的赛季做到的
Maris did it in a longer season,

622
00:26:18,720 --> 00:26:21,140
所以人们对此不予承认
so no one really gave him credit for it,

623
00:26:21,150 --> 00:26:23,340
最终以星号特别标记
and it went down in people's minds with an asterisk.

624
00:26:23,500 --> 00:26:26,180
我明白了  所以这是个比喻  真有文采
I see, so it's a parable. How literary of you.

625
00:26:26,180 --> 00:26:29,260
成为高级合伙人是你一辈子的事  路易
Becoming senior partner is your life's work, Louis.

626
00:26:29,260 --> 00:26:30,320
你确定想用投票来换
You really want to buy it with your vote?

627
00:26:30,320 --> 00:26:33,080
让我做合伙人  丹尼尔可没有附加条件
Daniel did not condition my partnership on anything.

628
00:26:33,080 --> 00:26:34,960
有可能  但那也会给你打上星号
Maybe, but it'll always have an asterisk.

629
00:26:34,960 --> 00:26:37,670
知道吗  你怎么就不能明白
You know what? It's like you just can't fathom

630
00:26:37,670 --> 00:26:39,110
这是我应得的
that I actually earned it.

631
00:26:39,110 --> 00:26:41,520
这是不是你应得的  都不是重点
Whether you earned it or not, that's not the point.

632
00:26:41,520 --> 00:26:42,520
这意味着一切
It's everything.

633
00:26:42,520 --> 00:26:45,060
我想说的是  你投给哈德曼
All I am saying is, you vote for Hardman,

634
00:26:45,060 --> 00:26:47,110
所有人都会认为这是交换条件
everyone will see this as quid pro quo.

635
00:26:47,120 --> 00:26:48,660
对  因为你会这么说
Yeah, because you're gonna tell them.

636
00:26:48,670 --> 00:26:49,740
不  我不会这么说
No, I won't tell them.

637
00:26:50,440 --> 00:26:52,610
他们会不由自主的怀疑
They'll wonder about it all on their own,

638
00:26:52,820 --> 00:26:54,100
就想你一样
just like you will.

639
00:26:54,840 --> 00:26:56,410
帮个忙…
Do me a favor right now...

640
00:26:59,040 --> 00:27:00,380
带着你的球棒走开
Take your bat and go.

641
00:27:01,690 --> 00:27:02,730
走
Go.

642
00:27:05,220 --> 00:27:06,710
路易
Louis...

643
00:27:07,630 --> 00:27:09,070
晚饭时你说的是对的
You were right at dinner.

644
00:27:09,580 --> 00:27:12,040
我以前是在利用你  是我不对
I was using you, and I was wrong.

645
00:27:12,430 --> 00:27:13,570
但这个决定
But this decision,

646
00:27:14,560 --> 00:27:15,910
不是关于我
it isn't about me.

647
00:27:16,900 --> 00:27:19,820
你一直被哈德曼压着  你讨厌他
You came up under Hardman. You hated him.

648
00:27:20,770 --> 00:27:22,170
你一直讨厌他
You always hated him.

649
00:27:24,080 --> 00:27:25,550
别让他这么对你
Don't let him do this to you.

650
00:27:25,840 --> 00:27:27,550
我还有其他选择吗  哈维
What's my alternative, Harvey?

651
00:27:27,700 --> 00:27:29,140
杰西卡都不愿给出起码的尊重
Jessica didn't even have the courtesy

652
00:27:29,140 --> 00:27:30,700
亲自找我拉票
to court my vote herself.

653
00:27:31,460 --> 00:27:35,220
而她派你来  猜怎么着
So she sends you. Well, guess what.

654
00:27:35,220 --> 00:27:36,250
你失败了
You failed.

655
00:27:36,520 --> 00:27:38,680
所以现在回去  你告诉她
So go back right now. You tell her,

656
00:27:38,940 --> 00:27:40,820
哈维·斯佩克特  最棒的律师
Harvey Specter, the great closer,

657
00:27:41,530 --> 00:27:42,970
搞不定我
couldn't close me.

658
00:28:05,430 --> 00:28:07,460
你不是应该出门领一个
Aren't you supposed to be off accepting the award

659
00:28:07,460 --> 00:28:08,730
世界最佳外孙奖吗
for world's best grandson?

660
00:28:08,730 --> 00:28:10,250
我不得不取消了
Uh, I had to cancel.

661
00:28:11,450 --> 00:28:13,310
你不是要带她吃晚饭
Weren't you taking her to dinner

662
00:28:13,510 --> 00:28:15,200
告诉她你给她买了套公寓
to tell her about the apartment you bought for her

663
00:28:15,200 --> 00:28:15,970
以此来弥补
to make up for the fact that

664
00:28:15,970 --> 00:28:17,970
你以后没时间带她吃晚饭了吗
you don't have time to take her to dinner anymore?

665
00:28:17,970 --> 00:28:19,270
我跟你说
For your information,

666
00:28:19,270 --> 00:28:21,600
她很高兴我打电话改了时间
she was happy when I called to reschedule.

667
00:28:21,780 --> 00:28:22,830
被放鸽子很高兴
Happy to be stood up.

668
00:28:22,830 --> 00:28:25,260
是很高兴我终于找到了让我忙碌工作
Happy that I have a job that fully engages me.

669
00:28:25,270 --> 00:28:27,400
以前她还担心我找不到活干呢
There was a time she was worried that wouldn't happen.

670
00:28:28,380 --> 00:28:30,270
哈佛法学院还没工作
Despite Harvard Law School?

671
00:28:32,340 --> 00:28:33,980
我是说  进法学院以前
No, I mean, when I was younger.

672
00:28:34,610 --> 00:28:36,020
她说得对  你很幸运
She's right that you're really lucky

673
00:28:36,020 --> 00:28:37,790
你有一份激发能力的工作
you get to do something that challenges you.

674
00:28:38,420 --> 00:28:39,780
我希望我也能有
I hope I have that someday.

675
00:28:39,940 --> 00:28:42,310
瑞秋  我说过  只要你想让我帮你
Rachel, I told you, whenever you want help with--

676
00:28:42,500 --> 00:28:45,680
我的老天  你参加了考试
Holy sh--, you took the LSA--

677
00:28:45,680 --> 00:28:46,860
你参加了入学考试
You took the LSATs?

678
00:28:47,070 --> 00:28:47,990
是的
I did.

679
00:28:47,990 --> 00:28:49,770
考得怎么样
How did you do?

680
00:28:49,770 --> 00:28:51,810
我…不知道
Um... I don't know.

681
00:28:52,100 --> 00:28:54,250
瑞秋  最难的部分你已经跨越了
Rachel, you already did the hard part.

682
00:28:54,250 --> 00:28:56,370
你去参加考试了  打开信封很容易
You took the test. Opening the envelope is easy.

683
00:28:56,370 --> 00:28:58,280
不  之前每次我打开信封都是…
No, every other time I've had to open the envelope--

684
00:28:58,280 --> 00:28:59,640
这次不是以前
This isn't every other time.

685
00:29:02,480 --> 00:29:03,540
我帮你开
Do you want me to open it?

686
00:29:03,950 --> 00:29:05,570
-不要  -你就是想我帮你开
- No. - Yes, you do.

687
00:29:05,970 --> 00:29:09,500
如果低于160
Okay, um, if I score below 160,

688
00:29:09,500 --> 00:29:11,030
你就把它扔掉
then I just want you to throw it away.

689
00:29:11,850 --> 00:29:14,290
也别告诉我  我不想知道  行吗
And don't tell me. I don't want to know, okay?

690
00:29:14,290 --> 00:29:15,490
-好的  -开吧
- Okay. - Okay.

691
00:29:20,880 --> 00:29:24,630
-瑞秋  -我懂了
- Um...Rachel, I'm... - Okay.

692
00:29:27,970 --> 00:29:29,300
172
172.

693
00:29:32,570 --> 00:29:34,390
-172  -你考了172分
- 172? - You got a 172.

694
00:29:34,400 --> 00:29:35,910
-我的天  我考了这么多  -是的
- Oh, my--I did? - Yes.

695
00:29:35,910 --> 00:29:37,420
我的天啊  我的天啊
That's--oh, oh, my god!

696
00:29:37,610 --> 00:29:40,170
我的天  你再敢这么逗我试试
Oh, my God, don't you ever do that to me again.

697
00:29:40,170 --> 00:29:42,840
瑞秋  你要成为律师了
Rachel, you're gonna be a lawyer.

698
00:29:44,120 --> 00:29:45,680
-看看  -天啊
- Look, look at it. - Oh, my God.

699
00:29:45,680 --> 00:29:46,670
看吧
Go.

700
00:29:47,540 --> 00:29:48,790
-彭  -我的天啊
- Bam. - oh, my God.

701
00:29:51,050 --> 00:29:52,170
哥马上就得失业了
I'm gonna be out of a job.

702
00:29:59,400 --> 00:30:00,990
哈维  我找到点东西
Harvey, I think I found something.

703
00:30:00,990 --> 00:30:02,690
这个“东西”  我希望是你找到了
And by "something," I assume you mean

704
00:30:02,690 --> 00:30:05,020
-梭利斯作弊的证据  -算是吧
- how Solis was cheating. - Um, maybe,

705
00:30:05,020 --> 00:30:07,260
但我肯定  我发现了兹林斯基的线人是谁
but I definitely figured out who Zielinski's source is.

706
00:30:07,440 --> 00:30:08,680
好吧  这也算是吧
Well, that counts as something.

707
00:30:08,680 --> 00:30:10,110
他们用录像带  我也用录像带
They used a hot mic, I used a hot mic.

708
00:30:10,110 --> 00:30:11,140
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?

709
00:30:11,140 --> 00:30:12,450
我在兹林斯基在春训时
I found some footage from a segment

710
00:30:12,450 --> 00:30:14,280
拍摄的一段录像中  有所发现
that Zielinski taped at spring training.

711
00:30:14,280 --> 00:30:16,480
制作组已经就位  他在后面
Uh, the crew is setting up, he's in the background,

712
00:30:16,480 --> 00:30:20,070
和鲁本·赫尔南德斯争执着
having a very intense conversation with Ruben Hernandez.

713
00:30:20,080 --> 00:30:21,020
一个二流捕手
Mediocre catcher.

714
00:30:21,020 --> 00:30:24,000
那又怎么样  兹林斯基是体育播报员
So? Zielinski's a sportscaster.

715
00:30:24,000 --> 00:30:25,920
他的工作就是和运动员谈话
Talking to athletes is what he does all day.

716
00:30:25,930 --> 00:30:28,120
他们当时在冬季公园
This conversation took place in Winter Park.

717
00:30:28,660 --> 00:30:30,950
赫尔南德斯应该在另一个地方训练  
Hernandez should have been practicing with his team in...

718
00:30:30,950 --> 00:30:31,870
圣彼得堡
St. Pete.

719
00:30:32,050 --> 00:30:33,040
他不应该在那儿
He never should have been there.

720
00:30:33,040 --> 00:30:33,760
我记得梭利斯待过的
Then I remembered the roster of

721
00:30:33,760 --> 00:30:35,810
每一支球队的花名册
every single team Solis ever played on.

722
00:30:35,810 --> 00:30:37,740
-他们没做过队友  -错了  曾经是队友
- They never played together. - Wrong, they did.

723
00:30:37,740 --> 00:30:39,140
赫尔南德斯还是新秀时
Ten games, three years ago,

724
00:30:39,140 --> 00:30:40,830
三年前  一起打了十场球
Hernandez's rookie year.

725
00:30:40,830 --> 00:30:43,120
所以他让赫尔南德斯替他做测试
So he got Hernandez to take the test for him.

726
00:30:43,360 --> 00:30:44,560
起码是找过他帮忙
Or at least approached him.

727
00:30:44,560 --> 00:30:46,430
因为兹林斯基的指控
Because Zielinski's accusations began

728
00:30:46,430 --> 00:30:48,110
开始与那个录像拍摄的一周后
one week after that tape that I watched.

729
00:30:48,110 --> 00:30:51,270
足够用来查赫尔南德斯告诉他的事了
Enough time for Zielinski to look into whatever Hernandez told him.

730
00:30:51,270 --> 00:30:54,210
而且用公司的手机  给赫尔南德斯打了六次电话
And call him six times from a company-issued cell phone.

731
00:30:54,390 --> 00:30:55,030
逮个正着
Boom!

732
00:30:55,030 --> 00:30:59,270
瞧瞧你  录像带  以牙还牙
Look at you! Hot mic, using their tricks against them.

733
00:30:59,270 --> 00:31:00,560
是的  没啥大不了的
Yeah, it's what we do, no big deal.

734
00:31:00,560 --> 00:31:02,230
让我想起来  不用再教你花招了
Remind me to stop teaching you my tricks.

735
00:31:02,230 --> 00:31:03,560
你还是要用点小花招
Well, you're gonna need one of your tricks.

736
00:31:03,560 --> 00:31:05,390
因为如果兹林斯基不让我们公之于众
Because what good does Zielinski's source do us

737
00:31:05,390 --> 00:31:06,650
知道来源对我们就没有意义了
if he's not going to let us go public?

738
00:31:06,650 --> 00:31:07,890
谁说我们要公之于众了
Who says we have to go public?

739
00:31:08,410 --> 00:31:09,410
我需要你这么做
Here's what I need you to do.

740
00:31:13,440 --> 00:31:14,540
我搞不定他
I couldn't close him.

741
00:31:16,030 --> 00:31:17,280
你是想跟我说
Are you trying to tell me

742
00:31:17,280 --> 00:31:19,480
为了投票  你都不愿意对路易好点吗
you couldn't be nice to Louis even for this?

743
00:31:19,710 --> 00:31:21,040
不是
No, I'm not.

744
00:31:21,250 --> 00:31:23,510
你说我是他心头的刺
You said I'm a thorn in his side.

745
00:31:23,710 --> 00:31:25,600
我想把刺拔了  但是你才是
I tried to take it out, but you're the one

746
00:31:25,600 --> 00:31:27,430
这些年来掌握了一切他想要的
who's had what he's wanted all these years

747
00:31:27,680 --> 00:31:29,800
-但却不给他  -资深合伙人资格
- and didn't give it to him. - Senior partnership.

748
00:31:29,800 --> 00:31:31,360
你得去告诉他  他当得起这个职位
You need to tell him he deserves it.

749
00:31:31,360 --> 00:31:32,620
这是我派给你的任务
That's what I sent you to do.

750
00:31:32,820 --> 00:31:34,050
他要听你亲口说
He needs to hear it from you.

751
00:31:36,190 --> 00:31:38,590
我就让你做一件事  你还做不到
You know, I send you to do this one thing and you can't--

752
00:31:40,530 --> 00:31:42,090
好  我去跟他谈
Fine, I'll talk to him.

753
00:31:43,140 --> 00:31:44,190
等一下
Wait a minute.

754
00:31:44,400 --> 00:31:46,820
你了解他  也了解我
You know him. You knew this.

755
00:31:47,090 --> 00:31:49,280
我俩一直都是这样的
This is where it always ended up.

756
00:31:51,340 --> 00:31:53,310
-被你发现了  -那为什么还先派我去
- You got me. - Why send me first?

757
00:31:53,310 --> 00:31:56,400
因为如果路易不费点功夫把我请过去
Because if Louis didn't have to work to get me there,

758
00:31:56,400 --> 00:31:57,840
他不会相信我的话
he wouldn't believe me when I went.

759
00:31:58,470 --> 00:31:59,680
其他人都在玩跳棋
You're playing chess

760
00:31:59,680 --> 00:32:01,200
你却在下国际象棋
while everybody else is playing checkers.

761
00:32:01,200 --> 00:32:02,800
你才发现吗
Are you just getting that,

762
00:32:02,800 --> 00:32:05,320
纽约最棒的律师先生
Mr. I'm-the-best-closer- this-city's-ever-seen?

763
00:32:05,320 --> 00:32:07,050
是你经常这么叫我的
Hey, you're the one who always calls me that.

764
00:32:07,540 --> 00:32:08,720
也许我不该这么叫
Well, maybe I shouldn't.

765
00:32:09,610 --> 00:32:10,850
恕我失陪了
Now if you'll excuse me,

766
00:32:11,250 --> 00:32:13,600
我现在要去告诉路易当得起资深合伙人
I have to tell Louis he deserves to be senior partner.

767
00:32:13,600 --> 00:32:16,610
我是纽约最棒的律师
You know what, I am the best closer this city's ever seen,

768
00:32:16,830 --> 00:32:19,180
-我在他那却丝毫没有进展  -你想说什么
- And I didn't even make a dent. - Do you have a point?

769
00:32:19,180 --> 00:32:21,000
他需要的不仅仅是花言巧语
He needs more than just words.

770
00:32:21,000 --> 00:32:22,410
我说过了  我不会贿赂他的
I told you, I'm not bribing him.

771
00:32:22,410 --> 00:32:23,680
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.

772
00:32:24,440 --> 00:32:26,120
他的不满很深
His anger is deep.

773
00:32:27,000 --> 00:32:29,710
-他想让我们不爽  -怎么不爽
- He wants us to feel pain. - How?

774
00:32:32,080 --> 00:32:33,080
把我的办公室给他
Give him my office.

775
00:32:35,010 --> 00:32:36,150
你真愿意这么做
You're willing to do that?

776
00:32:36,690 --> 00:32:37,760
记得你问我
Remember when you questioned

777
00:32:37,760 --> 00:32:39,520
会不会将你的利益放在我之上
if I could put your needs above mine?

778
00:32:40,690 --> 00:32:41,720
这就是你要的答案
Here's your answer.

779
00:32:44,230 --> 00:32:46,450
梭利斯先生  你的铁杆粉丝
Mr. Solis, big fan.

780
00:32:46,450 --> 00:32:47,830
-能给我签个名吗  -当然可以
- Can I get an autograph? - Sure, buddy.

781
00:32:47,830 --> 00:32:50,760
你能不能签“罗伯托·梭利斯  类固醇服用者”
Can you just sign it "Roberto Solis, steroid user"?

782
00:32:50,760 --> 00:32:51,630
什么
What?

783
00:32:51,820 --> 00:32:53,430
我是托尼· 兹林斯基的律师
I represent Tony Zielinski.

784
00:32:53,430 --> 00:32:55,020
我的律师不在  你不能和我讲话
You can't talk to me without my lawyer.

785
00:32:55,020 --> 00:32:56,100
说得对  我是不能
Ah, you're right, I can't.

786
00:32:56,100 --> 00:32:57,970
你去告我啊  到时候
You go ahead and turn me in. When you do,

787
00:32:58,280 --> 00:33:00,160
我就告诉他们兹林斯基的线人
I'll tell them all about Zielinski's source

788
00:33:00,160 --> 00:33:01,680
-就在你的俱乐部  -放屁
- inside your clubhouse. - Bullshit.

789
00:33:02,420 --> 00:33:03,720
棒球队就是兄弟连
Baseball is a brotherhood.

790
00:33:03,870 --> 00:33:05,490
我队里没人会出卖我
Nobody on my team would go public against me.

791
00:33:05,690 --> 00:33:08,030
但鲁本·赫尔南德斯已经不是你的队友了
But Ruben Hernandez isn't on your team anymore.

792
00:33:09,850 --> 00:33:11,750
如果鲁本会出卖以前的队友
If Ruben tries ratting out a former teammate,

793
00:33:12,150 --> 00:33:13,740
没有一个俱乐部会原谅他
no ball club in this league will forgive him.

794
00:33:13,740 --> 00:33:15,740
如果我们传讯他  他也别无选择
He might not have a choice when we subpoena him.

795
00:33:16,000 --> 00:33:17,400
不  不可能
No, no way.

796
00:33:17,630 --> 00:33:19,720
如果兹林斯基要放弃鲁本  他早就弃了
If Zielinski's giving up Ruben, he'd have done it already.

797
00:33:20,010 --> 00:33:21,410
他可能不想  但我会
He might not, but I will.

798
00:33:23,260 --> 00:33:24,770
你要被夹杀出局了  罗伯托
You're in a rundown, Roberto.

799
00:33:25,330 --> 00:33:27,850
撤销诉讼  宣布退役吧
Drop the suit and announce your retirement from baseball.

800
00:33:28,080 --> 00:33:29,790
-你脑子没进水吧  -按照我说的做
- Are you out of your mind? - You do it,

801
00:33:29,800 --> 00:33:32,260
兹林斯基再也不会提到你的名字
Zielinski will never mention your name on air again.

802
00:33:32,520 --> 00:33:34,740
不这么做  赫尔南德斯告发你
You don't, Hernandez outs you,

803
00:33:34,740 --> 00:33:36,390
全世界都会知道你的做得好事
and the whole world knows who you are.

804
00:33:45,350 --> 00:33:46,960
路易  你有时间吗
Louis, got a minute?

805
00:33:46,960 --> 00:33:48,500
有点小忙  你说吧
I'm a little busy, but sure.

806
00:33:48,780 --> 00:33:50,130
我活该
I deserve that.

807
00:33:50,610 --> 00:33:53,430
资深合伙人摆点架子是正常的
A little payback among senior partners is fair play.

808
00:33:55,020 --> 00:33:56,040
接着说
I'm listening.

809
00:33:57,210 --> 00:34:00,580
我就不拐弯抹角地挖苦你了
I'm not going to insult you by beating around the bush,

810
00:34:00,580 --> 00:34:01,900
我们开诚布公的谈谈吧
So let's talk about the elephant in the room.

811
00:34:02,430 --> 00:34:03,500
你想要什么
What's it gonna take?

812
00:34:03,660 --> 00:34:05,750
我对事务所一直无私奉献
My dedication to this firm knows no limits.

813
00:34:05,980 --> 00:34:08,800
我想要的  我只想要
And what I ask in return-- all I ask in return--

814
00:34:08,800 --> 00:34:09,730
被重视
is to be valued,

815
00:34:09,730 --> 00:34:10,830
让我相信有人
for someone to make me believe that

816
00:34:10,830 --> 00:34:12,250
认为我干得不错
they think that I'm great at what I do.

817
00:34:12,750 --> 00:34:13,750
这不是问题
Then we're all set.

818
00:34:14,390 --> 00:34:15,750
因为我一直这么认为
Because I've always felt that way.

819
00:34:15,750 --> 00:34:16,990
在哈维的案子上
That's not the way you made it seem

820
00:34:16,990 --> 00:34:18,040
大家并不觉得你是这样的
to everyone at Harvey's trial.

821
00:34:18,220 --> 00:34:19,360
路易  那是在模拟法庭
Louis, we were at trial.

822
00:34:19,570 --> 00:34:21,610
我在努力赢官司  和你一样
I was trying to make my case, same as you.

823
00:34:23,590 --> 00:34:24,800
你做得不错
Well, you did a good job.

824
00:34:27,640 --> 00:34:31,480
因为那个杰西卡  我完全相信她
Because that Jessica, I got no trouble believing.

825
00:34:31,480 --> 00:34:33,580
但那个天天牵着我鼻子走的杰西卡
But the Jessica that kept stringing me along,

826
00:34:33,580 --> 00:34:35,200
一遍遍的告诉我  有一天我终究会出头
telling me, one day, my time would come--

827
00:34:35,360 --> 00:34:36,590
那个人  我不相信
Her, I've come to doubt.

828
00:34:36,810 --> 00:34:38,590
我一向和直言不讳  路易
I've always been straight with you, Louis.

829
00:34:39,640 --> 00:34:41,590
我对你的话是真心诚意的
My message has never wavered.

830
00:34:41,820 --> 00:34:42,730
这包括你通过哈维
Does that include the message

831
00:34:42,730 --> 00:34:43,740
传达给我的话吗
that you sent to me through Harvey?

832
00:34:43,740 --> 00:34:45,010
哈维先来找你
Harvey came to you first

833
00:34:45,170 --> 00:34:46,320
是因为我想让你知道
because I wanted you to know

834
00:34:46,320 --> 00:34:48,550
我们都很看重你
that you are valuable to both of us.

835
00:34:48,560 --> 00:34:49,920
才不是  只有对我有所求时
No, there's only an "us"

836
00:34:49,920 --> 00:34:51,160
才有“我们”一说
when you want something from me.

837
00:34:51,160 --> 00:34:53,850
其他情况下  我是只能艳羡的旁观者
The rest of the time, it's me on the outside, looking in.

838
00:34:54,010 --> 00:34:55,470
你现在是资深合伙人了
Well, you're a senior partner now.

839
00:34:55,710 --> 00:34:57,580
你也是局内人
You're as on the inside as it gets.

840
00:34:57,580 --> 00:34:59,210
可不是  多谢了哈德曼
That's right, thanks to Hardman.

841
00:34:59,210 --> 00:35:00,530
你以为他重视你
You think he's valuing you.

842
00:35:01,390 --> 00:35:02,700
他是在贿赂你
He's buying you...

843
00:35:03,090 --> 00:35:06,360
在这关键时候  做顺水人情
with this one thing at this convenient time.

844
00:35:06,360 --> 00:35:08,900
你不明白  哈德曼真的懂我
You don't get it. Hardman actually sees me.

845
00:35:09,330 --> 00:35:11,480
而你  我永远是哈维这棵巨树下
With you, I'll always be this mushroom

846
00:35:11,480 --> 00:35:12,980
不起眼的小草
in the shadow of Harvey's tree.

847
00:35:13,170 --> 00:35:14,480
你在说什么  路易
What are you saying, Louis?

848
00:35:14,480 --> 00:35:16,590
我说  该让哈维活在我的阴影下了
I'm saying it's time you put Harvey in my shadow.

849
00:35:16,790 --> 00:35:19,040
那你又具体想让我怎么做
And how exactly would you like me to do that?

850
00:35:19,040 --> 00:35:20,660
我哪知道  你自己想去
You know, I don't know. You figure it out.

851
00:35:20,870 --> 00:35:22,110
不然  搞不准什么时候
Otherwise, maybe one of these days,

852
00:35:22,110 --> 00:35:22,940
你也要尝尝
you'll see what it's like to be

853
00:35:22,940 --> 00:35:24,340
这默默无闻的滋味
in someone's shadow for a while.

854
00:35:27,720 --> 00:35:28,920
你知道吗  路易
You know what, Louis?

855
00:35:30,810 --> 00:35:34,970
哈维让我把他的办公室给你
Harvey told me that I should give you his office.

856
00:35:35,490 --> 00:35:37,700
我来这就是准备这么做的
And I came in here prepared to do just that.

857
00:35:38,130 --> 00:35:39,750
但我可不向威胁妥协
But I don't respond to threats,

858
00:35:39,950 --> 00:35:41,620
也不会买通你这一票
and I'm not going to buy your vote

859
00:35:41,620 --> 00:35:42,750
因为那不是我的风格
because that's not who I am.

860
00:35:43,400 --> 00:35:44,290
但你记住
But know this:

861
00:35:44,960 --> 00:35:46,100
我会赢
I will win.

862
00:35:47,310 --> 00:35:49,500
而待明天投票结束
And tomorrow, after the vote,

863
00:35:49,510 --> 00:35:51,390
若你站错了队伍
if you are on the wrong side,

864
00:35:51,390 --> 00:35:53,690
可没有后悔药
there'll be no coming back.

865
00:36:18,570 --> 00:36:19,570
你偷公司的钱时
When you stole from this firm,

866
00:36:19,570 --> 00:36:20,900
有没有做手脚来遮掩
did you do anything to cover your tracks?

867
00:36:23,570 --> 00:36:25,310
我就知道他们留着这一手
I should have known they had this in their pocket.

868
00:36:25,310 --> 00:36:26,420
这么说你不否认
So you don't deny it.

869
00:36:26,570 --> 00:36:28,530
我不会侮辱你的智商
I wouldn't insult your intelligence.

870
00:36:28,760 --> 00:36:31,260
我相信他们给你看过证据
I'm sure they came to you armed with proof,

871
00:36:31,260 --> 00:36:33,210
而你比我更会追踪资金流动
and you followed the numbers better than I ever could.

872
00:36:33,210 --> 00:36:35,240
-为什么  -我能给的最委婉的回答
- Why? - The best I can offer you

873
00:36:35,240 --> 00:36:36,650
就是那事不含个人恩怨
is that it wasn't personal.

874
00:36:36,800 --> 00:36:39,600
只是鉴于你十分擅长金融
It was just that, given your financial expertise,

875
00:36:39,790 --> 00:36:41,990
我觉得你是合适的替罪羊
I thought you would seem plausible.

876
00:36:42,550 --> 00:36:43,450
替罪羊
"Plausible."

877
00:36:43,820 --> 00:36:45,440
明显  我的计划是
Obviously my plan was that

878
00:36:45,440 --> 00:36:47,970
一开始就没人会发现钱丢了
nobody would notice the money was missing in the first place.

879
00:36:48,130 --> 00:36:51,270
-我就是你的备胎  -可以这么说  路易
- So I was plan "B." - I suppose so, Louis.

880
00:36:51,270 --> 00:36:53,050
-我很抱歉  -抱个头
- I'm sorry. - You're sor--

881
00:36:55,240 --> 00:36:57,400
你没意识到你可能会毁了我的职业生涯
Do you realize you could have destroyed my entire career?

882
00:36:58,410 --> 00:36:59,840
甚至害我入狱
Maybe even sent me to prison.

883
00:37:01,550 --> 00:37:02,780
这么跟你说吧
And you know what?

884
00:37:04,310 --> 00:37:05,500
我可不关心
I didn't care.

885
00:37:06,310 --> 00:37:07,560
这就是实话
That's the truth.

886
00:37:09,210 --> 00:37:10,810
你还希望我投你一票吗
And you want me to vote for you?

887
00:37:14,610 --> 00:37:15,990
你当时喜欢我这个人吗
Did you like me back then?

888
00:37:16,300 --> 00:37:17,470
我也不喜欢你
I didn't.

889
00:37:17,670 --> 00:37:20,350
五年前的我不应该做执行合伙人
The man I was five years ago shouldn't be managing partner.

890
00:37:20,350 --> 00:37:21,460
甚至不该在这工作
He shouldn't even work here.

891
00:37:22,160 --> 00:37:23,600
但我不是那个人了
But I'm not that man.

892
00:37:23,830 --> 00:37:25,970
如果你不认同  不要投票给我
If you think otherwise, don't vote for me.

893
00:37:26,350 --> 00:37:27,280
是啊
Right.

894
00:37:29,100 --> 00:37:30,260
若我不支持你
And if I don't support you,

895
00:37:30,260 --> 00:37:32,340
我的资深合伙人不会飞了吗
what happens to my senior partnership?

896
00:37:33,370 --> 00:37:35,500
难道你认为我让你做资深合伙人
Do you think my making you senior partner

897
00:37:35,500 --> 00:37:37,400
是以你的票为条件的吗
is conditioned on my having your vote?

898
00:37:39,070 --> 00:37:41,670
-不是吗  -路易  我很失望
- Wasn't it? - Louis, I'm disappointed.

899
00:37:41,860 --> 00:37:45,640
你这么看不起自己  我很失望
I'm disappointed you think so little of yourself.

900
00:37:46,140 --> 00:37:48,740
你在哈维的模拟审时  辩得杰西卡哑口无言
I saw the way you dominated Jessica at Harvey's trial

901
00:37:48,740 --> 00:37:50,300
却因为小手段输了
and lost because of some trick.

902
00:37:51,340 --> 00:37:52,470
你觉得我让她哑口无言吗
You thought I dominated?

903
00:37:52,690 --> 00:37:54,430
我给予你的  是你应得的
I offered you what I thought you deserved.

904
00:37:54,430 --> 00:37:56,260
不多  也不少
No more, no less.

905
00:37:57,140 --> 00:37:58,530
我不求任何回报
I ask for nothing in return

906
00:37:58,530 --> 00:37:59,890
只要你凭良心投票
but that you vote your conscience.

907
00:38:05,980 --> 00:38:07,170
路易
Louis...

908
00:38:09,030 --> 00:38:10,380
不要怀疑自己
Don't doubt yourself.

909
00:38:19,460 --> 00:38:20,690
我有好消息
I've got good news.

910
00:38:20,840 --> 00:38:23,150
梭利斯不仅同意撤诉
Solis has not only agreed to drop the suit,

911
00:38:23,150 --> 00:38:25,080
而且还会退出联赛
but to retire from the game as well.

912
00:38:25,350 --> 00:38:27,810
看样子你不是我想的那么烂嘛
Well, maybe you're not the asshole I thought you were.

913
00:38:27,810 --> 00:38:28,890
我还没说完
I'm not done yet.

914
00:38:29,180 --> 00:38:30,050
相应的
In return...

915
00:38:30,530 --> 00:38:32,470
你不能再在节目上谈起他
you're never gonna talk about him again on the air.

916
00:38:33,770 --> 00:38:36,600
就让他保全名誉  全身而退吗
So he walks away with his reputation intact?

917
00:38:36,810 --> 00:38:38,460
-协议如此  -不不  不行
- That's the deal. - No, no, no, no.

918
00:38:38,460 --> 00:38:39,360
你明知我是对的
You know I'm right,

919
00:38:39,360 --> 00:38:40,830
还想我在已经抓到把柄时
and you want me to step off the gas

920
00:38:40,830 --> 00:38:42,930
放他一马吗  别做梦了
right when I got him? Screw that.

921
00:38:43,400 --> 00:38:44,970
想知道我怎么知道你是对的吗
You want to know how I know you're right?

922
00:38:45,940 --> 00:38:46,960
迈克
Mike?

923
00:38:48,210 --> 00:38:49,910
我相信你认识鲁本·赫尔南德斯
I believe you know Ruben Hernandez.

924
00:38:50,220 --> 00:38:52,350
你保证不会告诉任何人  我是线人
You promised you wouldn't tell anyone I was your source.

925
00:38:52,360 --> 00:38:53,360
我没告诉他们  绝没有
I didn't tell them. I didn't.

926
00:38:53,360 --> 00:38:55,430
-你放屁  -迈克  带他离开
- Bullshit! - Mike, get him out of here.

927
00:38:55,430 --> 00:38:57,160
我保证我们会解决的  走吧
I promise we'll fix this. Come on.

928
00:38:58,560 --> 00:39:00,710
狗娘养的  你不该帮我的吗
You son of a bitch! You're supposed to be on my side.

929
00:39:00,710 --> 00:39:02,340
我这就是在帮你
This is me being on your side.

930
00:39:02,340 --> 00:39:03,840
你要想在法庭里赢
You make me win this in court,

931
00:39:03,840 --> 00:39:06,270
我就得让鲁本出庭作证
I'll have to do it by making Ruben testify.

932
00:39:06,280 --> 00:39:08,650
让梭利斯身败名裂的代价
So the cost of ruining Solis' reputation

933
00:39:08,650 --> 00:39:10,090
将是这孩子的职业前途
will be that kid's career.

934
00:39:10,280 --> 00:39:12,970
另外  所有人都会像他那么想
And by the way, everyone will think the same as he does.

935
00:39:12,970 --> 00:39:14,830
你为了自保而供出了他
You gave him up to save your own ass.

936
00:39:14,830 --> 00:39:16,300
-不是这样的  -事实不重要
- That's a lie. - Doesn't matter.

937
00:39:16,300 --> 00:39:17,320
大家还是会这么想
They'll think it anyway.

938
00:39:17,320 --> 00:39:18,980
可是  注意了  这只是一家之言
But hey, that's just one man's opinion.

939
00:39:19,180 --> 00:39:20,580
想保护你的线人吗
You want to protect your source?

940
00:39:20,900 --> 00:39:21,870
签了协议
Take the deal.

941
00:39:23,910 --> 00:39:25,310
-怎样  -他答应了
- So? - He took the deal.

942
00:39:25,310 --> 00:39:27,250
-我们跟那混蛋两清了  -“混蛋”
- We're done with that asshole. - "Asshole"?

943
00:39:27,250 --> 00:39:29,890
不至于吧  他只是在保卫棒球的清白
Come on, he's just protecting the church of baseball.

944
00:39:29,890 --> 00:39:32,450
关于棒球运动的电影  蒂姆·罗宾斯是主演之一

945
00:39:29,890 --> 00:39:30,940
你准备来现实版《百万金臂》吗
You going Bull Durham on me?

946
00:39:30,940 --> 00:39:32,450
正是  我是蒂姆·罗宾斯
Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm Tim Robbins,

947
00:39:32,450 --> 00:39:34,850
注定会被大球队挖走的神投手
the hotshot pitcher who's destined for the majors,

948
00:39:34,850 --> 00:39:37,420
而你是那个奋斗无果的老男人
and you're that old man who never really made it there.

949
00:39:37,710 --> 00:39:38,430
你知道罗宾斯
You know Robbins wore

950
00:39:38,430 --> 00:39:39,880
在那部电影里  穿女性内衣吧
women's underwear in that movie, right?

951
00:39:39,880 --> 00:39:41,830
苏珊·萨兰登是此电影的女主演

952
00:39:39,880 --> 00:39:41,830
知道  他还跟苏珊·萨兰登有一腿
Yeah, after he slept with Susan Sarandon.

953
00:39:42,140 --> 00:39:42,930
不错啊
Good one.

954
00:39:43,110 --> 00:39:45,250
但你再敢叫我老男人
But if you ever call kevin costner an old man again,

955
00:39:45,250 --> 00:39:46,860
-就别想拿奖金了  -好吧
- you won't get another bonus. - Okay.

956
00:39:47,160 --> 00:39:48,650
对了  我的天  奖金
Whoa, my god, bonus.

957
00:39:48,900 --> 00:39:51,030
哈维  抱歉  我得去见我奶奶
Harvey, I'm sorry, I've got to go see my grandmother.

958
00:39:51,030 --> 00:39:54,070
好  你就去吧  我可不想她觉得我难缠
Fine, go, I wouldn't want her to think I was a hardass.

959
00:39:57,100 --> 00:39:58,580
诽谤案搞定了吗
Did you get rid of that libel case?

960
00:39:58,580 --> 00:40:00,630
哥毫无压力
Score one for free press.

961
00:40:00,630 --> 00:40:02,070
看你又找回水准了  很好
Good to see you back in stride.

962
00:40:02,620 --> 00:40:03,960
我什么时候没有了
When was I ever off?

963
00:40:04,160 --> 00:40:05,550
杰西卡  你有时间吗
Jessica, do you have a moment?

964
00:40:05,550 --> 00:40:08,210
当然  路易  哈维  让我们单独说会
Of course, Louis. Harvey, will you give us a sec?

965
00:40:08,210 --> 00:40:09,260
得了吧  不要来这套了
Oh, please, what, are you kidding?

966
00:40:09,260 --> 00:40:10,790
好像你俩间还有秘密似的
Not like there's any secrets between you two.

967
00:40:12,270 --> 00:40:14,590
好吧  我们听着呢
Well, we're listening.

968
00:40:15,630 --> 00:40:18,140
鉴于当下你是执行合伙人
I'm presenting my partnership buy-in check

969
00:40:18,150 --> 00:40:20,200
我把入股金的支票给你
to you in your current capacity as managing partner.

970
00:40:22,000 --> 00:40:23,060
“当下”啊
"Current."

971
00:40:23,610 --> 00:40:26,250
你是在含蓄地让我投你的票吗
Oh, is that your cryptic way of asking about my vote?

972
00:40:27,290 --> 00:40:28,970
你让我等了五年
You kept me waiting five years.

973
00:40:29,520 --> 00:40:31,150
你就再等上24小时吧
You can wait another 24 hours.

974
00:40:52,930 --> 00:40:54,120
惊喜吧
Surprise!

975
00:40:55,580 --> 00:40:57,690
瑞秋  你来这里干什么
Rachel...hey, what are you doing here?

976
00:40:57,690 --> 00:40:58,300
进来吧
Come in.

977
00:41:03,050 --> 00:41:06,980
迈克  有人一直打到公司来找你
Mike, someone kept calling the office for you.

978
00:41:07,230 --> 00:41:09,220
是养老院的
It was the nursing home and...

979
00:41:10,960 --> 00:41:13,840
我猜  这是他们有的紧急联系号码
I guess--I guess that's the emergency number they had.

980
00:41:14,530 --> 00:41:16,090
什么
Um...what?

981
00:41:18,170 --> 00:41:19,320
是你奶奶
It's your grandma.

982
00:41:20,910 --> 00:41:22,260
她去世了
She passed away.

983
00:41:25,290 --> 00:41:27,830
不会  不会  她…
No. No, she's--

984
00:41:29,670 --> 00:41:31,460
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.

985
00:41:35,030 --> 00:41:36,290
但是..
But...

986
00:41:39,100 --> 00:41:42,510
她甚至没来得及…  看看…
She didn't even get to... to see...

987
00:41:43,950 --> 00:41:45,140
我明白
I know.

988
00:41:45,140 --> 00:41:46,470
我…
I-I'm--

989
00:41:46,710 --> 00:41:47,800
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.

990
00:41:56,590 --> 00:41:58,070
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.

