1
00:05:35,750 --> 00:05:40,750
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:05:35,750 --> 00:05:40,750
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:05:35,750 --> 00:05:40,750
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:05:35,750 --> 00:05:40,750
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:05:35,750 --> 00:05:40,750
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:05:40,750 --> 00:05:45,750
{\an8}翻译：草草  潇湘月影  爱卿遛小鸟  王大可  香茗小焙  某羽  Reginamoon

7
00:05:45,750 --> 00:05:50,750
{\an8}翻译：小饭   鱼小姐啦   CS漫画家小明   校对：杳杳君    潇湘月影

8
00:05:50,750 --> 00:05:55,750
{\an8}时间轴：阿丹    猫   大鲧治水

9
00:05:55,750 --> 00:06:00,750
{\an8}后期：斯人&加森      精校&总监：某羽

10
00:06:01,660 --> 00:06:03,790
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

11
00:06:01,660 --> 00:06:03,790
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第四集

12
00:00:01,050 --> 00:00:02,410
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
Previously on Suits

13
00:00:02,410 --> 00:00:03,000
沃尔特
Walter...

14
00:00:03,000 --> 00:00:04,640
我不能保证我们会赢
I can't guarantee you we'll win,

15
00:00:05,050 --> 00:00:08,090
但我能保证我永远不会出卖你
but I can guarantee you that I will never sell you out.

16
00:00:08,150 --> 00:00:09,800
你曾经和我说迈克·罗斯不是威胁
You told me that Mike Ross wasn't a threat,

17
00:00:09,800 --> 00:00:11,600
然后他申请到临时禁令让我们束手束脚
and then he handcuffed us with a T.R.O.

18
00:00:11,600 --> 00:00:13,640
我要他放弃竞标的证据
I want proof that he's giving up his bid,

19
00:00:13,640 --> 00:00:14,870
如果今天上午没拿到
and if I don't get it by the morning,

20
00:00:14,870 --> 00:00:16,440
我会找我的私家侦探
I'm gonna call my private investigators,

21
00:00:16,440 --> 00:00:18,090
做我一开始要做的事
and I'm gonna finish what I started.

22
00:00:18,090 --> 00:00:19,390
哈维跟你说什么了
What did Harvey tell you?

23
00:00:19,540 --> 00:00:21,250
看来他说的是事实
Looks like he told me the truth.

24
00:00:21,250 --> 00:00:22,160
我们到此为止
We're done.

25
00:00:22,420 --> 00:00:24,570
我希望你能停止对迈克进行个人攻击
I want you to stop the personal attacks on Mike.

26
00:00:24,570 --> 00:00:26,250
你告诉我说这没问题的
You told me this wasn't gonna be a problem.

27
00:00:26,250 --> 00:00:27,980
我要你停手
You don't have to stop this

28
00:00:27,980 --> 00:00:29,880
不是因为你已经改过自新
because you're some changed man.

29
00:00:29,880 --> 00:00:31,880
我要你停手  因为你欠我的
You have to stop this, because you owe me.

30
00:00:31,880 --> 00:00:34,090
罗斯先生  我是埃里克·伍德尔
Mr. Ross, Eric Woodall.

31
00:00:34,390 --> 00:00:35,260
我是联邦检察官...
I'm the U.S. Attorney--

32
00:00:35,260 --> 00:00:36,680
负责纽约南部地区
For the southern district of New York.

33
00:00:36,680 --> 00:00:37,560
我知道你是哪位
Yeah, I know who you are.

34
00:00:37,560 --> 00:00:40,790
什么时候证监会开始通过盯上客户
Since when does the S.E.C. go around intimidating law firms

35
00:00:40,790 --> 00:00:42,250
来威胁律所了
by going after their clients?

36
00:00:42,250 --> 00:00:43,260
现在还没有  但等下周
They don't, but they will

37
00:00:43,270 --> 00:00:45,520
埃里克·伍德尔上任就会了
when Eric Woodall starts there next week.

38
00:00:46,250 --> 00:00:48,800
七名客户  七张传票
Seven clients, seven subpoenas,

39
00:00:48,800 --> 00:00:50,280
明天都会到
all coming tomorrow.

40
00:01:09,530 --> 00:01:10,800
抱歉  你没有预约
Uh, excuse me, you don't have an appointment.

41
00:01:10,800 --> 00:01:12,040
我不需要
I don't need an appointment.

42
00:01:12,070 --> 00:01:13,840
坐下  闭嘴  听好
Sit down, shut up, and listen.

43
00:01:14,340 --> 00:01:16,830
哈维或许因为你归还了唱片而原谅你了
Harvey might forgive you because you returned those recordings,

44
00:01:16,830 --> 00:01:17,540
但我没有
but I don't.

45
00:01:17,540 --> 00:01:18,660
-唐娜  -没说完
- Donna. - Not done.

46
00:01:18,930 --> 00:01:21,270
哈维对付吉利斯虽然狠
What Harvey did with Gillis, it was harsh,

47
00:01:21,310 --> 00:01:24,190
但你居然利用我们私下谈话的内容
but using what I told you in a private conversation--

48
00:01:24,200 --> 00:01:26,250
这突破了一道哈维都不会跨越的底线
that crosses a line that even Harvey never would.

49
00:01:26,250 --> 00:01:27,710
-唐娜  -还是没说完
- Donna. - Still not done.

50
00:01:28,100 --> 00:01:30,650
你离开公司  也离开了我
When you left our firm, you left me too,

51
00:01:31,060 --> 00:01:33,410
但我真心以为我们永远是朋友
but I honestly thought that we'd always be friends.

52
00:01:33,620 --> 00:01:35,210
现在  我不太确定了
Now I'm not so sure.

53
00:01:36,660 --> 00:01:38,620
艾米  你把包裹寄给唐娜了吗
Amy, did you send Donna the package?

54
00:01:38,620 --> 00:01:40,270
愧疚礼物  我没看
Guilt gift. Didn't open it.

55
00:01:40,380 --> 00:01:42,700
是一款巴黎世家的包包
It was a Balenciaga Classic Town bag.

56
00:01:42,700 --> 00:01:43,370
象牙白的吗
Ivory?

57
00:01:43,370 --> 00:01:45,020
炭黑色  有贴袋
Anthracite with an outside pocket.

58
00:01:45,020 --> 00:01:46,200
他的主意还是你的
His idea or yours?

59
00:01:46,200 --> 00:01:47,310
别回答
Don't answer that.

60
00:01:47,310 --> 00:01:48,400
肯定是你的
It was yours.

61
00:01:50,730 --> 00:01:51,890
对不起  唐娜
I'm sorry, Donna.

62
00:01:52,210 --> 00:01:53,670
你和哈维想打个头破血流
You and Harvey want to knock each other out,

63
00:01:53,670 --> 00:01:54,820
我不拦你
you go right ahead.

64
00:01:55,630 --> 00:01:57,310
但不许再背叛我
But don't ever betray me again.

65
00:02:00,290 --> 00:02:01,530
鞋不错
Nice shoes.

66
00:02:05,220 --> 00:02:07,000
她比我想的还厉害
She's even better than I imagined.

67
00:02:19,310 --> 00:02:20,370
在找这个吗
Looking for this?

68
00:02:22,190 --> 00:02:23,840
哈维·斯佩克特
Harvey Specter.

69
00:02:24,520 --> 00:02:27,060
你早晨7点跑来蒙特克莱尔干什么
What brings you to Montclair at 7:00 in the morning?

70
00:02:27,060 --> 00:02:28,870
这你很清楚
Oh, you know what brings me here.

71
00:02:28,990 --> 00:02:31,960
我一醒来发现这些在我门垫上
I woke up to find these on my welcome mat.

72
00:02:32,350 --> 00:02:34,390
虽然我很希望是我传唤了
Well, as much as I'd love to have been responsible

73
00:02:34,390 --> 00:02:37,420
你们律所的7位客户
for subpoenaing seven of your firm's top clients,

74
00:02:37,420 --> 00:02:39,840
但这事我也是现在才知道
I didn't even know about this till just now.

75
00:02:39,840 --> 00:02:42,280
你都没种直接冲我来
You didn't even have the balls to come at me directly.

76
00:02:42,280 --> 00:02:43,470
给我滚
Get off my property.

77
00:02:43,470 --> 00:02:44,670
怎么了  埃里克
What's the matter, Eric?

78
00:02:44,670 --> 00:02:46,540
怕我会第二次害你被炒吗
You're afraid I'll get you fired again?

79
00:02:47,750 --> 00:02:48,680
我懂
I get it.

80
00:02:49,510 --> 00:02:52,300
你想听我说我在利用我的新职位
You want to hear me say I'm using my new position

81
00:02:52,300 --> 00:02:53,860
毁掉你们律所
to destroy your business,

82
00:02:54,050 --> 00:02:56,700
因为就是你这人渣害我被炒
'cause you're the piece of garbage that got me fired.

83
00:02:57,170 --> 00:02:58,620
你不是就想听我说这个吗
Isn't that what you want to hear me say?

84
00:02:58,620 --> 00:03:00,550
我知道你不会说出来的
Oh, I know you'll never say that,

85
00:03:00,590 --> 00:03:01,950
但我想听你承认
but I do want you to admit that 

86
00:03:01,950 --> 00:03:04,660
你派了个代理人  布莱恩·哈里斯找我们麻烦
you sent an agent Brian Harris after my firm.

87
00:03:04,660 --> 00:03:07,750
抱歉  那个部门根本不归我管
Sorry. I don't even have jurisdiction over that department.

88
00:03:07,750 --> 00:03:10,410
那个部门的负责人是肖恩·卡荷尔
That department's run by a man name Sean Cahill.

89
00:03:10,410 --> 00:03:11,660
那么是肖恩·卡荷尔
So all on his own,

90
00:03:11,670 --> 00:03:14,300
他自己想针对我们公司喽
Sean Cahill just happened to target my firm?

91
00:03:14,300 --> 00:03:16,420
他的确是个厉害的法律人
Well, he is a killer attorney

92
00:03:16,470 --> 00:03:18,800
很善于发现流氓律师
with a nose for sleazy lawyers,

93
00:03:19,470 --> 00:03:20,130
这我最清楚了
and I should know.

94
00:03:20,130 --> 00:03:22,490
我们当初一起在司法部门任职过
We came up together at the justice department.

95
00:03:22,490 --> 00:03:24,750
就是庇护自己人的那个
You know, that little governmental agency

96
00:03:24,760 --> 00:03:26,050
政府机构
that protects their own?

97
00:03:26,050 --> 00:03:28,100
埃里克  你的大哥之前没法护着你
Well, Eric, your big brother couldn't protect you

98
00:03:28,100 --> 00:03:29,270
让你不被开除
from getting fired before,

99
00:03:29,270 --> 00:03:31,380
我看这次他也帮不了你
and I don't see how this is gonna be any different,

100
00:03:32,210 --> 00:03:35,450
对了  那是昨天的报纸
and by the way, that's yesterday's paper.

101
00:03:37,340 --> 00:03:38,290
你要见我
You wanted to see me?

102
00:03:38,330 --> 00:03:40,270
嗯  坐
Sure did. Have a seat.

103
00:03:42,780 --> 00:03:43,900
我在看我们的交易单
I was going over our trade sheets.

104
00:03:43,900 --> 00:03:44,620
突然发现
Couldn't help but notice

105
00:03:44,620 --> 00:03:47,640
你又买了吉利斯工业十万股
you bought another 100,000 shares of Gillis industries.

106
00:03:47,690 --> 00:03:48,660
不会有事的
It's gonna be fine.

107
00:03:48,660 --> 00:03:50,550
你觉得我像二货吗
Do I look like an asshole to you?

108
00:03:50,550 --> 00:03:51,790
你从哪儿弄来的钱
Where the hell did you get the money?

109
00:03:51,790 --> 00:03:53,280
这你知道
You know where I got the money.

110
00:03:54,410 --> 00:03:55,850
我用保证金买的股份
I bought those shares on margin.

111
00:03:55,850 --> 00:03:56,820
拿我的公司做赌注
And leveraged my company.

112
00:03:56,820 --> 00:03:58,130
公司章程里说我有这权力
The bylaws said I can do it.

113
00:03:58,130 --> 00:03:59,630
我才不管章程怎么说呢
I don't care what the bylaws say,

114
00:03:59,630 --> 00:04:00,930
你事先没跟我商量
you did this without asking.

115
00:04:00,930 --> 00:04:01,910
我知道你不高兴
Look, I know you're pissed.

116
00:04:01,910 --> 00:04:03,200
我没有不高兴
Oh, I'm not pissed.

117
00:04:04,040 --> 00:04:05,490
自从你来这儿
I've been waiting for you to have the balls 

118
00:04:05,500 --> 00:04:07,670
我就一直等你有勇气做出这种事
to do something like this since you got here.

119
00:04:08,150 --> 00:04:09,010
你提高了风险
You raised my risk,

120
00:04:09,010 --> 00:04:10,950
但你也提高了回报  而且
but you also raised my reward, and on top of it,

121
00:04:10,950 --> 00:04:13,080
你像个投资银行家那样
you did it like an investment banker,

122
00:04:13,740 --> 00:04:15,100
独断专行
without permission.

123
00:04:19,130 --> 00:04:20,680
谢谢  乔纳森
Well, thank you, jon.

124
00:04:21,460 --> 00:04:22,570
去拿下他们吧
Go get 'em.

125
00:04:25,850 --> 00:04:27,360
-还有件事  -嗯
- One more thing. - Yeah?

126
00:04:27,360 --> 00:04:29,590
给你一周去杠杆化[增加资本充足率]
You have a week to de-leverage my company.

127
00:04:30,040 --> 00:04:32,270
否则  你就会被解雇
If you don't, you're out of a job.

128
00:04:36,260 --> 00:04:37,250
愿意跟我解释一下
You want to explain to me why

129
00:04:37,250 --> 00:04:38,880
你今早为什么去埃里克·伍德尔家吗
you went to Eric Woodall's house this morning?

130
00:04:38,880 --> 00:04:40,420
我知道你很生气
I understand you're bent out of shape

131
00:04:40,420 --> 00:04:41,600
因为我踩上了你的地盘
because I stepped on your territory--

132
00:04:41,600 --> 00:04:43,610
你以为我在乎什么地盘吗
You think I give a shit about my territory?

133
00:04:44,370 --> 00:04:45,670
那你来干什么
What the hell are you doing in here?

134
00:04:45,670 --> 00:04:48,430
听着  我不在乎这事谁来做
Listen, I really don't care if you work this thing or I do,

135
00:04:48,440 --> 00:04:50,640
但不管谁做  必须放聪明点
but whoever it is has to not be an idiot.

136
00:04:50,640 --> 00:04:52,270
那我怎么不聪明了
And how, exactly, am I an idiot?

137
00:04:52,270 --> 00:04:53,160
你去招惹熊了
You poked the bear. 

138
00:04:53,160 --> 00:04:54,740
埃里克·伍德尔才不是熊呢
Eric Woodall isn't the bear.

139
00:04:54,740 --> 00:04:56,370
对  但我是
No. I am.

140
00:04:56,700 --> 00:04:58,840
不管你想说什么  省省吧
And whatever you were about to say, don't say it.

141
00:04:59,590 --> 00:05:02,010
哈维  这是他的案子
Harvey, this is his case.

142
00:05:02,010 --> 00:05:03,410
我们找他来就是为了这个
It's why we brought him in,

143
00:05:03,410 --> 00:05:04,800
我不希望你插手
and I don't want you involved.

144
00:05:04,800 --> 00:05:05,300
我
Me?

145
00:05:05,300 --> 00:05:08,100
是我发现找我们麻烦的不是伍德尔  是...
I'm the one who found out it's not Woodall coming after us, it's--

146
00:05:08,100 --> 00:05:09,340
肖恩·卡荷尔
Sean Cahill.

147
00:05:09,790 --> 00:05:10,830
你以为我不知道吗
You think I didn't know that?

148
00:05:10,830 --> 00:05:13,530
他们是我的客户  等他们惊慌地打来电话
These are my clients, and when they call in a panic,

149
00:05:13,530 --> 00:05:15,680
听到的必须是我的声音
I need to be the voice on the other end of the line.

150
00:05:15,680 --> 00:05:17,910
那就接你的电话
Then be the voice on the other end of the line,

151
00:05:17,910 --> 00:05:19,650
但你不能去对付证监会
but you're not handling the S.E.C.

152
00:05:19,650 --> 00:05:21,410
他们攻击我们就是因为我
I'm the reason they're coming after us.

153
00:05:21,410 --> 00:05:23,740
所以你才想雇佣杰夫
Which is why you wanted to hire Jeff in the first place.

154
00:05:23,740 --> 00:05:25,400
那是这些事发生前
That was before all this became real.

155
00:05:25,400 --> 00:05:26,240
现在事情真的发生了
Now that it's happening,

156
00:05:26,240 --> 00:05:27,900
他又不想在场边旁观了
he doesn't want to sit on the sidelines.

157
00:05:27,900 --> 00:05:28,800
我的确不想
Damn right I don't.

158
00:05:28,800 --> 00:05:30,940
那就找个位置旁听一下
Well, then find yourself a comfortable spot on the bench,

159
00:05:30,950 --> 00:05:33,420
因为不论你喜不喜欢  这案子交给杰夫了
because like it or not, Jeff's in charge.

160
00:06:11,220 --> 00:06:12,680
情况跟你预料的一样吗
So it go just like you said it would?

161
00:06:12,680 --> 00:06:14,040
是的  除了我一周内
Exactly, except for the part

162
00:06:14,040 --> 00:06:15,820
找不到新投资人的话
where if I don't find a new investor in a week,

163
00:06:15,820 --> 00:06:16,920
就要失业的部分
I'm out of a job.

164
00:06:16,920 --> 00:06:19,050
他居然给你一周时间
I'm surprised he gave you a week.

165
00:06:19,430 --> 00:06:21,190
-艾米  这事不好笑  -我知道
- Amy, it's not funny. - I know it isn't.

166
00:06:21,190 --> 00:06:23,450
我只是想尽量积极一点
I was just trying to make the best of the situation.

167
00:06:23,450 --> 00:06:25,050
你要想尽量积极一点
Well, if you want to make the best of the situation,

168
00:06:25,060 --> 00:06:26,870
就帮我约托尼·扬诺普洛斯见一面
get me a meeting with Tony Gianopolous,

169
00:06:26,880 --> 00:06:28,510
因为要是我见不着他
Because if I can't get in there...

170
00:06:30,890 --> 00:06:31,990
我就有麻烦了
I'm in trouble.

171
00:06:32,340 --> 00:06:33,520
是我们有麻烦了
We're in trouble.

172
00:06:34,640 --> 00:06:35,730
你是真心的吗
You really mean that?

173
00:06:35,840 --> 00:06:37,570
你觉得你要走人了我还会留在这里吗
You think I'm staying here if you leave?

174
00:06:39,600 --> 00:06:40,680
谢谢你  艾米
Thank you, Amy.

175
00:06:40,970 --> 00:06:42,010
逗你的
I'm just kidding.

176
00:06:42,060 --> 00:06:43,210
我来这儿的第一天
Epstein's been trying to poach me

177
00:06:43,210 --> 00:06:45,210
艾普斯坦就想挖我过去了
since the day I got here.

178
00:06:45,210 --> 00:06:47,160
你以为那些花是自己出现的吗
Yeah, you think those flowers bought themselves?

179
00:06:49,130 --> 00:06:50,060
你真是...
You--

180
00:06:58,320 --> 00:06:59,550
能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you a second?

181
00:07:00,400 --> 00:07:01,810
如果你要知道收购案的进展
If you want an update on the takeover,

182
00:07:01,810 --> 00:07:03,060
该直接去问哈维
you should talk to Harvey.

183
00:07:03,120 --> 00:07:04,330
我来不是为了这个
That's not why I'm here.

184
00:07:05,780 --> 00:07:07,490
洛根  我知道你...
Look, Logan, I-I know that you--

185
00:07:07,490 --> 00:07:09,980
这里有五家公司
I have five companies here

186
00:07:10,080 --> 00:07:11,590
作为我下一桩交易的候选人
that I'm looking at for my next deal,

187
00:07:11,590 --> 00:07:14,070
我需要人从法律角度
and I need someone to evaluate them

188
00:07:14,190 --> 00:07:15,690
帮我评估一下
from a legal standpoint.

189
00:07:17,130 --> 00:07:19,290
-你下一桩交易  -是的  我下一桩交易
- Your next deal. - Yeah, my next deal.

190
00:07:19,290 --> 00:07:21,580
哈维让我不要对迈克放暗箭
Harvey told me not to hurt my future

191
00:07:21,580 --> 00:07:23,070
以免影响自己的前途
by going below the belt with mike,

192
00:07:23,070 --> 00:07:24,610
我不想影响前途
so instead of not hurting my future,

193
00:07:24,610 --> 00:07:26,020
所以想开始好好计划
I thought I'd start planning for it.

194
00:07:26,020 --> 00:07:29,180
那也许你该跟哈维一起计划
So then maybe Harvey is who you should be planning it with.

195
00:07:29,180 --> 00:07:30,700
哈维有自己的事要忙
Well, Harvey's got stuff to do,

196
00:07:30,870 --> 00:07:33,270
而且可不是他让我不再针对迈克的
and he's not the one who convinced me to back off Mike.

197
00:07:33,470 --> 00:07:35,040
你的意思是这是我欠你的吗
Are you saying that I owe you?

198
00:07:35,040 --> 00:07:36,260
不  我没这个意思
No, I'm not saying that,

199
00:07:36,260 --> 00:07:37,640
但这是你说的
but that is what you said to me.

200
00:07:37,650 --> 00:07:40,030
那我们就要这样一直互还人情吗
So we're just gonna go back and forth, trading favors?

201
00:07:40,040 --> 00:07:41,510
瑞秋  这不是还人情
Rachel, this isn't a favor.

202
00:07:41,510 --> 00:07:43,140
我周五有个董事会要开
I have a board meeting on Friday.

203
00:07:43,140 --> 00:07:44,330
我需要做好准备
I need to be prepared.

204
00:07:44,330 --> 00:07:47,100
你到底做不做我的律师
So are you my lawyer or not?

205
00:07:48,790 --> 00:07:50,040
马上着手去办
I will get right on it.

206
00:07:50,120 --> 00:07:50,960
谢了
Thank you.

207
00:07:55,910 --> 00:07:57,670
路易  我需要你帮忙  我们要...
Louis, I need your help. We're gonna need to--

208
00:07:57,670 --> 00:07:58,490
别说话
Don't speak.

209
00:08:02,350 --> 00:08:03,370
现在可以说了
You may speak.

210
00:08:04,070 --> 00:08:05,380
你搞什么呢
What were you doing?

211
00:08:05,570 --> 00:08:07,380
感谢全能的上帝
Just thanking the Lord god almighty.

212
00:08:08,250 --> 00:08:10,180
我们要踢走杰西卡了吗  要跟马龙开战了吗
We taking down Jessica? We firing Malone?

213
00:08:10,180 --> 00:08:11,010
我激动得发抖
I am tingling.

214
00:08:11,010 --> 00:08:12,450
什么情况  哈维  快告诉我是怎样
What, Harvey? Just tell me what.

215
00:08:12,470 --> 00:08:15,440
迈克·罗斯刚刚又买下了吉利斯工业2%的股份
Mike Ross just bought another 2% of Gillis Industries.

216
00:08:15,440 --> 00:08:17,120
他一定很需要融资
He must be leveraged up to his scrawny little neck.

217
00:08:17,120 --> 00:08:19,850
是的  他会拼命争夺资金
Exactly, and he's gonna be scrambling for funding.

218
00:08:20,070 --> 00:08:21,930
你要我帮你处理掉法院的暂禁令
You want me to get your T.R.O. removed.

219
00:08:21,930 --> 00:08:22,820
你怎么知道
How do you know that?

220
00:08:22,820 --> 00:08:24,600
因为你惹毛了拉莫斯法官
Because you pissed off Judge Ramos

221
00:08:24,630 --> 00:08:26,190
她现在很受不了你
and now she can't stand you.

222
00:08:26,190 --> 00:08:27,180
这你又是怎么知道的
How do you know that?

223
00:08:27,180 --> 00:08:28,500
因为我把你的敌人都列了张表
Oh, because I keep a list of your enemies.

224
00:08:28,500 --> 00:08:30,150
-你要看看吗  -赶紧搞定就是了
- You want to see it? - Just get it done.

225
00:08:30,150 --> 00:08:31,150
我会的
Oh, I'm gonna get it done.

226
00:08:31,240 --> 00:08:32,760
简直是宝宝手里抢糖吃
It's like taking candy from a baby.

227
00:08:32,790 --> 00:08:34,200
路易  我们在分散迈克的注意
Louis, we're splitting Mike's focus.

228
00:08:34,200 --> 00:08:35,890
但这不代表他不会有所准备
That doesn't mean he won't be prepared.

229
00:08:35,900 --> 00:08:37,380
他想怎么准备都行
Oh, he can prepare all he wants,

230
00:08:37,440 --> 00:08:39,560
但姜还是老的辣
but the student is about to meet the master,

231
00:08:39,560 --> 00:08:41,500
拉尔夫·马奇奥在宫城先生面前
because Ralph Macchio doesn't stand a chance

232
00:08:41,500 --> 00:08:42,980
毫无胜算
against Mr. Miyagi.

233
00:08:43,410 --> 00:08:44,950
你还知道《龙威小子》
You know the karate kid?

234
00:08:53,970 --> 00:08:55,490
你真讨厌  哈维
That's not cool, Harvey.

235
00:08:58,860 --> 00:09:01,250
我看看能不能猜到你来这里干什么
Oh, let me see if I can guess why you're here.

236
00:09:01,460 --> 00:09:03,200
你来跟我说我今早对待哈维的方式
You came to tell me the way I handled Jarvey

237
00:09:03,200 --> 00:09:05,430
很性感
this morning was sexy.

238
00:09:05,920 --> 00:09:07,990
你是说  我让他别插手你的事那会吗
Oh, you mean when I told him to leave you alone?

239
00:09:07,990 --> 00:09:11,700
还有允许你那么对他的我非常性感
And the way that I allowed you to do that was very sexy.

240
00:09:13,520 --> 00:09:15,910
这是
And this is...

241
00:09:16,310 --> 00:09:17,690
格里芬彩妆公司的传票
the Griffen Cosmetics subpoena.

242
00:09:17,690 --> 00:09:18,830
我都看过了
I looked them all over.

243
00:09:18,840 --> 00:09:20,220
这是最弱的
This is the weakest one.

244
00:09:20,220 --> 00:09:22,240
-最弱的  -是的
- The weakest one? - Exactly.

245
00:09:22,240 --> 00:09:25,080
推翻了这张  其它的就会像多米诺骨牌一样倒下
Once this one goes down, the others fall like dominos.

246
00:09:25,080 --> 00:09:27,010
首先  就算我采取这个策略
First of all, if I were gonna take that strategy,

247
00:09:27,010 --> 00:09:28,780
我也会针对最强的那个
I would go for the hardest one.

248
00:09:28,790 --> 00:09:30,280
其次  你还是回到自己办公室
Second of all, why don't you walk yourself

249
00:09:30,280 --> 00:09:32,430
让我好好做我的事吧
back to your office and let me do my job?

250
00:09:33,080 --> 00:09:34,080
你说什么
Excuse me?

251
00:09:34,180 --> 00:09:36,620
你跟哈维说  你让我来处理这案子
You told Harvey you brought me in to handle this.

252
00:09:38,000 --> 00:09:41,100
你的工作不是管我跟哈维说了什么
Your job isn't to worry about what I told Harvey.

253
00:09:41,870 --> 00:09:44,050
而是管我交代了你什么
Your job is to worry about what I'm telling you.

254
00:09:44,620 --> 00:09:46,160
而我现在跟你说
And what I'm telling you

255
00:09:46,160 --> 00:09:48,900
我不会带着保姆去参加
is that I'm not walking into an S.E.C. negotiation

256
00:09:48,900 --> 00:09:49,880
证交会的谈判的
with a babysitter.

257
00:09:49,880 --> 00:09:50,950
谈判
Negotiation?

258
00:09:51,280 --> 00:09:52,480
这将是一场战争
This is going to be a war.

259
00:09:52,480 --> 00:09:54,960
我知道  而我会一击致命
I know that, and I'm gonna win it with one shot.

260
00:09:54,960 --> 00:09:56,630
那我建议你好好热身
Then I suggest you warm up to this.

261
00:09:56,640 --> 00:09:59,040
你不是带着保姆去证交会
You're not walking into the S.E.C. with a babysitter.

262
00:09:59,420 --> 00:10:01,660
你带着的是一枚火箭炮
You're walking in there with a bazooka.

263
00:10:05,170 --> 00:10:06,410
迈克  有些东西你得看看
Hey, Mike, you need to see something.

264
00:10:06,410 --> 00:10:08,100
不要  我没时间
No, I don't have time.

265
00:10:08,400 --> 00:10:10,070
我在做扬诺普洛斯的计划书呢
I'm working on the Gianopolous proposal.

266
00:10:10,070 --> 00:10:12,650
但如果他们赢了  你做这计划书也没意义了
Yeah, that proposal isn't gonna matter if they win this.

267
00:10:18,280 --> 00:10:20,620
该死
Goddamn it.

268
00:10:20,710 --> 00:10:22,550
哈维要撤掉暂禁令
Harvey's trying to roll back the T.R.O.?

269
00:10:22,550 --> 00:10:24,010
不  不是哈维  你看摘要
No, it's not Harvey. Check the docket.

270
00:10:24,010 --> 00:10:25,980
是个叫露易丝·利特的女人
It's some woman named Lois Litt.

271
00:10:30,930 --> 00:10:31,890
是吗
Yeah.

272
00:10:32,720 --> 00:10:34,200
我知道怎么对付她
I know how to handle her.

273
00:10:35,010 --> 00:10:36,510
给  完成了百分之九十了
Um, here. This is 90% done. 

274
00:10:36,510 --> 00:10:38,970
再检查一下标点符号什么的
Check it over. Make sure there's not one comma out of place.

275
00:10:39,430 --> 00:10:40,420
迈克  你知道我能做的比这个
Mike, come on, you know I can do more than--

276
00:10:40,420 --> 00:10:41,950
我没时间了  艾米  搞定它
I don't have time, Amy. Just do it.

277
00:10:42,800 --> 00:10:43,670
好吧
Okay.

278
00:10:47,170 --> 00:10:48,920
你在这破地方工作了多久
How long did you work in this shit hole?

279
00:10:49,900 --> 00:10:52,110
抱歉我迟到了  被各种工作缠身
Sorry I'm late. Been up to my neck in work.

280
00:10:52,200 --> 00:10:54,240
刚刚提请发出了七张重要传票
Just filed seven huge subpoenas.

281
00:10:54,240 --> 00:10:55,630
我们知道你发的是什么  
Yeah, we know what you filed. 

282
00:10:55,630 --> 00:10:57,110
你还带了夫人来啊
Oh. I see you brought the missus.

283
00:10:57,110 --> 00:10:59,530
杰西卡  不论你想说什么都忍住
Jessica, whatever you're about to say, don't say it.

284
00:11:00,920 --> 00:11:02,500
那我说说这个吧
How about I say it with this?

285
00:11:03,540 --> 00:11:04,510
一张传票吗
Ooh, a subpoena?

286
00:11:05,360 --> 00:11:06,870
-闻着像新鲜出炉  -是的
- Smells fresh. - It is.

287
00:11:06,870 --> 00:11:08,800
而你明天就得依传票上庭
And you'll be answering it in court tomorrow.

288
00:11:08,800 --> 00:11:10,270
那我最好看看你们准备了
Oh, well then I better see what flavor bullshit

289
00:11:10,270 --> 00:11:11,340
什么风味的胡扯
you're serving up.

290
00:11:12,740 --> 00:11:14,840
为交换
To exchange...

291
00:11:15,440 --> 00:11:16,310
这个不错
Ah, ah, now, this is a good one.

292
00:11:16,310 --> 00:11:19,970
诬告皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所客户
"Malicious prosecution of Pearson Specter clients,"

293
00:11:20,800 --> 00:11:22,170
我们具体是怎么做的呢
And how exactly are we doing that?

294
00:11:22,170 --> 00:11:23,320
我来告诉你
I'll tell you how.

295
00:11:23,430 --> 00:11:24,510
你追着我们的客户不放
You come at our clients.

296
00:11:24,510 --> 00:11:25,880
客户离开我们
Our clients leave us.

297
00:11:25,880 --> 00:11:27,150
你就撤诉
You drop their cases.

298
00:11:27,150 --> 00:11:28,420
我肯定不会告诉他们
Well, I certainly wouldn't tell them

299
00:11:28,430 --> 00:11:30,390
这是规避证监会调查的方法
that's how to avoid S.E.C. scrutiny,

300
00:11:30,410 --> 00:11:32,070
但离开皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所流行起来
But it's not my fault 

301
00:11:32,080 --> 00:11:34,750
可不能怪我
if dropping pearson specter starts catching on.

302
00:11:34,750 --> 00:11:35,950
别再胡扯了
Enough bullshit.

303
00:11:36,060 --> 00:11:37,570
你是代表埃里克·伍德尔
You're targeting my clients

304
00:11:37,570 --> 00:11:39,560
针对我的客户的  你很清楚这点
on behalf of Eric Woodall, and you know it.

305
00:11:39,560 --> 00:11:41,380
这个推测不错  但如果你有任何证据
That is a lovely theory, but if you had any proof,

306
00:11:41,380 --> 00:11:42,950
你现在就不会站在这里了
you wouldn't be standing here right now.

307
00:11:42,950 --> 00:11:44,560
我有证据  肖恩
I have proof, Sean.

308
00:11:44,880 --> 00:11:46,510
我能证明你在同一天申请了七宗
I have proof you filed seven cases 

309
00:11:46,510 --> 00:11:47,870
针对我们的客户的案件调查
in one day against our clients,

310
00:11:47,870 --> 00:11:49,200
我们都清楚这在证监会的历史上
which we both know has never happened

311
00:11:49,200 --> 00:11:50,990
是史无前例的
in the history of the S.E.C.

312
00:11:50,990 --> 00:11:52,150
现在有先例了
It has now.

313
00:11:52,290 --> 00:11:55,200
我们对韦尔-高特肖提请了九宗案件
We've filed nine cases against clients of Weil Gotshal,

314
00:11:55,200 --> 00:11:56,330
斯凯登八宗
Eight against Skaaden,

315
00:11:56,330 --> 00:11:57,760
奎瓦施六宗
and six against Cravath.

316
00:11:58,990 --> 00:12:00,900
欢迎来到崭新的证监会
Welcome to the new S.E.C.

317
00:12:00,900 --> 00:12:02,450
我们针对律所出击
We target law firms.

318
00:12:02,450 --> 00:12:04,340
只要我们不是针对你一家
And as long as we're not only targeting yours,

319
00:12:04,340 --> 00:12:07,470
唯一阻止我们的办法就是让我们关门大吉
the only way to shut this down is to shut us down.

320
00:12:07,470 --> 00:12:08,280
你和我都清楚
You and I both know

321
00:12:08,280 --> 00:12:10,080
这些到底是怎么回事  肖恩
what's really going on here, Sean,

322
00:12:10,890 --> 00:12:12,090
我会证明给你看的
And I'm gonna prove it.

323
00:12:12,090 --> 00:12:14,020
那祝你好运  但如果
Well, good luck, but how do you think

324
00:12:14,020 --> 00:12:16,260
霍普金斯法官知道所有这些论断都来自
Judge hopkins is gonna respond to your allegations

325
00:12:16,260 --> 00:12:17,710
一个马上要被解雇的人
when I tell him they're coming from a man

326
00:12:17,720 --> 00:12:19,390
他会怎么想呢
who is about to be fired?

327
00:12:22,030 --> 00:12:24,290
你  你没告诉她
Oh, you-- you didn't tell her.

328
00:12:25,550 --> 00:12:26,620
那可尴尬了
Ooh, that's awkward.

329
00:12:27,730 --> 00:12:28,750
我们法庭见
I'll see you in court.

330
00:12:32,230 --> 00:12:33,570
-杰西卡  -我不想听
- Jessica! - I don't want to hear it.

331
00:12:33,570 --> 00:12:35,320
-你必须听我解释  -解释什么
- Well, you need to hear it. - What?

332
00:12:35,320 --> 00:12:36,570
说你对我撒谎了吗
That you lied to me?

333
00:12:36,570 --> 00:12:37,720
你知道事实上我并不算撒谎
You know, I didn't actually lie to you.

334
00:12:37,730 --> 00:12:39,690
不  不  不  如果你敢说这不算撒谎
Oh, no, no, no. You tell me that you didn't lie

335
00:12:39,690 --> 00:12:41,200
因为我们并没有直接问过你这个问题
because we never directly asked you the question,

336
00:12:41,200 --> 00:12:42,740
那我就把你的头拧下来
and I will knock your head off.

337
00:12:42,740 --> 00:12:43,880
那好吧
All right, fine.

338
00:12:44,340 --> 00:12:45,260
我撒了谎
I lied.

339
00:12:45,500 --> 00:12:47,190
我撒谎是因为那不重要
I lied because it doesn't matter.

340
00:12:47,190 --> 00:12:49,380
我想为你战斗  而且我是最合适的人选
I want to fight for you, and I'm the best man to do it.

341
00:12:49,380 --> 00:12:51,050
但现在的情况是
Well, the new part of the equation

342
00:12:51,200 --> 00:12:53,190
你让我看起来像个傻子
is that you just made me look like a fool.

343
00:12:53,190 --> 00:12:54,890
-杰西  -别叫我杰西
- Jess. - Don't pull that Jess shit with me--

344
00:12:54,890 --> 00:12:56,300
我想知道你的档案里到底是怎么写的
I want to know what it says in your file.

345
00:12:56,300 --> 00:12:57,070
我不知道里面怎么写的
I don't know what it says. 

346
00:12:57,070 --> 00:12:58,110
你怎么可能不知道
How the hell do you not know?

347
00:12:58,110 --> 00:12:59,760
因为里面写的都是胡扯
'cause whatever it is is bullshit.

348
00:12:59,760 --> 00:13:01,420
因为他们想要解雇我是因为
Because the reason they were gonna fire me

349
00:13:01,430 --> 00:13:03,250
我拒绝追查你的公司
is that I refused to go after you.

350
00:13:03,420 --> 00:13:05,380
那你来向我们要职位的时候
Then why didn't you tell me that

351
00:13:05,670 --> 00:13:07,770
为什么不告诉我这些呢
when you came at us demanding a job?

352
00:13:07,770 --> 00:13:09,360
因为优秀的律师
Because good lawyers negotiate

353
00:13:09,360 --> 00:13:13,080
会站在优势立场谈判  而不是劣势
from a position of strength, not weakness.

354
00:13:13,640 --> 00:13:15,300
但你现在让我们
Well, the position you just put us in

355
00:13:15,300 --> 00:13:17,100
处在了绝对的劣势
is pretty goddamn weak.

356
00:13:26,080 --> 00:13:27,340
这不是青年才俊么
Aw. Is it the boy wonder.

357
00:13:27,710 --> 00:13:29,700
-路易  -别叫我路易
- Louis, hey. - Don't Louis me.

358
00:13:29,730 --> 00:13:31,770
你走的时候连句你父亲怎么样了都没说
You left without even the courtesy of a "How's your father?"

359
00:13:32,320 --> 00:13:33,490
什么意思
What does that mean?

360
00:13:34,090 --> 00:13:35,910
意思就是我不是来客套的
It means that I'm not here to exchange pleasantries.

361
00:13:35,910 --> 00:13:37,550
我是来取消禁令的
I'm here to get that T.R.O. Lifted.

362
00:13:37,550 --> 00:13:38,980
很抱歉你这么想
Well, I'm sorry you feel that way.

363
00:13:39,000 --> 00:13:40,630
还有关于希拉的事我也很遗憾
I'm also sorry to hear about Sheila.

364
00:13:40,630 --> 00:13:42,540
我才不信你会对希拉的事感到遗憾
Bullshit you're sorry to hear about She--

365
00:13:42,870 --> 00:13:43,960
你指的哪件事
What are you talking about?

366
00:13:43,960 --> 00:13:45,050
不是吧  你肯定听说了啊
Come on, you have to have heard.

367
00:13:45,050 --> 00:13:45,910
听说什么
Heard what?

368
00:13:46,680 --> 00:13:48,050
她订婚了
She's engaged.

369
00:13:48,680 --> 00:13:50,890
哈佛的脸书页面上全都是
It's all over Harvard's Facebook page.

370
00:13:58,290 --> 00:13:59,820
天哪  她怎么可以这样
Oh, my god, how could she do this?

371
00:13:59,820 --> 00:14:01,730
她说她对帅哥从来不感兴趣
She said she could never be attracted to a handsome man.

372
00:14:01,730 --> 00:14:03,990
是啊  他那张照片还不算上相
Yeah, and that picture doesn't even do him justice,

373
00:14:04,000 --> 00:14:05,170
但这张呢
but this one, however...

374
00:14:05,170 --> 00:14:06,510
-丁字裤  -是啊
- A thong? - Yeah.

375
00:14:07,520 --> 00:14:08,850
这  什么
That... - what the--

376
00:14:08,850 --> 00:14:11,740
是啊  全套的  可能是去海滩了
Yeah, it's a whole, like, beach thing, I guess.

377
00:14:11,740 --> 00:14:12,870
长周末
Long weekend.

378
00:14:14,700 --> 00:14:15,980
你真是个混蛋  迈克
You're a son of a bitch, Mike.

379
00:14:15,980 --> 00:14:17,020
你一点都不遗憾
You're not even sorry at all.

380
00:14:17,020 --> 00:14:18,400
你想利用这件事扰乱我的思维
You're using this to get into my head.

381
00:14:18,400 --> 00:14:20,030
路易  不是吧  难以置信
Louis, come on, I can't believe you.

382
00:14:20,030 --> 00:14:21,690
你竟然认为我会利用希拉订婚这件事
You think I would use Sheila's engagement

383
00:14:21,690 --> 00:14:22,740
来扰乱你的思维吗
just to get you off your game?

384
00:14:22,740 --> 00:14:23,460
不会有效果的
Never gonna work.

385
00:14:23,460 --> 00:14:24,520
我会告诉你
That I would stick it in your face

386
00:14:24,520 --> 00:14:26,220
她的全部精力都放在这个人身上
that she's all up in this guy's business

387
00:14:26,220 --> 00:14:28,100
其热情你见所未见吗
in a way that you've never seen before?

388
00:14:28,100 --> 00:14:29,080
没用的
Water off a duck's back.

389
00:14:29,080 --> 00:14:30,860
我会告诉你她现在八成在
That right now she's probably scrapbooking

390
00:14:30,860 --> 00:14:32,210
给他们恋情的开始做剪贴簿
the first day of their relationship,

391
00:14:32,210 --> 00:14:33,530
而他们显然是在你伤了她的心后没几周
which apparently happened just weeks

392
00:14:33,530 --> 00:14:35,270
就开始了吗
after you broke her heart?

393
00:14:37,280 --> 00:14:37,980
你简直是个恶魔
You're the devil.

394
00:14:37,980 --> 00:14:39,030
下一案件
Next up on the docket,

395
00:14:39,030 --> 00:14:41,630
西德威尔投资集团诉桑德斯集团案
Sidwell Investment group versus Sanders International.

396
00:14:42,130 --> 00:14:44,630
到我们了  庭上见
Looks like that's us, I'll see you in there.

397
00:14:47,720 --> 00:14:48,930
路易  我简直不敢相信
Louis, I can't believe it.

398
00:14:48,930 --> 00:14:51,200
我就让你帮我做一件事
I give you one goddamn job to do,

399
00:14:51,200 --> 00:14:52,540
结果你...你在那上面干什么  
and you-- what are you doing up there?

400
00:14:52,540 --> 00:14:54,140
哈维  拜托  我能解释的
Harvey, please, I can explain.

401
00:14:55,490 --> 00:14:58,360
解释为啥你像个傻子一样站在法官面前吗
Explain why you stood in front of the judge like a moron?

402
00:14:58,360 --> 00:14:59,810
有什么合理的解释能...
What possible explanation--

403
00:14:59,810 --> 00:15:01,080
希拉订婚了
Sheila got engaged.

404
00:15:02,470 --> 00:15:03,100
什么
What?

405
00:15:04,090 --> 00:15:04,800
什么时候
When?

406
00:15:05,220 --> 00:15:06,020
今天早上
This morning.

407
00:15:07,580 --> 00:15:08,680
路易  节哀
Louis, I'm sorry.

408
00:15:09,410 --> 00:15:11,580
我本来非常确定在生小孩的事上
I was so sure that she would just come around

409
00:15:11,580 --> 00:15:12,790
她会回心转意的
about having children, you know?

410
00:15:12,790 --> 00:15:15,490
这就是为什么我一直拒绝了
That's why I've been turning down

411
00:15:15,490 --> 00:15:16,860
所有那些犹太交友中心的请求
all those J-date requests.

412
00:15:16,860 --> 00:15:17,940
我们会用另一种方式打败迈克的
We'll get Mike another way.

413
00:15:17,940 --> 00:15:19,390
你说的太他妈对了  我们要打败他
Oh, you're goddamn right we're gonna get him.

414
00:15:19,390 --> 00:15:20,530
即使这是我能做的最后一件事
I'm gonna get that son of a bitch

415
00:15:20,530 --> 00:15:21,990
我也要打败那个浑小子
if it's the last thing I do.

416
00:15:22,420 --> 00:15:23,540
什么意思
What are you talking about?

417
00:15:24,680 --> 00:15:27,710
他用希拉的新闻来扰乱我的大脑  哈维
He used the Sheila news to get into my head, Harvey.

418
00:15:28,740 --> 00:15:32,650
是利用这新闻还是告诉你这新闻
Used the news or gave you the news?

419
00:15:32,650 --> 00:15:34,130
拜托  这有区别吗
Oh, please, what difference does it make?

420
00:15:34,130 --> 00:15:35,110
有什么区别
What difference does it make?

421
00:15:35,110 --> 00:15:36,750
这区别可大了
It makes all the difference.

422
00:15:36,750 --> 00:15:38,500
一种会让我同情你
Like on the one hand, I feel for you,

423
00:15:38,500 --> 00:15:40,390
另一种则会你成为世界上头号傻瓜
and on the other, you're the world's biggest idiot.

424
00:15:40,390 --> 00:15:41,310
看看我的电脑
Look at my computer.

425
00:15:41,310 --> 00:15:42,560
我盯着它三个小时了
I've been staring at it for three hours.

426
00:15:42,560 --> 00:15:43,480
是真的
It's real.

427
00:15:44,050 --> 00:15:45,290
简直不可置信
I don't believe it.

428
00:15:45,290 --> 00:15:47,010
是啊  那个在游艇上的帅哥
Yeah, that adonis on that yacht,

429
00:15:47,010 --> 00:15:48,130
他是希拉的未婚夫
Sheila's fiance.

430
00:15:48,130 --> 00:15:49,240
那个帅哥
That adonis

431
00:15:49,240 --> 00:15:53,380
是用洛伦佐·拉马斯1998年的图P的
is a photoshopped picture of Lorenzo Lamas from 1998!

432
00:15:49,240 --> 00:15:53,380
{\an8}洛伦佐·拉马斯: 美国早年著名动作男星

433
00:15:53,380 --> 00:15:54,650
洛伦佐·拉马斯是他妈的谁
Who the hell is Lorenzo Lamas?

434
00:15:54,650 --> 00:15:56,140
我能告诉你他不是谁
Well, I can tell you who he isn't.

435
00:15:56,310 --> 00:15:58,210
他不是希拉的未婚夫
He isn't Sheila's fiance!

436
00:16:04,080 --> 00:16:05,140
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.

437
00:16:05,510 --> 00:16:06,540
你有在听我讲话吗
Are you even listening?

438
00:16:07,100 --> 00:16:09,560
奈杰尔用那些关于猫的未读信件
It was bad enough that Nigel rattled you

439
00:16:09,560 --> 00:16:11,040
弄得你心烦意乱就够糟糕了
with your unread cat letters.

440
00:16:11,040 --> 00:16:12,540
现在你居然又中了迈克的计
Now you're letting Mike do this?

441
00:16:12,540 --> 00:16:14,280
-哈维  拜托  -你他妈给我闭嘴
- Harvey, please. - Shut the hell up!

442
00:16:14,280 --> 00:16:15,920
听着  我试图警告过你
Look, I tried to warn you,

443
00:16:15,920 --> 00:16:18,670
而你目空一切地站在那儿
And you stood there with your stupid leg up in the air,

444
00:16:18,670 --> 00:16:21,450
告诉我姜还是老的辣
telling me that the student was no match for the master

445
00:16:21,450 --> 00:16:25,740
但他只用了一张伪造的照片
and all it took was one doctored picture

446
00:16:25,740 --> 00:16:27,190
就玩死你了
for you to shit the bed!

447
00:16:27,190 --> 00:16:29,200
-我不是有意要...  -你他妈闭嘴
- I didn't mean to-- - Shut the hell up!

448
00:16:30,890 --> 00:16:31,450
上帝啊
God.

449
00:16:38,230 --> 00:16:40,360
遇见你真是惊喜
Well, fancy meeting you here.

450
00:16:40,360 --> 00:16:41,350
瑞秋  出去
Rachel, get out of here.

451
00:16:43,080 --> 00:16:46,510
我只是来复印一些东西的...
I was just coming to make some copy--

452
00:16:47,750 --> 00:16:48,600
路易  出什么事了
Louis, what's wrong?

453
00:16:48,960 --> 00:16:50,430
我不想谈这个  没事儿
I don't want to talk about it; nothing is wrong.

454
00:16:50,430 --> 00:16:51,830
这明显是有事啊
Well, obviously something's wrong.

455
00:16:51,830 --> 00:16:52,840
你知道吗  假如你这么好奇的话
You know what, if you're so curious,

456
00:16:52,840 --> 00:16:54,180
为何不去问问你的梦中情人呢
why don't you just go ask the man of your dreams?

457
00:16:54,180 --> 00:16:56,600
我确定你俩之后会一起开怀大笑的
I'm sure the two of you will have a big laugh about it later.

458
00:16:56,600 --> 00:16:59,270
好吧  我不明白你在说什么
Okay, I don't know what you're talking about,

459
00:16:59,270 --> 00:17:00,240
但是看到你这幅样子
but seeing you like this,

460
00:17:00,240 --> 00:17:02,090
我是绝对不可能再嘲笑你的
there's no way that I would laugh at you.

461
00:17:02,460 --> 00:17:03,220
到底怎么了
What is it?

462
00:17:03,220 --> 00:17:05,630
迈克骗我相信希拉订婚了
Mike convinced me that Sheila was engaged

463
00:17:05,630 --> 00:17:07,750
让我搞砸了案子
to throw me off my game.

464
00:17:07,750 --> 00:17:09,340
我很抱歉  路易
I'm so sorry, Louis.

465
00:17:09,340 --> 00:17:11,210
他可不这么觉得
Yeah, well, he sure wasn't.

466
00:17:11,210 --> 00:17:12,850
用她和另外一个男人在一起的消息
Stuck a knife in me, twisted it

467
00:17:12,850 --> 00:17:14,610
狠狠捅了我一刀  还拧了两圈
with the thought of her and another man.

468
00:17:14,940 --> 00:17:18,340
一整天下来我脑子里就像有个钻孔机
It felt like a drill in my skull all day,

469
00:17:18,340 --> 00:17:19,410
而最糟糕的是
and then to top it all off,

470
00:17:19,410 --> 00:17:24,570
这毁了我最好的朋友对我的尊敬
it cost me the respect of my best friend.

471
00:17:26,480 --> 00:17:27,250
也许...
Maybe--

472
00:17:27,250 --> 00:17:29,790
你别想为他辩护
Oh, don't you even try to defend him.

473
00:17:29,790 --> 00:17:31,150
没  我没打算为他辩护
No, I wasn't going to.

474
00:17:31,150 --> 00:17:32,370
我是想说
I was going to say,

475
00:17:32,960 --> 00:17:35,630
也许你正需要这样一个契机
maybe this is what you needed

476
00:17:35,630 --> 00:17:38,770
来让你下定决心重新联系希拉
to decide to reconnect with Sheila.

477
00:17:39,380 --> 00:17:40,360
那哈维那边怎么办
And what about Harvey?

478
00:17:40,360 --> 00:17:41,930
我要如何弥补
How do I repair that?

479
00:17:44,170 --> 00:17:45,710
发生了这种事我真的很抱歉  路易
I'm really sorry for what happened, Louis.

480
00:17:45,710 --> 00:17:46,620
真的
I am.

481
00:18:02,210 --> 00:18:02,830
你吃过了吗
Did you eat?

482
00:18:03,330 --> 00:18:05,020
你这么问是因为关心我
Are you asking because you're concerned about me

483
00:18:05,020 --> 00:18:07,050
还是因为你想知道我有没有给你留吃的
or because you want to know if I left you any food?

484
00:18:12,160 --> 00:18:13,570
-今天过得不舒心吗  -对不起
- Tough day? - I'm sorry.

485
00:18:13,570 --> 00:18:15,070
我连续几天每天工作16小时了
I've just been working 16-hour days,

486
00:18:15,070 --> 00:18:17,550
-我真的...  -压力很大
- and I'm really-- - Stressed.

487
00:18:18,550 --> 00:18:19,550
我理解这种感受
Yeah I know the feeling

488
00:18:20,140 --> 00:18:20,840
真的吗
Really?

489
00:18:22,210 --> 00:18:25,390
因为我听说你今天可是大胜了一场呢
'Cause I heard that you had a pretty big win today.

490
00:18:25,840 --> 00:18:26,620
你和哈维谈过了
You talked to Harvey.

491
00:18:26,620 --> 00:18:27,790
我和路易谈过了
I talked to Louis.

492
00:18:28,620 --> 00:18:30,090
迈克  我知道你想赢
Mike, I know you want to win,

493
00:18:30,090 --> 00:18:33,160
但你知道你的谎言对他伤害多大吗
but do you have any idea what your lie did to him?

494
00:18:33,160 --> 00:18:34,170
那不是谎言
It wasn't a lie.

495
00:18:34,170 --> 00:18:35,480
是策略
It was a strategy.

496
00:18:35,480 --> 00:18:38,520
两者都是  最终结果就是他快哭出来了
It was both, and it ended up with him near tears.

497
00:18:38,520 --> 00:18:39,640
拜托  瑞秋
Come on, Rachel.

498
00:18:39,640 --> 00:18:41,360
看起来你只在乎输赢了
It just seems like all that matters to you is winning

499
00:18:41,360 --> 00:18:42,790
而你丝毫不在意
and that you don't care about

500
00:18:42,790 --> 00:18:44,360
这会对你的朋友造成什么样的伤害
what it does to your friends.

501
00:18:44,360 --> 00:18:45,230
你知道吗
You know what?

502
00:18:46,130 --> 00:18:47,840
伤害了路易我很抱歉
I'm sorry that I hurt louis,

503
00:18:48,120 --> 00:18:49,240
但他之所以上法庭
But he was going to that courtroom

504
00:18:49,240 --> 00:18:51,190
是为了就他们的投标进行投票表决
so they could put their tender offer to a vote.

505
00:18:51,190 --> 00:18:51,860
我知道
I know.

506
00:18:52,930 --> 00:18:55,310
我们之前谈过  所以你也知道
You also know because we've had this discussion before

507
00:18:55,310 --> 00:18:56,800
一旦他达到目的
that if he got his way,

508
00:18:57,260 --> 00:18:59,570
他们会将公司拆散的
they would rip that company to shreds.

509
00:18:59,970 --> 00:19:02,740
你与其指责我对路易的所作所为
So instead of coming down on me for what I did to Louis,

510
00:19:02,740 --> 00:19:04,830
倒不如担心一下  一旦事情成真
why don't you start worrying about all the lives

511
00:19:04,830 --> 00:19:07,540
洛根·桑德斯将会毁掉的人们
that Logan Sanders is gonna destroy if that happens?

512
00:19:17,880 --> 00:19:18,640
真有意思
You know, it's funny.

513
00:19:18,640 --> 00:19:21,020
你说你不在乎谁管事
You told me you didn't care who was in charge.

514
00:19:21,020 --> 00:19:23,540
你只希望管事的不是个白痴
You just wanted whoever it was to not be an idiot.

515
00:19:23,540 --> 00:19:25,220
你说我是白痴吗
Are you saying that I was an idiot?

516
00:19:25,220 --> 00:19:26,560
咱俩都是白痴
I'm saying we both were.

517
00:19:26,560 --> 00:19:28,450
我不该去找伍德尔
I shouldn't have gone to Woodall,

518
00:19:28,790 --> 00:19:30,340
你也不该骗我们
and you shouldn't have lied to us.

519
00:19:31,870 --> 00:19:33,100
你看上去不怎么生气
You don't seem pissed.

520
00:19:33,820 --> 00:19:35,750
今天发生的事够多了
I've had enough happen already today.

521
00:19:36,520 --> 00:19:38,690
还有  骗我是不对
Besides, lying to me was wrong,

522
00:19:38,920 --> 00:19:41,090
但骗一个正在跟你交往的女人
but lying to the woman you're in a relationship with

523
00:19:41,090 --> 00:19:42,640
那可是大错特错了
is a whole other level.

524
00:19:43,270 --> 00:19:45,090
你觉得她什么时候能原谅我
When do you think she's gonna get past it?

525
00:19:45,090 --> 00:19:47,360
根据我个人的经验  这得花上一阵子了
From personal experience, that could take a while.

526
00:19:47,360 --> 00:19:48,670
这不是我要操心的了
That's not my problem.

527
00:19:49,170 --> 00:19:50,210
是你自己的事
That's yours.

528
00:19:50,210 --> 00:19:51,880
那你来这儿干什么  哈维
Then what are you doing here, Harvey?

529
00:19:51,880 --> 00:19:54,170
我来教你怎么做
I'm here to tell you what you're gonna do about it.

530
00:19:56,090 --> 00:19:56,660
不
No.

531
00:19:57,580 --> 00:19:58,400
不行
No way.

532
00:19:58,830 --> 00:20:00,380
我不会出庭作证的
I'm not taking the stand.

533
00:20:00,380 --> 00:20:01,880
那你来这儿做什么
Then what are you doing here?

534
00:20:01,880 --> 00:20:03,930
伍德尔要你调查我们的客户
Because Woodall telling you to go after our clients

535
00:20:03,930 --> 00:20:05,700
所以你才得到这份工作
is how you got this job in the first place

536
00:20:05,700 --> 00:20:07,330
这刚好对我们有帮助
and happens to make our case.

537
00:20:07,330 --> 00:20:08,870
他没直接指示我调查
He didn't outright tell me to do it,

538
00:20:08,870 --> 00:20:09,610
你知道的
and you know it.

539
00:20:09,610 --> 00:20:10,820
可你还是搞到了消息
You had to find out somehow.

540
00:20:10,820 --> 00:20:12,930
是布莱恩·哈里斯说的
I found out from Brian Harris.

541
00:20:13,480 --> 00:20:15,050
他说他有预感
He told me he had this funny feeling

542
00:20:15,050 --> 00:20:16,420
伍德尔一上任
that the day after Woodall arrived,

543
00:20:16,420 --> 00:20:18,850
我就得开始给皮尔逊-斯佩克特的客户们
that I was gonna start issuing subpoenas

544
00:20:18,850 --> 00:20:20,560
发传票了
to Pearson Specter clients.

545
00:20:20,900 --> 00:20:24,440
我问他为什么  他说"你懂的"
When I asked him why, he said, "You know why."

546
00:20:24,440 --> 00:20:25,660
所以你得出庭作证
Then you're gonna get up on the stand

547
00:20:25,660 --> 00:20:27,820
-把这事讲出来  -不行  我没有证据
- and tell them that. - I can't. I have no proof.

548
00:20:27,820 --> 00:20:30,360
他言语暧昧  而且是第三方谈话
It was vague, and it's a third party conversation.

549
00:20:30,360 --> 00:20:32,640
所以是传闻  我才不在乎
Which makes it hearsay, and I don't give a shit.

550
00:20:32,640 --> 00:20:35,060
我在乎  因此被控诽谤还算轻的
Well, I do, 'cause it opens me up to slander at best

551
00:20:35,060 --> 00:20:36,610
严重的话会被判作伪证的
and perjury charges at worst.

552
00:20:36,610 --> 00:20:38,250
杰夫  你用你的故事
Well, Jeff, you used that story

553
00:20:38,250 --> 00:20:39,450
得到了这里的职位
to get your ass in here.

554
00:20:39,450 --> 00:20:41,310
现在就得用它完成任务
Now use it to get the job done.

555
00:20:49,700 --> 00:20:50,800
艾米
Amy!

556
00:20:52,710 --> 00:20:55,040
我不是让你把扬诺普洛斯的提案放在我桌子上
I thought I asked you to leave the Gianopolous proposal on my desk.

557
00:20:55,040 --> 00:20:57,730
我放了  20分钟前
And I did, 20 minutes ago.

558
00:20:57,730 --> 00:20:58,900
什么  好吧
What? Okay.

559
00:20:59,210 --> 00:21:00,830
-你校对过吗  -没有
- Did you proof it? - No.

560
00:21:00,830 --> 00:21:01,860
我觉得要是这文件上都是拼写错误
I thought you'd have a better chance

561
00:21:01,860 --> 00:21:03,420
说不定你希望会大些
if the document was riddled with typos.

562
00:21:03,420 --> 00:21:04,790
-这很重要  -我知道
- This is important. - I know it is,

563
00:21:04,790 --> 00:21:06,800
所以我来来回回读了几遍
which is why I read it backwards and forwards.

564
00:21:06,800 --> 00:21:07,520
好的  你有把我要求的
Okay, did you add the part

565
00:21:07,520 --> 00:21:09,300
杠杆资本重组的内容加上去吗
about the leveraged recap like I asked?

566
00:21:09,530 --> 00:21:10,530
加了
I did,

567
00:21:10,530 --> 00:21:13,090
但是你关于无表决权股票的建议不太合理
but your figures on the non-voting stock didn't add up,

568
00:21:13,090 --> 00:21:14,570
我提议采用分级分期董事会制度
so I proposed a staggered board

569
00:21:14,570 --> 00:21:16,250
弥补这种不平衡
to make up for the imbalance.

570
00:21:16,450 --> 00:21:17,510
分级分期董事会
Staggered board?

571
00:21:17,510 --> 00:21:19,070
是啊  别这么惊讶
Yeah, don't act so surprised.

572
00:21:19,070 --> 00:21:20,580
抱歉  我以为你...
I'm sorry, I just thought that you--

573
00:21:20,580 --> 00:21:22,160
你以为我对这儿的业务
You just thought that I didn't know anything

574
00:21:22,160 --> 00:21:23,210
一无所知吗
about what goes on here?

575
00:21:23,770 --> 00:21:25,010
听着  T.B.皮肯斯[福布斯富豪]
Listen up, T. Boone Pickens,

576
00:21:25,010 --> 00:21:27,310
我其实很熟悉这方面的业务
I actually know a lot about this business.

577
00:21:27,310 --> 00:21:28,190
好吧  我都道歉了
Okay, I said I'm sorry--

578
00:21:28,190 --> 00:21:29,610
我更清楚
And I know more than enough to know

579
00:21:29,610 --> 00:21:31,350
那份提案和其他摆在我桌子上的提案
that that looks like every other proposal

580
00:21:31,350 --> 00:21:32,850
没什么两样
that's comes across my desk.

581
00:21:32,850 --> 00:21:35,710
这让我在会上的信心更足了
Well, that gives me a shit load of confidence going into this meeting.

582
00:21:35,710 --> 00:21:37,130
我不想打击你的自信
I'm not trying to destroy your confidence.

583
00:21:37,130 --> 00:21:38,510
这是你唯一的优势了
That's the one thing you have going for you.

584
00:21:38,510 --> 00:21:39,380
那你想干什么
Then what are you trying to do?

585
00:21:39,380 --> 00:21:40,490
迈克  你在这里
Mike, you're not here

586
00:21:40,490 --> 00:21:42,350
不是因为你帮西德威尔赚了点钱
because you crunched Sidwell some numbers.

587
00:21:42,350 --> 00:21:45,000
你在这里是因为你为他解决了问题
You're here because you solved a problem for him.

588
00:21:48,350 --> 00:21:48,950
好吧
All right.

589
00:21:49,460 --> 00:21:50,650
把这拿走  把...
Get rid of this, and bring--

590
00:21:50,650 --> 00:21:52,790
把所有能找到的有关托尼·扬诺普洛斯的资料给你
And bring you everything I can find on Tony Gianopolous.

591
00:21:52,790 --> 00:21:53,600
这就去
On it.

592
00:21:55,510 --> 00:21:56,200
艾米
Amy.

593
00:21:58,270 --> 00:21:58,980
你为什么...
Why aren't you--

594
00:21:58,980 --> 00:21:59,910
我为什么只是个助理
Why am I an assistant

595
00:21:59,910 --> 00:22:01,540
而不是投资银行家吗
and not an investment banker?

596
00:22:01,860 --> 00:22:03,720
我在读心理学的博士学位
I'm getting my PhD in psychology.

597
00:22:03,720 --> 00:22:05,020
我对钱没兴趣
Money bores me.

598
00:22:06,550 --> 00:22:08,520
我不明白你为什么要在我的办公室谈
I don't know why you needed to talk to me in chambers,

599
00:22:08,520 --> 00:22:09,310
马龙先生
Mr. Malone.

600
00:22:09,830 --> 00:22:11,030
我的裁决已经很清楚了
I was clear on my ruling.

601
00:22:11,030 --> 00:22:12,820
恕我直言  法官大人
Well, with all due respect, Your Honor,

602
00:22:12,820 --> 00:22:14,310
您的裁决忽略了一个事实
your ruling didn't cover the fact that

603
00:22:14,310 --> 00:22:16,930
证监会与皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所有私仇
the S.E.C. has a vendetta against Pearson Specter.

604
00:22:16,930 --> 00:22:18,310
这可是严重的指控
That's a serious accusation.

605
00:22:18,310 --> 00:22:19,260
如果这是真的
And if it were the truth,

606
00:22:19,260 --> 00:22:20,850
他在庭上就说了  不会在这儿说
he would have said it out there, not in here.

607
00:22:20,850 --> 00:22:21,840
肖恩  我是不想张扬
I'm doing it in private, Sean,

608
00:22:21,840 --> 00:22:23,640
因为我不想因为两个人的行为
because I don't want to slander an entire department

609
00:22:23,640 --> 00:22:25,300
就诋毁整个部门
based on the actions of two men.

610
00:22:25,300 --> 00:22:26,150
也就是说
Translation?

611
00:22:26,150 --> 00:22:27,520
他不想因为自己说谎
He doesn't want to be charged with perjury

612
00:22:27,520 --> 00:22:29,070
被控作伪证  这根本就是个笑话
because he's lying, and this is a joke.

613
00:22:29,070 --> 00:22:31,620
我被要求做和他一样的事时
It wasn't a joke when I was asked to do the exact same thing

614
00:22:31,620 --> 00:22:33,410
可不是开玩笑的
that he's doing right now.

615
00:22:33,410 --> 00:22:34,560
你们在说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?

616
00:22:34,560 --> 00:22:36,170
我离开证监会之前
Before I left the S.E.C.,

617
00:22:36,170 --> 00:22:38,390
有人要我对付皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所的客户
I was told to target Pearson Specter clients.

618
00:22:38,390 --> 00:22:40,110
-谁要你做的  -布莱恩·哈里斯
- And who exactly told you? - Brian Harris.

619
00:22:40,110 --> 00:22:40,770
那就去告他
Then go after him,

620
00:22:40,770 --> 00:22:42,250
你能用来告我的只有道听途说
'cause all you've got on me is hearsay,

621
00:22:42,250 --> 00:22:43,190
容我指出
and might I point out

622
00:22:43,190 --> 00:22:45,330
这一控告出自一个马上要被开除的人
this is the accusation of a man who is about to be fired,

623
00:22:45,330 --> 00:22:48,260
我建议您持审慎态度对待这份指控
which I'd say should be taken with a cubic meter of salt.

624
00:22:48,860 --> 00:22:51,230
如果肖恩同意开放文件
Well, that cubic meter of salt might actually get a little bit smaller

625
00:22:51,230 --> 00:22:53,350
让我们看他的书面记录
if Sean here were to, say, open up his files

626
00:22:53,350 --> 00:22:54,850
这指控可就可信多了
and show us his paper trail.

627
00:22:54,850 --> 00:22:57,410
我们的工作成果按联邦规章应予保密
Our work product is covered under federal regulation,

628
00:22:57,410 --> 00:22:58,370
他很清楚
and he knows that.

629
00:22:58,370 --> 00:22:59,800
我还知道你在以证监会做挡箭牌
I also know you're hiding behind your office

630
00:22:59,800 --> 00:23:00,820
利用法庭来开脱
and using his court to do it.

631
00:23:00,820 --> 00:23:02,240
好了  好了  别吵了
All right, all right, that's enough.

632
00:23:02,580 --> 00:23:03,840
马龙先生  我并不欣赏你
Mr. Malone, I don't appreciate you

633
00:23:03,840 --> 00:23:05,520
把我的办公室当法庭的行为
using my chambers to testify,

634
00:23:05,520 --> 00:23:07,220
他也许没有证据
and he may not have proof,

635
00:23:07,800 --> 00:23:09,950
但一旦有一位客户所受的指控
but if one client leaves his firm

636
00:23:09,950 --> 00:23:12,020
在离开律所后神奇撤销的话
and their charges miraculously disappear,

637
00:23:12,240 --> 00:23:13,510
等待你的可不止是处罚
you're looking at more than sanctions.

638
00:23:13,510 --> 00:23:14,870
你可是会坐牢的
You're looking at jail time.

639
00:23:20,200 --> 00:23:20,940
谢谢
Thank you.

640
00:23:22,190 --> 00:23:22,910
瑞秋
Rachel?

641
00:23:24,030 --> 00:23:24,900
才过了一天
It's only been a day.

642
00:23:24,900 --> 00:23:26,590
你对我的新交易就有想法了吗
You already have a suggestion for my new deal?

643
00:23:26,590 --> 00:23:27,860
-是的  -很好
- I do. - Good.

644
00:23:27,860 --> 00:23:29,670
这五个公司我该下手哪个
Then which of those five companies should I go after?

645
00:23:29,670 --> 00:23:30,660
都不要
None of them.

646
00:23:32,360 --> 00:23:33,230
所以你什么都没带来
So you brought me nothing?

647
00:23:33,230 --> 00:23:35,310
不  我带给你五个更好的选项
No, I brought you five better options.

648
00:23:35,310 --> 00:23:36,880
-我原来的选项有...  -你先看看
- What's wrong with the op-- - Just take a look.

649
00:23:43,490 --> 00:23:45,510
这些公司没有可任意支配资产
These companies have no disposable assets.

650
00:23:45,510 --> 00:23:47,420
确实没有  但它们都有资产运营不佳
No, they don't. They have underperforming assets

651
00:23:47,420 --> 00:23:49,620
可以将其改组
that can be turned around and built into something.

652
00:23:49,620 --> 00:23:51,270
你到底有没有调查我给你的那些公司
Did you even look into the companies I gave you?

653
00:23:51,450 --> 00:23:53,030
-当然看了  但是  -但是什么
- Yes, I did, but I-- - But what?

654
00:23:53,030 --> 00:23:54,100
听起来你也染上你男朋友的
Sounds like someone's been drinking

655
00:23:54,100 --> 00:23:56,520
-臭毛病了  -如果更多人这样做
- her boyfriend's kool-aid. - Maybe if more people did,

656
00:23:56,520 --> 00:23:58,270
-或许有可能  -该死的  瑞秋
- there just might be-- - God damn it, Rachel,

657
00:23:58,270 --> 00:24:00,040
我可不负责拯救世界
I'm not in business to save the world.

658
00:24:00,040 --> 00:24:01,770
我想要专业的意见
I asked for a professional opinion.

659
00:24:01,770 --> 00:24:03,520
我给你的就是专业的意见
And I gave you a professional opinion.

660
00:24:03,520 --> 00:24:05,130
-你只是不喜欢  -我确实不喜欢
- You just don't like it. - No, I don't.

661
00:24:05,500 --> 00:24:07,350
现在我们明天要花一整天
And now we're gonna have to work all day tomorrow

662
00:24:07,350 --> 00:24:09,150
来做我本来要求你做的事情
to do what I asked you to do in the first place.

663
00:24:09,150 --> 00:24:10,580
你是说我们明天要共处一天
You mean spend all day together.

664
00:24:10,580 --> 00:24:11,800
如果必要的话
If that's what it takes.

665
00:24:11,800 --> 00:24:13,400
你召开这次董事会
Did you call this board meeting

666
00:24:13,400 --> 00:24:15,100
就是为了能有更多的时间和我相处吗
just so we could spend more time together?

667
00:24:15,100 --> 00:24:16,910
你给我一份我肯定会拒绝的建议
Did you bring me deals you knew I'd reject

668
00:24:16,910 --> 00:24:18,250
就是为了避免这样吗
just to avoid it?

669
00:24:20,090 --> 00:24:22,310
听着  我说了
Look, like I said,

670
00:24:22,310 --> 00:24:23,780
我周五要开会
I have a meeting on Friday,

671
00:24:24,200 --> 00:24:25,350
我必须准备好
and I need to be prepared for it,

672
00:24:25,350 --> 00:24:26,700
所以你最好回你的办公室去
so maybe you should go back to your office,

673
00:24:26,700 --> 00:24:27,590
开始工作
get cracking,

674
00:24:27,590 --> 00:24:30,700
等你有结果了再给我打电话
and just give me a call when you have something.

675
00:24:33,220 --> 00:24:33,970
好的
Okay.

676
00:24:38,750 --> 00:24:39,460
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.

677
00:24:41,530 --> 00:24:42,650
这都是我的了吗
So this is all mine?

678
00:24:43,220 --> 00:24:43,790
是的
Yup.

679
00:24:44,970 --> 00:24:46,880
20天后  不再允许公众进入
In 20 days, the public access will be gone,

680
00:24:46,880 --> 00:24:50,200
你就拥有了一块400米长的私人海滩
and you will have yourself 1/4 mile of private beach.

681
00:24:50,200 --> 00:24:52,070
南安普顿市议会怎么办
What about the Southampton City Council?

682
00:24:52,480 --> 00:24:53,180
他们能怎么样
What about them?

683
00:24:53,760 --> 00:24:56,230
他们可是一群热爱向公众开放的混蛋
They're a bunch of public-access loving assholes.

684
00:24:57,010 --> 00:24:59,780
我说了  他们能怎么样
Like I said, what about them?

685
00:25:01,340 --> 00:25:02,520
你是怎么做到的  迈克
How'd you do this, Mike?

686
00:25:03,100 --> 00:25:04,940
你不该问我怎么做到的
Well, the question isn't how I did it,

687
00:25:04,940 --> 00:25:06,660
而是我为什么要这样做
it's why I did it.

688
00:25:06,660 --> 00:25:08,800
你有求于我
Oh. You want something from me.

689
00:25:09,550 --> 00:25:10,890
只是请你考虑我的提议
Just your consideration.

690
00:25:11,420 --> 00:25:13,450
你挣到了这个机会  说吧
Well, you've earned it. Go ahead.

691
00:25:21,540 --> 00:25:22,490
不感兴趣
Not interested.

692
00:25:25,340 --> 00:25:27,020
你都没有看
You didn't even look at it.

693
00:25:27,020 --> 00:25:28,110
我没必要看
Oh, I don't have to.

694
00:25:30,240 --> 00:25:32,370
你刚刚说我挣到了请你考虑的机会
You just said that I earned your consideration.

695
00:25:32,370 --> 00:25:33,890
你用完你的机会了
Mm-hmm, and you just got it.

696
00:25:35,690 --> 00:25:38,240
吉利斯工业转手的时机正好成熟
Gillis Industries is ripe for a turnaround,

697
00:25:38,240 --> 00:25:41,210
-而且我已经拥有7%了  -恭喜你
- and I already own 7%. - Congratulations.

698
00:25:41,210 --> 00:25:43,280
现在去找别人要钱吧
Now go beg someone else for money,

699
00:25:43,570 --> 00:25:45,180
因为我是不会给的
because you're not getting mine.

700
00:25:45,180 --> 00:25:46,440
我不明白
I don't understand.

701
00:25:46,440 --> 00:25:47,520
你不需要明白
You don't have to.

702
00:25:47,820 --> 00:25:49,160
现在滚出我的办公室
Now get the hell out of my office.

703
00:25:49,160 --> 00:25:51,510
-扬诺普洛斯先生  -我说了滚
- Mr. Gianopolous. - I said get the hell out.

704
00:26:00,650 --> 00:26:01,630
迈克  最近顺利吗
Hey, Mike. How's it going?

705
00:26:01,630 --> 00:26:02,700
很高兴在这里碰到你
Fancy meeting you here.

706
00:26:07,370 --> 00:26:08,050
是你搞的鬼
It was you.

707
00:26:08,880 --> 00:26:09,570
我干什么了
What was me?

708
00:26:10,680 --> 00:26:13,090
我只是来感谢你给我的建议的
I'm just here to thank you for the advice you once gave me.

709
00:26:14,600 --> 00:26:16,360
在我们还是朋友的时候
You know, back when we were friends.

710
00:26:18,710 --> 00:26:20,300
-路易  -不  不  不
- Louis. - No, no, no. No, no, no.

711
00:26:20,300 --> 00:26:23,370
你曾经告诉过我做事要承担后果
You once told me that my actions had consequences.

712
00:26:23,370 --> 00:26:24,170
还记得吗
Remember?

713
00:26:24,530 --> 00:26:26,770
你也要为昨天做的事承担后果
Your actions yesterday have consequences too.

714
00:26:28,120 --> 00:26:29,590
你对扬诺普洛斯说了什么
What did you say to Gianopolous?

715
00:26:29,590 --> 00:26:30,100
说得不多
Not much.

716
00:26:30,100 --> 00:26:31,590
只是告诉他  他的二把手
Just that you were the person responsible

717
00:26:31,590 --> 00:26:32,850
是因为你才离开他的
for his number two leaving him.

718
00:26:32,850 --> 00:26:33,790
因为我
I was responsible?

719
00:26:33,790 --> 00:26:34,770
他自己同意的
He agreed to it.

720
00:26:34,770 --> 00:26:36,590
但他不知道
But what he didn't know was is that

721
00:26:36,590 --> 00:26:38,400
那主意是他自己的律师想出来的
it was his own lawyer who came up with the idea.

722
00:26:39,160 --> 00:26:39,950
现在他知道了
Now he does.

723
00:26:39,950 --> 00:26:41,380
-这和现在  -有什么关系
- And what does that-- - Have to do with it?

724
00:26:41,990 --> 00:26:43,300
他的确同意了
He may have agreed to it,

725
00:26:43,560 --> 00:26:45,390
但那就意味着你背叛了他
but it was a betrayal by you.

726
00:26:45,690 --> 00:26:46,690
关于投资银行家
And here's a little something

727
00:26:46,690 --> 00:26:49,240
你显然不知道一件事
you obviously do not know about investment banking.

728
00:26:49,720 --> 00:26:52,480
那就是唯一比挣钱更让他们满足的
The only thing more satisfying to these guys than money

729
00:26:52,750 --> 00:26:55,140
就是以牙还牙
is sticking it to someone who stuck it to them.

730
00:27:02,880 --> 00:27:03,530
路易
Louis.

731
00:27:06,660 --> 00:27:08,630
我很抱歉我用希拉来伤害你
I'm sorry for hurting you with Sheila.

732
00:27:08,630 --> 00:27:11,000
不许和我提她的名字
Don't you ever mention her name to me again.

733
00:27:11,000 --> 00:27:14,060
好的  但那只是一步棋
Okay, but it was a move,

734
00:27:14,290 --> 00:27:15,290
就像你刚才做的一样
like you just did.

735
00:27:15,290 --> 00:27:17,260
我们可以翻篇了吗
So can we move on?

736
00:27:17,260 --> 00:27:18,360
翻篇
Move on?

737
00:27:20,680 --> 00:27:22,240
你利用我爱的女人
You used the woman I love 

738
00:27:22,240 --> 00:27:24,770
来延长你那该死的监时禁止令
to extend your goddamn T.R.O.

739
00:27:24,770 --> 00:27:25,980
你知道我对她的感情
You knew how I felt about her, 

740
00:27:25,980 --> 00:27:27,320
却还义无反顾地那么做
and you did it anyway.

741
00:27:29,090 --> 00:27:31,830
我至死都不会忘记的
I will never, ever forget it until the day I die.

742
00:27:32,690 --> 00:27:34,490
祝你没钱也能打败哈维
Good luck beating Harvey without money.

743
00:27:40,970 --> 00:27:42,050
我有好消息告诉你
I have good news.

744
00:27:42,520 --> 00:27:44,300
詹姆斯·多兰去世把尼克斯队留给我了
James Dolan died and left me the Knicks?

745
00:27:44,300 --> 00:27:46,470
路易阻止了迈克说服扬诺普洛斯的计划
Louis stopped Mike from getting Gianopolous.

746
00:27:46,800 --> 00:27:47,950
他截断了他的资金
He blocked his funding.

747
00:27:47,950 --> 00:27:48,560
好
Good.

748
00:27:54,990 --> 00:27:56,340
你求路易帮你解决问题
You went to Louis with a problem,

749
00:27:56,340 --> 00:27:57,350
他解决了
he fixed it,

750
00:27:57,350 --> 00:27:58,810
而你就只打算说"好"
and all you're gonna say is "Good"?

751
00:27:58,810 --> 00:28:00,330
唐娜  我很高兴他解决了问题
Donna, I'm glad he fixed the problem,

752
00:28:00,330 --> 00:28:02,020
但这问题是他自己搞出来的
but it was a problem he created.

753
00:28:02,300 --> 00:28:03,250
他之所以搞出这问题
He created it because

754
00:28:03,250 --> 00:28:04,870
是因为每次与他在乎的人有关
when it comes to people he cares about,

755
00:28:04,870 --> 00:28:06,460
路易就有了盲点
Louis has a blind spot.

756
00:28:06,460 --> 00:28:08,090
是  人啊猫啊都可以是他的盲点
Yeah, for people and cats 

757
00:28:08,090 --> 00:28:09,070
天知道还有什么
and who knows what else?

758
00:28:09,070 --> 00:28:10,460
我告诉你还有什么
I'll tell you what else.

759
00:28:10,910 --> 00:28:11,980
他在乎你
He cares about you.

760
00:28:14,890 --> 00:28:16,240
你要我怎么做  唐娜
What do you want from me, Donna?

761
00:28:16,690 --> 00:28:18,880
我要你告诉他  他做得很好
I want you to tell him he did a good job.

762
00:28:19,200 --> 00:28:21,190
等我们赢了这官司再说
I'll tell him when we come out on top.

763
00:28:21,420 --> 00:28:22,370
好吧  哈维
Okay, Harvey.

764
00:28:22,430 --> 00:28:23,780
你要怎么做都行
You do what you're gonna do,

765
00:28:24,650 --> 00:28:27,360
但别忘了  路易向希拉求婚时
but just remember, when Louis asked Sheila to marry him,

766
00:28:27,850 --> 00:28:29,830
他选了你当伴郎
you were the one he picked to be his best man,

767
00:28:30,950 --> 00:28:32,160
而你也答应了
and you said yes.

768
00:28:43,050 --> 00:28:45,120
抱歉  我们今天不做招聘
I'm sorry, but we're not hiring today.

769
00:28:45,120 --> 00:28:46,330
我是猜想你在找工作呢
I think you'd be looking for a job

770
00:28:46,330 --> 00:28:48,170
因为你在内庭已打击好惨的
given the beat-down you took in chambers.

771
00:28:48,170 --> 00:28:50,670
我不知道杰夫这个牢骚雇员对你说了什么
I'm not sure what Jeff disgruntled employee here told you,

772
00:28:50,670 --> 00:28:51,620
可我没被打倒
but I'm still standing.

773
00:28:51,620 --> 00:28:53,640
我告诉她你输了
Well, what I told her is that you lost.

774
00:28:54,570 --> 00:28:55,730
那你为什么过来
Then why are you here?

775
00:28:55,730 --> 00:28:57,030
我们来是给你个提议
We're here to make you an offer.

776
00:28:57,030 --> 00:28:58,330
你撤销那七件案子
You drop all seven cases,

777
00:28:58,330 --> 00:29:00,430
我们就不告你诬告
we drop the malicious prosecution claim.

778
00:29:00,670 --> 00:29:01,540
不可能
No deal.

779
00:29:01,600 --> 00:29:04,250
霍普金斯法官在等你采取行动
Judge Hopkins is going to be waiting for you to take action.

780
00:29:04,250 --> 00:29:06,120
时间拖得太久
Too much time goes by,

781
00:29:06,280 --> 00:29:07,800
他会觉得你满嘴胡言
he's gonna think you're full of shit.

782
00:29:08,040 --> 00:29:09,000
但如果你现在认输
But if you fold right now,

783
00:29:09,010 --> 00:29:11,210
他只会用我们要撤销的罪名
he's only gonna sanction you for the exact claim

784
00:29:11,210 --> 00:29:12,410
来处罚你罢了
that we're willing to drop.

785
00:29:12,420 --> 00:29:13,700
我们也会因此告诉法官
Which is why we'll tell the judge

786
00:29:13,700 --> 00:29:15,470
作为撤销案件的回报
that in exchange for those cases being dropped,

787
00:29:15,470 --> 00:29:17,620
我们愿意给证交会前所未有的权限
we'll give the S.E.C. unprecedented access

788
00:29:17,620 --> 00:29:19,300
查看客户的账簿
to our clients' books.

789
00:29:20,140 --> 00:29:21,910
你们肯定不会这么做
Which, of course, you won't be doing.

790
00:29:21,910 --> 00:29:23,460
确实我们不会
No, we won't.

791
00:29:23,460 --> 00:29:25,330
那我到底捞到了什么好处
So what exactly am I getting out of this?

792
00:29:25,330 --> 00:29:26,660
保住了你的颜面
You get to save face.

793
00:29:26,660 --> 00:29:27,660
我确实喜欢我的面子
I do like my face.

794
00:29:27,660 --> 00:29:28,900
但我也珍爱生命啊
However, I also like my ass,

795
00:29:28,900 --> 00:29:31,250
如果我接受了这个条件  命就不保了
which will be on the line if I take this deal.

796
00:29:31,400 --> 00:29:34,190
你有24个小时考虑更看重哪一个
Then you have 24 hours to decide which one you like more.

797
00:29:41,100 --> 00:29:42,810
傅滋曼先生  我是迈克·罗斯
Mr. Forstman, Mike Ross.

798
00:29:42,810 --> 00:29:43,630
不行
No.

799
00:29:45,020 --> 00:29:46,520
先生  我认为如果你听我说完...
Sir, I think that if you hear me out--

800
00:29:46,520 --> 00:29:48,270
你究竟是怎么知道我在这里的
How the hell did you find me here?

801
00:29:50,030 --> 00:29:51,150
《福布斯》上有篇文章说
The article in forbes said

802
00:29:51,150 --> 00:29:52,490
你不能超过三小时
you can't go more than three hours

803
00:29:52,490 --> 00:29:54,890
不喝罗莎咖啡馆的古巴咖啡
without Rosa's cafe cubanos.

804
00:29:54,890 --> 00:29:57,090
那篇文章是六年前的了
That article in forbes was six years ago.

805
00:29:57,090 --> 00:29:58,840
文章还说你从来不会变
It also said you never change.

806
00:29:59,070 --> 00:30:00,350
那你读过我会把每一个
Did you also read where I have

807
00:30:00,360 --> 00:30:03,080
想成为巴德·福克斯的家伙扔到垃圾堆吗
every Bud Fox wannabe dumped in a local landfill?

808
00:30:03,080 --> 00:30:03,760
如果你那么做
If you do that,

809
00:30:00,360 --> 00:30:03,080
\an8巴德·福克斯  1987年电影《华尔街》主角

810
00:30:03,760 --> 00:30:06,510
就错过了报复哈维·斯佩克特的好机会
you'll miss the opportunity to get back at Harvey Specter.

811
00:30:10,220 --> 00:30:11,580
你这个小屁孩知道什么
And what does a little shit like you

812
00:30:11,580 --> 00:30:13,130
我和哈维·斯佩克特的过节
know about Harvey Specter?

813
00:30:13,140 --> 00:30:15,090
我知道他在你眼皮底下
I know that he bought that '63 Aston Martin

814
00:30:15,090 --> 00:30:16,500
买走了63款阿斯顿马丁
out from under you, 

815
00:30:16,500 --> 00:30:17,530
你从此记恨他
and you've hated him ever since.

816
00:30:17,530 --> 00:30:19,120
你知道他总把那辆跑车放在车库吗
You know he keeps it in a garage?

817
00:30:19,120 --> 00:30:20,450
从来不开
Doesn't even drive it.

818
00:30:20,450 --> 00:30:21,380
你想要什么
What do you want?

819
00:30:25,300 --> 00:30:26,510
吉利斯工业
Gillis industries.

820
00:30:26,510 --> 00:30:28,140
吉利斯工业
Gillis industries...

821
00:30:28,700 --> 00:30:30,920
就是个坏账黑洞
Is a black hole of distressed debt.

822
00:30:30,920 --> 00:30:32,060
我才不想染指
I want nothing to do with it.

823
00:30:32,060 --> 00:30:33,260
不是这样的
No, it isn't.

824
00:30:33,260 --> 00:30:35,290
那可是块肥肉
It's a '63 Aston Martin.

825
00:30:38,610 --> 00:30:39,730
你替谁做事的
Who do you work for?

826
00:30:39,830 --> 00:30:41,210
为什么我不能是单干的呢
Who says I work for anyone?

827
00:30:41,210 --> 00:30:42,170
因为像你这样的小毛孩
Because a young kid like you

828
00:30:42,170 --> 00:30:44,070
要有能力跟吉利斯打交道
with enough clout to go after Gillis...

829
00:30:45,380 --> 00:30:46,340
我肯定知道你
I'd know you.

830
00:30:47,290 --> 00:30:49,020
我替乔纳森·西德威尔做事
I work for Jonathan Sidwell.

831
00:30:49,030 --> 00:30:52,470
好吧  我投2亿3千万
Okay. You've got my 230 mil.

832
00:30:55,120 --> 00:30:56,680
我只需要8千万
I only need 80.

833
00:30:56,810 --> 00:30:58,880
你不知道你要什么
You don't know what you need.

834
00:31:00,950 --> 00:31:02,920
怎么处置这家公司听我的
What happens to the company is my call.

835
00:31:03,250 --> 00:31:04,060
行
Done.

836
00:31:09,360 --> 00:31:11,440
你准备文件的时候记住一件事
Oh, one more thing, when you get those papers.

837
00:31:13,670 --> 00:31:15,890
我有预感文件里会藏着一个条款
I have a feeling there'll be a provision buried in there

838
00:31:15,890 --> 00:31:18,330
说一旦交易结束
that says that once the deal closes,

839
00:31:18,670 --> 00:31:19,990
你就会把西德威尔踢出去
you cut Sidwell out.

840
00:31:21,240 --> 00:31:22,080
抱歉  我没听懂
I'm sorry, what?

841
00:31:22,080 --> 00:31:23,530
我不认识他
I don't know him,

842
00:31:23,530 --> 00:31:25,290
这个交易没有我绝对成不了
and I don't want him sucking a chunk out of a deal

843
00:31:25,290 --> 00:31:27,370
我才不要让他占了大便宜
that can't happen without me.

844
00:31:40,750 --> 00:31:41,720
顺利吗
Well?

845
00:31:42,120 --> 00:31:43,240
他答应了
He went for it.

846
00:31:43,580 --> 00:31:44,840
那很好
That is great.

847
00:31:44,840 --> 00:31:46,430
也不是那么好
No, it's not all great.

848
00:31:46,980 --> 00:31:49,800
我答应踢了西德威尔  他才会给钱
He'll only give me the money if I agree to cut out Sidwell.

849
00:31:50,150 --> 00:31:51,070
什么
What?

850
00:31:51,230 --> 00:31:53,570
踢了西德威尔是什么意思
What does cut him out even mean?

851
00:31:53,570 --> 00:31:54,890
意思就是西德威尔不能
It means make sure Sidwell

852
00:31:54,900 --> 00:31:56,950
从这个交易里分到一毛钱
doesn't get a penny from this deal.

853
00:31:57,160 --> 00:32:00,440
迈克  一旦他发现你就得走人了
Mike, the second he finds that out, you're gone.

854
00:32:00,440 --> 00:32:02,730
在交易结束前他不会知道的
He's not gonna find out until the deal closes,

855
00:32:02,730 --> 00:32:05,380
如果我搞不到钱  照样得走人
And if I don't find the money, I'm out of a job anyway.

856
00:32:06,040 --> 00:32:08,350
我明白了
Oh, I get it.

857
00:32:08,350 --> 00:32:10,930
这么办  至少你还在赢的一方
At least this way, you get to leave on the winning side.

858
00:32:10,980 --> 00:32:13,850
-是我们还在  -谁说我要一起离开了
- We leave on the winning side. - Who says I'm gonna do that?

859
00:32:15,460 --> 00:32:17,740
你以前说"你觉得你走了我还会留吗"
What happened to, "You think I'm staying if you leave"?

860
00:32:17,740 --> 00:32:18,910
对  那是我知道
Yeah, that was before I knew

861
00:32:18,910 --> 00:32:20,070
你要伤害西德威尔之前
you were gonna screw over Sidwell.

862
00:32:20,070 --> 00:32:20,970
艾米  我...
Amy, I-- 

863
00:32:20,970 --> 00:32:22,320
不行  他有时可能挺混蛋的
No, he may be a dick sometimes,

864
00:32:22,320 --> 00:32:23,360
但因为他你才能在这儿
but he's the reason you're here.

865
00:32:23,360 --> 00:32:25,290
你以为我想这么做
You think I want this?

866
00:32:26,330 --> 00:32:28,160
我得在对沃尔特·吉利斯许的诺言
I have to make a choice between the promise 

867
00:32:28,160 --> 00:32:29,340
和欠乔纳森的人情
I made to Walter Gillis

868
00:32:29,340 --> 00:32:30,350
之间做抉择
and what I owe Jonathan.

869
00:32:30,350 --> 00:32:32,270
迈克  沃尔特·吉利斯现在
Mike, Walter Gillis doesn't give a shit

870
00:32:32,270 --> 00:32:33,120
根本不关心你的诺言了
about that promise anymore.

871
00:32:33,120 --> 00:32:34,280
是  但我关心
Yeah, but I do,

872
00:32:34,790 --> 00:32:36,830
所有为他工作的人也关心
and so do all the people that work for him.

873
00:32:39,370 --> 00:32:40,510
所以你要那么做了
So you're gonna do it.

874
00:32:43,620 --> 00:32:44,500
我不知道
I don't know.

875
00:32:46,250 --> 00:32:48,710
但我知道我要想赢
But I do know that I keep having to do shitty things

876
00:32:48,710 --> 00:32:50,390
还得继续做烂事
just to win this thing,

877
00:32:50,390 --> 00:32:52,420
而我得去弥补其中一件造成的后果了
but I'm gonna go make up for one of them right now.

878
00:32:58,150 --> 00:33:01,050
很抱歉我没有照你要求做事
I'm sorry I didn't do what you asked me to do.

879
00:33:01,350 --> 00:33:03,260
我应该尊重你的意见的
I should have evaluated your ideas.

880
00:33:03,260 --> 00:33:04,330
你是应该
You should have,

881
00:33:05,180 --> 00:33:06,140
但我也应该记得
but I should have remembered

882
00:33:06,140 --> 00:33:08,390
你并不总是按人期待做事
that you don't always do what people expect of you.

883
00:33:09,080 --> 00:33:11,610
你意思是说听人指挥做事吧
You mean what people tell me to do.

884
00:33:11,970 --> 00:33:13,490
我选了好听点的说法
I chose the nicer version.

885
00:33:13,500 --> 00:33:14,750
我...
Well, I, um...

886
00:33:14,910 --> 00:33:16,790
我搞定了一开始就该搞定的事
I finished what I should have done in the first place.

887
00:33:16,790 --> 00:33:19,310
-然后呢  -然后咱们过一遍吧
- And? - And let's go through them.

888
00:33:21,320 --> 00:33:22,890
-你在这儿做什么  -等你
- What are you doing here? - Waiting for you.

889
00:33:22,890 --> 00:33:24,370
我觉得如果我上楼去
I figured if I tried to go upstairs,

890
00:33:24,370 --> 00:33:25,250
你会杀了我
you'd have me killed.

891
00:33:25,250 --> 00:33:26,890
你是在讲笑话吗  可是我没笑
Oh, is that a joke, 'cause I'm not laughing.

892
00:33:26,890 --> 00:33:28,790
路易  我第一次没表达对
Louis, I didn't say it right the first time.

893
00:33:28,790 --> 00:33:30,730
我想再说一次  对不起
I want to say it again. I'm sorry.

894
00:33:33,050 --> 00:33:34,690
你以为"对不起"就能弥补你的行为吗
You think "I'm sorry" makes up for what you did?

895
00:33:34,690 --> 00:33:37,250
不  但我希望我们可以翻过这页
No, but I'm hoping that we can move past it

896
00:33:37,250 --> 00:33:38,400
重新做朋友
and be friends again.

897
00:33:39,490 --> 00:33:40,570
唯一的问题是
Well, the only problem with that is,

898
00:33:40,570 --> 00:33:42,420
你我都清楚你来的唯一原因
is that you and I both know that you're only here

899
00:33:42,420 --> 00:33:43,840
是我把你的金主抢走了
because I took away your sugar daddy,

900
00:33:43,840 --> 00:33:45,230
你现在想求我对你下手轻点
and now you want me to take it easy on you.

901
00:33:45,230 --> 00:33:48,240
路易  你不想接受我道歉  没关系
Louis, if you don't want to accept my apology, that's fine,

902
00:33:48,370 --> 00:33:49,840
但我不是作为弱势方前来的
but I'm not here from a position of weakness.

903
00:33:49,840 --> 00:33:51,430
我是强势一方
I'm here from a position of strength.

904
00:33:51,430 --> 00:33:52,550
胡说  你从哪弄到的钱
Bullshit. Where'd you get money?

905
00:33:52,550 --> 00:33:53,640
你在别处没有朋友
You don't have any friends out there.

906
00:33:53,650 --> 00:33:55,780
是没有  但哈维有敌人
No, but Harvey has enemies.

907
00:33:57,060 --> 00:33:58,170
那是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?

908
00:33:58,170 --> 00:33:59,590
你告诉我有人恨他
You told me these guys hold grudges.

909
00:33:59,600 --> 00:34:02,050
我只是找到了一个反对哈维的人
I just found a guy with one against Harvey.

910
00:34:02,050 --> 00:34:02,610
婊子养的
You son of a bitch.

911
00:34:02,610 --> 00:34:03,870
你不是来道歉的
You didn't come here to apologize.

912
00:34:03,870 --> 00:34:05,890
你是来炫耀  来羞辱我的
You came here to rub it in my face.

913
00:34:05,910 --> 00:34:07,480
我敢说你现在等不及要告诉哈维
Oh, and I bet you just can't wait to tell Harvey

914
00:34:07,480 --> 00:34:09,020
是我提醒你这办法的
that I'm the one who gave you the idea.

915
00:34:09,020 --> 00:34:10,210
我本来都不想告诉你
Louis, I wasn't even gonna tell you

916
00:34:10,210 --> 00:34:11,330
我怎么想到这主意的
how I got the idea at all.

917
00:34:11,340 --> 00:34:13,150
我现在依然不打算告诉哈维
I'm still not gonna tell Harvey.

918
00:34:13,190 --> 00:34:14,510
因为你想让我欠你的
Because you want me to owe you?

919
00:34:14,510 --> 00:34:15,610
因为我没有你想的
Because I'm not as much of an asshole

920
00:34:15,610 --> 00:34:17,030
那么混蛋
as you think I am.

921
00:34:17,750 --> 00:34:19,820
-我们买断怎么样  -根本不可能
- What about a buyout? - Never gonna happen.

922
00:34:19,820 --> 00:34:21,580
他有金色降落伞
He's got a golden parachute.

923
00:34:20,580 --> 00:34:22,580
{\an8}金色降落伞  公司控制权易手
管理人员离职时  会得到大额经济补偿的制度

924
00:34:21,840 --> 00:34:23,510
我在董事会有两人支持
Well, then I've got two people on the board.

925
00:34:23,510 --> 00:34:25,050
我可以强行推动投票
I can force a vote.

926
00:34:25,060 --> 00:34:27,060
你那么做  会导致股份拆分
You do that, it triggers a stock split.

927
00:34:27,070 --> 00:34:28,500
他的股份会有双倍投票权
His shares double in voting power.

928
00:34:28,500 --> 00:34:30,350
-而你的没有  -五家公司都过完了
- Yours don't. - I mean, that's all five.

929
00:34:30,350 --> 00:34:32,890
-没一个能成的  -对  都不行
- None of them work. - No, they don't.

930
00:34:33,700 --> 00:34:35,950
所以你跟我说应该尊重我的意见时
So when you told me you should have evaluated my ideas first,

931
00:34:35,950 --> 00:34:37,530
并没有说它们是好意见
you weren't saying that they were good.

932
00:34:37,530 --> 00:34:40,180
我只说我没做好工作
I was saying I wasn't doing my job.

933
00:34:40,370 --> 00:34:42,360
意思就是让我自己发现
Which was to let me figure out for myself

934
00:34:42,360 --> 00:34:44,110
我的主意都不好
that my ideas weren't good.

935
00:34:44,400 --> 00:34:46,130
我选了好听点的说法
I chose the nicer version.

936
00:34:47,060 --> 00:34:50,800
洛根  外面还有好多公司可以选
Logan, there are plenty of other companies out there.

937
00:34:51,460 --> 00:34:52,420
但我来不及在明天的董事会前
None that we're gonna find in time

938
00:34:52,420 --> 00:34:53,870
找一家出来了
for my board meeting tomorrow.

939
00:34:53,870 --> 00:34:55,270
-那就推掉董事会  -我不能
- So push it. - I can't.

940
00:34:55,270 --> 00:34:56,410
不是我召集的
I didn't call it.

941
00:34:58,390 --> 00:35:00,020
-我以为...  -我知道
- And I thought-- - Yeah, I know.

942
00:35:00,020 --> 00:35:02,760
以为我安排董事会是为了多跟你相处
That I only even arranged it to spend time with you?

943
00:35:02,760 --> 00:35:03,700
你还真没有
You really didn't.

944
00:35:03,700 --> 00:35:06,450
是的  而他们明天会问我
No, and now they're gonna ask me tomorrow

945
00:35:06,450 --> 00:35:07,610
对吉利斯的收购案怎么样了
how Gillis is going,

946
00:35:07,610 --> 00:35:09,620
我得回答我们可能会输
and I'm gonna have to tell them we might lose,

947
00:35:09,620 --> 00:35:11,250
他们会问我还有什么别的计划
and then they're gonna ask me what else I have,

948
00:35:11,250 --> 00:35:13,960
我只能说没有
and I'm gonna have to tell them nothing.

949
00:35:14,110 --> 00:35:15,420
也许你不用说没有
Or maybe you won't.

950
00:35:15,700 --> 00:35:17,560
我说过  那庄生意我没参与
I told you, I'm not in that business.

951
00:35:17,570 --> 00:35:20,200
那就说服董事会让你参与
Then convince the board that you should be.

952
00:35:20,200 --> 00:35:21,030
好吧
Okay.

953
00:35:21,240 --> 00:35:21,940
回办公室去
Go back to your office.

954
00:35:21,940 --> 00:35:22,860
准备好文件
Get your files.

955
00:35:22,860 --> 00:35:24,110
如你所说
Like you said,

956
00:35:24,110 --> 00:35:27,430
我并不总是按人期待做事
I don't always do what people expect me to do.

957
00:35:38,400 --> 00:35:40,120
路易  我能跟你说句话吗
Louis, can I talk to you for a minute?

958
00:35:40,250 --> 00:35:41,170
当然
Of course.

959
00:35:42,960 --> 00:35:45,250
我听说你在扬诺普洛斯的事上的表现了
I heard about what you did with Gianopolous.

960
00:35:45,530 --> 00:35:46,460
做得漂亮
Good job.

961
00:35:49,650 --> 00:35:51,570
我很感激  哈维  真的
I appreciate that, Harvey. I do.

962
00:35:54,410 --> 00:35:55,700
但那不重要了
But it doesn't matter.

963
00:35:56,000 --> 00:35:58,650
他去找了别人
You know, he went somewhere else.

964
00:36:00,090 --> 00:36:00,960
我知道
I know.

965
00:36:01,460 --> 00:36:02,700
他找了傅滋曼
He went to Forstman.

966
00:36:03,710 --> 00:36:05,980
无论如何  我只想告诉你做得不错
I just wanted to tell you you did a good job anyway.

967
00:36:07,050 --> 00:36:08,930
你看  那就是问题所在
See, that's the thing.

968
00:36:12,020 --> 00:36:12,890
我没把事做好
I didn't.

969
00:36:14,110 --> 00:36:15,480
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

970
00:36:20,240 --> 00:36:21,670
迈克想到这办法是经我提醒
Mike got the idea from me.

971
00:36:23,940 --> 00:36:24,760
什么
What?

972
00:36:26,540 --> 00:36:27,330
怎么可能
How?

973
00:36:29,180 --> 00:36:30,490
我阻止扬诺普洛斯帮他后
When I cut him off from Gianopolous,

974
00:36:30,490 --> 00:36:31,850
又当面羞辱他了
I stuck it in his face,

975
00:36:31,850 --> 00:36:35,130
告诉他人是会记仇的  而且我
and I told him that people hold grudges, and I--

976
00:36:36,680 --> 00:36:38,160
他一定是知道了你跟傅滋曼的过去
He must have known your history with Forstman,

977
00:36:38,160 --> 00:36:40,150
所以才去找他...
and that's why he went to him, so...

978
00:36:45,410 --> 00:36:46,300
抱歉
I'm sorry.

979
00:36:46,770 --> 00:36:48,290
该死  路易
God damn it, Louis.

980
00:36:49,460 --> 00:36:51,550
我不想一直生你的气
I don't want to keep being mad at you,

981
00:36:51,560 --> 00:36:54,070
但你却老搞出这些破事
but you keep doing the same shit.

982
00:36:54,070 --> 00:36:55,670
但是你看  我没被耍
But, see, this wasn't me being duped.

983
00:36:55,670 --> 00:36:58,720
对  但是你放任自己的情绪
No, it was you letting your emotions

984
00:36:59,560 --> 00:37:02,250
操控你去干蠢事
lead you into doing something stupid.

985
00:37:02,980 --> 00:37:03,940
屡次三番
Again.

986
00:37:04,690 --> 00:37:06,800
你就是非得当面羞辱他
You just had to stick it in his face.

987
00:37:08,240 --> 00:37:09,090
你知道吗
You know what?

988
00:37:11,770 --> 00:37:12,780
我受够了
I'm done.

989
00:37:14,790 --> 00:37:16,140
这不公平
It's not fair, you know.

990
00:37:19,110 --> 00:37:22,810
我很情绪化  你很冷酷
I'm emotional. You're cold.

991
00:37:25,230 --> 00:37:26,460
你深受爱戴
You're loved,

992
00:37:28,340 --> 00:37:29,530
我备受唾弃
and I'm hated.

993
00:37:31,230 --> 00:37:34,830
路易  如果我真的很冷酷
Louis, if I was so cold,

994
00:37:35,290 --> 00:37:37,600
一开始就不会来这里了
I wouldn't have come here in the first place.

995
00:37:49,980 --> 00:37:51,110
你在干什么
What are you doing?

996
00:37:51,250 --> 00:37:52,750
给咱俩倒酒
Pouring us a drink.

997
00:37:54,590 --> 00:37:55,590
卡荷尔接受协议了
Cahill took the deal.

998
00:37:55,600 --> 00:37:57,820
七个案子都撤销
All seven cases are officially dead.

999
00:38:00,770 --> 00:38:03,360
杰西卡  我很抱歉之前没跟你说实话
Jessica, I'm sorry that I didn't come clean with you before.

1000
00:38:05,040 --> 00:38:05,890
我也很遗憾
Me too.

1001
00:38:06,500 --> 00:38:09,160
欺骗你是个工作决定
Lying to you was a business decision,

1002
00:38:09,160 --> 00:38:10,460
也是错误的
and it was wrong,

1003
00:38:11,670 --> 00:38:12,310
但我希望你知道
but I want you to know

1004
00:38:12,310 --> 00:38:14,380
我再也不会骗你了  这是承诺
that I would never lie to you, man to woman.

1005
00:38:16,550 --> 00:38:17,850
非常感谢
I appreciate that.

1006
00:38:21,440 --> 00:38:22,650
我们碰到麻烦了
We have a problem.

1007
00:38:22,790 --> 00:38:24,700
我刚跟理查德·科尔曼打完电话
I just got off the phone with Richard Coleman.

1008
00:38:24,700 --> 00:38:26,610
上周  肖恩·卡荷尔问他
Last week, Sean Cahill asked him

1009
00:38:26,610 --> 00:38:28,790
我有没有在他面前做出什么出格的事
if I'd ever crossed any lines in his presence.

1010
00:38:28,790 --> 00:38:30,170
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.

1011
00:38:30,170 --> 00:38:31,620
他不希望我们的客户抛弃我们
He doesn't want our clients to leave us.

1012
00:38:31,620 --> 00:38:33,720
他想让他们往我身上泼脏水
He wants them to cough up dirt on me.

1013
00:38:33,840 --> 00:38:36,010
至少还没人这么干  不然我们现在就麻烦了
At least none of them did, or we'd be in trouble right now.

1014
00:38:36,020 --> 00:38:38,100
-你想怎么处理  -明天再说吧
- How do you want to handle it? - Let's talk about it tomorrow.

1015
00:38:38,100 --> 00:38:39,790
现在我还有别的事要做
Right now, I've got something else to do.

1016
00:38:40,750 --> 00:38:41,830
该死
Shit.

1017
00:38:42,400 --> 00:38:44,050
他们不会围攻哈维的
They wouldn't turn on Harvey.

1018
00:38:44,770 --> 00:38:46,960
卡荷尔想让我们逼他撤诉
Cahill wanted us to drop those cases anyway,

1019
00:38:46,960 --> 00:38:48,700
我真是帮他大忙了
and I just did him a big favor.

1020
00:38:48,700 --> 00:38:50,100
你之前也不可能知道啊
You couldn't have known that.

1021
00:38:50,400 --> 00:38:52,190
调查清楚是我的职责
It was my job to know that.

1022
00:38:58,860 --> 00:38:59,520
迈克
Hey, Mike?

1023
00:38:59,520 --> 00:39:01,600
-怎么了  -哈维·斯派克特来...
- Yeah. - Harvey Specter's here to--

1024
00:39:02,200 --> 00:39:03,970
哈维  有事吗
Harvey, what can I do for you?

1025
00:39:07,040 --> 00:39:08,820
我要感谢你送我的唱片带
I wanted to thank you for the recordings.

1026
00:39:08,820 --> 00:39:11,360
你专门过来就为了说这个吗
Is that why you came all the way down here?

1027
00:39:11,390 --> 00:39:13,820
我是来告诉你  我觉得你勾搭傅滋曼
I came to tell you I think you're making a big mistake

1028
00:39:13,820 --> 00:39:16,580
-是个大错误  -我就知道
- getting into bed with Forstman. - I knew it.

1029
00:39:16,580 --> 00:39:17,420
迈克  你不了解这家伙
Mike, you don't know this guy.

1030
00:39:17,420 --> 00:39:19,420
你几天前就可以来谢我
You could have thanked me for those recordings days ago,

1031
00:39:19,420 --> 00:39:21,240
但却偏偏挑在
but instead you picked the exact day

1032
00:39:21,240 --> 00:39:22,810
我找到新投资人的时候过来
that I find a new investor to show up

1033
00:39:22,810 --> 00:39:25,220
表达谢意  顺便给点友善的建议
with your thank-you and your friendly advice.

1034
00:39:25,590 --> 00:39:26,430
这不是什么招数
This isn't some move.

1035
00:39:26,430 --> 00:39:28,160
-你每一步都是招数  -迈克
- You only make moves. - Mike.

1036
00:39:28,160 --> 00:39:29,420
那你就告诉我
Hey, tell me right now

1037
00:39:29,420 --> 00:39:30,580
如果换作是你
that you wouldn't do the same thing

1038
00:39:30,580 --> 00:39:32,210
你不会这么做
if you were in my position.

1039
00:39:32,330 --> 00:39:33,500
我也曾这样
I was.

1040
00:39:34,570 --> 00:39:35,700
也确实那么做了
And I did.

1041
00:39:36,430 --> 00:39:37,200
怎么
What?

1042
00:39:37,200 --> 00:39:39,780
你以为我们之间的恩怨是因为什么车吗
You think our grudge is about some car?

1043
00:39:39,980 --> 00:39:40,840
你他妈在说什么啊
What the hell are you talking about?

1044
00:39:40,840 --> 00:39:43,420
我早几年曾跟他做了一笔黑幕交易
When I was younger, I made a shady deal with him,

1045
00:39:43,420 --> 00:39:45,160
-因此付出了代价  -谁说我在做
- and I paid for it. - Who says that I'm making--

1046
00:39:45,170 --> 00:39:46,550
如果你还没做  总有一天会做的
If you haven't, you will,

1047
00:39:46,550 --> 00:39:48,680
因为傅滋曼可不会做没有回报
because Forstman doesn't throw money around

1048
00:39:48,690 --> 00:39:50,160
白白撒钱的亏本生意
without getting something in return.

1049
00:39:50,160 --> 00:39:51,950
他会赚到钱
He's gonna get money in return.

1050
00:39:51,950 --> 00:39:53,240
他的心中钱只排在第三位
Money is third on his list.

1051
00:39:53,240 --> 00:39:55,170
前两位是报复人
The first two are getting back at people

1052
00:39:55,170 --> 00:39:56,200
和控制人
and getting control of people.

1053
00:39:56,200 --> 00:39:57,370
也许你在让路易阻止我
Maybe you should have thought of that

1054
00:39:57,370 --> 00:39:59,750
找扬诺普洛斯帮忙前就该想到这点了
before you had Louis cut me off from Gianopolous,

1055
00:39:59,750 --> 00:40:02,490
因为现在我别无选择了
because now I have no other choice!

1056
00:40:09,800 --> 00:40:11,410
你永远都有得选
You always have a choice.

1057
00:40:19,050 --> 00:40:22,700
皮尔蒙特航空电子全面逆袭
Here's to turning around Piedmont Avionics.

1058
00:40:24,850 --> 00:40:25,640
怎么了
What?

1059
00:40:25,950 --> 00:40:26,740
没什么
Nothing.

1060
00:40:28,830 --> 00:40:29,880
现在几点了
What time is it?

1061
00:40:29,970 --> 00:40:32,530
已经太晚了  来不及改主意了
Too late for you to change your mind.

1062
00:40:33,460 --> 00:40:36,570
洛根  董事会一定会惊艳的
Logan, the board is going to be wowed.

1063
00:40:36,580 --> 00:40:38,350
要是我像你这么自信就好了
Well, I wish I had your confidence.

1064
00:40:38,350 --> 00:40:42,010
你一点都不缺自信
You are not short in the confidence department.

1065
00:40:42,070 --> 00:40:44,370
你不用恭维我
Oh, you don't have to pay me compliments.

1066
00:40:44,370 --> 00:40:45,830
我是想羞辱你的
I meant it as an insult.

1067
00:40:46,780 --> 00:40:49,290
如果在律所干得不顺心
You know, if this law thing doesn't work out--

1068
00:40:49,290 --> 00:40:51,190
我还可以去搞风投
Then I could have a career in venture capital?

1069
00:40:51,200 --> 00:40:53,420
不  我是想请你来当我的助理
No, I was gonna say you could be my assistant.

1070
00:40:54,250 --> 00:40:55,680
搞笑
Hilarious.

1071
00:40:56,180 --> 00:40:57,580
说真的  瑞秋  我...
Seriously, Rachel, I--

1072
00:40:59,030 --> 00:41:00,850
没有你  我根本做不到
I couldn't have done it without you.

1073
00:41:01,300 --> 00:41:02,540
不  你可以的
Yes, you could have.

1074
00:41:03,700 --> 00:41:05,330
只是不可能这么好
It just wouldn't have been as good.

1075
00:41:06,220 --> 00:41:07,290
谦虚
Humility.

1076
00:41:07,770 --> 00:41:09,420
也是我喜欢你的一点
Another thing I love about you.

1077
00:41:26,610 --> 00:41:28,030
洛根  我该走了
Logan, I should go.

1078
00:41:29,570 --> 00:41:30,750
瑞秋  我
Rachel, I--

1079
00:41:35,080 --> 00:41:36,260
祝你明天好运
Good luck tomorrow.

