1
00:00:00,930 --> 00:00:02,250
《诉讼双雄》前情提要

2
00:00:02,280 --> 00:00:04,580
113个女性员工
113 female employees

3
00:00:04,650 --> 00:00:06,150
来自所有22个不同部门
across all 22 divisions.

4
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:07,690
知道她们的共同点吗
You know what they have in common?

5
00:00:07,760 --> 00:00:10,020
都因是女性而被拒绝升职
All denied promotions due to the fact that they're women.

6
00:00:10,090 --> 00:00:12,930
路易多久约你出去一次
How often does Louis ask you out?

7
00:00:12,990 --> 00:00:15,130
-每天  -有法律保护你
- Every single day. - There are laws

8
00:00:15,200 --> 00:00:17,100
不受性骚扰的
to protect you from sexual harassment, you know.

9
00:00:17,160 --> 00:00:18,530
-你来这干嘛  -给你送香槟
- What are you doing here? - Delivering champagne.

10
00:00:18,600 --> 00:00:20,170
你肯定喝得起
I see you can afford it,

11
00:00:20,170 --> 00:00:22,540
毕竟你从客户那儿捞的钞票
since the money you've been stealing from our clients

12
00:00:22,600 --> 00:00:24,370
又没拿去给你老婆治病
hasn't been going to your wife's cancer treatments.

13
00:00:24,440 --> 00:00:25,740
莫妮卡  你好吗
Hey, Monica, how's it going?

14
00:00:25,810 --> 00:00:27,470
你干的好事
What the hell are you doing?

15
00:00:27,540 --> 00:00:30,030
要让莫妮卡·伊顿起诉丹尼尔·哈德曼
Trying to get Monica Eton to file a sexual harassment suit

16
00:00:30,030 --> 00:00:31,280
性骚扰
against Daniel Hardman?

17
00:00:31,350 --> 00:00:33,780
你以为是在帮我  就此打住
I know you think you're trying to help me, but drop it.

18
00:00:33,850 --> 00:00:35,650
-迈克做到了吗  -很到位
- Did mike pull it off? - Yep.

19
00:00:35,720 --> 00:00:37,780
-他怀疑你知情吗  -没有
- He suspect you were in on it? - Nope.

20
00:00:37,850 --> 00:00:39,690
签了这份保密协议
Sign this confidentiality agreement.

21
00:00:39,750 --> 00:00:41,090
我不会跟公司要一分钱
I'll waive my claim.

22
00:00:41,160 --> 00:00:42,790
机不可失  签不签随你
One-time offer, take it or leave it.

23
00:00:42,860 --> 00:00:44,490
我把案子移交他人了
I decided to farm out the case.

24
00:00:44,560 --> 00:00:48,600
我猜是  丹尼尔·哈德曼
Let me guess. Daniel Hardman.

25
00:00:50,630 --> 00:00:53,100
请说出您的姓名
Please state your name for the record.

26
00:00:53,170 --> 00:00:54,600
斯洛恩· 莫斯利
Sloane Moseley.

27
00:00:54,670 --> 00:00:56,800
您在福尔松食品公司所任何职
And what is your position at Folsom Foods?

28
00:00:56,870 --> 00:00:59,270
这在我方当事人前两次取证中
This was all established during my client's first

29
00:00:59,340 --> 00:01:01,370
-都陈述过了  -抱歉
- and second deposition. - I'm sorry.

30
00:01:01,440 --> 00:01:02,740
我只是想了解清楚
I'm just getting up to speed.

31
00:01:02,810 --> 00:01:04,310
完成我自己的取证材料
I like to establish my own facts.

32
00:01:04,380 --> 00:01:06,350
-或者伪造材料  -你说什么
- Or manufacture them. - Excuse me?

33
00:01:06,410 --> 00:01:09,380
给对方律师一些尊重吧
Let's show opposing counsel some respect.

34
00:01:09,450 --> 00:01:10,880
-人渣  -人渣
- Douchebag. - Douchebag.

35
00:01:10,950 --> 00:01:13,520
负责市场研究的区域副总裁
Regional vice president of marketing and research.

36
00:01:13,590 --> 00:01:15,690
有多少女性高管和您共职
And how many female executives work alongside you?

37
00:01:15,760 --> 00:01:17,060
-三个  -九个高管中
- Three. - Making a total

38
00:01:17,120 --> 00:01:19,460
-一共有四名女性  -有问题可问吗
- of four in a department of nine. - Is there a question?

39
00:01:19,530 --> 00:01:20,830
有
Yes.

40
00:01:20,900 --> 00:01:23,060
男女资深合伙人的比例
What is the ratio of men to women senior partners

41
00:01:23,130 --> 00:01:24,660
在皮尔逊·哈德曼是多少
at Pearson Hardman?

42
00:01:24,730 --> 00:01:27,200
什么  她可不知道这些
Wha--she has no knowledge of that.

43
00:01:27,270 --> 00:01:28,500
那我就问你
Then I direct the question to you.

44
00:01:28,570 --> 00:01:29,740
我知道答案
And I have the answer,

45
00:01:29,800 --> 00:01:31,240
但和这个案子无关
But it's not relevant to this case.

46
00:01:31,310 --> 00:01:32,970
什么意思  杰西卡·皮尔逊的
What do you mean? Jessica Pearson's hiring

47
00:01:33,040 --> 00:01:35,280
雇佣行为和本案直接相关
and firing practices are directly relevant to the case.

48
00:01:35,340 --> 00:01:37,640
如果下一个问题仍和福尔松食品公司无关
If the next question isn't regarding Folsom Foods,

49
00:01:37,710 --> 00:01:39,950
这次取证就结束了
this deposition's over.

50
00:01:40,010 --> 00:01:42,680
福尔松食品公司
Folsom Foods?

51
00:01:44,490 --> 00:01:47,220
抱歉  你们也知道  我刚刚接手了
So sorry. As you know, I just took over

52
00:01:47,290 --> 00:01:49,890
45个不同的案子  我搞糊涂了
45 different cases. I get confused.

53
00:01:49,960 --> 00:01:51,590
以为今天是针对皮尔逊·哈德曼取证
I thought we were deposing Pearson Hardman today.

54
00:01:51,660 --> 00:01:54,490
你在说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?

55
00:01:54,560 --> 00:01:56,530
上帝啊  难道
Oh, my God. Did--

56
00:01:56,600 --> 00:01:59,270
难道我忘了给你们法庭传票吗
did I forget to give you the subpoena?

57
00:01:59,330 --> 00:02:01,200
皮尔逊·哈德曼律所被诉不公正解雇
Pearson Hardman is being sued for wrongful termination

58
00:02:01,270 --> 00:02:04,100
赔偿金一千万  正式告知你们
in the amount of $10 million. You have been served.

59
00:02:04,170 --> 00:02:06,610
不公正解雇  你不进监狱已经是万幸了
Wrongful termination? You're lucky you're not in jail.

60
00:02:06,670 --> 00:02:10,080
当事人不是他  是莫妮卡·伊顿
It's not on his behalf. It's on Monica Eton's.

61
00:02:10,140 --> 00:02:11,540
实际上是你给的我灵感
I actually got the idea from you.

62
00:02:11,610 --> 00:02:12,950
你说什么
Excuse me?

63
00:02:13,010 --> 00:02:16,280
这家公司对那位女士的所作所为是不公的
What this firm did to that woman was unconscionable.

64
00:02:16,350 --> 00:02:18,480
你这个人渣
You piece of shit.

65
00:02:18,550 --> 00:02:20,720
莫妮卡·伊顿活该被开除
Monica Eton deserved to get fired.

66
00:02:20,790 --> 00:02:22,420
我要向陪审团传证的
The eight women I'm gonna stack

67
00:02:22,490 --> 00:02:24,320
八位女性可不同意你这么说
the jury with might disagree with that.

68
00:02:24,390 --> 00:02:25,960
当他们知道你挪用公司资金
Not once they learn she was sleeping with you

69
00:02:26,030 --> 00:02:27,530
而同时她还在和你睡觉后  就会同意了
While you were embezzling from this firm.

70
00:02:27,600 --> 00:02:29,760
确切的说  他们怎么会知道呢
And how, exactly, are they going to learn that?

71
00:02:29,830 --> 00:02:32,170
屋里的三人之一会告诉他们
One of the three people in this room is gonna tell them.

72
00:02:32,230 --> 00:02:33,570
我猜不会是你
I'm guessing it won't be you.

73
00:02:33,630 --> 00:02:35,440
我猜也不会是你们俩
I'm afraid it won't be one of you either.

74
00:02:35,500 --> 00:02:36,740
你要杀了我们吗
You gonna kill us?

75
00:02:36,800 --> 00:02:38,640
用不着
Oh, I won't need to.

76
00:02:38,710 --> 00:02:40,410
我离开这里那晚
You're bound by the confidentiality agreement

77
00:02:40,470 --> 00:02:43,510
杰西卡签署的保密协议会约束你
Jessica signed the night I left.

78
00:02:45,480 --> 00:02:47,650
丹尼尔·哈德曼的所有行为
"All knowledge of any activity of Daniel Hardman--"

79
00:02:47,720 --> 00:02:48,880
我知道上面写了什么
I know what it goddamn says.

80
00:02:48,950 --> 00:02:50,850
你那么快就签字了  我都不确定
You signed it so quickly, I wasn't sure.

81
00:02:50,920 --> 00:02:52,320
好吧
Fine.

82
00:02:52,390 --> 00:02:53,890
我知道这是敲诈
I know a shakedown when I see one.

83
00:02:53,950 --> 00:02:55,790
-你想要什么  -不是我想要什么
- What do you want? - It's not what I want.

84
00:02:55,860 --> 00:02:56,920
而是莫妮卡想要什么
It's what Monica wants.

85
00:02:56,990 --> 00:02:58,520
到底要什么
And what is that?

86
00:02:58,590 --> 00:03:00,760
补偿  当迈克·罗斯
Payback. You see, when Mike Ross

87
00:03:00,830 --> 00:03:02,530
把那份捏造的诉状给她时
brought that trumped-up suit to her,

88
00:03:02,530 --> 00:03:03,930
她非常伤心
she was very upset.

89
00:03:04,000 --> 00:03:05,930
她回想起你对她的作为
It brought back the memory of what you did to her.

90
00:03:06,000 --> 00:03:07,270
我什么都没对她做
I didn't do shit to her.

91
00:03:07,330 --> 00:03:08,740
她可不这么认为
That wasn't how she saw it.

92
00:03:08,800 --> 00:03:10,140
但你一点都没有帮助她
Yet you didn't lift a finger to help her.

93
00:03:10,200 --> 00:03:12,070
我当时想帮
I wanted to at the time.

94
00:03:12,140 --> 00:03:14,240
但我不能伤害自己的公司  现在可以了
But I couldn't very well attack my own firm, now could I?

95
00:03:14,310 --> 00:03:16,510
-以前不是没伤过  -说得好
- Never stopped you before. - Touche.

96
00:03:16,580 --> 00:03:17,910
但现在你也不能说出来
But you can't mention that either.

97
00:03:17,980 --> 00:03:19,080
这里完事了
We're done.

98
00:03:19,150 --> 00:03:21,880
哈维  请你把这个人渣送出去
Harvey, will you escort this piece of filth out of the building,

99
00:03:21,950 --> 00:03:25,290
确保他在出去的路上不犯事
make sure he doesn't commit any crimes on the way out?

100
00:03:35,260 --> 00:03:36,460
顺便告诉你  迈克·罗斯
Oh, by the way, Mike Ross,

101
00:03:36,530 --> 00:03:39,100
他写的那个控诉草案真是艺术品
virtuoso job drafting that complaint.

102
00:03:39,170 --> 00:03:40,470
我所做的一切
All I had to do was search

103
00:03:40,530 --> 00:03:43,000
只是把“丹尼尔·哈德曼”替换成“某人”
and replace "Daniel Hardman" with "Anonymous."

104
00:03:43,070 --> 00:03:45,140
他的另一件大师级作品就是
Almost as virtuoso as the job he did

105
00:03:45,210 --> 00:03:50,080
让你相信劳伦斯·坎普签署了书面陈述
convincing you lawrence kemp signed that affidavit.

106
00:03:50,140 --> 00:03:52,150
你快忍不了了吧
Must stick in your craw...

107
00:03:52,210 --> 00:03:54,250
每天都走过写着我名字的墙
having to walk by my name day after day.

108
00:03:54,320 --> 00:03:55,680
我们会习惯的
Oh, we'll get to it.

109
00:03:55,750 --> 00:03:57,020
首先我们把你的办公室
First we had to turn your old office

110
00:03:57,080 --> 00:03:58,520
变成了新的会议室
into the new conference room.

111
00:03:58,590 --> 00:04:00,390
杰西卡和我在公司政变的时候
When Jessica and I engineered our coup,

112
00:04:00,450 --> 00:04:02,090
几分钟之内她就把那几个名字摘下了
She had that sign down within minutes.

113
00:04:02,160 --> 00:04:04,020
施密特  高登  范·戴克
Schmidt, Gordon, Van Dyke.

114
00:04:04,090 --> 00:04:06,230
你走时杰西卡就想把你名字弄下来
Jessica wanted it down the second you were gone.

115
00:04:06,290 --> 00:04:08,830
我跟她说太早
I told her it was too soon.

116
00:04:08,900 --> 00:04:10,560
不对
No.

117
00:04:10,630 --> 00:04:13,430
你对她说你想当冠名合伙人  她说不行
You asked her to be name partner, and she said "No."

118
00:04:13,500 --> 00:04:15,270
知道为什么吗
And do you know why?

119
00:04:15,340 --> 00:04:19,210
因为在内心深处  她不信任你
Because deep in her heart, she doesn't trust you.

120
00:04:19,270 --> 00:04:21,410
她信任我  让我把你打得满地找牙
She trusted me to kick your ass.

121
00:04:21,480 --> 00:04:23,240
两次
Twice.

122
00:04:23,310 --> 00:04:26,050
或许吧
Maybe.

123
00:04:28,350 --> 00:04:30,080
但我看到那时的表情了
But I saw that look back there.

124
00:04:30,150 --> 00:04:33,320
她没告诉你保密协议的事情
She didn't tell you about the confidentiality agreement,

125
00:04:33,390 --> 00:04:35,220
不是吗
Did she?

126
00:04:41,580 --> 00:04:44,580
人人影视
YYeTs.com

127
00:04:41,580 --> 00:04:44,580
原创翻译  双语字幕

128
00:04:41,580 --> 00:04:44,580
■

129
00:04:41,580 --> 00:04:44,580
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

130
00:04:44,580 --> 00:04:49,580
 翻译：油炸电风扇 小饭 贺天天 圈圈 米苏

131
00:04:44,580 --> 00:04:49,580
■

132
00:04:49,580 --> 00:04:54,580
时间轴：lemony 迟迟  校对：lemony 油炸电风扇

133
00:04:49,580 --> 00:04:54,580
■

134
00:04:54,580 --> 00:04:59,580
后期 & 特效：仓鼠sama     总监：月月

135
00:04:54,580 --> 00:04:59,580
■

136
00:05:06,240 --> 00:05:08,410
第二季 第十四集

137
00:05:06,240 --> 00:05:08,410
诉 讼 双 雄

138
00:05:06,240 --> 00:05:08,410
蓝光-1080P-SHORTBREHD版调轴风格微修：字幕雷哥

139
00:05:14,490 --> 00:05:15,560
你脑子里当时想什么呢
What the hell were you thinking?

140
00:05:15,630 --> 00:05:17,890
我不想说这件事了  哈维
I don't want to discuss this, Harvey.

141
00:05:17,960 --> 00:05:19,900
他放弃合伙人资格  放弃股份
He gave up his partnership, his money,

142
00:05:19,960 --> 00:05:21,830
还有投票权  这个买卖很合适
and his voting rights. It was a good deal.

143
00:05:21,900 --> 00:05:23,130
我做了交易  已成定局
I did it, and it's done.

144
00:05:23,200 --> 00:05:25,000
现在他回来  反咬我们一口
And now it's come back to bite us in the ass.

145
00:05:25,070 --> 00:05:26,070
咱们得和解
We have to settle.

146
00:05:26,140 --> 00:05:27,840
我不会和解
I am not settling.

147
00:05:27,900 --> 00:05:29,670
咱们已经无路可走
Our backs are against the wall,

148
00:05:29,740 --> 00:05:31,670
还要把资源耗尽在一宗必败的案子上吗
and we're gonna drain our resources on a case

149
00:05:31,740 --> 00:05:33,980
而必败的原因是你切断了我们的路
that we can't win just because you boxed us in?

150
00:05:34,040 --> 00:05:35,880
那是个接受或放弃的出价
It was a take-it-or-leave-it offer.

151
00:05:35,950 --> 00:05:37,650
我只有一分钟时间
I had one minute.

152
00:05:37,710 --> 00:05:39,850
我想和那个人尽快了断  于是我就签了字
I wanted to be done with the man, so I took it.

153
00:05:39,920 --> 00:05:42,050
你告诉我  别匆忙做决定
You told me never to make rash decisions

154
00:05:42,120 --> 00:05:43,320
而你却做了这样的事
And then you do this.

155
00:05:43,390 --> 00:05:45,620
我说了  我当时别无选择
I told you, I didn't have a choice.

156
00:05:45,690 --> 00:05:48,060
你决定不告诉我时  也不能选择吗
Did you have a choice when you decided to keep it from me?

157
00:05:48,120 --> 00:05:50,030
我以为这件事不会再露出水面了
I didn't think it would ever come up again.

158
00:05:50,090 --> 00:05:52,630
这个理由不充分
That is not a good enough reason.

159
00:05:56,070 --> 00:06:00,900
他对你说什么了
What did he tell you?

160
00:06:00,970 --> 00:06:04,240
他对我说  你永远不会让我的名字上墙
He told me you'd never put my name on the door.

161
00:06:04,310 --> 00:06:06,540
他对我说  有一天你会盯上我
He told me you'd come after me someday,

162
00:06:06,610 --> 00:06:10,450
或许威胁到我的家庭  就像你对他那样
maybe even threaten my family the same way you threatened his.

163
00:06:10,510 --> 00:06:12,350
一件你从未咨询过我的小事
A little something you never bothered to consult me on.

164
00:06:12,420 --> 00:06:13,580
我不需要咨询你
I didn't have to.

165
00:06:13,650 --> 00:06:15,280
你告诉过我不惜一切代价
You'd have told me to do whatever it took.

166
00:06:15,350 --> 00:06:17,120
-那不是重点  -什么是重点
- That's not the point. - Well, what's the point?

167
00:06:17,190 --> 00:06:19,050
你隐瞒了我
You kept it from me.

168
00:06:19,120 --> 00:06:20,890
我没在意
I let it go

169
00:06:20,960 --> 00:06:22,690
因为我知道他只是想对我洗脑
because I knew he was just trying to get into my head,

170
00:06:22,760 --> 00:06:26,600
就如同他现在又想洗你的脑
the same way he's trying to get into your head now.

171
00:06:26,660 --> 00:06:28,100
那他要对你取证
What's gonna happen when he deposes you,

172
00:06:28,160 --> 00:06:29,630
而你又不能说出全部  怎么办
and you can't tell the full story?

173
00:06:29,700 --> 00:06:30,970
哈维  我不知道
I don't know, Harvey.

174
00:06:31,030 --> 00:06:32,940
但我之前相信你能打败他
But I trusted you to beat him before,

175
00:06:33,000 --> 00:06:37,270
现在我同样相信  你能再次打败他
and I'm trusting you to beat him again now.

176
00:06:40,440 --> 00:06:42,080
你有时间吗
Hey, uh, do you have a minute?

177
00:06:42,150 --> 00:06:43,350
也只有一分钟了  我压力很大
That's about all I have. I'm under pressure.

178
00:06:43,410 --> 00:06:45,150
-我得赶快做完这个  -我知道
- I've got to get this done. - Yeah, I know.

179
00:06:45,220 --> 00:06:47,850
我们都被卷入了福尔松食品公司的案子
We're all swamped with this Folsom Foods thing, but, uh,

180
00:06:47,920 --> 00:06:52,490
但我有个案子需要你帮忙  私下的
I need your help with a case that's a little more...personal.

181
00:06:52,560 --> 00:06:53,820
我的确卷入了福尔松食品公司的案子
I am swamped with Folsom Foods,

182
00:06:53,890 --> 00:06:55,220
但我早来了一个小时
but I came in early to carve out

183
00:06:55,290 --> 00:06:57,330
为的是做一些我个人的事情
an hour to work on something personal of my own.

184
00:06:57,390 --> 00:07:01,630
什么事
Hmm, what is it?

185
00:07:01,700 --> 00:07:04,430
哈佛入学申请
Harvard application.

186
00:07:04,500 --> 00:07:05,740
瑞秋  好极了
Rachel, that's great.

187
00:07:05,740 --> 00:07:06,800
能被录取才是好极了
It's great if I get in,

188
00:07:06,870 --> 00:07:08,470
而如果我不做完这个  就不会被录取
and I'm not gonna get in if I don't get this done,

189
00:07:08,540 --> 00:07:10,510
而如果大家一直烦我  我就做不完这个
and I'm not gonna get it done if people keep bothering me.

190
00:07:10,570 --> 00:07:11,640
有人一直在烦你吗
Do people keep bothering you?

191
00:07:11,710 --> 00:07:12,910
没有
No.

192
00:07:12,980 --> 00:07:16,210
好吧  那一切都很顺利啊
Okay. So this is going well then.

193
00:07:16,280 --> 00:07:19,450
录取比例低于十二分之一
Less than 1 out of every 12 people who applies gets in.

194
00:07:19,520 --> 00:07:20,880
如果我不是那一个呢
What if I'm not one of those people?

195
00:07:20,950 --> 00:07:24,690
不知道  或许你可以去别的学校
I don't know, maybe you'll get in somewhere else.

196
00:07:26,560 --> 00:07:27,690
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.

197
00:07:27,760 --> 00:07:29,560
我不想安排一个撤退路线
I don't want to have a fallback.

198
00:07:29,630 --> 00:07:33,060
你是说备选方案吗  一个合理的备选方案
You mean a backup? A logical plan "B"?

199
00:07:33,130 --> 00:07:35,000
迈克  在考法学院这件事上
Mike, I've been half-in, half-out

200
00:07:35,070 --> 00:07:37,530
我踌躇不决很多年了  我受够了
of committing to this for years. I'm done with that.

201
00:07:37,600 --> 00:07:39,470
读法学院是大事
Going to law school is committing.

202
00:07:39,540 --> 00:07:40,800
我不是只想读法学院
I don't want to go to law school.

203
00:07:40,870 --> 00:07:42,170
我想读哈佛
I want to go to Harvard.

204
00:07:42,240 --> 00:07:43,570
只是因为你父亲读了哈佛  不意味着
Just because your father went there doesn't mean

205
00:07:43,640 --> 00:07:44,770
你也要读哈佛
you need to go there too.

206
00:07:44,840 --> 00:07:48,640
不是那个原因
That's not why.

207
00:07:48,710 --> 00:07:50,850
你想来皮尔逊·哈德曼工作
You want to work at pearson hardman.

208
00:07:50,910 --> 00:07:53,880
如果我不读哈佛  我就不能来这里工作
And if I don't go there, then I can't work here.

209
00:07:53,950 --> 00:07:56,220
需要帮忙否
You need any help?

210
00:07:56,290 --> 00:08:00,690
不用  没事  我自己来
No, it's okay. I'm gonna do this on my own.

211
00:08:00,760 --> 00:08:03,960
-好的  -我很抱歉
- Okay. - I'm so sorr...

212
00:08:04,030 --> 00:08:05,430
你要我帮你干嘛来着
What did you need help with?

213
00:08:05,500 --> 00:08:09,000
没事了  我自己来
It's okay. I'm gonna do it on my own.

214
00:08:09,070 --> 00:08:11,100
唐娜  我需要你帮忙
Donna, I need your help.

215
00:08:11,170 --> 00:08:13,800
帮什么忙
With what?

216
00:08:13,870 --> 00:08:15,370
-哈德曼  -说服哈维
- Hardman. - I want you to convince Harvey

217
00:08:15,440 --> 00:08:16,840
让我做莫妮卡·伊顿的案子
to let me on the Monica Eton case.

218
00:08:16,910 --> 00:08:18,040
抱歉  路易  我无能为力
I'm sorry, Louis. I can't do that.

219
00:08:18,110 --> 00:08:19,540
唐娜  别这样
Donna, come on.

220
00:08:19,610 --> 00:08:21,940
-他搞得我像个傻子  -他也这样对我
- He made me look like a fool. - He did the same thing to me!

221
00:08:22,010 --> 00:08:23,210
我要报复
Well, I need revenge.

222
00:08:23,280 --> 00:08:24,550
我也是
So do I.

223
00:08:24,610 --> 00:08:25,950
瞧吧  那你为什么不帮我向哈维说情
See, then why won't you ask Harvey for me?

224
00:08:26,020 --> 00:08:28,750
因为哈维要自己处理
Because Harvey needs to handle this himself.

225
00:08:31,320 --> 00:08:33,560
就是说你的拒绝
So this has nothing to do with any residual issues you've had

226
00:08:33,620 --> 00:08:34,990
跟我曾经的所作所为无关了
with me and my past behavior?

227
00:08:35,060 --> 00:08:37,860
对
No.

228
00:08:37,930 --> 00:08:41,000
因为我从没跟他说过
Because I never told him.

229
00:08:41,060 --> 00:08:43,170
我从未对哈维说过
I never told Harvey how sorry I was

230
00:08:43,230 --> 00:08:45,100
错信叛徒的我对有多抱歉
for trusting someone that betrayed us all.

231
00:08:45,170 --> 00:08:47,240
-路易  他知道  -要不是我的错
- Louis, he knows. - I mean, that bastard

232
00:08:47,300 --> 00:08:49,170
那混蛋根本不会还待在这里
wouldn't even be here right now if it wasn't for me.

233
00:08:49,240 --> 00:08:50,810
最多是个鬼鬼祟祟的合伙人
He'd just be some partner skulking around,

234
00:08:50,870 --> 00:08:52,310
要是我没给他投票  他才不会赢
never having won if I hadn't voted for him.

235
00:08:52,380 --> 00:08:54,010
听着  会没事的
Look, it's gonna be okay.

236
00:08:54,080 --> 00:08:56,050
成功就是最好的报复
Success is the best revenge.

237
00:08:56,110 --> 00:08:59,450
屁话
Bullshit.

238
00:08:59,520 --> 00:09:02,950
报复才是最好的报复
Revenge is the best revenge.

239
00:09:05,860 --> 00:09:07,920
哈维  你去哪里  现在才十点半
Harvey, where are you going? It's only 10:30.

240
00:09:07,990 --> 00:09:09,960
-你要扣我工资吗  -我是认真的
- You gonna dock my pay? - I'm serious.

241
00:09:10,030 --> 00:09:11,360
我拿到了些好东西
I've got some really good stuff here.

242
00:09:11,430 --> 00:09:13,630
首先  哈德曼的非竞争条款仍然有效
First of all, Hardman's non-compete is still in effect.

243
00:09:13,700 --> 00:09:16,270
-他现在还不能当律师  -只是在纽约
- He can't even be practicing law. - In New York.

244
00:09:16,330 --> 00:09:18,070
那你以为咱们是在哪里
Where the hell do you think we are?

245
00:09:18,130 --> 00:09:20,770
他在新泽西工作  有独立的工作室
He's working out of Jersey. He's got an office of one.

246
00:09:20,840 --> 00:09:22,600
银行账户  汽车服务  手机
Bank account, car service, cell phone.

247
00:09:22,670 --> 00:09:23,840
这些都是在纽约开的户
I mean, all of them are based in New York.

248
00:09:23,910 --> 00:09:25,040
咱们可以打这个点
We can fight it.

249
00:09:25,110 --> 00:09:28,180
-那正中他下怀  -什么
- That's exactly what he wants. - What?

250
00:09:28,240 --> 00:09:30,850
他的公司章程  办公室  电话
Articles of incorporation, office, landline,

251
00:09:30,910 --> 00:09:32,780
公司汽车  都在新泽西
company car, all in Jersey.

252
00:09:32,850 --> 00:09:35,320
他下好了套  想诱使我们起诉他
He's constructed it, so we'd be tempted to fight him,

253
00:09:35,390 --> 00:09:36,890
浪费我们的时间和资源  最后败诉
waste our time and resources, then lose.

254
00:09:36,950 --> 00:09:38,050
好吧  那我们接下来
Okay, fine. Then what we need to do next

255
00:09:38,120 --> 00:09:39,120
该好好调查莫妮卡·伊顿  我觉得
is dig into Monica Eton. I think--

256
00:09:39,190 --> 00:09:40,390
等等
Hold on.

257
00:09:40,460 --> 00:09:41,430
你跟的是福尔松食品公司的案子
You're on folsom foods,

258
00:09:41,430 --> 00:09:42,260
而不是莫妮卡·伊顿
not Monica Eton.

259
00:09:42,330 --> 00:09:44,290
哈维  他们用的正是我写的诉讼
Harvey, they're using the exact lawsuit I wrote,

260
00:09:44,360 --> 00:09:46,200
一字不差  我知道官司该怎么打
word for word. I know how to fight it.

261
00:09:46,260 --> 00:09:47,630
他告诉你的吗
Did he tell you that?

262
00:09:47,700 --> 00:09:49,870
不是  没必要  我读过了
No, he didn't need to. I read it.

263
00:09:49,930 --> 00:09:51,330
他不仅用了我的点子
I mean, he didn't just get the idea from me.

264
00:09:51,400 --> 00:09:52,870
整个执行令状也是我的
He got the whole execution from me.

265
00:09:52,940 --> 00:09:56,170
他这么做是想阻挠你
He's doing that because he's trying to get in your head.

266
00:09:56,240 --> 00:09:58,440
这不是你的错  是我们共同造成的
This isn't your fault. We did this together.

267
00:09:58,510 --> 00:09:59,880
那就让我帮你纠正它
Then let me help you fix it.

268
00:09:59,940 --> 00:10:01,580
抱歉  那些文件帮不了我
I'm sorry. Those papers can't help me,

269
00:10:01,640 --> 00:10:03,280
你也帮不了
and neither can you.

270
00:10:03,350 --> 00:10:07,220
哈
Har--

271
00:10:12,060 --> 00:10:13,360
我叫瑞秋
Rachel.

272
00:10:13,420 --> 00:10:14,390
对  对  我知道你是谁
Yes, yes. I know who you are.

273
00:10:14,460 --> 00:10:15,960
只是没想到你在这
I just wasn't expecting you.

274
00:10:16,030 --> 00:10:18,660
我并不住这里
Um, I don't live here.

275
00:10:21,200 --> 00:10:22,300
-你一定是来见我爸的  -是的
- You must be here to see my dad. - Yes, I am.

276
00:10:22,370 --> 00:10:23,700
请进
Please, come in.

277
00:10:23,770 --> 00:10:25,400
他在里面  在看录下来的比赛
He's just in the back. He TiVo'd the game.

278
00:10:25,470 --> 00:10:28,570
-喷气机队吗  -巨人队
- Jets? - Giants.

279
00:10:28,640 --> 00:10:31,910
知我心者
Man after my own heart.

280
00:10:31,980 --> 00:10:34,280
为什么防线上总挤满
Why is it the defensive line is always packed with a bunch

281
00:10:34,340 --> 00:10:36,950
大个壮实黑人  进攻线上
of big, strong, black guys and the offensive line

282
00:10:37,010 --> 00:10:39,450
全堆着大个白人胖子
packed with big, fat, white guys?

283
00:10:39,520 --> 00:10:41,320
不知道  但瞧瞧你
Well, I don't know. But looking at you,

284
00:10:41,380 --> 00:10:44,420
倒是两边都适合
you've got a foot in both camps.

285
00:10:44,490 --> 00:10:46,090
我猜你不是来求助的吧
I guess you're not here to ask a favor.

286
00:10:46,160 --> 00:10:48,120
不是  我是来帮你的
No. I'm here to do you a favor.

287
00:10:49,430 --> 00:10:50,330
趁时机未晚  赶紧摆脱他
Get rid of him while you still can.

288
00:10:50,390 --> 00:10:51,760
杰西卡
Jessica--

289
00:10:51,830 --> 00:10:53,200
你不了解你同伴的底细 罗伯特
You do not know who you are in bed with, Robert.

290
00:10:53,260 --> 00:10:55,500
我们在法学院是同窗
I went to law school with the man.

291
00:10:55,570 --> 00:10:56,900
也许那时他像个王子
Well, he might have been a prince back then,

292
00:10:56,970 --> 00:10:58,200
但现在完全不是
but he sure as hell isn't one now.

293
00:10:58,270 --> 00:10:59,840
那来启发启发我
Then enlighten me.

294
00:10:59,900 --> 00:11:01,440
据我所知
Because from what I know,

295
00:11:01,500 --> 00:11:03,510
他离开公司是为了照顾他妻子
he left the firm to take care of his wife,

296
00:11:03,570 --> 00:11:05,240
而他回来后  你却逼他退出
and when he came back, you forced him out.

297
00:11:05,310 --> 00:11:08,080
这故事离真相远着呢
That's nowhere near the full story.

298
00:11:08,140 --> 00:11:12,710
事实如何  我洗耳恭听
What else is there? I'm listening.

299
00:11:12,780 --> 00:11:14,480
你签署了保密协议
You signed a confidentiality agreement.

300
00:11:14,550 --> 00:11:17,750
我不能说
I am precluded from speaking on that topic.

301
00:11:17,820 --> 00:11:19,290
恐怕你也不能说服我
Then I'm afraid you're precluded

302
00:11:19,360 --> 00:11:20,790
不让他负责这个案子
from convincing me to take him off this case.

303
00:11:20,860 --> 00:11:22,290
-罗伯特  -违背保密协议
- Robert-- - What's it gonna cost you

304
00:11:22,360 --> 00:11:24,090
你会被罚多少钱
to violate the agreement?

305
00:11:24,160 --> 00:11:26,800
跟我说说
Give me a number. Hmm?

306
00:11:26,860 --> 00:11:29,160
我估计得上百万吧
I'll assume it's in the millions.

307
00:11:29,230 --> 00:11:33,070
一千五百万
15.

308
00:11:33,140 --> 00:11:36,000
你还说我不了解我的合作伙伴
You said I didn't know the kind of man I was in bed with?

309
00:11:36,070 --> 00:11:38,770
现在看起来  我的合作伙伴
From the looks of it, I'm in bed with the kind of man

310
00:11:38,840 --> 00:11:43,550
已经扼住了你的喉咙
who's got you by the balls.

311
00:11:43,610 --> 00:11:45,480
别说我没警告过你
Don't say I didn't warn you.

312
00:11:45,550 --> 00:11:47,380
好好看比赛吧
Enjoy your game.

313
00:11:47,450 --> 00:11:49,420
顺便说一句
Oh, by the way...

314
00:11:49,490 --> 00:11:53,890
巨人队差一分落败
Giants lost by one.

315
00:11:54,510 --> 00:11:55,630
好了  哈维
All right, Harvey.

316
00:11:55,630 --> 00:11:57,430
你大半夜跑来我家
It's the middle of the night, you wanted in.

317
00:11:57,500 --> 00:11:59,400
要我帮你做什么
What can I do for you?

318
00:11:59,470 --> 00:12:02,000
我想谈些假设
I need to talk hypothetically.

319
00:12:02,070 --> 00:12:04,300
这假设跟一位前任冠名合伙人
Is this hypothetically about a suit being brought

320
00:12:04,370 --> 00:12:06,410
对抗他老东家的案子有关吗
by an ex-name partner against his old firm?

321
00:12:06,470 --> 00:12:08,670
我不能谈我诉讼表上的案子
You know I can't talk about a case that's on my own docket.

322
00:12:08,740 --> 00:12:09,910
那我向国税局报告
Would you prefer I tell the IRS

323
00:12:09,980 --> 00:12:12,240
九年前我与一位前途远大的法官
about a hypothetical conversation I had

324
00:12:12,310 --> 00:12:14,580
谈到的一些假设怎么样
with an up-and-coming judge nine years ago?

325
00:12:17,250 --> 00:12:17,950
说吧
Give it to me.

326
00:12:18,020 --> 00:12:20,050
这位冠名合伙人挪用公款时
The name partner in question was the one she had

327
00:12:20,120 --> 00:12:22,820
曾与她有过一段婚外情
an affair with while he was embezzling money from the firm.

328
00:12:22,890 --> 00:12:24,420
那就起诉  立案啊
So bring it up. Make your case.

329
00:12:24,490 --> 00:12:26,120
不行
We can't.

330
00:12:26,190 --> 00:12:28,060
他让你们签署了保密协议
He got you to sign a confidentiality agreement.

331
00:12:28,130 --> 00:12:29,430
是的
Yes.

332
00:12:29,500 --> 00:12:31,630
但协议的目的在于隔离他
But the spirit of the agreement was to shield him.

333
00:12:31,700 --> 00:12:33,230
如果开一个封闭听证会
If we had a sealed hearing,

334
00:12:33,300 --> 00:12:36,100
对于公开秘密你会怎么裁决
how would you rule on tossing the confidentiality?

335
00:12:36,170 --> 00:12:38,500
-恐怕你们还是得输  -为什么
- I'm afraid you'd lose. - Why?

336
00:12:38,570 --> 00:12:39,600
如果他是原告  那是一回事
If he were the plaintiff, it'd be one thing,

337
00:12:39,670 --> 00:12:41,070
但他是代理律师
but he's the attorney.

338
00:12:41,140 --> 00:12:42,870
我不能因为她所选择的律师而惩罚她
I can't punish the woman for her choice of attorney.

339
00:12:42,940 --> 00:12:45,940
如果他没有拿这个当论据呢
What if he doesn't make that argument?

340
00:12:46,010 --> 00:12:47,410
他会的
He will.

341
00:12:47,480 --> 00:12:49,680
他也来找你了
He came to see you too.

342
00:12:49,750 --> 00:12:53,450
两周前
Two weeks ago.

343
00:12:53,520 --> 00:12:55,390
抱歉  哈维
Sorry, Harvey.

344
00:13:07,190 --> 00:13:08,290
打扰一下
Excuse me.

345
00:13:08,360 --> 00:13:09,660
我是来
I'm here for my--

346
00:13:09,730 --> 00:13:11,970
我知道你来做什么
Oh, I know what you're here for.

347
00:13:12,030 --> 00:13:14,300
杰西卡的取证  三点很准时嘛
Jessica's deposition. 3:00 on the nose.

348
00:13:14,370 --> 00:13:15,970
我是准时的代言人
I'm nothing if not prompt.

349
00:13:16,040 --> 00:13:19,140
你是混蛋的代言人
You're nothing if not an asshole.

350
00:13:19,210 --> 00:13:20,370
你今天就是为此坐在这的吗
Is that why you're sitting out here?

351
00:13:20,440 --> 00:13:21,540
为了骂我吗
To call me that?

352
00:13:21,610 --> 00:13:23,340
不是  我只是想
No. I just wanted to personally

353
00:13:23,410 --> 00:13:24,840
亲自陪你去会议室
escort you to the conference room.

354
00:13:24,910 --> 00:13:27,350
我真幸运
Mm. Lucky me.

355
00:13:27,410 --> 00:13:30,220
这得走着瞧
We'll see about that.

356
00:13:35,760 --> 00:13:36,890
这是我原来的办公室
My old office.

357
00:13:36,960 --> 00:13:39,330
-哈维没说笑啊  -我出的主意
- Harvey wasn't kidding. - My idea.

358
00:13:39,390 --> 00:13:42,000
做了好多风水才把邪气驱走
It took a while to feng shui the evil out.

359
00:13:42,060 --> 00:13:45,800
听着  唐娜  我理解
Look, donna, I understand--

360
00:13:45,870 --> 00:13:48,470
你个卑鄙小人
You piece of shit.

361
00:13:48,540 --> 00:13:49,700
就这点能耐吗
Is that all you've got?

362
00:13:49,770 --> 00:13:52,340
我现在就走
Oh, I will go right now.

363
00:13:52,410 --> 00:13:54,170
你要起诉我吗
Are you gonna sue me?

364
00:13:54,240 --> 00:13:57,210
这里可没人能作证
Because I don't think anybody here is gonna testify.

365
00:13:57,280 --> 00:13:58,750
我从没想要伤害你
I never meant to hurt you.

366
00:13:58,810 --> 00:14:00,710
放那份备忘  害我被炒时也没吗
You mean when you planted that memo and got me fired?

367
00:14:00,780 --> 00:14:03,420
不是我做的
I did no such thing.

368
00:14:03,480 --> 00:14:04,880
而且任何涉及这个公司内部的案子
And any implication otherwise

369
00:14:04,950 --> 00:14:06,690
都可以被起诉
from within this firm is actionable.

370
00:14:06,750 --> 00:14:09,220
是啊没错  你从没想伤害我
Yeah, right. But you never meant to hurt me.

371
00:14:09,290 --> 00:14:11,920
我想无论是谁放的那份备忘
I'd imagine whoever planted that memo

372
00:14:11,990 --> 00:14:13,730
都以为你会拿出来当证据
thought that you would bring it forward.

373
00:14:13,790 --> 00:14:15,600
而且要是你这样做了的话
And if you had, the only thing that would have happened

374
00:14:15,660 --> 00:14:17,300
结果最多是被批评两句
to you is you would have been scolded.

375
00:14:17,360 --> 00:14:20,700
而哈维的律师生涯就玩完了
And Harvey's career would have been over.

376
00:14:20,770 --> 00:14:24,200
看来你俩真有一腿啊
So it really is like that between the two of you.

377
00:14:30,510 --> 00:14:33,350
你现在可以走了
You can go now.

378
00:14:33,410 --> 00:14:38,180
杰西卡的取证在另一间会议室
Jessica's deposition is in the other conference room.

379
00:14:44,290 --> 00:14:46,230
为了这次记录请陈述全名
Please state your full name for the record.

380
00:14:46,290 --> 00:14:49,500
杰西卡·卢尔德·皮尔逊
Jessica Lourdes Pearson.

381
00:14:49,560 --> 00:14:51,800
莫妮卡·伊顿从03年到07年的审核
Monica Eton's reviews from '03 to '07,

382
00:14:51,870 --> 00:14:54,200
全是优秀  是吗
all excellent, agreed?

383
00:14:54,270 --> 00:14:55,400
是的
Yes.

384
00:14:55,470 --> 00:14:57,700
那为什么要解雇她
Then why was she let go?

385
00:14:57,770 --> 00:15:00,140
原因有多个
That was determined by a variety of factors.

386
00:15:00,210 --> 00:15:01,470
其中之一是不是她曾与一位合伙人
Was one of the factors that she was having

387
00:15:01,540 --> 00:15:03,040
有过婚外情
an affair with a partner?

388
00:15:03,110 --> 00:15:04,680
我真高兴你把这点提出来
I'm so glad you brought that up,

389
00:15:04,750 --> 00:15:05,810
你个狗娘养的  因为
you little son of a bitch, because--

390
00:15:05,880 --> 00:15:06,880
暂停记录
Off the record.

391
00:15:06,950 --> 00:15:09,850
这么快
Hmm, so soon.

392
00:15:09,920 --> 00:15:11,650
我跟你说过可能会这样
I told you this would happen.

393
00:15:11,720 --> 00:15:13,920
他想引诱你违反保密协议
He's baiting you into breaching confidentiality.

394
00:15:13,990 --> 00:15:16,120
我准备好咬住他  同归于尽了
And I'm ready to bite down and drag him in with me.

395
00:15:16,190 --> 00:15:19,230
别这样  我们玩不起
Don't. We can't afford it.

396
00:15:22,100 --> 00:15:23,760
不
No.

397
00:15:23,830 --> 00:15:25,770
外遇本身不是原因
The affair itself was not a factor.

398
00:15:25,830 --> 00:15:28,870
她和谁发生的婚外情
With whom was she having this affair?

399
00:15:28,940 --> 00:15:30,700
-我拒绝回答  -为什么
- I refuse to answer that. - why?

400
00:15:30,770 --> 00:15:34,410
你当时和他陷入爱河了
Were you in love with him?

401
00:15:34,480 --> 00:15:35,910
爱他
In love with him?

402
00:15:35,980 --> 00:15:37,680
我觉得她是饥不择食
I thought she was bottom-feeding.

403
00:15:37,740 --> 00:15:39,580
我刚听说的时候
I might have actually vomited

404
00:15:39,650 --> 00:15:41,180
-恶心的差点吐了  -好了  够了
- when I heard. - Okay, that's enough.

405
00:15:41,250 --> 00:15:43,120
我们不会回答这些问题的
We're not answering this line of questioning.

406
00:15:43,180 --> 00:15:44,720
继续
Move on.

407
00:15:44,790 --> 00:15:46,350
你刚说我客户被解雇
You said my client's dismissal

408
00:15:46,420 --> 00:15:48,550
由多种原因导致
was due to a variety of factors.

409
00:15:48,620 --> 00:15:49,690
接着你又说不是因为外遇
And then you said it wasn't the affair,

410
00:15:49,760 --> 00:15:50,890
也不是工作表现
and it wasn't job performance.

411
00:15:50,960 --> 00:15:54,030
那我现在问你  到底是为什么
So I ask you, what was it?

412
00:15:54,090 --> 00:15:55,190
是个人喜恶吗
Is it a personal dislike?

413
00:15:55,260 --> 00:15:57,830
你嫉妒她吗
Are you jealous of her?

414
00:15:57,900 --> 00:15:59,430
还是因为你就讨厌别的女人
Or do you just hate other women?

415
00:15:59,430 --> 00:16:00,970
小心说话  丹尼尔
Tread lightly, Daniel.

416
00:16:01,030 --> 00:16:03,800
问些你的客户能答的问题吧
Let's try some questions your client can answer.

417
00:16:03,870 --> 00:16:05,340
我的客户被解雇时
Were you in a relationship at the time

418
00:16:05,410 --> 00:16:06,650
你在和人约会吗
of my client's dismissal?

419
00:16:06,650 --> 00:16:07,470
你说什么
Excuse me?

420
00:16:07,540 --> 00:16:09,780
此事无关杰西卡·皮尔逊的私人生活
Jessica Pearson's personal life is not an issue here.

421
00:16:09,840 --> 00:16:11,240
恕我不能同意
Well, I beg to differ.

422
00:16:11,310 --> 00:16:12,980
既然你的客户今天不愿多说
And since your client can't seem to find her words today,

423
00:16:13,050 --> 00:16:14,580
我可以作证
I, for one, can testify that

424
00:16:14,650 --> 00:16:17,980
她当时无人约会
She was not in a relationship at the time.

425
00:16:18,050 --> 00:16:19,820
一直以来她都全身心投入到工作中
She's always been married to her job.

426
00:16:19,890 --> 00:16:21,350
她希望她的女同事
And she wants her female associates

427
00:16:21,420 --> 00:16:22,860
也能和她一样
to be equally committed,

428
00:16:22,920 --> 00:16:25,220
所以只要她们的生活中有了别的事
so that as soon as they have anything else in their lives--

429
00:16:25,290 --> 00:16:28,430
也就是性生活  她就会解雇她们
in other words, sex-- she cuts 'em loose.

430
00:16:30,600 --> 00:16:32,370
胡编乱造
This is bullshit.

431
00:16:32,430 --> 00:16:33,550
反驳我啊
Then tell me differently.

432
00:16:33,550 --> 00:16:34,670
到此为止
we're done here.

433
00:16:34,740 --> 00:16:36,040
事实就是
The truth is,

434
00:16:36,100 --> 00:16:38,300
莫妮卡比你年轻漂亮
Monica was younger than you, prettier than you,

435
00:16:38,370 --> 00:16:41,370
性生活丰富  正值生育年龄
sexually active, and of child-bearing age--

436
00:16:41,440 --> 00:16:47,110
这些你都没有  所以炒了她
All of the things you are not, and you fired her for it.

437
00:16:58,930 --> 00:16:59,930
要谈谈吗
We gonna talk about what happened?

438
00:16:59,990 --> 00:17:01,630
-今晚不行  -杰西卡
- Not tonight. - Jessica--

439
00:17:01,700 --> 00:17:03,830
那浑蛋就差没骂我刻薄和不能生育了
Son of a bitch all but called me bitter and barren.

440
00:17:03,900 --> 00:17:06,330
你确实这么骂了你  但事情只会更糟
He did call you that, but it's only gonna get worse.

441
00:17:06,400 --> 00:17:07,970
你应该毫不犹豫
And you should have jumped to my defense

442
00:17:08,040 --> 00:17:09,200
立即替我辩护
sooner than you did.

443
00:17:09,270 --> 00:17:11,100
我是你的律师  不是你丈夫
I'm your lawyer, not your husband.

444
00:17:11,170 --> 00:17:13,470
要不是我适时打断  我们就破产了
And if I didn't jump in when I did, we'd be broke.

445
00:17:13,540 --> 00:17:15,270
我早说了  必须和解
Look, I told you before, we need to settle.

446
00:17:15,340 --> 00:17:17,710
我也说了  我们不会和解
And I told you before, we're not settling.

447
00:17:17,780 --> 00:17:19,050
你没看穿他的把戏吗
Don't you see what he's doing?

448
00:17:19,110 --> 00:17:20,510
他想把案子转移到性别问题上
He's trying to make this case about gender.

449
00:17:20,580 --> 00:17:22,420
-这无关性别  -这不重要  听着
- It's not! - It doesn't matter. Look,

450
00:17:22,420 --> 00:17:26,190
在我们以性别歧视起诉福尔松公司时
you can't be the name defendant on a gender discrimination case

451
00:17:26,250 --> 00:17:28,690
你不能成为一个类似案件的被告
while we're suing Folsom Foods for the same thing.

452
00:17:28,760 --> 00:17:31,490
我不会向他投降的
I am not capitulating to that man.

453
00:17:31,560 --> 00:17:32,890
那你会看起来像个傻子
Then you're gonna look like a fool.

454
00:17:32,960 --> 00:17:34,360
够了
That's enough.

455
00:17:34,430 --> 00:17:36,460
这事不是你做主  而是我做主
You're not calling the shots, I am.

456
00:17:36,530 --> 00:17:38,760
不管你认为我的决定是对是错
And whether you think my call is wrong or not,

457
00:17:38,830 --> 00:17:43,240
那该死的墙上挂的是我的名字
it is still my name on that goddamn wall.

458
00:17:43,300 --> 00:17:45,170
你
You--

459
00:17:56,780 --> 00:17:58,850
抱歉  如果你还在写申请
Hey, um, sorry, I don't want to bother you

460
00:17:58,920 --> 00:18:00,290
我也不想打扰你
if you're still working on your application.

461
00:18:00,350 --> 00:18:02,720
但我需要帮忙
But I need a favor.

462
00:18:02,790 --> 00:18:05,760
没事  我写完了  帮什么忙
Uh, no, I finished. What do you need?

463
00:18:05,830 --> 00:18:09,330
我得看看杰西卡的证词
I need to see a transcript of Jessica's deposition.

464
00:18:09,400 --> 00:18:10,060
那是机密
That's confidential.

465
00:18:10,060 --> 00:18:11,400
所以我需要你帮忙
That's why I need your help.

466
00:18:11,470 --> 00:18:13,100
-迈克  -瑞秋  拜托了
- Mike-- - Rachel, please?

467
00:18:13,170 --> 00:18:17,000
我要看看
I need it.

468
00:18:20,670 --> 00:18:23,580
另外  恭喜你写完了申请
By the way, congratulations on finishing your application.

469
00:18:23,640 --> 00:18:25,910
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.

470
00:18:25,980 --> 00:18:27,780
你在找什么特别的内容吗
Are you looking for anything in particular?

471
00:18:27,850 --> 00:18:29,030
没有
No, not exactly.

472
00:18:29,030 --> 00:18:32,120
糟了
Uh-oh.

473
00:18:32,190 --> 00:18:35,990
-天哪  -真是咄咄逼人
- Oh, my god. - It just keeps going.

474
00:18:36,060 --> 00:18:38,960
而且越来越糟糕
It's worse and worse.

475
00:18:39,030 --> 00:18:40,490
她还得忍受这些
She had to sit through this.

476
00:18:40,560 --> 00:18:42,260
这都是我的错
Oh, god. This is all my fault.

477
00:18:42,330 --> 00:18:43,420
等等  迈克
Wait, Mike--

478
00:18:43,420 --> 00:18:45,360
不  我利用你接近莫妮卡
No, I-I used you to get to Monica,

479
00:18:45,360 --> 00:18:46,270
然后我又利用了她
and then I used her.

480
00:18:46,330 --> 00:18:48,170
他现在把气撒在杰西卡身上
And now he's taking it out on Jessica.

481
00:18:48,240 --> 00:18:49,770
你不可能预知事情的发展
Yeah, you couldn't have known it was gonna lead to this.

482
00:18:50,940 --> 00:18:52,540
没关系
It's okay.

483
00:18:52,610 --> 00:18:56,580
不行  我要用这个笔录
No, it isn't. I need to use this.

484
00:18:56,640 --> 00:18:58,310
你打印出来或者我凭记忆打出来
Either you print it or I type it out from memory,

485
00:18:58,380 --> 00:18:59,360
我必须这么做
But I have to.

486
00:18:59,360 --> 00:19:00,480
为何
Why?

487
00:19:02,050 --> 00:19:03,320
你说你想去哈佛读书
You said you wanted to go to Harvard

488
00:19:03,380 --> 00:19:04,980
是为了能在皮尔逊·哈德曼工作吧
so that you could work at Pearson Hardman, right?

489
00:19:05,230 --> 00:19:05,650
没错
Yeah.

490
00:19:05,650 --> 00:19:08,750
如果我不解决这个问题
Well, if I don't fix this,

491
00:19:08,820 --> 00:19:10,560
皮尔逊·哈德曼也许会消失
there might not be a Pearson Hardman.

492
00:19:23,300 --> 00:19:25,100
你不能和我说话
You can't talk to me.

493
00:19:25,170 --> 00:19:26,330
其实我可以
Actually, I can.

494
00:19:26,400 --> 00:19:27,770
我没有公司股份
I don't have any equity in the firm,

495
00:19:27,840 --> 00:19:29,370
这个案子也不归我管
and I'm not working on this case.

496
00:19:29,440 --> 00:19:30,540
你是相关的一方
You're an interested party.

497
00:19:30,610 --> 00:19:32,140
而且你起草了最初的诉状
And you drafted the original complaint.

498
00:19:32,210 --> 00:19:33,710
是个法官就会站我这边
Any judge in the world sides with me.

499
00:19:33,770 --> 00:19:35,440
听着  莫妮卡
Listen, Monica. Monica!

500
00:19:35,510 --> 00:19:36,680
我不是要陷害你
I'm not trying to set you up.

501
00:19:36,740 --> 00:19:37,880
我想负起责任
I'm trying to take responsibility here.

502
00:19:37,950 --> 00:19:39,250
负什么责任
For what?

503
00:19:39,310 --> 00:19:41,080
就像你说的那样
For doing exactly what you just said I did.

504
00:19:41,150 --> 00:19:42,620
是我起草了最初的诉状
for drafting the original complaint,

505
00:19:42,680 --> 00:19:46,120
挑起了整个事端  对不起
starting this whole thing off. I'm--I'm sorry.

506
00:19:46,190 --> 00:19:48,050
不  你唯一抱歉的就是
No, no. The only thing you're sorry

507
00:19:48,120 --> 00:19:50,020
你的小计策倒戈相向
about is your little maneuver backfired.

508
00:19:50,090 --> 00:19:51,420
对  但不是冲着我
Yeah, but it didn't backfire on me.

509
00:19:51,490 --> 00:19:53,040
而是杰西卡
It backfired on Jessica.

510
00:19:53,040 --> 00:19:53,460
真不幸啊
That's too bad.

511
00:19:53,530 --> 00:19:55,960
不过正合我意
That's exactly what I'm happy about.

512
00:19:56,030 --> 00:19:57,030
什么  杰西卡又没坏你事
What? Jessica didn't screw you,

513
00:19:57,100 --> 00:19:58,870
是哈德曼
Hardman did.

514
00:19:58,930 --> 00:20:01,470
来办公室开除我的可不是丹尼尔·哈德曼
Daniel Hardman didn't show up in my office to fire me,

515
00:20:01,540 --> 00:20:04,070
毫无缘由  通知或者推荐信都没有
without cause, notice, or a letter of recommendation.

516
00:20:04,140 --> 00:20:05,910
-她有理由  -是吗
-She had cause. - Did she?

517
00:20:05,970 --> 00:20:07,940
我说不知道丹尼尔挪用公款
When I told her I knew nothing about Daniel's embezzlement,

518
00:20:08,010 --> 00:20:11,040
你猜她说什么  “我不在乎”
do you know what she said? "I don't care."

519
00:20:11,110 --> 00:20:13,860
结果五年后她派你劝我背叛他
And then five years later, she sends you to turn me against him.

520
00:20:13,860 --> 00:20:14,780
她没有
That's just it, she didn't.

521
00:20:14,850 --> 00:20:15,950
瞧瞧
Look at that.

522
00:20:16,020 --> 00:20:17,780
咬人的狗想维护他的主人呢
The attack dog defends its owner.

523
00:20:17,850 --> 00:20:19,490
怪我吧  怪哈维都行
Blame me, you can even blame Harvey.

524
00:20:19,550 --> 00:20:21,620
但杰西卡与此事无关
But Jessica had nothing to do with it.

525
00:20:21,690 --> 00:20:23,490
如果你觉得我会相信
If you think I'm gonna buy for one second

526
00:20:23,560 --> 00:20:25,290
不是她派你拿诉状来找我
she wasn't behind you coming to me with that lawsuit,

527
00:20:25,360 --> 00:20:27,160
那你比我还天真
you are even more naive than I was.

528
00:20:27,230 --> 00:20:29,760
请你看看他对她做了什么吧
Please just look at what he did to her.

529
00:20:29,830 --> 00:20:32,570
我没必要看  因为我不在乎
I don't have to because I don't care.

530
00:20:47,680 --> 00:20:49,320
莫妮卡
Monica.

531
00:20:49,380 --> 00:20:51,920
-路易  -你最近怎么样
- Louis. - How are you?

532
00:20:51,990 --> 00:20:53,420
-还不错  -很好
- I'm fine. - Good.

533
00:20:53,490 --> 00:20:55,460
我想告诉你
You know, I wanted to tell you--

534
00:20:55,520 --> 00:20:57,420
我现在不能说话  路易
I can't really talk right now, Louis.

535
00:20:57,490 --> 00:20:59,160
没错  因为你要参加取证吧
Right, because you've got the deposition?

536
00:20:59,230 --> 00:21:03,100
-我来见丹尼尔  -丹尼尔
- I'm meeting Daniel. - Daniel.

537
00:21:03,160 --> 00:21:04,400
好吧  能见到你
Okay, well, it was really--

538
00:21:04,470 --> 00:21:06,130
我很开心
it was really nice seeing you.

539
00:21:06,130 --> 00:21:07,310
我也是
You too.

540
00:21:19,730 --> 00:21:21,230
我现在有点忙
A little busy at the moment.

541
00:21:21,230 --> 00:21:22,460
忙莫妮卡·伊顿的事  我知道
Monica Eton, I know.

542
00:21:22,460 --> 00:21:23,880
哈维不让我帮忙
Look, Harvey didn't want my help,

543
00:21:23,880 --> 00:21:24,880
但我觉得你会
but I thought that maybe you would.

544
00:21:24,880 --> 00:21:26,010
哈维是对的
Harvey is right.

545
00:21:26,060 --> 00:21:27,890
我要你跟福尔松食品公司的案子
I need you on top of Folsom Foods.

546
00:21:27,900 --> 00:21:29,440
就是福尔松食品公司的案子
This is about Folsom Foods.

547
00:21:30,750 --> 00:21:31,360
你有什么想法
What do you have?

548
00:21:31,360 --> 00:21:34,910
如果你能让莫妮卡承认她和丹尼尔有私情
If you can get Monica to admit that her affair was with Daniel,

549
00:21:34,950 --> 00:21:36,590
这件事就无关性别了
this isn't about gender anymore.

550
00:21:37,350 --> 00:21:38,810
因为他们俩都被开除了
Because they were both dismissed.

551
00:21:38,870 --> 00:21:39,640
一个男人和一个女人
A man and a woman.

552
00:21:39,640 --> 00:21:41,890
你就能重新主导福尔松食品公司的案子
Puts you back in the driver's seat on Folsom Foods.

553
00:21:42,360 --> 00:21:43,750
好  列出要问的问题了吗
Okay, do you have a line of questioning?

554
00:21:43,750 --> 00:21:44,790
在这里
Right here.

555
00:21:48,250 --> 00:21:49,090
准备好了没
You ready?

556
00:21:50,010 --> 00:21:51,020
他准备好了
He is.

557
00:21:51,130 --> 00:21:53,050
我要求你让他负责这事
I want you to let him take the lead on this.

558
00:21:53,300 --> 00:21:55,000
-什么  -没得商量
- What? - Not a discussion.

559
00:21:55,340 --> 00:21:56,420
你要去哪
Where are you going?

560
00:21:56,700 --> 00:21:58,140
我可不想再跟那些人
Oh, I'm not spending another moment

561
00:21:58,140 --> 00:21:59,680
呆在一个房间里
in the same room with those people.

562
00:22:06,320 --> 00:22:07,630
-伊顿小姐  -就他吗
- Miss Eton-- - Him?

563
00:22:08,010 --> 00:22:09,500
你把“二流队伍”带来了
You're bringing in the "B" Team?

564
00:22:09,690 --> 00:22:10,890
正如你所说
As you pointed out,

565
00:22:10,890 --> 00:22:13,150
这支“二流队伍”最初起草了诉状
the "B" Team drafted this suit in the first place.

566
00:22:13,150 --> 00:22:14,130
弄得你无处躲藏
And ran you out of dodge.

567
00:22:14,130 --> 00:22:15,660
跑去了新泽西
Right into jersey.

568
00:22:16,000 --> 00:22:19,140
这次不行  他可以再一次
Well, if he doesn't do well, he can always approach my client

569
00:22:19,140 --> 00:22:21,520
到我客户的工作场所外找她
outside of her place of employment, again.

570
00:22:24,880 --> 00:22:25,970
我猜他先斩后奏
I guess he must have learned from you

571
00:22:25,970 --> 00:22:27,920
是跟你学的
not to always tell dad what he's up to.

572
00:22:27,920 --> 00:22:29,200
想知道他跟我学到了什么吗
You want to know what he learned from me?

573
00:22:29,210 --> 00:22:31,700
不让败过两次的人打乱阵脚
not to let some two-time loser get in his head.

574
00:22:34,950 --> 00:22:35,960
伊顿小姐  外界有很多传言
Miss Eton, there's been a lot of talk

575
00:22:35,960 --> 00:22:38,090
说你在皮尔逊·哈德曼工作时有了私情
about the affair you had while at Pearson Hardman.

576
00:22:38,100 --> 00:22:39,990
我只有一个问题
I have just one question.

577
00:22:40,640 --> 00:22:42,060
是和谁有私情呢
Who was that affair with?

578
00:22:42,080 --> 00:22:43,580
我从未说过我有私情
I never said I had an affair.

579
00:22:44,170 --> 00:22:45,750
可你的律师说你有
But your lawyer said you did.

580
00:22:45,750 --> 00:22:47,210
你们的人说这事不相干
Your people said it was irrelevant.

581
00:22:47,210 --> 00:22:48,500
我没说  而且这事很重要
I didn't, and it's not,

582
00:22:48,500 --> 00:22:49,890
我可有很多问题
And I have a lot of questions about it.

583
00:22:49,890 --> 00:22:51,380
我们不会回答的
Which we won't be answering.

584
00:22:51,380 --> 00:22:52,740
你在法庭上也得回答
Well, you'll have to in court.

585
00:22:52,740 --> 00:22:53,800
我们又不在法庭
We're not in court.

586
00:22:53,800 --> 00:22:55,410
是不会  但我们正在录口供
No, but you are on the record.

587
00:22:56,300 --> 00:22:57,810
既然你不想回答问题
But since you don't want to answer the question,

588
00:22:57,810 --> 00:22:59,370
我再问你个问题
let me ask you another question.

589
00:22:59,370 --> 00:23:01,110
如果你没有偷情
If you didn't have an affair,

590
00:23:01,110 --> 00:23:02,850
是什么原因导致
then what reason could there possibly be

591
00:23:02,850 --> 00:23:04,150
你被解雇了呢
for you to be fired?

592
00:23:05,510 --> 00:23:06,980
因为我被骚扰了
Because I was being harassed,

593
00:23:06,980 --> 00:23:08,360
我说得很清楚  我不喜欢那样
and I made it clear I didn't like it.

594
00:23:08,360 --> 00:23:09,320
骚扰  谁干的
Harassed? By who?

595
00:23:09,320 --> 00:23:10,530
别回答
Don't answer that.

596
00:23:10,530 --> 00:23:12,250
不  我的客户会回答
Oh, no. My client is going to

597
00:23:12,250 --> 00:23:14,140
你助理提出的问题
answer the question that your associate asked,

598
00:23:14,140 --> 00:23:16,030
并且会将此记录在案
And we're gonna get some things on the record, right here.

599
00:23:16,030 --> 00:23:16,720
不  我们到此为止
No, we're done.

600
00:23:16,720 --> 00:23:18,440
我被路易·利特骚扰了
I was being harassed By Louis Litt.

601
00:23:18,750 --> 00:23:19,480
什么
What?

602
00:23:21,530 --> 00:23:22,660
继续  莫妮卡
Go on, Monica.

603
00:23:23,390 --> 00:23:24,860
他多次想约我出去
He asked me out repeatedly,

604
00:23:24,860 --> 00:23:26,820
当我一次次地拒绝他之后
after I rebuffed him again and again.

605
00:23:27,690 --> 00:23:31,120
他会盯着我看  在办公室外的电梯前等我
he would stare at me, wait at the elevator outside my office,

606
00:23:31,120 --> 00:23:32,620
还有餐厅  无处不在
the diner, everywhere.

607
00:23:33,040 --> 00:23:34,520
-还有什么吗  -还有
- Anything else? - Yes.

608
00:23:35,080 --> 00:23:37,160
他是合伙人  我不得不拒绝他
He was partner, and I had to say "No" to him.

609
00:23:37,740 --> 00:23:40,020
每一天我都倍感厌恶
And it made me feel disgusting every single day.

610
00:23:40,480 --> 00:23:42,250
有人证实你所说的吗
Will people corroborate your account?

611
00:23:42,270 --> 00:23:44,040
整个公司都知道
It was common knowledge within the firm.

612
00:23:44,410 --> 00:23:46,490
所有人都清楚  也包括他
Any number of people knew, including him.

613
00:23:47,550 --> 00:23:49,240
请在记录里写上我的委托人
Let the record show that my client

614
00:23:49,250 --> 00:23:50,720
指的是哈维·斯佩克特
indicated Harvey Specter.

615
00:23:50,730 --> 00:23:52,860
莫妮卡  我还有一个问题问你
Monica, I have one more question for you.

616
00:23:53,400 --> 00:23:56,460
杰西卡让你把辞呈交给谁
To whom did Jessica tell you to hand in your resignation?

617
00:23:56,590 --> 00:23:57,520
路易·利特
Louis Litt.

618
00:23:57,630 --> 00:23:59,630
所以总结一下
So in conclusion,

619
00:23:59,670 --> 00:24:02,110
你受到了性骚扰
you were being sexually harassed,

620
00:24:02,130 --> 00:24:05,440
这事众所周知  杰西卡·皮尔逊解雇了你
it was well-known, Jessica Pearson dismissed you,

621
00:24:05,440 --> 00:24:08,970
并且还让你把辞呈递给
and you were actually told to hand in your resignation

622
00:24:08,990 --> 00:24:12,000
那个骚扰你的人
to the very man who did the harassing.

623
00:24:12,000 --> 00:24:14,940
没错  这一切都属实
Yes. That statement is entirely true.

624
00:24:15,340 --> 00:24:16,470
谢谢你  莫妮卡
Thank you, Monica.

625
00:24:18,870 --> 00:24:19,850
先生们
Gentlemen?

626
00:24:23,020 --> 00:24:25,080
我明白了  你一直就这么打算
I get it, that was your plan,

627
00:24:25,100 --> 00:24:26,960
把一切都怪罪在路易头上
to blame it on Louis the whole time.

628
00:24:27,350 --> 00:24:29,080
莫妮卡一直都是个很棒的律师
Monica always was a good lawyer.

629
00:24:29,970 --> 00:24:31,680
她在取证时所说的一切都是事实
Nothing she said in there wasn't true.

630
00:24:33,130 --> 00:24:35,090
你要怎样才愿意和解
What's it gonna take to settle this case?

631
00:24:35,600 --> 00:24:36,910
你有何提议
What ever do you mean?

632
00:24:37,250 --> 00:24:39,290
我们违反保密协议  莫妮卡败诉
We break confidentiality, Monica loses,

633
00:24:39,290 --> 00:24:41,150
你拿到你的一千五百万
you get your $15 million.

634
00:24:41,150 --> 00:24:42,000
还挺诱人
Tempting.

635
00:24:42,000 --> 00:24:44,040
但你知道我们不可能这么做
But we're not gonna do that, and you know it.

636
00:24:44,280 --> 00:24:46,350
你想跟莫妮卡和解
So you want to settle with Monica

637
00:24:46,550 --> 00:24:47,770
摆脱这个麻烦
and get out of your jam.

638
00:24:47,770 --> 00:24:50,310
开个价  最好别高于三百万
I want a number, and it better be less than three.

639
00:24:50,340 --> 00:24:51,460
这不是钱的事
This isn't about numbers.

640
00:24:51,460 --> 00:24:53,180
是责任
It's about responsibility.

641
00:24:53,220 --> 00:24:55,710
莫妮卡想要看到杰西卡被判有罪
Monica wants to see a jury find Jessica guilty.

642
00:24:55,710 --> 00:24:56,880
胡扯
Bullshit.

643
00:24:56,890 --> 00:24:59,670
是你想要看到杰西卡被判有罪
You want to see a jury find jessica guilty.

644
00:24:59,710 --> 00:25:02,500
不  千真万确是莫妮卡
Nope. I assure you, it is Monica.

645
00:25:02,880 --> 00:25:04,070
杰西卡是否被判有罪
I don't really care whether a jury

646
00:25:04,070 --> 00:25:05,690
我一点都不在乎
finds Jessica guilty or not.

647
00:25:06,350 --> 00:25:07,690
你就是惟恐天下不乱
You just want blood.

648
00:25:07,760 --> 00:25:10,100
-已经大乱了  -都是因为你
- It's already there. - Because of you.

649
00:25:10,100 --> 00:25:12,490
不管怎样  我闻到血腥味了
Huh. Nonetheless, I smell it.

650
00:25:12,740 --> 00:25:15,860
艾莉森·霍特和罗伯特·赞恩都来找你们麻烦
Allison Holt, Robert Zane both came after you,

651
00:25:15,870 --> 00:25:19,650
还有根本负担不起的45桩官司
and now you have 45 cases you can't afford.

652
00:25:19,860 --> 00:25:22,000
如果付给我一千五百万
So pay me $15 million,

653
00:25:22,000 --> 00:25:24,860
不管莫妮卡的官司你们打输还是打赢
fight Monica, and lose. Fight Monica and win.

654
00:25:25,680 --> 00:25:26,840
都无关紧要
It doesn't matter.

655
00:25:26,940 --> 00:25:28,240
不管你怎么玩
Any way you slice it,

656
00:25:29,160 --> 00:25:30,520
我都会把你们榨干
I'm gonna bleed you dry.

657
00:25:42,510 --> 00:25:44,140
他们说好要找个棕色头发的
They promised a brunette.

658
00:25:45,770 --> 00:25:47,110
好吧  大概你头上还是有几根棕色的
Well, I guess there's a few.

659
00:25:47,140 --> 00:25:50,810
我想好好跟你谈谈
I want to talk to you like a person.

660
00:25:53,060 --> 00:25:54,180
是肯尼·基
Kenny G?

661
00:25:53,060 --> 00:25:54,400
美国萨克斯演奏大师

662
00:25:59,110 --> 00:26:00,410
你想说什么  路易
What's on your mind, Louis?

663
00:26:00,410 --> 00:26:03,200
我知道唐娜跟我说了你不需要我帮忙
I know Donna told me that, uh, you didn't need my help,

664
00:26:03,200 --> 00:26:04,180
而且自从你撕掉我的辞呈后
and I know we haven't really spoken

665
00:26:04,180 --> 00:26:06,600
我们就没怎么好好讲过话
since you ripped up my letter of resignation.

666
00:26:08,590 --> 00:26:09,840
但是我想帮忙
But I want to help.

667
00:26:10,820 --> 00:26:12,030
我需要出点力
I need to help.

668
00:26:12,030 --> 00:26:13,750
相信我  这不是什么好主意
Trust me. It's not a good idea.

669
00:26:13,800 --> 00:26:16,730
他在利用莫妮卡  就像之前利用我一样
He's using Monica the same way that he used me.

670
00:26:19,210 --> 00:26:22,380
没有人比我更了解他的这种行径
And no one knows that better than me.

671
00:26:22,850 --> 00:26:23,890
我知道
I know.

672
00:26:24,110 --> 00:26:25,210
要是我能不顾这些条条框框
If I could just talk to her outside

673
00:26:25,210 --> 00:26:26,940
告诉她所有真相就好了
the confines of everything, you know?

674
00:26:26,950 --> 00:26:28,000
要是我能
If I could--

675
00:26:28,030 --> 00:26:30,550
我知道我一定能说服她撤销控告
I just know I can convince her to drop this case, I know it.

676
00:26:31,020 --> 00:26:31,990
-路易  -哈维  拜托
- Louis-- - Harvey, please.

677
00:26:31,990 --> 00:26:32,920
求你了
I'm begging you.

678
00:26:39,610 --> 00:26:42,160
-这是什么  -你先看看
- What's this? - Just read it.

679
00:26:50,090 --> 00:26:51,540
是迈克主持了取证会
Mike led the deposition.

680
00:26:53,280 --> 00:26:54,650
开局很大胆啊
Starts off bold.

681
00:26:55,020 --> 00:26:56,450
他不该问这个的
Oh, he shouldn't have asked that.

682
00:26:56,460 --> 00:26:57,700
完全是新手的失误
That's a rookie move.

683
00:27:00,090 --> 00:27:02,840
这是…  什么
What-- what?

684
00:27:13,570 --> 00:27:15,140
“一次次地断然回绝”
"Rebuffed again and again."

685
00:27:18,820 --> 00:27:20,370
她感到恶心
She felt disgusted.

686
00:27:22,310 --> 00:27:24,260
-“所有人都知道”  -路易
- "Common knowledge." - Louis--

687
00:27:24,260 --> 00:27:25,730
她指向你
She pointed at you.

688
00:27:27,020 --> 00:27:28,810
-这不代表…  -不  不不
- That doesn't mean-- - No, no, no, no, no.

689
00:27:28,810 --> 00:27:30,380
你以前总拿她开我玩笑
You used to tease me about her.

690
00:27:33,580 --> 00:27:35,660
还记得我那时是怎么盯着她的吗
Remember how I used to stare at her?

691
00:27:35,660 --> 00:27:36,790
那是开玩笑
That was teasing.

692
00:27:38,110 --> 00:27:39,400
这全是扯淡
This is bullshit.

693
00:27:40,120 --> 00:27:42,220
-他们完全是在颠倒黑白  -的确
- They're twisting everything. - They are.

694
00:27:45,950 --> 00:27:47,320
都是他
He is.

695
00:27:48,390 --> 00:27:49,590
喝一杯吧
Drink your drink.

696
00:28:07,530 --> 00:28:09,160
你来这儿做什么
What are you doing here?

697
00:28:09,410 --> 00:28:10,610
呼吸点空气
I needed some air.

698
00:28:11,400 --> 00:28:12,980
你怎么知道从哪儿上来的
How'd you know how to get up here?

699
00:28:13,190 --> 00:28:15,740
-唐娜说的  你呢  -也是她
- Donna. You? - Donna.

700
00:28:22,670 --> 00:28:24,050
我说谎了
I lied.

701
00:28:25,460 --> 00:28:28,020
-论文的事  -我写不出来
- The essay? - I couldn't do it.

702
00:28:28,040 --> 00:28:29,930
就当作是写结案陈词好了
Just think of it like a closing argument.

703
00:28:29,930 --> 00:28:32,000
-他们为什么要录取你  -就是啊
- Why should they take you? - Exactly.

704
00:28:32,450 --> 00:28:34,050
他们为什么要录取我
Why should they take me?

705
00:28:34,860 --> 00:28:35,980
你为什么想做律师
Why do you want to be a lawyer?

706
00:28:35,980 --> 00:28:37,450
别多想  直接回答我
Just-- don't think, tell me.

707
00:28:38,080 --> 00:28:40,510
-因为我爸  -好  为什么
- My dad. - Okay. Why?

708
00:28:42,770 --> 00:28:44,070
你还记得我告诉过你
Do you remember when I told you

709
00:28:44,080 --> 00:28:46,130
我小时候人们总是跟他说
that, when I was a little girl, people would just tell him

710
00:28:46,130 --> 00:28:47,590
他有多聪明吗
how smart he was?

711
00:28:48,300 --> 00:28:50,290
跟他的肤色毫无关系
Right, it had nothing to do with him being black or white,

712
00:28:50,290 --> 00:28:51,940
他就是出类拔萃
he was just amazing.

713
00:28:53,330 --> 00:28:55,560
我也想做这么出色的人
And I want to be amazing too.

714
00:28:57,440 --> 00:28:58,540
你的确很出色
You are.

715
00:28:59,350 --> 00:29:00,400
是吗
Am I?

716
00:29:01,020 --> 00:29:03,660
可每次我坐在那间办公室里  我就想
Because every time I sit down at that keyboard, I think,

717
00:29:04,110 --> 00:29:06,890
“我是名法律助理  到现在我一直做这个
"I'm a paralegal. That's all I've ever been.

718
00:29:06,890 --> 00:29:08,160
以后也会一直干这个”
That's all I'll ever be."

719
00:29:08,970 --> 00:29:11,450
我跟你说过哈维面试我的情景吗
Did I ever tell you about my interview with Harvey?

720
00:29:12,430 --> 00:29:15,670
没有  但我猜一定进行得无比顺利
No...but I'm assuming it went well.

721
00:29:15,670 --> 00:29:17,350
他觉得我真是傻到极点了
He laughed me out of the room.

722
00:29:18,910 --> 00:29:20,810
-你骗我呢吧  -不  我没有
- Are you kidding? - No, I'm not.

723
00:29:20,810 --> 00:29:23,260
他基本上就跟我说我根本没资格参加面试
He basically told me I didn't even belong in the interview.

724
00:29:23,260 --> 00:29:24,720
他直接让我离开
He actually told me to leave.

725
00:29:26,420 --> 00:29:27,750
那你是怎么做的
What did you do?

726
00:29:28,230 --> 00:29:29,380
我决定根本不管
I decided I didn't give a shit

727
00:29:29,380 --> 00:29:31,060
其他申请者有什么优势  而我没有
what the other applicants had that I didn't.

728
00:29:32,290 --> 00:29:33,060
如果要我就这么离开
If I was going through that door,

729
00:29:33,060 --> 00:29:35,060
除非他亲自把我扔出去
he'd have to pick me up and throw me out.

730
00:29:35,940 --> 00:29:37,340
你肯定跟他说了什么
You must have said something.

731
00:29:38,570 --> 00:29:39,720
对
Yeah.

732
00:29:40,340 --> 00:29:42,230
我告诉他我会是他见过的
Yeah, I told him I'd be the best damn lawyer

733
00:29:42,240 --> 00:29:43,400
最棒的律师
he'd ever seen.

734
00:29:46,640 --> 00:29:48,800
真希望我当时是只苍蝇  趴在墙上看着
I wish I could have been a fly on that wall.

735
00:29:49,720 --> 00:29:51,200
没错  绝对出乎意料
Yeah, you have no idea.

736
00:30:01,950 --> 00:30:03,610
你到底是怎么回事
What the hell is wrong with you?

737
00:30:04,440 --> 00:30:05,340
我
Me?

738
00:30:05,360 --> 00:30:06,570
你打算跟丹尼尔和解
You tried to settle with Daniel.

739
00:30:06,570 --> 00:30:07,620
我当然要这么做
You're damn right I did.

740
00:30:07,620 --> 00:30:09,730
你知道取证会上发生了什么吗
Did you read what happened in that deposition?

741
00:30:09,730 --> 00:30:11,560
我才不管取证会上发生了什么
I don't care what happened in that deposition.

742
00:30:11,560 --> 00:30:13,700
但我在乎  你完全失控了
I do. You're out of control.

743
00:30:13,710 --> 00:30:14,850
你刚才说我什么
What did you just say to me?

744
00:30:14,850 --> 00:30:16,430
迈克·罗斯还没准备好这个
Mike Ross wasn't ready for this.

745
00:30:16,430 --> 00:30:19,120
-他自愿帮忙的  -他去见了莫妮卡·伊顿
- He volunteered. - He went to see Monica Eton.

746
00:30:19,120 --> 00:30:20,240
这种事你也做过
You've done the same.

747
00:30:20,260 --> 00:30:22,330
我是高级合伙人  又不是助理律师
I'm a senior partner, not an associate.

748
00:30:22,970 --> 00:30:25,670
我高于你  你高于他
Me to you, you to him.

749
00:30:27,270 --> 00:30:28,330
随便吧
Fine.

750
00:30:30,970 --> 00:30:32,680
你想知道他为什么去找莫妮卡吗
You want to know why he went to see Monica?

751
00:30:32,680 --> 00:30:33,620
你直接告诉我吧
I'm sure you're gonna tell me.

752
00:30:33,620 --> 00:30:35,880
因为他完全不知道是你提议
Because he doesn't know the idea to stir her up

753
00:30:35,880 --> 00:30:38,130
找她出来对付丹尼尔的
against Daniel was yours in the first place.

754
00:30:38,140 --> 00:30:39,450
他没必要知道这个
He doesn't need to know.

755
00:30:40,450 --> 00:30:41,850
你对他的信任不足以让他知道这个
So you don't trust him with that,

756
00:30:41,850 --> 00:30:44,300
但却能够让他独自挑衅丹尼尔
but you trust him to go up against Daniel himself.

757
00:30:44,300 --> 00:30:46,870
他来找我  带着能让我们
He came to me with a way to put us back in a position

758
00:30:46,870 --> 00:30:48,380
打赢福尔松食品的办法
to win Folsom Foods.

759
00:30:48,380 --> 00:30:51,090
但是现在失败了  我们两个官司都占下风了
Well, it failed. We're behind on both.

760
00:30:51,090 --> 00:30:52,160
-打扰一下  -迈克
- Excuse me. - Mike.

761
00:30:52,160 --> 00:30:54,530
我想为昨天的事情向你们俩道歉
I just wanted to apologize to you both for yesterday.

762
00:30:55,710 --> 00:30:56,770
那想法的确不错
It was a good idea,

763
00:30:57,000 --> 00:30:58,650
就是执行时出了些问题
just didn't have the right execution.

764
00:30:58,680 --> 00:31:01,190
-你什么意思  -我是说这想法很好
- What are you saying? - I'm saying it was a good idea,

765
00:31:01,270 --> 00:31:03,730
但是提问的对象不对
but the questions were being asked of the wrong person.

766
00:31:08,830 --> 00:31:10,560
三个人一起出动
Three on one.

767
00:31:10,750 --> 00:31:13,430
就为了给这么微不足道的我来取证
All for a deposition of little, old me.

768
00:31:13,430 --> 00:31:15,430
你坐那边会不会更舒服些
Would you be more comfortable over there,

769
00:31:15,620 --> 00:31:17,140
毕竟你原来的办公桌放在那里
where your old desk used to be?

770
00:31:17,190 --> 00:31:19,590
不必了  我们不会需要很久的
No need. We won't be here long.

771
00:31:19,590 --> 00:31:22,780
保密协议几乎让你们不能问任何问题
Our confidentiality agreement prohibits most questions.

772
00:31:22,790 --> 00:31:25,060
其实只是让我们无法说出去
Actually, it only prohibits disclosures.

773
00:31:25,220 --> 00:31:27,820
我们可以像所有未签保密协议的律师一样
We can ask you any question that any lawyer who hadn't signed

774
00:31:27,820 --> 00:31:30,270
问你任何问题
a non-disclosure agreement could ask.

775
00:31:30,270 --> 00:31:31,760
我们只是不能作证供
We just can't make statements.

776
00:31:31,760 --> 00:31:35,320
我相信要是你在亨德森法官的
I'm sure if you were to ask Judge Henderson,

777
00:31:35,450 --> 00:31:38,380
泳池边问他  他也会这么说
say, out by his pool, he would agree.

778
00:31:40,560 --> 00:31:41,870
这里没有法院书记官
There's no court reporter here.

779
00:31:41,870 --> 00:31:43,740
我猜你可能想私下聊聊
I thought you might want to talk off the record.

780
00:31:45,970 --> 00:31:48,010
如果你想问我有关盗用公款的事
If you ask me anything about embezzlement,

781
00:31:48,020 --> 00:31:49,060
我不会承认的
I'll deny it.

782
00:31:49,560 --> 00:31:50,860
如果你拿出任何证据
If you bring any proof forward,

783
00:31:50,860 --> 00:31:52,290
那就违反了我们的保密协议
it's a violation of our non-disclosure.

784
00:31:52,290 --> 00:31:54,580
所以我们不打算问你盗用公款的事
That's why we won't be asking about your embezzlement.

785
00:31:54,580 --> 00:31:57,020
我们要问你和莫妮卡的外遇
We'll be asking you about your affair with Monica.

786
00:31:57,020 --> 00:31:58,380
如果你有一丁点隐瞒
And if you lie about that,

787
00:31:58,380 --> 00:32:00,320
根本不需要我们拿出任何证据
we won't be the ones who need to come forward with proof.

788
00:32:00,330 --> 00:32:02,530
因为我们找到了六位酒店员工
Because we found six people working at the hotel

789
00:32:02,530 --> 00:32:03,840
他们愿意出来作证
who are willing to provide it.

790
00:32:04,540 --> 00:32:06,530
不  你们没有
No, you didn't.

791
00:32:06,540 --> 00:32:09,130
客房服务  门卫  清洁工
Room service, concierge, housekeeping.

792
00:32:09,500 --> 00:32:10,990
你真应该多给点小费的  丹尼尔
You really should tip better, Daniel.

793
00:32:10,990 --> 00:32:12,340
还是你需要来根烟
Maybe you want a cigarette?

794
00:32:12,670 --> 00:32:14,330
才能想起你背叛的女人
Remind you of the woman you cheated on.

795
00:32:21,990 --> 00:32:23,990
来吧  随便问
Go ahead. Ask your questions.

796
00:32:23,990 --> 00:32:25,430
你在皮尔逊·哈德曼律所工作时
Did you have an affair with Monica Eton

797
00:32:25,430 --> 00:32:27,160
是否跟莫妮卡·伊顿发生了婚外情
while you were employed at Pearson Hardman?

798
00:32:27,160 --> 00:32:29,850
对  我有过  还有其它问题吗
Yes, I did. Any other questions?

799
00:32:30,190 --> 00:32:31,380
没有了
I think we're good.

800
00:32:31,860 --> 00:32:34,760
好  你让我出丑了
Yep. You got me to embarrass myself.

801
00:32:34,760 --> 00:32:37,360
但是你当着办公室所有人的面
But you already did that, the day you told everyone

802
00:32:37,360 --> 00:32:39,040
说出这事的那天  就已经让我出过丑了
in the office about my affair with monica.

803
00:32:39,040 --> 00:32:40,370
你们俩
You and you.

804
00:32:40,660 --> 00:32:43,330
对  我知道你跟莫妮卡说过
Yeah, I know what you told Monica

805
00:32:43,330 --> 00:32:44,810
杰西卡对这事并不知情
about Jessica not knowing.

806
00:32:45,340 --> 00:32:46,540
但好好看看
But take a good look.

807
00:32:47,300 --> 00:32:48,540
她才是幕后主谋
She was behind it.

808
00:32:50,060 --> 00:32:51,650
现在该轮到谁需要根烟了
Who needs a cigarette now?

809
00:32:54,110 --> 00:32:55,800
不管我的证词有多大用处
And as far as my admission goes?

810
00:32:55,800 --> 00:32:57,260
开除她的还是你
You're still the one who fired her,

811
00:32:57,260 --> 00:32:58,960
而且是在你发现了的24小时之后
24 hours after you found out.

812
00:32:59,190 --> 00:33:00,990
陪审团会更关注这一点
That's what a jury's gonna focus on.

813
00:33:01,220 --> 00:33:03,230
没人会在意我做了什么
Nobody's gonna care about what I did.

814
00:33:22,520 --> 00:33:24,110
你这个狗屎
You piece of shit.

815
00:33:24,970 --> 00:33:26,630
原来是我培养出来的人才啊
There's the fire I helped nurture.

816
00:33:26,630 --> 00:33:28,460
你什么都没有培养出来
You didn't nurture a goddamn thing.

817
00:33:28,460 --> 00:33:31,620
你不会教  不会启发  不会指导
You don't teach. You don't inspire. You don't mentor.

818
00:33:31,650 --> 00:33:33,380
你所做的只有背叛
All you do is betray.

819
00:33:33,380 --> 00:33:35,100
就像上次投票时你背叛我一样
Like you betrayed me at that last vote.

820
00:33:35,100 --> 00:33:37,530
-你怎么敢  -我怎么敢什么
- How dare you. - How dare I what?

821
00:33:37,910 --> 00:33:39,540
若与你的目的相符
You were more than happy to help out

822
00:33:39,540 --> 00:33:40,770
你非常乐意排忧解难
when it served your purposes.

823
00:33:40,780 --> 00:33:42,590
在我意识到那全都是谎言时
I voted the way I did the second I realized

824
00:33:42,590 --> 00:33:43,670
我才那么做
it was all a lie.

825
00:33:43,670 --> 00:33:45,170
看看结果如何
And look how it turned out.

826
00:33:45,480 --> 00:33:46,980
你现在是资深合伙人了
You're a senior partner now.

827
00:33:47,250 --> 00:33:49,200
-不用谢  -你觉得我在乎
- You're welcome. - You think I give a shit?

828
00:33:49,250 --> 00:33:51,420
我觉得你只在乎这个
I think that's all you ever cared about.

829
00:33:51,420 --> 00:33:52,860
你知道我在乎什么
You know what I cared about?

830
00:33:53,600 --> 00:33:54,690
莫妮卡
Monica.

831
00:33:54,890 --> 00:33:56,980
她如此聪颖美丽
She was so smart and so beautiful.

832
00:33:56,980 --> 00:33:58,000
我知道她和我不是一个层面的人
And I knew she was out of my league,

833
00:33:58,000 --> 00:33:59,380
但是我一直努力着  因为我认为
but I kept trying because I just thought

834
00:33:59,380 --> 00:34:01,710
如果她能了解我
if she just got to know me--

835
00:34:04,770 --> 00:34:06,750
然后我发现原来她一直
And then I found out that whole time she was--

836
00:34:06,750 --> 00:34:09,750
-和我在一起  -是的  和你在一起
- With me. - Yeah. With you.

837
00:34:10,080 --> 00:34:11,520
你为什么要告诉我这事
Why are you telling me this?

838
00:34:14,250 --> 00:34:17,660
我希望你知道你到底扭曲了什么
I want you to know exactly what it is that you twisted,

839
00:34:17,910 --> 00:34:21,890
这样你就知道逼疯我会有什么后果
so you know exactly what it was that put me over the edge.

840
00:34:22,620 --> 00:34:24,290
路易  你是在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me, Louis?

841
00:34:24,290 --> 00:34:26,240
威胁你  当然不是  我只是告诉你
Threatening you? No, I'm telling you.

842
00:34:26,840 --> 00:34:29,690
你要是再对我做出什么
You ever do anything to me ever again,

843
00:34:30,320 --> 00:34:34,060
甚至于你再跟我说时机不对
you ever so much as tell me the incorrect time,

844
00:34:34,880 --> 00:34:36,030
我会杀了你
I'll kill you.

845
00:34:37,320 --> 00:34:39,140
我会从你肥壮的脖子上
I will rip your smug face

846
00:34:39,140 --> 00:34:40,960
扯下那张自以为是的脸
off your fat neck,

847
00:34:41,520 --> 00:34:42,770
我会杀了你
and I'll kill you.

848
00:35:05,920 --> 00:35:07,270
你又来找我取证吗
You here to depose me again?

849
00:35:07,700 --> 00:35:09,300
上一次可没有什么好结果
Didn't go too well for you last time.

850
00:35:10,370 --> 00:35:11,760
不  我是来道歉的
No, I'm here to say I'm sorry.

851
00:35:12,810 --> 00:35:15,960
有关杰西卡的事  你说得没错
You were right... about Jessica.

852
00:35:17,310 --> 00:35:18,810
你真的不知道是她
You really didn't know it was her.

853
00:35:20,080 --> 00:35:21,460
欢迎来到现实世界
Welcome to the world.

854
00:35:21,460 --> 00:35:23,160
-很讽刺  是吧  -是的
- Stings, doesn't it? - Yeah.

855
00:35:23,760 --> 00:35:24,710
是的
It does.

856
00:35:25,100 --> 00:35:27,440
你大老远跑来就是为了说抱歉吗
So you came all the way here just to tell me you're sorry?

857
00:35:27,440 --> 00:35:29,250
不是
No, I didn't.

858
00:35:29,580 --> 00:35:31,370
杰西卡开除你的确不对
Jessica was wrong to fire you,

859
00:35:31,790 --> 00:35:33,400
但她开除你并不是因为你是女人
but she didn't fire you because you're a woman.

860
00:35:33,400 --> 00:35:35,500
她开除你是因为她不相信你
She fired you because she didn't trust you.

861
00:35:35,610 --> 00:35:37,010
-我知道  -那么你也知道
- I know that. - So then you also know

862
00:35:37,010 --> 00:35:39,450
继续指控对她并不公平
that keeping this suit alive is sticking it to her.

863
00:35:39,870 --> 00:35:41,080
这才是重点
That's the whole point.

864
00:35:41,110 --> 00:35:42,310
不  重点是她并不是
No, the whole point is that she's not

865
00:35:42,310 --> 00:35:43,920
唯一一个你不公平对待的人
the only one you're sticking it to.

866
00:35:43,920 --> 00:35:46,460
我之前所说有关路易·利特的事情完全属实
What I said about Louis Litt is factually accurate.

867
00:35:46,460 --> 00:35:48,130
如果你觉得我会因为他而撤销指控
And if you think I'm gonna drop the case because of him, I'm--

868
00:35:48,130 --> 00:35:49,590
我说的不是他
I'm not talking about him.

869
00:35:49,850 --> 00:35:52,140
我说的是113位正在指控
I'm talking about the 113 women who are suing

870
00:35:52,140 --> 00:35:54,930
福尔松食品公司性别歧视的女性
Folsom Foods right now for gender discrimination.

871
00:35:55,700 --> 00:35:57,450
那些案子是她们自己的事情
Those cases are their own thing.

872
00:35:58,680 --> 00:36:00,760
有人告诉她们  她们不能得到想要得到的
They're being told they can't get where they want

873
00:36:00,760 --> 00:36:02,220
因为她们不够好
because they're not good enough.

874
00:36:02,220 --> 00:36:04,240
这跟我一点关系都没有
That has nothing to do this me.

875
00:36:05,160 --> 00:36:06,630
现在是谁太天真了
Who's being naive now?

876
00:36:06,650 --> 00:36:08,800
他在利用你的指控将我们压制住
He's using your suit to drive us into the ground,

877
00:36:08,800 --> 00:36:11,990
压制住我们就意味着输掉这些案子
and driving us into the ground means losing these cases.

878
00:36:12,550 --> 00:36:13,550
你想要什么
What do you want?

879
00:36:14,600 --> 00:36:17,080
看看这些文件  自己决定
Just read these files. Decide for yourself.

880
00:36:18,180 --> 00:36:20,640
这些女人应受到和你一样的待遇吗
These women deserve to be treated the same way you were?

881
00:36:22,590 --> 00:36:24,220
你凭什么认为我会在乎
What makes you think I would even care?

882
00:36:25,890 --> 00:36:28,290
我很天真  记得吗
I'm naive, remember?

883
00:36:41,120 --> 00:36:43,580
迈克·罗斯又去找了莫妮卡·伊顿
Mike Ross went to see Monica Eton again.

884
00:36:43,590 --> 00:36:45,490
-你让他去的吗  -他自己去的
- At your direction? - On his own.

885
00:36:45,890 --> 00:36:47,310
该死的孩子
Goddamn kid.

886
00:36:47,510 --> 00:36:49,710
-他就像另一个你  -并不完全是
- He's another you. - Not exactly.

887
00:36:50,230 --> 00:36:53,570
他去为刚开始骗了她而道歉
He went to apologize for lying to her the first time.

888
00:36:53,620 --> 00:36:55,210
-他没说谎  -没错
- He didn't lie. - No.

889
00:36:56,020 --> 00:36:56,990
是我们
We did.

890
00:36:57,120 --> 00:36:59,840
就像你们俩骗我  说他是律师
Like the two of you lied to me about him being a lawyer?

891
00:36:59,940 --> 00:37:01,040
不如就算咱俩扯平了吧
How about we call it even?

892
00:37:01,040 --> 00:37:02,780
还差得远
It's nowhere near even.

893
00:37:06,040 --> 00:37:07,540
-不是吗  -这是什么
- Isn't it? - What's this?

894
00:37:08,310 --> 00:37:09,540
他让她提出了和解
He got her to settle.

895
00:37:09,570 --> 00:37:11,390
-之前并没有开价  -现在有了
- There wasn't an offer. - There is now.

896
00:37:13,370 --> 00:37:14,770
我们还是要付出赔款
This does not get us off easy.

897
00:37:14,770 --> 00:37:16,790
总比一千五百万少多了
Hell of a lot less than $15 million.

898
00:37:16,790 --> 00:37:18,940
-她根本不配拿一分钱  -这不重要
- she doesn't deserve a dime. - Doesn't matter.

899
00:37:19,030 --> 00:37:20,460
我开除她没错
I was right to fire her.

900
00:37:20,530 --> 00:37:23,050
那和这事无关  你知道的
That's not what this is about, and you know it.

901
00:37:32,330 --> 00:37:35,620
那时他和她在一起  让我看起来像个傻瓜
He made me look like a fool with her then,

902
00:37:37,190 --> 00:37:39,230
现在他还是让我看起来像个傻瓜
and he's made me look like a fool with her now.

903
00:37:40,270 --> 00:37:42,630
没人会在乎他取证时说了什么
No one cares what he said in that deposition.

904
00:37:42,690 --> 00:37:44,650
你觉得我在乎他取证时所说的话吗
You think I give a shit about what he said in that deposition?

905
00:37:44,650 --> 00:37:46,770
我是说他让我签下那个协议的事
I meant getting me to sign that agreement.

906
00:37:46,770 --> 00:37:48,490
你不可能每步都赢
You can't win every move.

907
00:37:48,490 --> 00:37:49,890
我应该预料到会有这一幕
I should have seen it coming.

908
00:37:49,890 --> 00:37:51,700
你只是在重压下做了决定
You made a decision under the gun.

909
00:37:51,760 --> 00:37:53,880
-是我让他有这个机会  -我们打败他
- I let him put me there. - We beat him

910
00:37:53,880 --> 00:37:56,640
是因为在我失去冷静时  你能保持冷静
because you kept your cool when I wanted to lose mine.

911
00:37:58,470 --> 00:38:01,180
保持冷静  签了协议
Keep your cool now, sign this agreement,

912
00:38:01,180 --> 00:38:02,920
让我们再次打败他
and let's beat him again.

913
00:38:12,580 --> 00:38:14,010
你看起来很高兴
You look happy.

914
00:38:14,940 --> 00:38:16,200
你也是
So do you.

915
00:38:16,660 --> 00:38:19,570
没压力了  不用再写论文了
The pressure's off. No more essay.

916
00:38:20,580 --> 00:38:22,740
-你完成了  -我有了重大突破
- You finished it. - I had a breakthrough.

917
00:38:22,860 --> 00:38:24,680
是什么
What was it?

918
00:38:26,140 --> 00:38:27,430
我是一名律师助理
I'm a paralegal.

919
00:38:27,930 --> 00:38:29,310
瑞秋  不要告诉我那是…
Rachel, please tell me that that doesn't--

920
00:38:29,310 --> 00:38:31,250
不  不是  不是坏事
No, I don't-- I don't mean that in a bad way.

921
00:38:31,780 --> 00:38:33,040
我是说好事
I mean it in a great way.

922
00:38:33,290 --> 00:38:34,120
你知道企业律师的
Do you know what the length

923
00:38:34,120 --> 00:38:36,260
平均职业生涯是多久吗
of an average corporate lawyer's career is?

924
00:38:37,090 --> 00:38:37,960
30年
30 years.

925
00:38:37,960 --> 00:38:39,150
错了
Wrong.

926
00:38:43,470 --> 00:38:45,360
因为他们讨厌这个职业
Because they hate it.

927
00:38:46,200 --> 00:38:47,050
我不是这样
Not me.

928
00:38:47,080 --> 00:38:49,760
我在这里比75%的助理待得都久
I've been here longer than 75% of our associates,

929
00:38:49,760 --> 00:38:50,970
而且我喜欢这里
and I love it.

930
00:38:50,970 --> 00:38:53,510
也就是说你要是离开  你的幻想不会破灭
Which means when you get out, you won't be disillusioned.

931
00:38:53,510 --> 00:38:56,270
不  那样对我是一种解脱
No. I'll be unleashed.

932
00:38:56,270 --> 00:38:58,110
在论文里我也是这么说的
And that's what I told them in my essay.

933
00:38:58,650 --> 00:38:59,710
-换句话说  -你将会是
- In other words... - You're gonna be

934
00:38:59,710 --> 00:39:01,960
他们见过的最好的律师
the best damn lawyer they've ever seen.

935
00:39:01,960 --> 00:39:03,980
-我要去哈佛啦  -真的
- I'm going to Harvard. - You really are.

936
00:39:03,980 --> 00:39:06,450
是啊  是啊
Yeah. Yeah.

937
00:39:11,850 --> 00:39:12,890
怎么了
What?

938
00:39:12,930 --> 00:39:15,560
没什么  只是有点打击到我
Nothing. It just--just hit me.

939
00:39:16,850 --> 00:39:18,460
你再也不会在这里了
You're not gonna be here anymore.

940
00:39:19,540 --> 00:39:21,330
我是说  你会…你知道你会在那里
I mean, you'll-- you know, you'll be there.

941
00:39:21,970 --> 00:39:24,100
-波士顿  -剑桥
- Boston. - Cambridge.

942
00:39:26,160 --> 00:39:27,990
我想我只能习惯如此了
I guess I'll just have to get used to that.

943
00:39:30,360 --> 00:39:32,310
我想我也得习惯如此了
I guess I'll have to get used to that too.

944
00:39:41,380 --> 00:39:42,240
你要回家吗
You going home?

945
00:39:42,240 --> 00:39:43,700
除非还有什么急事
Unless there's something pressing?

946
00:39:43,700 --> 00:39:45,960
-没  我只是…  -那里怎么了
- No, I was just gonna, uh-- - Hey, what happened here?

947
00:39:45,960 --> 00:39:46,970
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

948
00:39:46,970 --> 00:39:49,220
-歪了  -我觉得很正常
- It's off. - Looks fine to me.

949
00:39:49,720 --> 00:39:50,960
不正常
It isn't.

950
00:39:54,810 --> 00:39:57,230
等一下  你很关注细节的吧
Wait a second. Your eye for detail?

951
00:39:57,240 --> 00:40:00,290
有一个标志倾斜  我会听你念叨一周
One record askew, and I don't hear the end of it for a week.

952
00:40:00,590 --> 00:40:02,960
你刮坏了我的迈尔士·戴维斯的唱片
You scratched my Miles Davis.

953
00:40:06,280 --> 00:40:07,430
是我干的
It was me.

954
00:40:07,450 --> 00:40:09,320
-你想什么呢  -我生气了
- What were you thinking? - I was pissed.

955
00:40:09,330 --> 00:40:11,070
-你真情绪化  -我不冷静
- You're so emotional. - I lost my cool.

956
00:40:11,070 --> 00:40:12,920
-你不该那么做  -我知道
- You shouldn't have done that. - I know.

957
00:40:12,930 --> 00:40:14,400
我不该打哈德曼
I shouldn't have hit Hardman.

958
00:40:15,200 --> 00:40:16,980
-你不是吧  -我打了
- You didn't. - I did.

959
00:40:17,060 --> 00:40:19,540
-什么时候  -就在杰西卡取证前
- When? - Right before Jessica's depo.

960
00:40:19,610 --> 00:40:21,400
-握紧的拳头  -张开的手掌
- Closed fist? - Open palm.

961
00:40:21,400 --> 00:40:23,250
-甩巴掌  -非常狠
- Bitch slap! - Damn straight.

962
00:40:23,340 --> 00:40:24,230
感觉怎么样
How'd it feel?

963
00:40:24,230 --> 00:40:25,900
好到让我又甩了他一次
Good enough that I did it again.

964
00:40:26,270 --> 00:40:28,640
瞧瞧你  真是漂亮
Look at you. You're beautiful.

965
00:40:29,250 --> 00:40:32,200
-你有约会  -事实上  是的
- You have a date? - As a matter of fact, I do.

966
00:40:32,530 --> 00:40:34,450
刻薄  不能生育  狗屁
Bitter and barren, my ass.

967
00:40:34,620 --> 00:40:35,730
特别的人吗
Someone special?

968
00:40:35,780 --> 00:40:38,320
谁知道呢  也许就是我的白马王子呢
You never know. Could be the one.

969
00:40:42,020 --> 00:40:46,120
帮忙把那个该死的名字拿下来吧
Oh, and why don't you go ahead and take that damn name down.

970
00:40:53,710 --> 00:40:56,690
你老是来这里  劳拉会收拾你的
You keep showing up here, Laura's gonna kick your ass.

971
00:40:57,300 --> 00:40:59,890
妒火中烧的女人比你想像的要可怕多了
Oh, you'd be surprised at the strength of a jealous woman.

972
00:41:00,770 --> 00:41:03,170
她完全不用担心
She has nothing to worry about.

973
00:41:03,940 --> 00:41:06,480
再一次  我猜你来这里不是为了寻求帮助
Once again, I guess you're not here to ask for a favor.

974
00:41:06,480 --> 00:41:08,260
你想了解丹尼尔
You want to know who Daniel is?

975
00:41:08,850 --> 00:41:10,520
自己读读他的话吧
Read his own words.

976
00:41:13,990 --> 00:41:15,840
他不是第一个有外遇的男人
He's not the first man to have an affair.

977
00:41:16,210 --> 00:41:17,830
也许他是第一个反过来
Maybe the first to turn around and sue

978
00:41:17,830 --> 00:41:19,930
为自己的举动起诉前同事的人
his former colleagues for his own actions.

979
00:41:19,930 --> 00:41:21,720
你就这点料吗
That's all you have?

980
00:41:21,740 --> 00:41:22,990
冰山一角而已
Tip of the iceberg.

981
00:41:23,000 --> 00:41:26,170
如果你让他加入  他也会反过来对付你
Believe me, he will turn on you if you let him in.

982
00:41:26,170 --> 00:41:28,420
没人让他加入  他只是个承包人
No one's letting him in. He's a contractor.

983
00:41:28,420 --> 00:41:30,600
他不是合伙人  也不是顾问
He's not a partner, he's not of counsel,

984
00:41:30,600 --> 00:41:32,320
-他也不是助理  -我要说
- he's not an associate. - I'm telling you,

985
00:41:32,320 --> 00:41:33,790
把他从福尔松食品公司的案子里赶出去
kick him off of Folsom Foods.

986
00:41:33,790 --> 00:41:34,830
别让他进你地盘
Don't let him in your house.

987
00:41:34,830 --> 00:41:37,200
我刚告诉你了  他并没有进我地盘
And I just told you, he's not in my house.

988
00:41:37,220 --> 00:41:38,580
你在我的地盘上
You're in my house.

989
00:41:40,250 --> 00:41:42,240
如果我们的拥有的是同一块地盘呢
What if our houses were the same?

990
00:41:42,690 --> 00:41:45,380
现在  你速度颇快啊
Oh, now. You're moving pretty fast.

991
00:41:45,420 --> 00:41:48,200
我说过了  我老婆很爱吃醋的
I told you, my wife's the jealous type.

992
00:41:48,590 --> 00:41:50,720
你提过一次合并
You offered a merger once.

993
00:41:50,730 --> 00:41:52,730
我们和解了这些案子  就合并
Let's settle these cases, get it done.

994
00:41:55,960 --> 00:41:57,150
你那么恨他吗
You hate him that much?

995
00:41:57,150 --> 00:41:58,380
要还是不要
Yes or no?

996
00:41:59,690 --> 00:42:00,990
问题是这样的
Here's the problem.

997
00:42:01,210 --> 00:42:02,410
之前合并看起来很不错
Merger looked good before,

998
00:42:02,410 --> 00:42:04,190
但是现在我们让你们命悬一线
but now we have you on the ropes.

999
00:42:04,870 --> 00:42:08,530
所以当皮尔逊什么的破产了
So when Pearson whatever goes under,

1000
00:42:08,830 --> 00:42:10,820
我们就能免费拾遗
we'll pick up the pieces for free.

1001
00:42:11,080 --> 00:42:12,990
你并没有让我们命悬一线
You do not have us on the ropes.

1002
00:42:12,990 --> 00:42:14,890
明天你就知道了
You'll get it tomorrow.

1003
00:42:14,910 --> 00:42:16,980
我们将会在七个司法管辖区内
We're filing to try seven different cases

1004
00:42:16,980 --> 00:42:19,540
同时提出七个不同案件
in seven different jurisdictions all at the same time.

1005
00:42:20,400 --> 00:42:22,600
-高效办案  -没错
- Rocket Docket. - Yeah.

1006
00:42:22,610 --> 00:42:24,250
这是丹尼尔的主意
It was Daniel's idea.

1007
00:42:25,660 --> 00:42:27,180
他会和你在法庭见
He'll see you in court.

