1
00:00:36,930 --> 00:00:37,760
紧张吗
Nervous?

2
00:00:39,640 --> 00:00:41,070
说不紧张那是撒谎
I'd be lying if I said no.

3
00:00:41,350 --> 00:00:42,900
撒谎可不好
Well, I wouldn't want you to lie.

4
00:00:44,830 --> 00:00:46,170
-她都知道了  -不可能
- She knows. - She can't.

5
00:00:46,180 --> 00:00:46,950
是真的
She does.

6
00:00:47,420 --> 00:00:49,010
我的斯温顿并购案遇到什么麻烦了
What's holding on my Swinton merger?

7
00:00:49,120 --> 00:00:49,930
你是在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?

8
00:00:49,940 --> 00:00:51,090
这事我们讨论过了
We've been over this, okay?

9
00:00:51,100 --> 00:00:52,590
如果她知道了  你也会知道的
If she knew, you'd know.

10
00:00:52,600 --> 00:00:54,470
我就知道  她连我叫什么都不知道
I do know. The woman barely knows my name,

11
00:00:54,480 --> 00:00:55,860
居然约我去吃饭
and she just summoned me for dinner.

12
00:00:55,870 --> 00:00:57,000
有什么好笑的
What is so funny?

13
00:00:57,010 --> 00:00:59,890
华生  克莱曼  加洛  高德伯格  斯佩克特
Watson, Klyman, Gallo, Goldberg, and Specter.

14
00:00:59,970 --> 00:01:02,580
-你说的是  -倒数五位成为高级合伙人的人
- Why are you naming- - The last five senior partners?

15
00:01:02,590 --> 00:01:05,490
我们来公司的第一年都被杰西卡约出去吃过饭
Every one of us was taken to dinner by Jessica as a first-year.

16
00:01:05,500 --> 00:01:06,960
现在她又约你去吃饭  就是说
And now she's taking you, which means--

17
00:01:06,970 --> 00:01:08,630
-这是件好事  -没错
- This is a good thing. - Exactly.

18
00:01:08,980 --> 00:01:10,120
天呐
Oh, God.

19
00:01:10,250 --> 00:01:11,560
-又怎么了  -我该穿什么
- What now? - What do I wear?

20
00:01:11,570 --> 00:01:13,700
去了说什么  穿什么去
Wh-what do I say? What do I wear?

21
00:01:13,710 --> 00:01:15,740
休息时再讨论这么幼稚的问题吧
We can discuss the prom at recess.

22
00:01:16,100 --> 00:01:18,100
先说说我的斯温顿并购案遇到什么麻烦了
Tell me what the hell's holding up my Swinton Merger.

23
00:01:18,110 --> 00:01:19,430
就是个“无聊诉讼”
Oh, it's just a nuisance suit

24
00:01:18,110 --> 00:01:19,430
明知打不赢  只为干扰原告提出的诉讼

25
00:01:19,440 --> 00:01:21,470
得把它搞定才能完成托管
that needs to be cleaned up before we can clear escrow.

26
00:01:21,470 --> 00:01:22,190
我在办了
I'm all over it.

27
00:01:22,450 --> 00:01:23,840
为什么不先汇报这个
Why wasn't that the first thing you told me?

28
00:01:23,850 --> 00:01:25,470
我以为我的事要曝光了
Uh, I thought I was getting exposed.

29
00:01:25,480 --> 00:01:26,840
这件事就没那么要紧了
This is a little less important.

30
00:01:27,020 --> 00:01:29,630
我的并购案比你的恐慌重要得多
My merger-- your panic attack.

31
00:01:29,640 --> 00:01:30,730
你这人有没有同情心
Your compassion.

32
00:01:30,740 --> 00:01:32,710
何况我没有恐慌
And I didn't have a panic attack.

33
00:01:32,720 --> 00:01:34,330
我的担心有充分的理由
I had a legitimate reason for concern.

34
00:01:34,340 --> 00:01:37,050
是吗  她为开除你还专门约你吃饭吗
Really? Why would she ask you to dinner just to fire you?

35
00:01:37,050 --> 00:01:38,530
不好说  有部电影叫做《盗亦有道》
I don't know. A little movie called Goodfellas.

36
00:01:38,540 --> 00:01:39,310
你看过吗
Did you see it?

37
00:01:39,910 --> 00:01:41,940
乔·佩西以为他要加入黑手党了呢  结果被杀了
Joe Pesci thought he was getting made--he got dead.

38
00:01:41,950 --> 00:01:43,400
这就是你所谓的充分理由
That's your idea of a legitimate reason?

39
00:01:43,410 --> 00:01:45,650
“凯伦  我的钱呢  凯伦”
"Karen! Where's the money, Karen?"

40
00:01:47,220 --> 00:01:48,080
“凯伦”
Karen?"

41
00:01:48,900 --> 00:01:49,720
他们就没核实过
They never checked.

42
00:01:49,790 --> 00:01:51,340
这是什么意思
What do you mean "They never checked"?

43
00:01:51,420 --> 00:01:54,140
以前互联网可没这么发达
The internet was not what it is today.

44
00:01:54,730 --> 00:01:56,630
那会儿剽窃不容易被抓
It was not so easy to catch plagiarism.

45
00:01:56,910 --> 00:01:58,630
上帝  真爽
God, that's awesome.

46
00:01:59,390 --> 00:02:00,290
等等
Wait a minute.

47
00:02:00,820 --> 00:02:02,670
如果你是那会儿从法学院毕业的  那
If you graduated college then, then that--

48
00:02:03,140 --> 00:02:03,730
那就意味着你
that would make you--

49
00:02:03,740 --> 00:02:05,490
有足够的资历办自己的律所了
Old enough to run my own law firm.

50
00:02:05,630 --> 00:02:06,790
但是你看起来很年轻啊
But you look so young.

51
00:02:06,940 --> 00:02:09,200
常言说得好
Well, you know what they say.

52
00:02:09,210 --> 00:02:10,900
-美丽不分年龄  -黑人不易老
- True beauty is ageless. - Black don't crack.

53
00:02:13,960 --> 00:02:15,140
我就是那个意思
That's what I meant to say.

54
00:02:18,040 --> 00:02:20,770
别说我了  我想听听你的故事
Well, enough about me. I want to hear about you.

55
00:02:22,170 --> 00:02:23,220
上哈佛是个什么感觉
What was Harvard like?

56
00:02:28,220 --> 00:02:29,690
三岁的时候  我意识到
I was three when I realized

57
00:02:29,700 --> 00:02:32,320
我和其他孩子不同
that I wasn't like the other kids.

58
00:02:32,620 --> 00:02:35,480
读书对我就像游戏一样
When school started, it was like a joke.

59
00:02:35,490 --> 00:02:37,800
我从不记笔记  也不学习
I didn't take notes. I never studied.

60
00:02:38,240 --> 00:02:40,460
每年人们都会对我说
Every year people would tell me,

61
00:02:40,840 --> 00:02:43,460
你明年再这样就会跟不上了
"Next year you won't get away with it."

62
00:02:44,120 --> 00:02:46,250
我一直等着跟不上的那天  但是
Kept waiting for it to get harder, but...

63
00:02:47,170 --> 00:02:48,030
那一天一直没来
It just never did.

64
00:02:49,260 --> 00:02:50,340
在哈佛呢
And Harvard?

65
00:02:50,680 --> 00:02:53,510
我知道偷懒的日子到头了  毫无疑问
I knew it would end. I mean, it had to.

66
00:02:53,980 --> 00:02:58,210
我以为终于能找到一个让我
I thought, "Yeah, I'd finally found a place where I'd be, uh...

67
00:02:58,640 --> 00:02:59,420
搞不定的地方
exposed."

68
00:03:00,100 --> 00:03:03,760
结果发现  即使是强大的哈佛法学院
But it turns out, even at the mighty Harvard Law--

69
00:03:03,890 --> 00:03:05,500
你仍然超凡脱俗
You weren't the same as the other kids.

70
00:03:06,310 --> 00:03:08,140
-我知道听着很自大  -我不觉得
- I know it sounds cocky. - Not to me.

71
00:03:08,770 --> 00:03:11,040
事实上  你也不觉得自己有多聪明
The fact is, you don't think of yourself as smart.

72
00:03:12,380 --> 00:03:14,690
你有超人的智商  事实就是如此
You've always had your mind, it just is what it is.

73
00:03:14,700 --> 00:03:16,540
是  就是这样
Yeah, that's exactly what it is.

74
00:03:16,550 --> 00:03:18,250
我不觉得自己有多聪明
I don't think of myself as smart, you know.

75
00:03:18,260 --> 00:03:19,530
我只是觉得别人都…
I just think of everybody else as...

76
00:03:19,540 --> 00:03:21,200
-白痴  -不聪明
- Idiots. - Not smart.

77
00:03:23,250 --> 00:03:24,510
我就是那个意思
That's what I meant to say.

78
00:03:27,980 --> 00:03:28,970
为什么选法律
Why the law?

79
00:03:29,970 --> 00:03:31,720
个人原因
It's kind of, uh, personal.

80
00:03:31,730 --> 00:03:33,180
我们不就是来谈你的吗
Isn't that why we're here?

81
00:03:40,340 --> 00:03:41,360
我十一岁那年
When I was 11,

82
00:03:41,370 --> 00:03:43,650
我父母吃完饭回家
my parents were on their way home from dinner,

83
00:03:44,710 --> 00:03:47,920
路上他们遇到了一起严重事故
and they were involved in a really horrible accident.

84
00:03:48,510 --> 00:03:49,830
他们…
And, uh, they--

85
00:03:54,150 --> 00:03:55,640
我的奶奶收留了我
My grandmother took me in.

86
00:03:57,720 --> 00:04:01,090
很多年后我才发现
And it wasn't until I was, uh, much older

87
00:04:01,100 --> 00:04:04,040
其实我们可以打官司的
that I realized that we had a case.

88
00:04:04,770 --> 00:04:06,680
因为那个餐厅
See, it turns out this restaurant...

89
00:04:07,590 --> 00:04:10,250
他们很早就发现
They kept feeding this Mr. Fenton drinks

90
00:04:10,260 --> 00:04:12,020
他们出售的饮品…
long after they knew--

91
00:04:16,570 --> 00:04:17,370
都过去了
Didn't matter.

92
00:04:18,640 --> 00:04:19,700
我只是
I just--

93
00:04:20,780 --> 00:04:22,510
当时我感觉很无助
I felt so helpless.

94
00:04:25,950 --> 00:04:27,630
我不想再有这样的感觉
And I didn't want to feel that way...

95
00:04:28,560 --> 00:04:29,480
永远不想
Ever again.

96
00:04:34,570 --> 00:04:35,690
哈维没错
Harvey was right.

97
00:04:37,920 --> 00:04:38,900
什么没错
About what?

98
00:04:39,810 --> 00:04:41,210
希望你带了支票簿
I hope you brought your checkbook.

99
00:04:42,800 --> 00:04:43,750
这顿算你的
Dinner's on you.

100
00:04:46,810 --> 00:04:48,770
等等  哈维什么事情没错
Wait. What was Harvey right about?

101
00:05:05,380 --> 00:05:07,430
-晚餐如何  -免费鱼子酱
- How was dinner? - Free caviar.

102
00:05:07,940 --> 00:05:09,000
还有什么好挑剔的呢
What's not to love?

103
00:05:09,140 --> 00:05:10,420
如果你想打听我的事
If you want to know something about me,

104
00:05:10,430 --> 00:05:11,510
可以直接来问我
you should have just asked me.

105
00:05:12,470 --> 00:05:14,370
为什么我不能用了解你的方式
Why can't I just be getting to know Mr. Ross

106
00:05:14,380 --> 00:05:15,390
去了解罗斯先生
the way I got to know you?

107
00:05:15,400 --> 00:05:17,380
因为如果你真是想了解他
Because if you're just trying to get to know him,

108
00:05:17,390 --> 00:05:18,750
就不会瞒着我晚餐的事
you would have told me about the dinner.

109
00:05:18,800 --> 00:05:21,190
这里面有蹊跷  我要知道实情
Something's going on, and I want to know what it is.

110
00:05:22,740 --> 00:05:23,900
有人举报
An allegation was made

111
00:05:23,910 --> 00:05:25,630
迈克·罗斯根本没上过哈佛
that Mike Ross never went to Harvard,

112
00:05:25,640 --> 00:05:27,920
也没上过其他法学院
or any other law school for that matter.

113
00:05:28,630 --> 00:05:29,850
所以我查了查
So I had him checked out.

114
00:05:31,930 --> 00:05:33,350
毫无嫌疑
Squeaky clean.

115
00:05:34,000 --> 00:05:35,520
毕业成绩全班第一
Graduated top of his class.

116
00:05:35,970 --> 00:05:37,430
所以我邀他吃饭
So I took him to dinner.

117
00:05:37,790 --> 00:05:40,570
我想知道你为什么对他另眼相待
I wanted to see what you saw in him that makes him so special.

118
00:05:40,840 --> 00:05:41,800
结果呢
And?

119
00:05:42,890 --> 00:05:43,750
我明白了
I get it.

120
00:05:44,880 --> 00:05:46,100
他绝对是可造之材
He's a total package.

121
00:05:46,220 --> 00:05:48,510
或许比我们两人都强
Maybe even the best of both of us.

122
00:05:49,550 --> 00:05:51,990
你不是想让我负责招聘吧
I hope this doesn't mean you're gonna put me in charge of recruiting.

123
00:05:52,000 --> 00:05:53,900
别担心  放过你了
Not to worry. You are off the hook.

124
00:05:57,490 --> 00:05:59,900
哈维  还有一件事
Harvey, one more thing.

125
00:06:02,490 --> 00:06:03,990
我虽然没查出问题来
He might have checked out clean,

126
00:06:04,680 --> 00:06:06,390
但我知道那孩子就是满嘴跑火车
But I know that kid's full of shit.

127
00:06:07,250 --> 00:06:09,910
他虽然有哈佛法学院的毕业证书
Because there may be a record of him graduating from Harvard Law,

128
00:06:09,920 --> 00:06:11,360
但地球上任何一家大学
But there's no record of him graduating

129
00:06:11,370 --> 00:06:14,340
都没有他毕业的记录
from any college anywhere on the face of the earth.

130
00:06:15,750 --> 00:06:17,450
在没有证据之前
So I'm gonna give you the benefit of the doubt

131
00:06:17,890 --> 00:06:19,560
我就当你不知情
that you didn't know.

132
00:06:20,010 --> 00:06:22,700
因为如果你知情  我就只能大义灭亲
Because I don't want to do what I would do if you did.

133
00:06:22,790 --> 00:06:26,170
而你要做的  就是开除那个死孩子
And what you're going to do is fire that goddamn kid.

134
00:06:38,110 --> 00:06:42,110
 本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
 更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
 

135
00:06:38,110 --> 00:06:42,110
■

136
00:06:42,110 --> 00:06:46,110
■

137
00:06:42,110 --> 00:06:46,110
翻译：NoNopig控大叔  壹不贰  宁馨儿
swears控正太  真月镜威  丢丢曳很蛋疼

138
00:06:46,110 --> 00:06:50,110
■

139
00:06:46,110 --> 00:06:50,110
时间轴：迟迟 饿得慌 加森  校对：饿得慌  油炸电风扇  草草

140
00:06:50,110 --> 00:06:54,110
■

141
00:06:50,110 --> 00:06:54,110
特效&后期：灰灰是菇凉   总监： 丢丢呼啦啦

142
00:06:54,380 --> 00:06:56,480
第二季 第一集

143
00:06:54,380 --> 00:06:56,480
蓝光-1080P-SHORTBREHD版调轴风格微修：字幕雷哥

144
00:06:54,380 --> 00:06:56,480
诉 讼 双 雄

145
00:07:07,260 --> 00:07:08,110
唐娜  帮个忙
Donna, do me a favor

146
00:07:08,110 --> 00:07:10,900
请帮我接谢尔曼先生  谢谢
and get Mr. Sherman on the phone, please. Thank you.

147
00:07:13,410 --> 00:07:16,000
-怎么回事  -什么
- What was that? - Excuse me?

148
00:07:16,120 --> 00:07:18,050
“请”  “帮个忙”还有“谢谢”
"Please," "Do me a favor," and "Thank you,"

149
00:07:18,050 --> 00:07:19,240
出现在一句话里
all in the same sentence?

150
00:07:19,240 --> 00:07:20,580
你以为我不会发觉吗
You think I'm not gonna notice that?

151
00:07:20,580 --> 00:07:22,260
-我没时间说这个  -你有
- I don't have time for this. - You got time.

152
00:07:22,330 --> 00:07:23,050
你就坐着吧
You're gonna sit right there

153
00:07:23,050 --> 00:07:24,430
我会搞清楚到底发生了什么
while I figure out what the hell's going on.

154
00:07:24,670 --> 00:07:25,650
什么都没发生
Nothing's going on.

155
00:07:26,130 --> 00:07:27,920
领带褶太靠左
Dimple in your tie's too far to the left.

156
00:07:27,920 --> 00:07:29,900
说明你在想别的事
That says that your mind is on something else.

157
00:07:29,900 --> 00:07:32,290
谢尔曼先生打过136通电话
Mr. Sherman's called 136 times,

158
00:07:32,290 --> 00:07:33,510
你一个都没回
you've never called him back,

159
00:07:33,570 --> 00:07:35,600
说明你觉得很愧疚
which means you're feeling guilty

160
00:07:35,600 --> 00:07:37,580
-在想办法补偿  -我没有
- and you're trying to compensate. - I'm not trying to--

161
00:07:37,580 --> 00:07:39,330
我没说过分补偿啊
I didn't say overcompensate.

162
00:07:39,330 --> 00:07:40,520
明白就好
As long as we're clear.

163
00:07:41,650 --> 00:07:43,030
我唯一一次见你喷薰衣草古龙水
The only time I've ever seen you wear lavender

164
00:07:43,030 --> 00:07:44,670
就是你弟弟住院那次
was when your brother was in the hospital.

165
00:07:46,550 --> 00:07:48,400
要么是你妈妈突然出现了
Either your mother's somehow appeared in your life,

166
00:07:48,400 --> 00:07:50,090
要么是杰西卡发现了迈克的事
or Jessica found out about Mike.

167
00:07:52,280 --> 00:07:53,410
我的天
Oh, my God.

168
00:07:54,560 --> 00:07:55,460
他自己知道吗
Does he know?

169
00:08:11,630 --> 00:08:12,690
听什么呢
What's playing on that thing?

170
00:08:12,690 --> 00:08:15,430
有声书  《罗马帝国衰亡史》
Audiobook. The Fall of the Roman Empire.

171
00:08:17,510 --> 00:08:19,450
你这么开心
So you're awfully chipper.

172
00:08:19,450 --> 00:08:22,290
-是不是有好消息呢  -是的
- Maybe you got some good news? - Uh, yeah.

173
00:08:22,290 --> 00:08:24,690
我刚与一位极品女士愉快地共进了晚餐
That led to an amazing dinner with an incredible woman.

174
00:08:26,190 --> 00:08:28,410
我很高兴你和珍妮这么开心
I'm really happy to hear things are going well with you and Jenny.

175
00:08:28,410 --> 00:08:29,860
不是  不是  不是
Whoa, no. No, no, no.

176
00:08:29,860 --> 00:08:31,310
昨晚那是和杰西卡
I was out with Jessica last night.

177
00:08:32,240 --> 00:08:34,650
她对你来说是不是有点老了
Isn't she just a little old for you?

178
00:08:35,000 --> 00:08:37,200
我对熟女没问题
Uh, I do okay with the cougars.

179
00:08:37,470 --> 00:08:39,680
你知道你说的是本律所的执行合伙人吧
You realize you're talking about the managing partner of the firm?

180
00:08:41,700 --> 00:08:43,320
别告诉别人我说过这话啊
Please don't tell anyone I said that.

181
00:08:45,710 --> 00:08:46,970
你准备怎么办
What are you gonna do?

182
00:08:47,230 --> 00:08:48,210
我要炒了他
I'm gonna fire him.

183
00:08:48,210 --> 00:08:49,880
你们好啊  焚蛋们
What's up, mother fleckers?

184
00:08:50,330 --> 00:08:53,090
天呐  真是美好的一天
Wow. Oh, my God. That's a beautiful day.

185
00:08:58,200 --> 00:09:00,560
你们俩怎么了  有人去世了吗
What's wrong with you two? Somebody die?

186
00:09:01,140 --> 00:09:02,210
我先出去了
I'm gonna be outside.

187
00:09:03,540 --> 00:09:05,940
“我先出去了  我好严肃
"I'm gonna be outside. I'm so serious.

188
00:09:05,940 --> 00:09:06,800
从来如此”
All the time."

189
00:09:07,280 --> 00:09:08,890
迈克
Mike.

190
00:09:09,050 --> 00:09:09,740
坐下
Sit down.

191
00:09:09,740 --> 00:09:11,710
不行啊  我现在精力泛滥
No can do. I've got too much energy.

192
00:09:11,710 --> 00:09:14,440
我来是想告诉你斯温顿并购案的进展
I just wanted to come and give you an update on the Swinton Merger.

193
00:09:14,660 --> 00:09:18,220
有个女人认为出版商偷了一个她的点子
Turns out this woman thinks that publishing stole one of her book ideas.

194
00:09:18,220 --> 00:09:19,610
-于是提起诉讼  -听着
- Filed suit. - Listen.

195
00:09:19,610 --> 00:09:21,240
一般我会建议和解
Normally, I'd suggest that we settle.

196
00:09:21,410 --> 00:09:22,570
但是我开始想
But then I got to thinking.

197
00:09:22,980 --> 00:09:24,520
WWHD
WWHD--

198
00:09:25,170 --> 00:09:26,460
哈维会怎么做
What would Harvey do?

199
00:09:27,010 --> 00:09:28,470
-击垮她  -没错
- Steamroll her. - Exactly.

200
00:09:28,540 --> 00:09:29,490
我也会这么做
Which is what I'm gonna do.

201
00:09:29,490 --> 00:09:32,780
迈拉·哈里森  等着被秋风扫落叶吧
Myra Harrison is not gonna know what hit her.

202
00:09:32,860 --> 00:09:34,780
为什么现在接受我的理论了
Why embrace my philosophy now?

203
00:09:34,890 --> 00:09:37,990
你的并购案在这  迈拉·哈里森在这
Come on. Your merger--Myra Harrison.

204
00:09:39,960 --> 00:09:41,130
迈克
Mike.

205
00:09:42,850 --> 00:09:43,700
坐下来
Sit down.

206
00:09:56,580 --> 00:09:57,680
你还好吗
You okay?

207
00:09:58,020 --> 00:09:59,330
我现在没法说话
I can't talk right now.

208
00:10:02,760 --> 00:10:04,730
别纠结了  快跟我讲讲
Okay, just get it over with. Tell me what happened.

209
00:10:04,800 --> 00:10:07,200
谈话  计划和“我会怎么做”
The talk and the plan and the whole "What I would do,"

210
00:10:07,200 --> 00:10:08,510
都算了吧
is just whatever.

211
00:10:09,310 --> 00:10:10,290
你做不到
You couldn't do it.

212
00:10:10,410 --> 00:10:12,020
我没做
I didn't do it.

213
00:10:12,020 --> 00:10:15,080
对他的感情突入袭来  排山倒海
You got overwhelmed with a wave of emotion you didn't see coming.

214
00:10:15,080 --> 00:10:16,780
-哭着让他留下来  -没有
- You cried, and you let him stay. - No.

215
00:10:16,780 --> 00:10:19,480
我想到炒了他还得费事再找人替他
I thought of the amount of work I would have to go through to replace him

216
00:10:19,480 --> 00:10:20,710
决定留下他了
and decided against it.

217
00:10:20,760 --> 00:10:22,970
你想到这些的时候是不是泪眼婆娑
Did you see the amount of work through a pool of tears?

218
00:10:22,970 --> 00:10:24,880
-你说完没有  -要我给你拿点什么吗
- Are you finished? - Can I get you anything?

219
00:10:24,970 --> 00:10:26,940
纸巾  水  还是卫生巾
Tissue? Glass of water? Tampon?

220
00:10:27,730 --> 00:10:28,920
等一下
Okay, wait a second.

221
00:10:29,170 --> 00:10:31,370
你偷听我所有的私人谈话
You listen to all my private conversations.

222
00:10:33,060 --> 00:10:34,600
-那又怎样  -这次没有
- So? - This time you didn't.

223
00:10:35,050 --> 00:10:36,930
-我很忙  -忙吗
- Yeah, I was busy. - Busy?

224
00:10:38,000 --> 00:10:39,530
-这就是你的借口吗  -非常忙
- That's what you're going with? - Very busy.

225
00:10:39,530 --> 00:10:41,550
你没听是因为你不敢听
You didn't listen because you couldn't listen.

226
00:10:41,550 --> 00:10:43,890
感情排山倒海的是你
Because you were too overwhelmed with emotion.

227
00:10:43,890 --> 00:10:45,630
我不是事件的主角
I am not the topic of conversation here.

228
00:10:45,630 --> 00:10:47,570
要我给你拿点什么吗  纸巾  水
Can I get you anything? Tissue? Water?

229
00:10:47,570 --> 00:10:48,550
我明白了
I got it.

230
00:10:50,920 --> 00:10:51,810
哈维
Harvey,

231
00:10:52,290 --> 00:10:54,460
你说了你不炒他  杰西卡也会
you said if you didn't fire him, Jessica would.

232
00:10:55,310 --> 00:10:56,480
你准备怎么办
What are you gonna do?

233
00:10:56,850 --> 00:10:58,030
争取时间
Buy us some time.

234
00:11:00,850 --> 00:11:01,960
如果你什么都没说
If you didn't tell him anything,

235
00:11:01,960 --> 00:11:04,250
他怎么像丢了魂一样
why was he so dazed when he walked out of here?

236
00:11:04,360 --> 00:11:05,770
我说我为他骄傲
I told him I was proud of him.

237
00:11:06,220 --> 00:11:08,150
你得多给那孩子点鼓励
You need to give that boy more encouragement.

238
00:11:15,820 --> 00:11:17,080
请问詹姆斯·詹金斯的新书
Could you tell me where I could find a copy

239
00:11:17,080 --> 00:11:18,550
摆在哪里
of James Jenkins' latest book?

240
00:11:19,470 --> 00:11:21,840
在最新上架区
Um, right there in new releases.

241
00:11:22,500 --> 00:11:24,210
很有趣
Oh, that's funny.

242
00:11:24,380 --> 00:11:26,220
我这儿有份投诉写着
'cause I have a complaint here that says

243
00:11:26,270 --> 00:11:28,290
你声称这本书是你写的
that you're claiming to have written his newest book.

244
00:11:29,730 --> 00:11:30,870
不好意思  你是
Sorry, who are you?

245
00:11:30,870 --> 00:11:33,540
迈克·罗斯  德瑞克出版社聘请的律师
My name's Mike Ross. I represent Drecker Publishing.

246
00:11:33,650 --> 00:11:34,530
让我来告诉你
I want to tell you the story

247
00:11:34,530 --> 00:11:36,360
你这个狗屁诉讼的结果吧
of how your bullshit lawsuit pans out.

248
00:11:36,360 --> 00:11:38,750
最佳情况  你证明他们偷了你的创意
Best case, you prove that they stole your idea.

249
00:11:38,750 --> 00:11:40,250
但是  这也没用
You know what? It doesn't matter.

250
00:11:40,250 --> 00:11:43,690
因为你签了雇佣合同
Because you signed an employment agreement

251
00:11:43,770 --> 00:11:45,430
这里面赋予德瑞克出版社
Giving Drecker Publishing the rights

252
00:11:45,510 --> 00:11:47,460
对你的所有作品享有版权
to all work product that you create.

253
00:11:47,460 --> 00:11:49,080
算你走运  
Now lucky for you,

254
00:11:49,080 --> 00:11:50,700
我们碰巧正忙着并购
we happen to be in the middle of a merger,

255
00:11:50,700 --> 00:11:52,550
而你则给我们添了乱
And you're kind of being an inconvenience.

256
00:11:52,550 --> 00:11:54,470
所以就由我来当这个好人
So I get to be the good guy who comes down here

257
00:11:54,470 --> 00:11:57,760
强烈建议你现在就放弃
and strongly advises you to just go ahead and give up now

258
00:11:57,760 --> 00:11:59,250
也给自己省一大笔钱
and save yourself a whole lot of money.

259
00:12:00,190 --> 00:12:01,550
总之  要说的就这么多
Anyway, that's all.

260
00:12:01,670 --> 00:12:02,990
谢谢你的耐心聆听
Thank you so much for your time,

261
00:12:03,100 --> 00:12:04,080
祝一天快乐
and have a nice day.

262
00:12:06,190 --> 00:12:07,560
你妈妈一定以你为荣
I bet your mother's proud of you.

263
00:12:09,630 --> 00:12:10,960
-你说什么  -你听到了
- Excuse me? - You heard me.

264
00:12:12,130 --> 00:12:15,780
打扮得西装革履  说我的诉讼是狗屁
Standing there in your fancy suit calling my story bullshit?

265
00:12:15,780 --> 00:12:16,880
你都没听过我的说法
You don't even know what it is.

266
00:12:16,940 --> 00:12:18,320
哈里森女士  这不是我分内的事
Ms. Harrison, it's not my job to--

267
00:12:18,320 --> 00:12:19,590
所以你就漠不关心
To what? To care?

268
00:12:19,630 --> 00:12:22,180
不能有点人性听我说两句
To be a human being? To listen for two seconds?

269
00:12:27,300 --> 00:12:29,800
我在德瑞克做了五年的助理
I was an assistant at Drecker for five years,

270
00:12:29,840 --> 00:12:32,630
终于有了灵感  想出一本自己的书
and I finally got an idea for my own book.

271
00:12:33,020 --> 00:12:35,720
而我的老板  我还拿她当朋友
And my boss, who I thought was my friend,

272
00:12:35,720 --> 00:12:37,990
她鼓励我把创意告诉她
encouraged me to pitch my idea to her.

273
00:12:38,010 --> 00:12:39,970
我告诉她了  她就偷了我的创意
So I did. And she took that idea,

274
00:12:39,970 --> 00:12:42,510
拿给了詹姆斯·詹金斯  把我甩在一边
served it up to James Jenkins, and completely shut me out.

275
00:12:45,630 --> 00:12:46,670
迈拉
Myra, wh--

276
00:12:47,650 --> 00:12:48,880
你到底想怎么样
What are you looking for here?

277
00:12:48,950 --> 00:12:50,440
这些灵感来之不易
These ideas aren't easy to come by.

278
00:12:50,440 --> 00:12:52,910
或许我这辈子都不会再有了
I might not have another one in my entire life.

279
00:12:53,790 --> 00:12:55,780
我只想讨回我灵感的价值
I just want to be paid for my idea.

280
00:13:04,370 --> 00:13:06,530
终于晋升到档案管理员了吗
Finally get your big promotion to file clerk?

281
00:13:06,690 --> 00:13:07,540
告诉你一声
For your information,

282
00:13:07,540 --> 00:13:09,210
我正在为斯温顿并购案
I happen to be compiling a redundancy list

283
00:13:09,210 --> 00:13:10,200
编辑裁员名单
for the Swinton Merger.

284
00:13:10,430 --> 00:13:12,130
对了  你顺便编辑一下
Well, while you're at it, why don't you compile

285
00:13:12,130 --> 00:13:13,990
斯温顿并购案的裁员名单吧
a redundancy list for the Swinton Merger?

286
00:13:14,010 --> 00:13:15,270
你是不是少在这儿搞笑
Instead of trying to be hilarious,

287
00:13:15,450 --> 00:13:17,010
去把并购搞定
maybe you can just close the deal,

288
00:13:17,040 --> 00:13:18,100
我也能做我的本职工作
so then I can do my job

289
00:13:18,100 --> 00:13:20,350
决定该对哪些部门下手
and determine which departments get bashed in the head.

290
00:13:20,380 --> 00:13:22,540
-你在猎杀海豹吗  -那还好了
- What, are you killing seals? - Would that it were.

291
00:13:23,210 --> 00:13:24,250
他们就是大海里的老鼠
Rodents of the sea.

292
00:13:24,320 --> 00:13:26,950
听着  你得让迈克·罗斯休息一段时间
Listen, I need you to lay off Mike Ross for a while.

293
00:13:28,120 --> 00:13:29,160
你说了算吗
Oh, do you now?

294
00:13:29,490 --> 00:13:30,640
他虽然是你的助理
Because he may be your associate,

295
00:13:30,640 --> 00:13:33,240
但我告诉过你无数次了
but as I've told you, like, I don't know, a million times,

296
00:13:33,280 --> 00:13:36,020
-助理们归我管  -我不否认
- I run the associates. - I'm not disputing that.

297
00:13:36,060 --> 00:13:38,070
只是现在杰西卡对他有了兴趣…
It's just with Jessica's new interest in him--

298
00:13:40,010 --> 00:13:41,680
-什么兴趣  -你还没听说吗
- What interest? - Hadn't you heard?

299
00:13:41,680 --> 00:13:42,620
-听说什么  -那算了
- Heard what? - Never mind.

300
00:13:42,620 --> 00:13:44,070
不  告诉我  现在立刻马上
No, tell me. Tell me now.

301
00:13:45,170 --> 00:13:47,490
杰西卡昨晚带迈克去吃饭了  在伊阿古
Jessica took Mike to dinner last night. Iago's.

302
00:13:47,510 --> 00:13:48,340
伊阿古
Iag--

303
00:13:51,810 --> 00:13:52,940
我们当年也去的那儿
That's where she took me.

304
00:13:53,050 --> 00:13:55,220
真的吗
Really? Oh.

305
00:13:55,910 --> 00:13:58,330
反正  就算帮我个忙
Anyway, I'd consider it a personal favor

306
00:13:58,330 --> 00:14:00,090
让迈克休息几天就好
if you'd just lay off mike for a few days,

307
00:14:00,130 --> 00:14:01,170
你决定吧
but it's your call.

308
00:14:12,360 --> 00:14:14,120
你好  谢谢
Hey. Thanks.

309
00:14:14,820 --> 00:14:15,870
你在这儿做什么
What are you doing here?

310
00:14:17,270 --> 00:14:20,120
现在就告诉我你跟瑞秋是怎么回事
Right now, i want to know what's going on with you and Rachel.

311
00:14:21,340 --> 00:14:23,200
-没事  -没事
- Nothing. - Nothing?

312
00:14:23,200 --> 00:14:25,010
珍妮  这个问题还要我回答多少遍
Jenny, how many times do I have to answer this?

313
00:14:25,010 --> 00:14:25,970
你说什么
Excuse me?

314
00:14:26,030 --> 00:14:27,820
你每天都为新的问题而不信任我
Every day it's a new time you don't trust me.

315
00:14:27,820 --> 00:14:30,400
不  我一直都没法信任你
No, everyday it's the same "I don't trust you."

316
00:14:31,520 --> 00:14:32,490
你亲了她
You kissed her.

317
00:14:33,970 --> 00:14:34,980
告诉我这不是真的
Tell me that's not true.

318
00:14:34,980 --> 00:14:37,500
我没亲她  是她亲了我
I- I didn't kiss her. She kissed me.

319
00:14:37,500 --> 00:14:39,590
-这有区别吗  -当然有
- Like that makes a difference. - It does, all right?

320
00:14:39,590 --> 00:14:41,330
她亲了我  但我并没有回应
It happened, but I didn't follow up on it.

321
00:14:41,330 --> 00:14:42,510
而你忽略的事实是
And what you're leaving out

322
00:14:42,510 --> 00:14:43,850
即使发生了这一切
is that even after all that happened,

323
00:14:43,850 --> 00:14:45,410
你让我做出选择  我选择了你
you asked me to choose, and I chose you.

324
00:14:45,440 --> 00:14:47,980
我问你你们之间有没有什么
I asked you if anything ever happened between the two of you,

325
00:14:47,980 --> 00:14:48,730
你骗了我
and you lied.

326
00:14:48,730 --> 00:14:49,310
你问这话时
When you asked me that,

327
00:14:49,310 --> 00:14:51,300
你指的不是接吻  这你心里清楚
You weren't asking about a kiss, and you know it.

328
00:14:51,300 --> 00:14:52,080
我没有骗你
I didn't lie,

329
00:14:52,080 --> 00:14:54,230
我只是回答了你真正想知道的事
I just answered the question that you really asked.

330
00:14:54,230 --> 00:14:56,210
你真是个好律师
Oh, you are such a goddamn lawyer.

331
00:14:57,440 --> 00:14:59,180
等一下  你不是
Oh, wait, that's right-- you're not.

332
00:14:59,620 --> 00:15:01,330
如果亲别人是天大的罪恶
All right, if kissing someone else is so awful,

333
00:15:01,330 --> 00:15:02,240
那你呢
then what about you?

334
00:15:02,280 --> 00:15:04,440
我记得你还跟特雷弗在一起时就亲了我
I seem to remember you kissing me when you were still with Trevor.

335
00:15:04,440 --> 00:15:06,200
我亲你是因为
When I kissed you, it was because

336
00:15:06,200 --> 00:15:08,080
我想跟你在一起
you were the person that I wanted to be with.

337
00:15:09,090 --> 00:15:10,940
很显然  你对瑞秋也是同样的感觉
Obviously, that's how you feel about Rachel.

338
00:15:10,940 --> 00:15:12,080
我那时没有那种感觉
That wasn't true!

339
00:15:13,820 --> 00:15:14,620
那时没有
Wasn't?

340
00:15:18,280 --> 00:15:19,650
我祝福你们
Well, I hope...

341
00:15:20,920 --> 00:15:22,750
幸福快乐
that you two are really happy together.

342
00:15:23,560 --> 00:15:24,700
对不起
I'm sorry.

343
00:15:25,260 --> 00:15:27,700
你都没问我是怎么知道的
You know, you didn't ask me how I knew.

344
00:15:28,930 --> 00:15:29,980
特雷弗告诉我的
Trevor told me.

345
00:15:30,340 --> 00:15:31,830
-什么  -两天前
- What? - Two days ago.

346
00:15:32,490 --> 00:15:33,580
然后他还说
Right before he told me

347
00:15:33,580 --> 00:15:35,140
他要告诉杰西卡·皮尔逊
that he was gonna tell Jessica Pearson

348
00:15:35,640 --> 00:15:36,690
你是个冒牌货
that you're a fraud.

349
00:16:30,050 --> 00:16:32,630
某人的前途一片大好啊
Well, if it isn't the anointed one.

350
00:16:33,780 --> 00:16:34,770
你去哪儿了
Where the hell you been?

351
00:16:35,930 --> 00:16:37,430
我感觉不太舒服
Well, I'm not feeling very well.

352
00:16:37,440 --> 00:16:38,410
我才不在乎
I don't really care.

353
00:16:39,130 --> 00:16:42,090
我也不在乎杰西卡觉得你多特别
And I also don't care how special Jessica thinks you are.

354
00:16:42,180 --> 00:16:44,540
因为你还得听命于我
Because you still answer to me.

355
00:16:45,320 --> 00:16:47,270
你仍要完成我交给你的每项工作
And you're gonna do every piece of work that I sign to you

356
00:16:47,280 --> 00:16:48,140
直到你高升
until you don't.

357
00:16:48,180 --> 00:16:50,770
我得先见见哈维
Yeah, um, I just have to see Harvey first.

358
00:16:50,780 --> 00:16:52,140
不必了  哈维也帮不了你
Oh, no, no, no. Harvey can't help you.

359
00:16:52,200 --> 00:16:53,800
给我一份斯温顿并购案中
Now I want the detailed listing

360
00:16:53,810 --> 00:16:56,020
所有要裁员职位的详单
of every redundant position in the Swinton Merger.

361
00:16:56,030 --> 00:16:57,840
迅速火速飞速拿给我  懂吗
And I want it yesterday, capisce?

362
00:16:59,140 --> 00:17:01,000
吃点薄荷  你嘴太臭了
And get a mint, because your breath is disgusting.

363
00:17:07,480 --> 00:17:09,190
你借酒劲打给他了
You drunk dial him?

364
00:17:09,190 --> 00:17:11,840
那不叫借酒劲  我就是打给他了
I didn't drunk dial him. I called him.

365
00:17:11,850 --> 00:17:13,220
我不过走了两分钟
Yeah, I left the room for two minutes,

366
00:17:13,220 --> 00:17:14,720
你藉着一杯威士忌给他打电话
and you called him after a glass of whiskey.

367
00:17:14,720 --> 00:17:16,880
-你说这叫什么  -犯傻
- What would you call it? - Stupid.

368
00:17:17,620 --> 00:17:18,930
你跟他说什么了
So what did you say on the message?

369
00:17:18,930 --> 00:17:22,800
我告诉他我忘不了那一吻
I said that I couldn't stop thinking about our kiss.

370
00:17:24,840 --> 00:17:26,290
-你吻了他  -对
- You kissed him? - Yes.

371
00:17:26,290 --> 00:17:28,650
-吻在哪了  -嘴上
- Where? - On the mouth.

372
00:17:29,200 --> 00:17:31,610
-在什么地方吻的  -图书馆
- Where did it happen? - In the library.

373
00:17:31,610 --> 00:17:33,180
皮尔逊·哈德曼图书馆
The pearson hardman library?

374
00:17:33,180 --> 00:17:34,310
不  国会图书馆
No, the library of congress.

375
00:17:34,310 --> 00:17:35,180
约翰·博纳在那吗
Was John Boehner there?

376
00:17:34,310 --> 00:17:36,240
约翰·博纳：美国众议院议长

377
00:17:35,180 --> 00:17:36,240
你是要帮我
Are you gonna help me?

378
00:17:36,240 --> 00:17:37,400
还是拿我消遣
Or are you gonna amuse yourself?

379
00:17:37,400 --> 00:17:38,600
我可以同时进行
I can multitask.

380
00:17:40,430 --> 00:17:41,590
那有什么问题呢
So what's the problem?

381
00:17:41,590 --> 00:17:45,410
问题是那条留言已经三天了
The problem is I left him that message three nights ago,

382
00:17:45,500 --> 00:17:47,240
他至今没有给我任何回复
and he hasn't said anything.

383
00:17:47,780 --> 00:17:49,130
我不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what to do.

384
00:17:49,380 --> 00:17:51,850
一般来说  一个人收到这样的留言
Well, when a person gets a message like that,

385
00:17:51,850 --> 00:17:54,390
又假装没收到  有两种可能
and they act like they didn't, it's one of two things.

386
00:17:54,390 --> 00:17:55,890
要么他收到留言了
Either they got the message,

387
00:17:55,890 --> 00:17:56,710
但对你没感觉
and they don't feel the same way,

388
00:17:56,710 --> 00:17:58,460
要么他压根没收到留言
or they didn't get the message.

389
00:17:59,840 --> 00:18:02,250
留言怎么可能收不到呢
And who doesn't get their messages?

390
00:18:04,840 --> 00:18:06,370
他已经做出选择了
He made his choice.

391
00:18:06,370 --> 00:18:08,840
-天呐  -怎么了
- Whoa. - What?

392
00:18:08,840 --> 00:18:10,160
我得走了
I got to go.

393
00:18:10,530 --> 00:18:12,810
-好吧  -等一下
- Okay. - Wait a second.

394
00:18:13,140 --> 00:18:14,190
感觉如何
How was it?

395
00:18:14,190 --> 00:18:15,430
那个吻吗
The kiss?

396
00:18:16,780 --> 00:18:19,200
好到我会借酒劲给他打电话
Good enough to make me drunk dial him.

397
00:18:25,660 --> 00:18:27,210
你想要谁呢
Well, what are we talking about?

398
00:18:27,370 --> 00:18:30,560
林书豪  我能搞定
Jeremy Lin? Yeah, I can make that happen.

399
00:18:34,360 --> 00:18:35,190
你知道了
You knew.

400
00:18:35,190 --> 00:18:36,460
我先挂了
I got to go.

401
00:18:37,940 --> 00:18:39,770
-什么时候  -昨晚
- When? - Last night.

402
00:18:41,330 --> 00:18:42,490
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?

403
00:18:42,490 --> 00:18:43,970
没办法
We've got no choice.

404
00:18:45,640 --> 00:18:48,600
-我们得私奔  出国  -什么
- We have to leave the country. - What?

405
00:18:48,600 --> 00:18:50,590
我能搞到两张去布宜诺斯艾利斯的机票
I can get us two tickets to Buenos Aires

406
00:18:50,590 --> 00:18:52,860
直升机十分钟内就能在停机坪等着我们
and have the chopper on the helipad in ten minutes.

407
00:18:52,860 --> 00:18:54,680
等下  她知道了  你知道她知道了
Wait. She knows? And you know she knows?

408
00:18:54,680 --> 00:18:56,270
你还拿我的人生开玩笑  
And you're joking about my life?

409
00:18:56,270 --> 00:18:56,930
有没有搞错
What the hell is wrong with you?

410
00:18:56,930 --> 00:18:57,690
你生我气了吗
Are you mad at me?

411
00:18:57,690 --> 00:18:58,820
不  我杀你的心都有
No, I want to kill you!

412
00:18:58,820 --> 00:19:00,980
很好  如果你生气了  说明你没惊慌
Good, because if you're mad, that means you're not panicking.

413
00:19:00,980 --> 00:19:02,750
给我冷静下来
Now calm the hell down.

414
00:19:08,590 --> 00:19:10,470
好了  她说了什么
Okay, what did she say?

415
00:19:11,050 --> 00:19:12,530
她让我开除你  
She told me to fire you.

416
00:19:12,530 --> 00:19:14,010
这让我怎么冷静
That's not calming me down.

417
00:19:14,010 --> 00:19:16,160
我不是教过你有人拿枪指着你头
Haven't I taught you that there's more than one response

418
00:19:16,160 --> 00:19:17,920
有很多种应对方式
when someone has a gun to your head?

419
00:19:17,920 --> 00:19:19,910
现在  这儿连枪都没有
And right now, there's not even a gun in here.

420
00:19:19,910 --> 00:19:21,300
对  不在这儿
No, no. It's not in here.

421
00:19:21,300 --> 00:19:22,470
她在大厅里漫步呢
It's out there roaming the halls.

422
00:19:22,470 --> 00:19:24,050
一看到我  立马开火
And when it sees me, it's gonna start shooting.

423
00:19:24,050 --> 00:19:25,660
你不是该去让那个原告尝尝
Weren't you supposed to give that plaintiff

424
00:19:25,660 --> 00:19:28,010
-哈维·斯佩克特式的厉害吗  -是
- the Harvey Specter treatment? - Yes.

425
00:19:28,020 --> 00:19:29,780
-你搞定了吗  -正在进行中
- Did you wrap it up? - I'm working on it.

426
00:19:29,780 --> 00:19:32,150
就是说你没给她哈维·斯佩克特式的厉害
That means you didn't give her  the harvey specter treatment.

427
00:19:32,150 --> 00:19:33,650
所以你还是去做好你的工作
So why don't you go do your job

428
00:19:33,650 --> 00:19:35,450
相信我也会做好我的
and have some goddamn faith that I'll do mine?

429
00:19:35,450 --> 00:19:36,570
唐娜  现在不方便
Donna, not now.

430
00:19:36,570 --> 00:19:38,390
-这个消息你一定想知道  -怎么了
- Oh, you're gonna want to hear this. - What?

431
00:19:38,660 --> 00:19:40,580
艾丽西娅·哈德曼昨晚去世了
Alicia Hardman died last night.

432
00:19:40,840 --> 00:19:42,610
哈德曼  是我们律所的创办人吗
Hard-- as in Pearson Hardman?

433
00:19:42,610 --> 00:19:45,150
-是他的妻子  消息公开了吗  -还没有
- Wife. Is it public yet? - No.

434
00:19:45,150 --> 00:19:46,810
你原本想什么时告诉我她知道了  哈维
When were you going to tell me she knew, Harvey?

435
00:19:46,810 --> 00:19:48,210
没想告诉你
I wasn't.

436
00:19:51,950 --> 00:19:52,900
-杰西卡  -路易
- Jessica. - Louis.

437
00:19:52,900 --> 00:19:54,590
-今天过得怎样  -很不错  你呢
- How are you? - Never better. You?

438
00:19:54,590 --> 00:19:55,960
好的不得了
Top of the world.

439
00:19:57,580 --> 00:19:59,080
-有事吗  -没什么
- Did you need me? - No.

440
00:19:59,620 --> 00:20:02,650
但是我这儿有个会让你…开心的消息
But I do have something that... will make you happy.

441
00:20:02,650 --> 00:20:04,000
那尽管说吧
Oh. Fire away.

442
00:20:04,000 --> 00:20:05,660
你也知道  我一直在整理
Well, as you know, I've been compiling a list

443
00:20:05,670 --> 00:20:07,240
斯温顿并购案中需裁员部门的清单
of redundant departments for the Swinton merger.

444
00:20:07,240 --> 00:20:08,770
你也该考虑整理斯温顿并购案中
You should also think about compiling a list

445
00:20:08,770 --> 00:20:11,030
需裁员部门的清单了
of redundant departments for the Swinton merger.

446
00:20:12,130 --> 00:20:13,350
你真是幽默
That is awesome.

447
00:20:13,350 --> 00:20:14,820
总之  你知道这个会高兴的
Anyway, I thought you'd be happy to know

448
00:20:14,820 --> 00:20:17,220
我把这个活儿交给迈克·罗斯了
that I, uh, assigned it to Mike Ross.

449
00:20:18,260 --> 00:20:20,060
真有你的  什么时候的事
Excellent. When?

450
00:20:20,060 --> 00:20:21,200
就在刚才
Just now.

451
00:20:21,260 --> 00:20:22,160
哈维说起晚餐的事
Harvey mentioned your dinner,

452
00:20:22,160 --> 00:20:24,500
我知道那表示你十分欣赏…
and I knew that was an indicator of you being very fond--

453
00:20:24,510 --> 00:20:26,370
路易  这就是我欣赏你的原因之一
Louis, it's one of the things I love about you.

454
00:20:26,370 --> 00:20:27,800
-咱俩总是心有灵犀  -没错
- You get me. - I do.

455
00:20:27,800 --> 00:20:28,940
嗯
Yes.

456
00:20:29,730 --> 00:20:32,790
我有东西忘拿了  你先走吧
Oh, I forgot something. You go ahead, all right?

457
00:20:32,790 --> 00:20:35,480
另外  路易  谢谢你
And Louis, thank you.

458
00:20:35,720 --> 00:20:36,880
小事一桩
Sure.

459
00:20:43,650 --> 00:20:45,180
你到底想怎么样
What the hell is wrong with you?

460
00:20:45,240 --> 00:20:46,400
这儿不方便
Not here.

461
00:20:49,940 --> 00:20:51,090
走开
No.

462
00:20:52,170 --> 00:20:53,940
你以为我不知道你在打什么算盘吗
You think I don't know what you're doing?

463
00:20:53,940 --> 00:20:55,110
我知道你看穿我的小把戏了
I know you know what I did.

464
00:20:55,110 --> 00:20:57,120
你诱导路易把工作交给罗斯
You baited Louis into working with Ross,

465
00:20:57,120 --> 00:20:58,650
如果罗斯突然被辞退
So if he leaves abruptly,

466
00:20:58,650 --> 00:20:59,890
路易会猜疑的
Louis will start asking questions.

467
00:20:59,890 --> 00:21:02,370
我说我知道被你看穿了  你还要再炫耀一下
I said I knew you knew. Now you're just showing off.

468
00:21:02,370 --> 00:21:03,610
你觉得我会放你一马吗
You think I'm gonna let you get away with it?

469
00:21:03,620 --> 00:21:05,500
我觉得我们得分清轻重缓急
I think we've got bigger fish to fry.

470
00:21:10,580 --> 00:21:11,800
艾丽西娅·哈德曼去世了
Alicia Hardman's dead,

471
00:21:11,800 --> 00:21:14,070
这意味着丹尼尔·哈德曼要回来了
which means Daniel Hardman's coming back.

472
00:21:15,170 --> 00:21:16,070
那可不一定
You don't know that.

473
00:21:16,070 --> 00:21:18,160
不  我确定  你心里也清楚
Yes, I do. And so do you.

474
00:21:18,160 --> 00:21:20,220
你只是想利用这个
No, you're just using this situation

475
00:21:20,220 --> 00:21:22,350
让我放迈克·罗斯一马
to get Mike Ross out of the crosshairs.

476
00:21:22,350 --> 00:21:23,330
要不要我提醒你
Need I remind you

477
00:21:23,330 --> 00:21:24,780
我们当初能够
that the only reason we were able to

478
00:21:24,780 --> 00:21:26,480
踢走律所另一个合伙人
get rid of the other half of Pearson Hardman

479
00:21:26,480 --> 00:21:30,170
全靠威胁丹尼尔要把外遇的事告诉他老婆
in the first place was by threatening to tell her about his affair?

480
00:21:30,170 --> 00:21:31,900
那只是手段  不是目的
That was the means, not the end.

481
00:21:31,900 --> 00:21:33,370
你也知道  我们的初衷是好的
We had a good reason, and you know that.

482
00:21:33,370 --> 00:21:34,390
我想说的不是这个
That's not my point.

483
00:21:34,390 --> 00:21:36,790
艾丽西娅死了  我们的筹码没了
Alicia's dead. Our leverage is gone.

484
00:21:38,510 --> 00:21:39,870
那是五年前的事情了
That was five years ago.

485
00:21:39,990 --> 00:21:41,280
五年时间里能发生很多事
A lot can happen in five years.

486
00:21:41,280 --> 00:21:43,780
而丹尼尔·哈德曼在过去的五年里
And what Daniel Hardman's been doing for the last five years

487
00:21:43,780 --> 00:21:45,970
就一直梦想着他回来的那一天
is dreaming of the day he comes back

488
00:21:45,970 --> 00:21:48,440
然后把咱俩都除掉
and screws us both out of our jobs.

489
00:21:50,540 --> 00:21:51,890
有个办法能试探出他的心思
There's an easy way to find out.

490
00:21:51,890 --> 00:21:53,020
那就着手办吧
Then let's do it.

491
00:21:53,020 --> 00:21:56,220
因为那个混球要回来了
'Cause I can tell you this, that asshole's coming back.

492
00:21:56,220 --> 00:21:58,800
而且他可不是冲着二把手的位置回来的
And he isn't coming because he wants to be number two.

493
00:22:06,140 --> 00:22:07,900
我得说  他看上去气色不错
I got to say, he looks good.

494
00:22:08,300 --> 00:22:10,470
为恶者终得颜
Being a prick keeps you handsome.

495
00:22:10,610 --> 00:22:12,330
你是在间接夸我帅吗
Are you saying that I'm handsome?

496
00:22:12,330 --> 00:22:14,290
你会认为我的话是夸奖你
The fact that you think that comment was directed at you

497
00:22:14,290 --> 00:22:16,990
说明你又自我为中心又虚荣
makes you self-centered and vain at the same time.

498
00:22:16,990 --> 00:22:18,750
可这也不意味着你没在夸我
Doesn't mean it wasn't directed at me.

499
00:22:18,750 --> 00:22:20,000
没错
It was.

500
00:22:20,870 --> 00:22:23,360
这说明我不仅无所不知
Which means I'm also omniscient

501
00:22:23,360 --> 00:22:24,510
而且还英俊潇洒
and handsome.

502
00:22:24,510 --> 00:22:26,280
还有自大呢
You left out arrogant,

503
00:22:26,320 --> 00:22:28,390
你和丹尼尔就是一路货色
you know, you and Daniel are cut from the same cloth.

504
00:22:28,390 --> 00:22:30,060
所以我不待见他
That's why I don't like him.

505
00:22:30,750 --> 00:22:32,640
“一山不容二虎”
"There can be only one."

506
00:22:32,640 --> 00:22:35,230
我们在参加葬礼  你还有心情引用《挑战者》
We're at a funeral, and you're quoting Highlander?

507
00:22:35,230 --> 00:22:36,480
那电影里死了很多人
Yeah, a lot of people die in it.

508
00:22:36,480 --> 00:22:37,900
还蛮应景的
Seems appropriate.

509
00:22:38,860 --> 00:22:41,510
你知道我和他的根本区别是什么吗
You know the one key difference between the two of us?

510
00:22:42,100 --> 00:22:45,640
他是个信口雌黄的恶毒小人为达目的不择手段
He's a lying snake in the grass who'll say or do anything.

511
00:22:55,630 --> 00:22:57,300
罗斯先生  事实上我记不太清
Mr. Ross, the truth is I don't remember

512
00:22:57,300 --> 00:22:59,360
詹姆斯·詹金斯的创意是哪来的
where the James Jenkins pitch came from.

513
00:22:59,360 --> 00:23:00,910
那就可能是迈拉的
Then it could have come from Myra.

514
00:23:00,910 --> 00:23:02,550
有可能  不过无关紧要
Well, it could have, but it doesn't matter.

515
00:23:02,560 --> 00:23:05,520
即使我剽窃了创意  她也是签署了员工合同的
Even if I had stolen it, she signed the employee agreement.

516
00:23:05,520 --> 00:23:07,980
因此德瑞克出版社对她的作品有版权
Which gives Drecker publishing the rights to her work product.

517
00:23:07,980 --> 00:23:08,770
这点我知道
Yes, I know.

518
00:23:08,770 --> 00:23:09,530
那你也该知道
Well, then you also know

519
00:23:09,530 --> 00:23:12,620
我不会将她加入致谢名单  那有损我公司的名声
I'm not going to taint my company's reputation by giving Myra credit.

520
00:23:12,620 --> 00:23:13,900
我没说致谢的事
I'm not asking you to give her credit.

521
00:23:13,900 --> 00:23:15,460
我是要你给她补偿
I'm asking you to give her compensation

522
00:23:15,460 --> 00:23:17,630
以换来一份秘密和解协议
in exchange for a confidential settlement agreement,

523
00:23:17,630 --> 00:23:19,730
这才能维护你公司的声誉
which protects your reputation.

524
00:23:20,820 --> 00:23:22,660
听着像敲诈
That sounds like blackmail.

525
00:23:23,960 --> 00:23:25,150
贝克曼女士
Ms. Beckman.

526
00:23:26,530 --> 00:23:29,400
这起诉讼案是这桩十亿美元并购案的唯一障碍
This lawsuit is the only thing holding up a billion-dollar merger.

527
00:23:29,400 --> 00:23:30,610
每多拖延一天
And every day that it drags on,

528
00:23:30,610 --> 00:23:32,420
贵公司就要蒙受更多损失
it's costing your company more money.

529
00:23:32,420 --> 00:23:34,090
我的建议是
What I'm talking about

530
00:23:34,090 --> 00:23:36,990
给迈拉·哈里森些皮毛
is giving Myra Harrison a crumb of a crumb.

531
00:23:37,210 --> 00:23:38,730
别再纠结听着像什么
So stop worrying about what it sounds like,

532
00:23:38,740 --> 00:23:40,380
去开支票吧
and start writing a check.

533
00:23:42,730 --> 00:23:44,210
要开多少钱的支票
How much is it gonna cost?

534
00:23:45,040 --> 00:23:46,380
终于说到点子上了
That's what I want to hear.

535
00:23:47,870 --> 00:23:49,070
瞧瞧他们的德性
Just look at 'em.

536
00:23:49,560 --> 00:23:52,110
阿谀奉承  真令人作呕
Sycophants. It makes me sick.

537
00:23:52,110 --> 00:23:52,990
我可不会排队
I'm not gonna stand in line

538
00:23:52,990 --> 00:23:55,600
去拍丹尼尔·哈德曼的马屁  你也不许
for the privilege of kissing Daniel Hardman's ass, and neither are you.

539
00:23:55,600 --> 00:23:58,160
-这可是葬礼  -那家伙可是个奴隶主
- It's a funeral. - The man was a slave driver.

540
00:23:58,160 --> 00:23:59,710
他除了蔑视侮辱我
All he ever did was shit on me

541
00:23:59,710 --> 00:24:01,610
就是让我为他加班加点干活儿
and make me work long hours for him.

542
00:24:01,750 --> 00:24:03,070
从来都是恶言相向
I mean, where was the kind word?

543
00:24:03,070 --> 00:24:05,210
美言善举  永远不在他的字典里
You know, the tiny gesture? Yeah, I don't think so.

544
00:24:05,210 --> 00:24:07,000
-说句公道话  那…  -大人说话小孩少插嘴
- To be fair, it's not-- - Zip it, I'm talking.

545
00:24:07,000 --> 00:24:08,840
然后他就卷铺盖走人了  你知道吗
And then he just ups and leaves, you know?

546
00:24:08,840 --> 00:24:11,130
那是为了照顾他垂危的妻子
To take care of his dying wife.

547
00:24:12,210 --> 00:24:14,910
那又如何  反正我不会去排队的
So? I'm not waiting in line, okay?

548
00:24:14,910 --> 00:24:16,650
我不会给这家伙任何沾沾自喜的机会
I'm not gonna give the guy the satisfaction.

549
00:24:16,650 --> 00:24:18,850
我的意思是说  现在他妻子死了
What I meant was now that she's dead,

550
00:24:18,850 --> 00:24:21,030
那他是不是也要回来了
does that mean that he's coming back?

551
00:24:23,320 --> 00:24:25,440
看样子  拍马屁的队伍要拉长了
Actually, this line looks like it's flowing.

552
00:24:25,730 --> 00:24:28,080
你不能…那是什么
And you're not com--no. What is that?

553
00:24:28,400 --> 00:24:30,790
-那是我的癌症丝带  -我当然知道那是什么
- That's my, uh, cancer ribbon. - No, I know what it is.

554
00:24:30,790 --> 00:24:32,390
我是想问你为什么要戴着它
Why are you wearing it?

555
00:24:32,400 --> 00:24:34,350
我想要借此表达对哈德曼夫人的哀悼
Well, I wanted to show my support for Mrs. Hardman.

556
00:24:34,350 --> 00:24:38,420
她就是死于癌症的  我有一个姑妈她也…
It's what she died of, and I-I also had this aunt that, um, she--

557
00:24:46,310 --> 00:24:47,870
三万美元
$30,000.

558
00:24:47,870 --> 00:24:49,800
-这可真是一大笔钱  -是啊
- That is a lot of money. - Yeah, it is.

559
00:24:49,800 --> 00:24:52,500
他们从没为自由撰稿人的创意掏过这么多钱呢
It's as much as they've ever paid for a freelance pitch.

560
00:24:52,670 --> 00:24:54,020
但是那些撰稿人也获得了致谢
But those people also got credit,

561
00:24:54,020 --> 00:24:56,470
这样他们下个创意就能卖到更高的价钱
which helped them sell their next idea for more.

562
00:24:57,580 --> 00:24:58,730
你不是说你担心
I thought you said you were worried

563
00:24:58,740 --> 00:25:00,470
你再也想不出什么好的创意了
you'd never have another good idea.

564
00:25:01,540 --> 00:25:02,840
迈拉  这是…
Myra, this is--

565
00:25:02,840 --> 00:25:04,580
这是你能得到的最好的结果了
This is the best deal you're going to get.

566
00:25:04,580 --> 00:25:06,380
我对此表示怀疑
I'm not exactly sure that's true.

567
00:25:06,840 --> 00:25:09,000
相信我  这是最好的结果
No, trust me, it is.

568
00:25:10,920 --> 00:25:12,600
你说你忙着做并购案
You said you're in the middle of a merger

569
00:25:12,600 --> 00:25:13,970
而我给你添了乱
and that I'm an inconvenience.

570
00:25:13,980 --> 00:25:16,600
我做了调查  这可是个大并购案
I did my research. It's a huge merger.

571
00:25:16,610 --> 00:25:19,620
-我那么说是为了帮你  -你那么说是为了欺负我
- I told you that to help you. - You told me that to bully me.

572
00:25:19,620 --> 00:25:22,040
-你之后才想要帮我的  -我帮到你了
- You only tried to help later. - And I succeeded.

573
00:25:22,040 --> 00:25:25,160
所以你现在手上才会有三万美元的支票
Which is why you have a check for $30,000 in your hands.

574
00:25:26,000 --> 00:25:27,820
你相信那是我的创意吗
Do you believe that was my idea?

575
00:25:28,720 --> 00:25:30,310
我知道你相信  所以你才会答应帮我
I know you do. That's why you agreed to help.

576
00:25:30,310 --> 00:25:32,660
-你想说什么  -我想说的是…
- What's your point? - My point is...

577
00:25:33,390 --> 00:25:36,520
莱斯利曾是我老板  我本以为我俩是朋友
Lesley was my boss, but I thought we were friends.

578
00:25:36,520 --> 00:25:39,810
所以当她要我相信她的时候  我照做了
So when she asked me to trust her, I did.

579
00:25:40,040 --> 00:25:41,710
可她背叛了我
And she betrayed me.

580
00:25:41,710 --> 00:25:44,980
你能体会到那种感觉吗
Can you imagine what that would be like?

581
00:25:56,280 --> 00:25:58,460
不得不说  我有点替他难过
Got to say, up close, I feel bad for him.

582
00:25:58,460 --> 00:26:00,490
别忘了我们为什么而来
Just don't forget why we're here.

583
00:26:02,730 --> 00:26:04,060
丹尼尔
Daniel.

584
00:26:04,490 --> 00:26:06,090
请节哀
I'm sorry for your loss.

585
00:26:06,090 --> 00:26:07,240
谢谢
Thank you.

586
00:26:07,870 --> 00:26:09,050
哈维
Harvey.

587
00:26:09,770 --> 00:26:11,230
节哀顺变
My condolences.

588
00:26:11,420 --> 00:26:13,510
听上去可有点言不由衷呢
Doesn't sound the same, coming from you.

589
00:26:13,510 --> 00:26:15,310
我很同情你妻子的遭遇
You have my sympathy for your wife,

590
00:26:15,310 --> 00:26:17,780
可我不会装作我们已经不计前嫌了
but I don't pretend this is page one of the story.

591
00:26:17,930 --> 00:26:19,760
你一定以为我还记恨你们两个
You must think I hate you both.

592
00:26:19,760 --> 00:26:21,370
那很可能是因为我们上次谈话时
Well, that might have something to do with the fact

593
00:26:21,370 --> 00:26:24,020
你对我们俩出言不逊  恶语相加
that I was listening the last time you spoke to me.

594
00:26:24,870 --> 00:26:26,400
我当时暴跳如雷  是吧
I was pissed, wasn't I?

595
00:26:26,400 --> 00:26:27,730
你把电话扔到我头上
You threw your phone at my head.

596
00:26:27,740 --> 00:26:28,900
不过当时并没砸中
I did miss though.

597
00:26:28,900 --> 00:26:30,770
那是因为你扔得没有力道和准头
That's because you throw like a girl.

598
00:26:30,770 --> 00:26:33,580
你还是那么耿耿于怀  哈维  我理解
You're still angry, Harvey, and I don't blame you.

599
00:26:33,930 --> 00:26:35,780
但是你不知道的是
But what you don't understand

600
00:26:35,780 --> 00:26:39,150
过去的五年改变了我整个人生
is the last five years have changed everything for me.

601
00:26:39,670 --> 00:26:40,930
怎么说
How so?

602
00:26:42,280 --> 00:26:44,080
我和艾丽西娅重修旧好了
I reconnected with Alicia.

603
00:26:44,300 --> 00:26:45,720
我爱她
I cared for her.

604
00:26:46,680 --> 00:26:50,350
我知道我错过的家庭时光再也无法重来
I know you can't get back lost time with your family,

605
00:26:51,160 --> 00:26:52,670
但我能尽力弥补
but you can make up for it.

606
00:26:55,110 --> 00:26:56,320
看看萨拉
Look at Sarah.

607
00:26:56,790 --> 00:26:59,640
我以前根本不了解她  现在不同了
I never really knew her, and now I do.

608
00:26:59,640 --> 00:27:02,030
上次我看见她的时候  她还是个小女孩
Last time I saw her, she was a little girl.

609
00:27:02,120 --> 00:27:04,100
她才刚从高中毕业
She just graduated high school.

610
00:27:04,300 --> 00:27:06,820
今年秋天  就要去哈佛读书了
Going to Harvard, this fall.

611
00:27:07,830 --> 00:27:09,140
事实上
The truth is...

612
00:27:09,380 --> 00:27:10,740
你们当年对我做的那些事
What you did to me

613
00:27:10,750 --> 00:27:13,620
是我这一生中最大的恩惠
was the best thing anyone could have done for me.

614
00:27:13,730 --> 00:27:15,380
那你会回公司吗
That mean you're coming back?

615
00:27:16,670 --> 00:27:18,720
这可是我妻子的葬礼  哈维
It's my wife's funeral, Harvey.

616
00:27:20,220 --> 00:27:23,240
我都还没认真想过这事
I haven't given it any real thought yet.

617
00:27:26,430 --> 00:27:28,310
我已经洗心革面了  杰西卡
I am a changed man, Jessica.

618
00:27:28,370 --> 00:27:30,050
这都多亏了你
And I have you to thank for it.

619
00:27:33,720 --> 00:27:35,720
你真的相信那些鬼话吗
You actually buying that pious bullshit?

620
00:27:35,720 --> 00:27:37,180
完全不信
Not for a second.

621
00:27:37,180 --> 00:27:38,790
他会来报复我们的
He's coming for us.

622
00:27:39,000 --> 00:27:41,510
我能把他挡在大门外
I can stop him before he even gets through the door.

623
00:27:41,510 --> 00:27:43,240
我想像不出你怎么能做到
I don't see how you're gonna be able to do that.

624
00:27:43,240 --> 00:27:44,980
我有附加条件
I'll have extra motivation.

625
00:27:46,190 --> 00:27:48,830
-你要那孩子留下  -是的
- You want the kid to stay. - Yes.

626
00:27:48,940 --> 00:27:51,390
我就说  你们都是一丘之貉
Like I said, cut from the same cloth.

627
00:27:51,790 --> 00:27:53,110
阻止哈德曼
Make it happen.

628
00:27:53,730 --> 00:27:55,270
我就不开除迈克  一言为定
You've got yourself a deal.

629
00:28:05,640 --> 00:28:07,920
我怎么还没收到那件并购案完成的消息
Why haven't I been notified that my merger's closing?

630
00:28:07,920 --> 00:28:10,600
原告要求获得致谢  否则不肯和解
Uh, the plaintiff's refusing to settle without credit.

631
00:28:10,600 --> 00:28:12,040
你不是要击垮她吗
What happened to steamrolling her?

632
00:28:12,040 --> 00:28:15,280
她意识到她打的官司能妨碍公司的并购
She realized that she's in a unique position to hold up the merger.

633
00:28:15,280 --> 00:28:17,110
她是怎么意识到的
How the hell did she realize that?

634
00:28:17,140 --> 00:28:19,120
不  等等  我猜猜
Oh, no, wait. Don't tell me.

635
00:28:19,120 --> 00:28:21,170
你对她一见钟情然后全盘托出了
You fell in love with her, and then you told her.

636
00:28:21,170 --> 00:28:22,980
不  我没爱上她
No, I did not fall in love with her,

637
00:28:22,980 --> 00:28:25,860
但…是啊  我相信她
But...yeah, I believe her.

638
00:28:26,030 --> 00:28:28,120
-你开什么玩笑  -怎么了
- You're kidding me. - What?

639
00:28:28,250 --> 00:28:29,720
我在努力保住你的饭碗
I'm fighting for your job,

640
00:28:29,720 --> 00:28:31,220
而你却要搞砸这个并购案
and you're gonna screw up this merger?

641
00:28:31,220 --> 00:28:33,770
-是这样吗  -什么意思
- Are you? - Am I what?

642
00:28:33,770 --> 00:28:35,320
你真在努力保我吗
Fighting for my job.

643
00:28:36,230 --> 00:28:38,450
如果不是这样  这可是我最后一桩案子了
Because you're not, this is gonna be my last case,

644
00:28:38,450 --> 00:28:40,640
我可不想帮了恶人的忙
And I'm not sure I want to go down fighting for the wrong side.

645
00:28:40,640 --> 00:28:42,760
你怎么会怀疑我不在为你努力
What makes you think I'm not fighting for you?

646
00:28:42,880 --> 00:28:45,200
谁知道呢  你一直以自身利益为重什么的
Mm, I don't know. Your career--my anything.

647
00:28:45,200 --> 00:28:46,960
你小子真有胆啊
Oh, you got a lot of nerve.

648
00:28:47,100 --> 00:28:48,880
你根本不知道我为你付出了多少
You have no idea what I've been doing for you.

649
00:28:48,880 --> 00:28:50,390
也许  但我们都心知肚明
Maybe. But you and I both know

650
00:28:50,390 --> 00:28:52,650
你那天本来是想开除我的  不是吗
you were gonna fire me the other day, don't we?

651
00:28:53,590 --> 00:28:56,030
不用回答了  答案写在你脸上呢
Don't answer that. I can see the look on your face.

652
00:28:56,440 --> 00:28:58,760
其实那天早上开始  我就看出来了
It's the same look I can see in here, from that morning,

653
00:28:58,760 --> 00:28:59,750
再明显不过
clear as a bell.

654
00:28:59,750 --> 00:29:03,420
我的计划和行动不是一回事
What I was going to do and what I did aren't the same thing.

655
00:29:03,420 --> 00:29:04,920
就像我遇见你的第一天
Like the first day I met you,

656
00:29:04,920 --> 00:29:07,510
你正打算贩毒  但你没有
when you were gonna deal drugs and you didn't.

657
00:29:07,510 --> 00:29:10,740
我现在没法把所有的情况都告诉你  好吗
Look, I can't tell you everything that's going on here, all right?

658
00:29:10,750 --> 00:29:12,470
但你得相信我
But you have to trust me.

659
00:29:12,890 --> 00:29:15,410
只要我还在  你就不会被炒
You are not getting fired on my watch.

660
00:29:19,650 --> 00:29:21,410
瑞秋  你有空吗
Hey, Rachel, do you have a minute?

661
00:29:21,410 --> 00:29:22,200
-我需要…  -不  我没空
- I need to-- - No, I don't.

662
00:29:22,200 --> 00:29:23,890
你的意思清楚明了  我懂的
Got your message loud and clear.

663
00:29:23,890 --> 00:29:26,140
-等等  什么  -听着  我不生气
- Wait. What? - Look, I'm not mad.

664
00:29:26,140 --> 00:29:27,620
但我现在有一大堆工作忙不过来
I'm just in the middle of a lot of work right now.

665
00:29:27,620 --> 00:29:29,910
所以如果你是要找个朋友倾诉
So if you're looking for a friend, I--

666
00:29:30,060 --> 00:29:32,470
真抱歉  我没时间
I just really don't have the time. Sorry.

667
00:29:35,840 --> 00:29:37,060
你在说什么啊
What message?

668
00:29:44,450 --> 00:29:46,820
你是真缺爱啊
You must really be needing some love.

669
00:29:46,820 --> 00:29:48,280
为什么这么说
Why do you say that?

670
00:29:48,280 --> 00:29:51,880
Eisenhower：艾森豪威尔  美国第34任总统  任期1953年-1957年

671
00:29:48,280 --> 00:29:51,880
这些饼干放了大半个世纪了
Those cookies are from the Eisenhower administration.

672
00:29:54,120 --> 00:29:55,430
你知道…
You know...

673
00:29:56,270 --> 00:29:57,690
有时候
sometimes--

674
00:29:58,790 --> 00:30:00,810
有时候我真希望能回到过去
sometimes I wish I could go back.

675
00:30:01,030 --> 00:30:02,320
回到什么时候
To when?

676
00:30:02,430 --> 00:30:06,620
回到…那事发生之前
Before...it.

677
00:30:09,440 --> 00:30:10,320
我小时候
When I was little,

678
00:30:10,320 --> 00:30:14,060
每次不开心  都会去找我奶奶
I used to sit with my grandmother whenever I was upset.

679
00:30:14,060 --> 00:30:16,980
母亲会爱你  但是奶奶…
A mother loves you, but a grandmother--

680
00:30:16,980 --> 00:30:18,570
会永远支持你
Always on your side.

681
00:30:18,570 --> 00:30:20,420
你记不记得  有一次…
Do you remember that time that I...

682
00:30:21,080 --> 00:30:22,900
我离家出走  跑去你家
ran away to your place?

683
00:30:22,900 --> 00:30:25,410
你妈不让你熬夜看《考斯比一家》〔美国情景喜剧〕
You were so mad they wouldn't let you stay up

684
00:30:25,410 --> 00:30:27,320
你气得要死
to watch the cosby show.

685
00:30:27,320 --> 00:30:29,090
我知道  那太不讲理了  不是吗
I know. It's so unreasonable, right?

686
00:30:29,090 --> 00:30:30,890
但你那时才六岁
But you were six.

687
00:30:31,570 --> 00:30:33,870
你带我进屋  给我讲了个故事
You took me in, told me that story--

688
00:30:33,880 --> 00:30:35,720
你以前离家出走的事
The time you ran away from your parents.

689
00:30:35,720 --> 00:30:38,000
是啊  我在离家三英里的地方
Yeah, I ended up getting found by some

690
00:30:38,000 --> 00:30:40,670
被几个码头工人发现了
dock workers3 miles from the house.

691
00:30:40,670 --> 00:30:42,610
没错  就是这事儿
Yeah, that's the one.

692
00:30:43,610 --> 00:30:45,950
-这事是我编的  -什么
- Never happened. - What?

693
00:30:45,950 --> 00:30:49,710
我只是想让你思念你父母
I just wanted to make you miss your mom and dad.

694
00:30:49,710 --> 00:30:52,940
我不过是照搬了《糖果屋》〔格林童话〕的情节
I basically told you Hansel and Gretel.

695
00:30:52,950 --> 00:30:55,360
什么  这不可能  结局完全不一样
What? No. It ends so differently.

696
00:30:55,360 --> 00:30:57,300
我自己做了些改编
I added some touches.

697
00:30:57,590 --> 00:31:01,480
我要是说我被码头工人吃了你肯定不信啊
You wouldn't have bought me getting eaten by the dock workers.

698
00:31:01,480 --> 00:31:04,100
你是才六岁  但你可不是个傻子
You were six, you weren't an imbecile.

699
00:31:04,100 --> 00:31:05,810
这简直就是…
There is nothing new un--

700
00:31:07,410 --> 00:31:08,790
故事新编
under the sun.

701
00:31:09,570 --> 00:31:10,750
什么
What?

702
00:31:11,280 --> 00:31:13,000
我瞬间精神起来了
I suddenly feel so much better.

703
00:31:14,110 --> 00:31:16,030
谢谢你
Thank you. Mwah!

704
00:31:19,560 --> 00:31:21,930
你好  我是哈维·斯佩克特
Hi. Harvey Specter.

705
00:31:21,940 --> 00:31:23,250
我是萨拉
I'm sarah.

706
00:31:23,690 --> 00:31:26,600
我看见你在葬礼上和我父亲讲话
Um, I saw you talking to my father at the service.

707
00:31:26,600 --> 00:31:28,090
我们以前是同事
We used to work together.

708
00:31:28,320 --> 00:31:29,770
你认识我母亲吗
Did you know my mom?

709
00:31:29,840 --> 00:31:31,640
很遗憾  并不熟悉
Not as well as I would have liked.

710
00:31:32,900 --> 00:31:35,450
我正准备出去
Um, I was just going out.

711
00:31:35,450 --> 00:31:36,910
我想散散步
I need a walk.

712
00:31:37,390 --> 00:31:39,030
爸爸就在那
Dad's just over there.

713
00:31:39,220 --> 00:31:41,040
他见到你一定很高兴
I'm sure he'll be happy to see you.

714
00:31:41,910 --> 00:31:43,610
节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.

715
00:31:44,050 --> 00:31:45,280
谢谢
Thank you.

716
00:31:56,630 --> 00:31:57,830
哈维
Harvey?

717
00:31:58,620 --> 00:31:59,720
你带了食物
You brought food.

718
00:31:59,720 --> 00:32:01,010
纽约的极品美食
New York's finest.

719
00:32:01,020 --> 00:32:02,840
你不想空手而来
You didn't want to come empty-handed.

720
00:32:02,840 --> 00:32:04,650
我根本不想来
I didn't want to come here at all.

721
00:32:04,930 --> 00:32:07,450
但你想确定我不会回公司
But you want to make sure I don't come back.

722
00:32:07,450 --> 00:32:09,450
当我们发现你的小骗局时
When we found out about your little scam,

723
00:32:09,450 --> 00:32:11,920
我想公诸于世  但杰西卡不同意
I wanted to go public. Jessica said no.

724
00:32:11,920 --> 00:32:14,030
她不想影响律所的声誉
Didn't want to damage the firm's reputation.

725
00:32:14,030 --> 00:32:16,350
她总是这么精明  万无一失
She always was a strategic thinker.

726
00:32:16,350 --> 00:32:18,450
但你已经离开很长时间了
But you've been gone a long time.

727
00:32:18,450 --> 00:32:20,550
如果我们现在把你以前那些事公开
Now when we tell everyone what you were up to,

728
00:32:20,550 --> 00:32:22,700
我们的声誉不会受到损害  你可就惨了
Our reputation will be fine, yours won't.

729
00:32:22,700 --> 00:32:23,990
就像我之前说的
As I said before,

730
00:32:23,990 --> 00:32:26,570
我还没决定好之后要走怎样的路
I haven't decided what the future holds for me.

731
00:32:28,110 --> 00:32:30,860
而你这些微不足道的威胁…
And all your little threat is doing is...

732
00:32:30,870 --> 00:32:32,950
只会让我更想回公司
making me want to come back.

733
00:32:34,410 --> 00:32:36,130
我小时候  有个朋友
When I was growing up, I had a friend

734
00:32:36,130 --> 00:32:39,360
发现他母亲从没爱过他父亲
who found out that his mother never loved his father.

735
00:32:39,440 --> 00:32:42,450
她从头到尾都在欺骗他  最后一走了之
She cheated on him their whole marriage, then left him.

736
00:32:42,450 --> 00:32:44,150
他一直没原谅她
He never forgave her.

737
00:32:44,150 --> 00:32:46,390
如果你回来  这个故事会在你身上重演
If you come back, here's what's gonna happen.

738
00:32:46,390 --> 00:32:49,780
你女儿将发现她的父亲是个怎样的恶人
Your daughter's gonna find out what kind of man her father is.

739
00:32:50,350 --> 00:32:51,580
得知所有内幕
Everything.

740
00:32:51,580 --> 00:32:53,460
你以为我不会伤害你女儿吗
You think I won't do that?

741
00:32:53,740 --> 00:32:55,100
我会的
I will.

742
00:32:57,490 --> 00:32:59,180
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?

743
00:32:59,400 --> 00:33:01,290
保护我自己的孩子
To protect my own.

744
00:33:03,630 --> 00:33:07,360
给大家都行个方便  去其他地方开店吧
Do us all a favor and set up shop somewhere else.

745
00:33:14,180 --> 00:33:16,880
我想我找到两全其美的办法了
Think I figured out a way to get everybody what they want.

746
00:33:16,880 --> 00:33:18,390
那就好
Well, that's good.

747
00:33:20,170 --> 00:33:21,520
她在这儿干什么
What's she doing here?

748
00:33:21,700 --> 00:33:23,600
来获得她想要的东西
Well, she's here to get what she wants.

749
00:33:23,830 --> 00:33:25,080
你到底想要什么
Which is what, exactly?

750
00:33:25,080 --> 00:33:27,690
-致谢  -这就是她要的
- Credit. - That's all Myra's looking for.

751
00:33:27,750 --> 00:33:29,530
你就承认这是她的创意
So just admit that you remember the pitch

752
00:33:29,530 --> 00:33:31,470
也清楚你做了什么
and that you know what you did.

753
00:33:31,470 --> 00:33:33,920
我不想这么做  因为这是一派胡言
I have no intention of doing that because it's not true.

754
00:33:33,920 --> 00:33:37,410
那你一定愿意接受测谎以证实你的话
So you'd be willing to take a lie-detector test to that effect, then?

755
00:33:38,050 --> 00:33:39,910
我不会接受测谎
I most certainly will not.

756
00:33:39,920 --> 00:33:42,480
事实上  莱斯利  迈拉不是唯一
Well, the thing is, Lesley, that Myra's not the only one

757
00:33:42,480 --> 00:33:44,590
和德瑞克出版社签约的人
who signed an agreement with Drecker publishing.

758
00:33:44,590 --> 00:33:45,630
你也是
So did you.

759
00:33:45,630 --> 00:33:46,880
如果你拒绝接受测谎
And that agreement gives them the right

760
00:33:46,890 --> 00:33:49,660
根据这份协议  他们有权开除你
to terminate you if you refuse to submit to a polygraph.

761
00:33:49,660 --> 00:33:52,640
而我是他们的律师  不是你的
And I happen to represent them, not you.

762
00:33:55,970 --> 00:33:57,170
是我做的
I took it.

763
00:33:57,170 --> 00:33:58,380
我顶着重压
I was under the gun.

764
00:33:58,380 --> 00:34:00,170
我有权这么做  我就做了
I was entitled to it, so I took it.

765
00:34:00,170 --> 00:34:02,650
你给了我意见  我相信了你
You offered me advice, and I trusted you.

766
00:34:02,650 --> 00:34:04,540
你威胁到她了  迈拉
She's threatened by you, Myra.

767
00:34:04,790 --> 00:34:06,700
只能说你没选好导师
Not a good choice of mentor.

768
00:34:06,700 --> 00:34:09,670
你获得了你想要的致谢
Now look, you got the credit you wanted...

769
00:34:10,600 --> 00:34:11,970
签和解吧
So sign the deal.

770
00:34:13,850 --> 00:34:15,960
我要获得公开致谢  不是私下的
No, I want public credit. Not credit in here.

771
00:34:16,140 --> 00:34:17,890
我就知道你会这么说
I thought you might say that.

772
00:34:17,890 --> 00:34:21,620
所以我用了一天时间
Which is why I have spent the last 24 hours

773
00:34:21,620 --> 00:34:25,030
浏览了德瑞克出版社的所有书目
scanning the entire Drecker publishing catalog.

774
00:34:25,410 --> 00:34:26,870
罗伯特·费罗
Robert Fallow,

775
00:34:27,330 --> 00:34:28,890
乔纳森·戴肯
Jonathan Daken,

776
00:34:29,920 --> 00:34:33,030
还有我个人的最爱  莱斯特·柯林斯
And, my personal favorite, Lester Collins.

777
00:34:33,510 --> 00:34:35,850
任何一本书都有可能基于你的创意
Any one of them could have been written on the basis of your pitch.

778
00:34:35,850 --> 00:34:37,030
但这并不可能
But they weren't

779
00:34:37,030 --> 00:34:39,310
因为这些书比你的创意早了好几年
because they were written years before it.

780
00:34:39,450 --> 00:34:41,910
你是说我抄袭了他们吗
Are you saying I plagiarized them?

781
00:34:42,130 --> 00:34:45,420
我只是说天下作文一大抄
I'm--I'm saying there's nothing new under the sun.

782
00:34:45,420 --> 00:34:48,130
我建议你签了和解  然后回家洗洗睡
Now I suggest you sign that deal and go home.

783
00:34:48,130 --> 00:34:49,700
不然我们就反诉你
Otherwise we're gonna countersue

784
00:34:49,700 --> 00:34:52,460
从已出版作品中抄袭创意
for plagiarizing your pitch from our previous works.

785
00:34:52,460 --> 00:34:53,460
但这不是事实
But it's not true.

786
00:34:53,460 --> 00:34:54,660
这跟你声称我们偷了
It's no less legitimate than claiming

787
00:34:54,660 --> 00:34:56,790
我们有权偷你的东西是一样合法的诉讼
we stole something you gave us the rights to.

788
00:35:09,850 --> 00:35:11,090
迈拉
Myra.

789
00:35:11,470 --> 00:35:12,880
你想当作家吗
You want to be writer?

790
00:35:13,230 --> 00:35:14,400
那就好好写作
Then write.

791
00:35:15,040 --> 00:35:17,660
但再别来威胁我或我们律所
But don't ever threaten me or my firm again.

792
00:35:25,390 --> 00:35:27,300
-看上去心情很好嘛  -心情是不错
- You look happy. - I am happy.

793
00:35:27,300 --> 00:35:28,370
有话要跟我说吗
Anything I should know?

794
00:35:28,370 --> 00:35:30,490
欢迎加入皮尔逊·哈德曼律所
Welcome to Pearson Hardman.

795
00:35:31,200 --> 00:35:32,610
有话要跟我说吗
Anything I should know?

796
00:35:33,470 --> 00:35:34,590
案子搞定了
Settled the case.

797
00:35:34,590 --> 00:35:36,070
并购文件马上就能准备好
Merger paperwork's on the way.

798
00:35:36,070 --> 00:35:37,280
你收拾了原告
You slammed the plaintiff?

799
00:35:37,280 --> 00:35:39,940
-我把所有人都收拾了  -正合我意
- Oh, I slammed everybody. - What I like to hear.

800
00:35:42,570 --> 00:35:44,830
我经营皮尔逊·哈德曼的时候
When I ran Pearson Hardman...

801
00:35:45,780 --> 00:35:50,550
我风趣幽默  受人敬重
I was charming, witty and adorable.

802
00:35:51,930 --> 00:35:54,580
可同时  我不择手段
I was also unscrupulous...

803
00:35:55,030 --> 00:35:57,150
追名逐利  贪得无厌
Power-hungry and greedy.

804
00:35:57,190 --> 00:35:58,790
我以为我可以为所欲为而不受责罚
I thought I could get away with anything.

805
00:35:58,800 --> 00:36:00,580
而我也曾想尽办法逃脱罪责
And that's exactly what I tried to do.

806
00:36:00,580 --> 00:36:04,020
我危及公司的名声和各位的前途
I risked the firm's reputation and the careers of everyone in it.

807
00:36:06,220 --> 00:36:09,420
这几年的事情改变了我
These last few years have humbled me.

808
00:36:10,210 --> 00:36:11,570
因此我决定回来
And I've decided to come back

809
00:36:11,570 --> 00:36:13,470
告诉世人我们律所规规矩矩做事
and show that we can be a successful law firm

810
00:36:13,470 --> 00:36:15,090
也能获得成功
without breaking the rules.

811
00:36:16,680 --> 00:36:18,350
可惜  我如果要这么做
Unfortunately, the only way that I can do that

812
00:36:18,350 --> 00:36:20,590
就必须承认我的过去
is by coming clean about my past.

813
00:36:21,730 --> 00:36:24,600
因为如果我们忙于遮掩过去的罪行
Because if we are busy hiding what we have done...

814
00:36:26,370 --> 00:36:27,940
这就成了我们的软肋
It leaves us vulnerable

815
00:36:28,330 --> 00:36:30,330
落把柄于他手
to anyone who discovers our secrets.

816
00:36:30,330 --> 00:36:34,820
为了掩盖这些丑事
And we become so consumed with keeping them,

817
00:36:34,820 --> 00:36:38,450
我们会做更多的丑事去弥补
that it is a slippery slope to doing even worse things.

818
00:36:39,750 --> 00:36:41,090
当我还是这家公司的主管时
While I was head of this firm,

819
00:36:41,090 --> 00:36:46,820
我从很多第三方账户拆借过资金
I borrowed funds from various escrow accounts.

820
00:36:46,830 --> 00:36:48,230
客户从来都没发现过
The clients never found out about it.

821
00:36:48,230 --> 00:36:50,660
我都如数补上了  但毫无疑问
I paid back every cent but make no mistake.

822
00:36:50,800 --> 00:36:53,970
这显然足以构成挪用公款的罪名
I could have been convicted of theft, plain and simple.

823
00:36:54,180 --> 00:36:58,140
我想让这里的各位都了解我曾经的为人
I want everyone here to know the kind of man I was.

824
00:36:59,340 --> 00:37:01,700
并见证我现在的为人
And the kind of man I am.

825
00:37:02,940 --> 00:37:04,190
谢谢
Thank you.

826
00:37:09,710 --> 00:37:11,100
快回家
Go home now.

827
00:37:11,510 --> 00:37:12,910
别回公司
Don't come back.

828
00:37:17,640 --> 00:37:19,440
我们得谈一谈
You and I are gonna have a talk.

829
00:37:22,320 --> 00:37:25,320
我明白你为何让哈维阻止我回来
I understand why you had Harvey do what he did.

830
00:37:25,680 --> 00:37:27,510
但我已经不是从前那个我了
But I'm not the same person.

831
00:37:30,160 --> 00:37:31,760
我向女儿坦白了一切
I told my daughter everything.

832
00:37:32,560 --> 00:37:35,150
希望我们能和平共事
I hope we can figure out a way to work together.

833
00:37:44,870 --> 00:37:46,600
没想到你还有胆子来
Didn't think you'd have the guts to show up.

834
00:37:46,600 --> 00:37:48,160
-你想怎样  -我想怎样
- What do you want? - What do I want?

835
00:37:48,160 --> 00:37:50,370
我想知道我最好的朋友怎么能做出这种事
I want to know how my best friend could do this to me.

836
00:37:50,380 --> 00:37:52,330
哪种事
Do what to you?

837
00:37:52,330 --> 00:37:54,320
背叛你  在你背后玩阴的吗
Betray you? Go behind your back?

838
00:37:54,330 --> 00:37:57,770
我站在那儿和你称兄道弟
I stood there joking with you-- my friend, my buddy.

839
00:37:57,800 --> 00:37:59,640
而我女朋友就在你的浴室里
And my girlfriend was in your shower,

840
00:37:59,640 --> 00:38:01,030
离我不到一米
three feet away.

841
00:38:01,550 --> 00:38:03,590
你们俩是不是把我当笑话看
Hope you two had a good laugh about that.

842
00:38:03,860 --> 00:38:04,950
我正准备告诉你的  特雷弗
I was gonna tell you, Trevor.

843
00:38:04,950 --> 00:38:06,380
但你没有
But you didn't.

844
00:38:07,630 --> 00:38:09,820
我本不想和珍妮说瑞秋的事
And I wasn't gonna tell Jenny about Rachel,

845
00:38:09,920 --> 00:38:11,160
但我说了
But I did.

846
00:38:11,160 --> 00:38:12,960
你是怎么知道我和瑞秋的事的
How'd you even know about me and Rachel?

847
00:38:12,960 --> 00:38:14,280
你不是够聪明吗
You know what? You're so smart,

848
00:38:14,290 --> 00:38:15,110
自己想吧
you figure it out.

849
00:38:15,110 --> 00:38:17,210
好吧  你成功了  珍妮和我分手了
Okay, yeah, you got me. Jenny broke up with me.

850
00:38:17,210 --> 00:38:20,560
但你竟然去找我的老板  试图毁掉我的人生
But you went to my boss. You tried to ruin my life.

851
00:38:22,310 --> 00:38:23,570
我们扯平了
We're even.

852
00:38:24,700 --> 00:38:28,000
990-36-7249
990-36-7249.

853
00:38:29,840 --> 00:38:31,810
你的社保号  对吧
It's your social security number, right?

854
00:38:31,830 --> 00:38:34,770
六年级的时候我在你爸桌上看到的
I saw it on your dad's desk when we were in the sixth grade.

855
00:38:36,250 --> 00:38:37,940
你以为你能搞得我生活一团糟
See, you think that you can mess with my life,

856
00:38:37,940 --> 00:38:40,110
我对你就没辙了吗  大错特错
And I can't mess with yours, but I can.

857
00:38:41,070 --> 00:38:42,560
可到目前为止我都没这么做
The only thing that's stopped me until now

858
00:38:42,560 --> 00:38:44,350
全都是因为我在乎你
is the fact that I actually cared about you.

859
00:38:44,350 --> 00:38:45,260
但今天之后
But now, after this,

860
00:38:45,260 --> 00:38:48,010
我再也不会管你死活了
I really don't give a sh-- about you anymore.

861
00:38:49,650 --> 00:38:50,790
你也许脑子没我好使
You might not have my memory,

862
00:38:50,790 --> 00:38:52,440
但这话最好给我记清楚了
ut you better remember that.

863
00:38:59,100 --> 00:39:00,780
你到底对丹尼尔说了什么
What the hell did you say to Daniel?

864
00:39:00,780 --> 00:39:01,960
还重要吗
Does it matter?

865
00:39:01,970 --> 00:39:03,150
重要的是我不想再在
What matters is I don't ever want

866
00:39:03,150 --> 00:39:04,830
这间办公室里看见迈克·罗斯
to see Mike Ross in this office again.

867
00:39:04,840 --> 00:39:07,490
-恕我难以从命  -你说什么
- Well, that's not gonna happen. - Excuse me?

868
00:39:08,380 --> 00:39:10,150
我不会开除他的
I'm not firing him.

869
00:39:10,370 --> 00:39:11,920
那我开
Then I'll fire him.

870
00:39:12,650 --> 00:39:13,630
你不会的
No, you won't.

871
00:39:13,630 --> 00:39:15,380
你说如果我一直知道迈克的事
You said you gave me the benefit of the doubt

872
00:39:15,380 --> 00:39:16,740
你就会把我开除
that I didn't know about Mike,

873
00:39:16,740 --> 00:39:18,800
但你打算当我不知道
otherwise you'd fire me too.

874
00:39:23,050 --> 00:39:24,380
我知道迈克的事
Well, I knew.

875
00:39:25,320 --> 00:39:26,790
你是想逼我开除你吗
You trying to force my hand?

876
00:39:26,790 --> 00:39:28,100
我是想让你手下留情
I'm trying to stay your hand.

877
00:39:28,100 --> 00:39:29,490
他走  我也走
He goes, I go.

878
00:39:31,860 --> 00:39:34,340
收拾好东西  你被解雇了
Pack up your things. You're done.

879
00:39:34,620 --> 00:39:36,380
这样做你会有个麻烦
There's only one problem with that.

880
00:39:36,880 --> 00:39:38,550
丹尼尔可盯着你的位子
Daniel's coming for your job.

881
00:39:38,550 --> 00:39:39,890
如果我现在走了
If I leave now,

882
00:39:39,890 --> 00:39:42,220
他会嗅到异常  再查出问题
He'll smell something's wrong, he'll figure out what it is.

883
00:39:42,220 --> 00:39:43,490
你或是疏忽大意
You'll look reckless

884
00:39:43,490 --> 00:39:45,750
让我雇了一个没有学历的孩子
for letting me hire a kid without a degree,

885
00:39:45,750 --> 00:39:47,490
或是愚蠢之极  竟然对此毫不知情
or foolish for not knowing I did it.

886
00:39:47,490 --> 00:39:49,750
不管怎么说都让我看上去很不称职
Neither quality being an asset in a managing partner.

887
00:39:49,750 --> 00:39:51,020
这将成为你的软肋
Which makes you vulnerable.

888
00:39:51,020 --> 00:39:54,090
但全都因为你当初雇了这个死孩子
All because you hired the goddamn kid in the first place.

889
00:39:54,090 --> 00:39:57,110
就算如此  他也会利用这个对付你
Be that as it may, he'll use it against you.

890
00:39:57,830 --> 00:39:59,240
你需要我
You need me.

891
00:39:59,440 --> 00:40:01,470
而我誓死要和迈克在一起
And I'm not staying without Mike.

892
00:40:30,980 --> 00:40:33,270
迈克  我是瑞秋
Hey, Mike, it's Rachel.

893
00:40:33,270 --> 00:40:34,650
我知道我不该这么做
I know I shouldn't be doing this,

894
00:40:34,650 --> 00:40:36,580
我知道你在跟珍妮约会
And I-I know you're seeing jenny,

895
00:40:36,590 --> 00:40:39,580
但我忘不了那一吻
But I can't stop thinking about the kiss.

896
00:40:39,580 --> 00:40:42,370
我做不到还像从前一样了
And...I can't go back.

897
00:40:45,700 --> 00:40:47,430
-喂  -给我滚过来
- Hello-- - Get your ass in here.

898
00:40:48,780 --> 00:40:50,030
这就来
On my way.

899
00:41:18,520 --> 00:41:19,720
我以为
I thought--

900
00:41:22,420 --> 00:41:23,970
哈维说他要见我
Harvey said he wanted to see me.

901
00:41:23,970 --> 00:41:25,700
他只让你滚过来
He said, "Get your ass in here."

902
00:41:26,580 --> 00:41:27,650
我被开除了吗
Am I fired?

903
00:41:27,650 --> 00:41:29,000
本该如此
You should be.

904
00:41:31,570 --> 00:41:33,000
意思是现在不开除我了
That imply that I'm not?

905
00:41:33,000 --> 00:41:34,340
也不尽然
Not necessarily.

906
00:41:34,510 --> 00:41:38,340
但要想让我接受这个情况
However, if I'm going to accept this situation...

907
00:41:39,100 --> 00:41:41,530
你就得对我坦白一切
Then I want to know everything there is to know.

908
00:41:42,340 --> 00:41:43,540
好吧
Okay.

909
00:41:44,360 --> 00:41:45,600
从何说起呢
Where do I start?

910
00:41:45,830 --> 00:41:46,570
干脆就从
Why don't you tell me

911
00:41:46,570 --> 00:41:50,330
你当初是如何让哈维收了你开始
how the hell you got Harvey to hire you in the first place.

912
00:41:50,600 --> 00:41:52,740
启动那台电脑  我演示给你看
Fire up that laptop and I'll show you.

913
00:41:53,960 --> 00:41:56,480
随便问我任何关于法律的问题
Ask me anything there is to know about the law.

914
00:41:57,060 --> 00:41:58,610
原来是这样
That's how you did it?

915
00:41:59,940 --> 00:42:01,340
你打败他了吗
You beat him?

916
00:42:04,470 --> 00:42:07,530
我可不是哈维
Well, I'm not Harvey.

917
00:42:12,350 --> 00:42:13,910
我不需要电脑
I don't need a computer.

