1
00:06:40,280 --> 00:06:45,280
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:06:40,280 --> 00:06:45,280
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:06:40,280 --> 00:06:45,280
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:06:40,280 --> 00:06:45,280
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:06:40,280 --> 00:06:45,280
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:06:45,280 --> 00:06:50,280
{\an8}翻译：猫咪赐我速死  CS漫画家小明  潇湘月影

7
00:06:50,280 --> 00:06:55,280
{\an8}翻译：王大可  鱼小姐  小饭  校对：油炸电风扇   潇湘月影

8
00:06:55,280 --> 00:07:00,280
{\an8}时间轴：今    芒果树叶

9
00:07:00,280 --> 00:07:05,280
{\an8}后期：斯人&加森      精校&总监：某羽

10
00:07:06,140 --> 00:07:08,270
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

11
00:07:06,140 --> 00:07:08,270
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第九集

12
00:00:01,040 --> 00:00:02,680
{\pos(189,213)}《诉讼双雄》前情提要

13
00:00:02,430 --> 00:00:05,360
我想让你决定你对我的爱
I want you to decide if you love me 

14
00:00:05,370 --> 00:00:07,500
和对我行为的厌恶哪个更深
more than you hate What I did,

15
00:00:07,500 --> 00:00:08,750
如果你爱我
and if you do,

16
00:00:09,010 --> 00:00:11,020
我希望你回家
then I want you to come home.

17
00:00:11,020 --> 00:00:12,570
如果他们检查这些文件
and the only they'll definitely find 

18
00:00:12,570 --> 00:00:13,740
只会发现
if they get a look at those files, 

19
00:00:13,740 --> 00:00:15,160
你贪污受贿
is that you embezzled money.

20
00:00:15,160 --> 00:00:18,770
听我说  该死的  我们得撤销这个交易
Listen to me, god damn it. We need to undo this deal.

21
00:00:18,790 --> 00:00:21,480
-我们没什么好遮掩的  -不  这是他的策略
- We have nothing to hide. - No, no, this is a ploy.

22
00:00:21,530 --> 00:00:23,290
他是想证明我们拿到了
He's trying to get me on record stating that 

23
00:00:23,290 --> 00:00:25,760
全部文件  如果我一无所获
we have everything, and if I find nothing,

24
00:00:25,760 --> 00:00:28,100
他会以诬告起诉我
he's gonna file malicious prosecution charges.

25
00:00:28,100 --> 00:00:31,320
事实上  肖恩  我现在就要以诬告起诉你
Actually, sean, I'm filing those charges right now.

26
00:00:31,320 --> 00:00:32,720
今早哈维去了法院
Harvey went to court this morning,

27
00:00:32,720 --> 00:00:36,450
同意交出一切关于吉利斯收购的文件
and agreed to hand over every single document on the Gillis takeover,

28
00:00:36,450 --> 00:00:38,650
包括傅滋曼的文件
including Forstman.

29
00:00:38,860 --> 00:00:40,040
该死
Shit!

30
00:00:42,180 --> 00:00:43,160
那我带着手铐被警察带走
Then it's only a matter of time before 

31
00:00:43,170 --> 00:00:44,370
只是时间问题了
I'm marched out of here in handcuffs.

32
00:00:44,370 --> 00:00:45,970
如果他真的跟傅滋曼达成了非法协议
If he did make a dirty deal with Forstman,

33
00:00:45,970 --> 00:00:47,720
证据不会在那些文件里
it wouldn't have been in those documents.

34
00:00:47,720 --> 00:00:48,790
-而会在  -那些
- It would've been in-- - The documents

35
00:00:48,790 --> 00:00:51,310
我们刚刚答应法院愿意上交的文件里
we just told the court we're happy to turn over.

36
00:00:51,310 --> 00:00:52,110
你想做什么
What are you going to do?

37
00:00:52,110 --> 00:00:54,260
我要去查出路易究竟做了什么
I'm gonna find out what the hell Louis did.

38
00:00:57,960 --> 00:00:59,500
我犯了个大错
I made a huge mistake.

39
00:01:06,810 --> 00:01:07,840
发生了什么事
What's going on?

40
00:01:08,440 --> 00:01:10,630
路易  把你刚才跟我说的话
Louis, I want you to tell Harvey exactly 

41
00:01:10,630 --> 00:01:12,230
原封不动告诉哈维  你不说的话我说
what you just told me, or I will.

42
00:01:12,230 --> 00:01:13,090
他不用说了
He doesn't have to.

43
00:01:13,090 --> 00:01:15,030
他跟傅滋曼达成了非法协议
He made a dirty deal with Forstman.

44
00:01:15,350 --> 00:01:16,260
哈维  我可以解释的
Harvey, I can explain.

45
00:01:16,260 --> 00:01:18,160
解释什么  解释你将律所置于危机中
Explain what, that you put the firm in jeopardy

46
00:01:18,160 --> 00:01:19,650
只是因为自己想当英雄吗
all because you had to be the hero?

47
00:01:19,690 --> 00:01:21,070
我那样做不是为了当英雄
I didn't do it to be the hero.

48
00:01:21,070 --> 00:01:23,710
-我都不知道我会那样做  -什么
- I didn't even know I was gonna do it at all. - What?

49
00:01:23,710 --> 00:01:26,450
交易达成了  你看到我们赢了那么高兴
The deal was closed, and you were so happy we won.

50
00:01:27,050 --> 00:01:29,480
之后我又回去了  傅滋曼说如果
Then I went back that night, Forstman said if I didn't

51
00:01:29,480 --> 00:01:31,480
我不将钱转到海外  他就取消交易
funnel the money overseas, the deal was off,

52
00:01:31,480 --> 00:01:32,500
所以我就那样做了
so I did it.

53
00:01:36,050 --> 00:01:37,180
肯定还有别的
There's more.

54
00:01:38,180 --> 00:01:39,530
你怎么知道还有别的
How do you know there's more?

55
00:01:39,530 --> 00:01:41,750
因为他是在和傅滋曼做交易
Because with Forstman there's always more.

56
00:01:45,760 --> 00:01:49,910
他让我从交易中收了一百万美金
He made me take a million dollars out of the deal so

57
00:01:49,910 --> 00:01:51,620
好让我之后不会检举他
I couldn't turn on him later.

58
00:01:52,660 --> 00:01:54,590
-我的天哪  -我没得选
- Jesus Christ. - I had no choice!

59
00:01:54,590 --> 00:01:56,470
去你的没得选
Bullshit, you had no choice!

60
00:01:56,470 --> 00:01:59,040
你可以在任何一个时点上说不
You could've said no at any goddamn point along the way,

61
00:01:59,040 --> 00:02:00,890
但你没有  因为你只在乎你自己
but you didn't, because all you cared about was yourself.

62
00:02:00,890 --> 00:02:02,580
好吧  如果我那么在乎我自己
Okay, if I care about myself so much,

63
00:02:02,580 --> 00:02:04,730
我怎么会在这里跟你说我要去自首呢
how come I'm in here telling you that I'm gonna confess?

64
00:02:04,730 --> 00:02:06,290
你要自首  随你便
You want to confess? Be my guest!

65
00:02:06,290 --> 00:02:08,780
哈维  够了
Harvey, that's enough.

66
00:02:10,390 --> 00:02:13,940
路易  这样做的问题是
Louis...the problem with that 

67
00:02:13,940 --> 00:02:15,660
我们是无辜的
is that we're innocent.

68
00:02:16,060 --> 00:02:18,230
卡荷尔的计划就是广泛撒网
Cahill's plan is to throw mud against the wall

69
00:02:18,230 --> 00:02:19,400
看你哪里有漏洞
and see what sticks.

70
00:02:19,400 --> 00:02:21,660
你如果告诉他了
You tell him about what you did,

71
00:02:21,760 --> 00:02:23,080
突然之间
and all of a sudden,

72
00:02:23,080 --> 00:02:25,520
-所有事都会变成漏洞  -好吧
- everything sticks. - Okay.

73
00:02:27,730 --> 00:02:29,220
但我一定要出一份力
But I have to do something to help.

74
00:02:29,220 --> 00:02:32,030
会有机会的  等到时机成熟的时候
You will, when the time comes.

75
00:02:33,150 --> 00:02:34,880
现在  我需要和哈维谈谈
Right now, I need to talk to Harvey.

76
00:02:46,760 --> 00:02:48,040
我不敢相信你竟然
I can't believe you're taking 

77
00:02:48,040 --> 00:02:49,080
如此平静地接受了这件事
this as well as you are.

78
00:02:49,080 --> 00:02:50,620
我一点也不平静
I'm not taking this well at all.

79
00:02:50,620 --> 00:02:53,160
那你对他那么和善是为什么
Then what the hell are you being so nice to him for?

80
00:02:53,270 --> 00:02:54,360
你没听到吗
Did you hear?

81
00:02:54,680 --> 00:02:55,940
他要去自首
He was going to confess.

82
00:02:55,940 --> 00:02:57,280
我必须安抚他
I had to calm him down.

83
00:02:57,280 --> 00:02:58,890
所以你不是要纵容他吗
So you're not gonna stand by him?

84
00:02:58,890 --> 00:03:00,350
纵容他
Stand by him?

85
00:03:00,790 --> 00:03:02,300
件事一结束
The second this thing is over,

86
00:03:02,300 --> 00:03:05,050
我就解雇他
I'm gonna fire his goddamn ass.

87
00:03:08,850 --> 00:03:10,230
澡洗得怎么样
How was your shower?

88
00:03:10,230 --> 00:03:12,140
感觉不错  瑞秋
It was great. Rachel, 

89
00:03:12,410 --> 00:03:14,210
你不用专门为我收拾  这也是我家
you don't have to clean up for me. I live here.

90
00:03:14,210 --> 00:03:18,510
我知道  只是  我想让一切都完美些
I know, I just...I want everything to be perfect.

91
00:03:18,510 --> 00:03:19,560
已经很完美了
It is.

92
00:03:21,940 --> 00:03:23,690
这是我父母的相册吗
Is this my parents' photo album?

93
00:03:24,040 --> 00:03:27,180
是的  之前在衣帽间角落放着
Oh, yeah, it was in the back of the closet.

94
00:03:27,180 --> 00:03:29,590
是的  我知道  但为什么被拿出来了
Yeah, I know where it was. Why is it out here?

95
00:03:31,200 --> 00:03:34,260
因为我想找找
Because I was looking for 

96
00:03:34,890 --> 00:03:35,990
你的照片
pictures of you.

97
00:03:39,790 --> 00:03:41,410
今天晚餐你有什么打算
What do you want to do for dinner tonight?

98
00:03:41,750 --> 00:03:42,780
我想也许我们可以去
I was thinking maybe we could hit

99
00:03:42,790 --> 00:03:44,250
那家墨西哥小馆子
that little Mexican spot.

100
00:03:44,450 --> 00:03:46,800
不行  你刚回来
No. You just got back here.

101
00:03:46,800 --> 00:03:47,940
我哪里也不想去
I don't want to go anywhere.

102
00:03:47,950 --> 00:03:50,220
我也不想  但我们什么吃的也没有
I don't either, but we don't have anything to eat.

103
00:03:50,920 --> 00:03:52,560
-真的吗  -我肯定
- Don't we? - well, I know for a fact

104
00:03:52,560 --> 00:03:54,610
我们没有豆子芝士墨西哥卷饼
we don't have any bean and cheese burritos.

105
00:03:54,610 --> 00:03:57,170
那为什么冰箱里现在有六个卷饼呢
Mm, then why are there six of them in the fridge right now?

106
00:04:06,380 --> 00:04:07,640
你讨厌吃这个
You hate them.

107
00:04:07,670 --> 00:04:11,070
是的  但你喜欢吃  而且
I do, but you love them, and 

108
00:04:11,070 --> 00:04:12,880
我希望在你回家的时候能有的吃
I wanted you to have them here when you came home.

109
00:04:12,880 --> 00:04:14,380
我今晚要是不回来呢
And what if I didn't come home tonight?

110
00:04:14,380 --> 00:04:18,330
那我明天就得再去买新鲜的了
Then I would have bought fresh ones again tomorrow.

111
00:04:20,190 --> 00:04:21,250
谢谢  瑞秋
Thanks, Rachel.

112
00:04:23,290 --> 00:04:24,700
你能回家来真好
It's good to have you home.

113
00:04:26,470 --> 00:04:27,610
回家的感觉也很好
It's good to be home.

114
00:04:34,560 --> 00:04:35,600
发生了什么事
What happened?

115
00:04:36,730 --> 00:04:38,100
我以为你今晚有约
I thought you had a date.

116
00:04:38,500 --> 00:04:40,550
我推掉了  而且我在问你话呢
I canceled it, and I asked you a question.

117
00:04:40,550 --> 00:04:41,480
我不想说这件事
I don't want to talk about it,

118
00:04:41,480 --> 00:04:42,660
因为我知道你会说什么
because I know what you're going to say.

119
00:04:42,670 --> 00:04:45,030
哈维  我连路易做了什么都不知道
Harvey, I don't even know what exactly Louis did.

120
00:04:45,030 --> 00:04:47,310
他为了和傅滋曼交易违法了
He broke the law to close Forstman.

121
00:04:47,990 --> 00:04:49,760
他违法了还是傅滋曼逼他那么做的
He broke it or Forstman made him break it?

122
00:04:49,760 --> 00:04:51,320
-有什么区别吗  -哈维
- What's the goddamn difference? - Harvey--

123
00:04:51,320 --> 00:04:52,450
你不用说了  唐娜
You don't have to say it, Donna,

124
00:04:52,450 --> 00:04:53,990
我都听过上千次了
I've heard it a thousand times.

125
00:04:54,000 --> 00:04:55,610
路易这么做只是为了得到我的认同
Louis only did this to get my approval.

126
00:04:55,610 --> 00:04:56,860
但你知道吗  
And you know what, 

127
00:04:56,860 --> 00:04:58,880
我不在乎我答应过当他的伴郎
I don't give a shit that I agreed to be his best man.

128
00:04:58,880 --> 00:05:01,120
他把你  我  还有我们每个人置于危险之中
He put you, me, and every one of us in jeopardy

129
00:05:01,120 --> 00:05:02,380
就为了得到自己想要的
to get what he wanted.

130
00:05:02,390 --> 00:05:03,540
我确实本想说那些
Well, I was gonna say that,

131
00:05:03,540 --> 00:05:04,820
但我现在要说的是
but instead I'll say this:

132
00:05:04,820 --> 00:05:06,750
你也把我们都置于危险之中了
You put us all in jeopardy too.

133
00:05:06,750 --> 00:05:08,230
我什么时候那么做了
When the hell did I do that?

134
00:05:08,230 --> 00:05:10,440
你雇佣迈克的那天  而且顺便一提
The day you hired Mike, and by the way,

135
00:05:10,440 --> 00:05:12,400
我猜如果不是路易做了那些事
I'm guessing he wouldn't even be back here

136
00:05:12,400 --> 00:05:14,050
他根本回不来
if Louis hadn't done what he did.

137
00:05:14,360 --> 00:05:16,810
那就去跟杰西卡说  因为这事结束以后
Then tell that to Jessica, 'cause when it's over,

138
00:05:16,910 --> 00:05:18,490
她就会解雇他
she's gonna fire him.

139
00:05:24,880 --> 00:05:27,580
他们为了你延迟打烊吗
They keep this place open late for you?

140
00:05:28,220 --> 00:05:30,650
业主总是有特权的
Ownership has its privileges.

141
00:05:31,740 --> 00:05:33,130
你想怎样  哈维
What do you want, Harvey?

142
00:05:33,630 --> 00:05:35,130
我想你撤销和路易·利特
I want you to undo the dirty deal 

143
00:05:35,130 --> 00:05:36,360
达成的违法交易
you made with Louis Litt.

144
00:05:36,360 --> 00:05:38,930
违法交易  不像是我会做的事情
Dirty deal. Doesn't sound like me at all.

145
00:05:39,090 --> 00:05:40,500
那监狱像吗
How does prison sound?

146
00:05:41,000 --> 00:05:42,950
因为证监会会收到一份
Because the S.E.C. is gonna get a record

147
00:05:42,950 --> 00:05:45,070
你做过的肮脏事的记录
of the shit you pulled tomorrow morning.

148
00:05:45,130 --> 00:05:48,370
根本没有那样的记录  因为我什么都没做
There is no record, 'cause I didn't do anything.

149
00:05:48,370 --> 00:05:50,080
是路易·利特来找我的
Louis Litt came to me,

150
00:05:50,510 --> 00:05:52,470
也是他贪污了赃款
and he's the one who embezzled money.

151
00:05:52,670 --> 00:05:54,240
你恨的不是路易
And your grudge isn't with Louis.

152
00:05:54,240 --> 00:05:57,060
是我  放过他吧
It's with me, so let him go.

153
00:05:57,710 --> 00:05:59,710
保全自己  择日再跟我斗
Live to fight me another day.

154
00:05:59,720 --> 00:06:03,370
我放过他  就是放过了你
If I let him off, I let you off,

155
00:06:04,480 --> 00:06:06,160
我不觉得我愿意那样做
and I don't think I want to do that.

156
00:06:06,160 --> 00:06:08,060
那你就是逼我
Then you're forcing me to turn you in 

157
00:06:08,060 --> 00:06:10,080
检举你12年前做的事情
for what you did 12 years ago.

158
00:06:12,260 --> 00:06:14,670
不可能  你不会的
No way. You're not gonna do that,

159
00:06:15,260 --> 00:06:17,210
因为你也牵涉其中了  伙计
because you did it too, pal.

160
00:06:18,200 --> 00:06:19,800
但你如果对路易那样做了
But if you did it to Louis

161
00:06:19,800 --> 00:06:20,900
对我也那样做了
and you did it to me,

162
00:06:20,900 --> 00:06:22,970
那你肯定也对很多人那样做过
you did it to a hundred others.

163
00:06:23,170 --> 00:06:25,070
如果你不按照我说的做
And if you don't do what I'm asking,

164
00:06:25,330 --> 00:06:27,290
我只需要在那很多人中
I'll just have to find the one in a hundred

165
00:06:27,290 --> 00:06:29,380
找到一个愿意检举你的人
that's in a position to turn on you.

166
00:06:29,380 --> 00:06:31,780
我愿意赌一把  哈维
I'll take my chances, Harvey.

167
00:06:32,200 --> 00:06:33,300
现在  从我面前消失
Now, get out of my face.

168
00:06:33,300 --> 00:06:35,550
让我好好享受我的雪茄
Let me finish my cigar in peace.

169
00:07:18,390 --> 00:07:20,840
-你知道了  -我当然知道
- You know? - Of course I do.

170
00:07:21,760 --> 00:07:23,270
-我从来没想过  -路易
- I never meant to-- - Louis...

171
00:07:23,270 --> 00:07:25,220
我理解你为什么那样做
I understand why you did what you did.

172
00:07:25,500 --> 00:07:27,310
-真的吗  -是的
- You do? - Yes. 

173
00:07:27,320 --> 00:07:29,810
你的出发点是好的
You went down a path with the best intentions,

174
00:07:29,810 --> 00:07:31,070
但事情却演变的越来越糟
and then it just got worse and worse

175
00:07:31,080 --> 00:07:32,400
直到一切都太迟了
until it was too late.

176
00:07:36,090 --> 00:07:38,110
-我感觉糟透了  -你是该感觉糟糕
- Feel like shit. - And you should.

177
00:07:38,120 --> 00:07:39,000
什么
What?

178
00:07:41,210 --> 00:07:43,550
-但你刚刚还说  -说我理解  对
- But you just said-- - I understand? I do.

179
00:07:43,550 --> 00:07:45,160
但我觉得你没明白
But I don't think you understand 

180
00:07:45,160 --> 00:07:48,010
以前你搞砸事情  都是失误
that every other time you screwed up, it was a mistake,

181
00:07:48,020 --> 00:07:50,190
但这次  是你选的
and this time, it was a choice!

182
00:07:50,220 --> 00:07:51,130
哈维就是这么说的
That's what Harvey said.

183
00:07:51,130 --> 00:07:52,500
当然是哈维说的
Of course that's what Harvey said.

184
00:07:52,500 --> 00:07:53,610
我能理解你
And just because I get what happened,

185
00:07:53,610 --> 00:07:55,330
但那不意味着应该放你一马
it doesn't mean that you deserve to be let off the hook,

186
00:07:55,330 --> 00:07:57,010
所以如果你又是来求我
so if you've come in here to ask me

187
00:07:57,020 --> 00:07:58,610
和以前一样在他面前说好话  我
to go to him for the millionth time, I'm--

188
00:07:58,620 --> 00:08:00,220
不  我找你不是为了这个
No, I'm not here for that.

189
00:08:00,680 --> 00:08:02,490
那  那你来这干嘛
Then--then what are you here for?

190
00:08:02,880 --> 00:08:05,460
我来问你我会不会被解雇
I'm here to ask you if I'm gonna get fired.

191
00:08:06,640 --> 00:08:08,600
-什么  -我看到他的眼神了  唐娜
- What? - I saw how he looked at me, Donna.

192
00:08:08,610 --> 00:08:09,940
我知道他信任你
I know he trusts you,

193
00:08:10,220 --> 00:08:13,060
但我需要知道哈维是不是打算解雇我
but I need to know if Harvey's planning on firing me.

194
00:08:15,440 --> 00:08:16,720
不  路易
No, Louis.

195
00:08:17,540 --> 00:08:18,690
就我所知
To my knowledge,

196
00:08:18,690 --> 00:08:22,040
哈维没打算解雇你
Harvey isn't planning to fire you.

197
00:08:24,620 --> 00:08:26,030
谢谢你  唐娜
Thank you, Donna.

198
00:08:27,150 --> 00:08:28,760
我就知道你靠得住
I knew I could count on you.

199
00:08:38,880 --> 00:08:40,950
我都记不清上回在这见到你是什么时候了
Can't remember the last time I saw you in here.

200
00:08:40,950 --> 00:08:43,860
我也记不清这家律所多久没被起诉了
I can't remember the last time this firm faced prosecution.

201
00:08:43,860 --> 00:08:46,550
-我记得  艾娃·海辛顿  -那以后
- I can. Ava Hessington. - And after that,

202
00:08:46,550 --> 00:08:47,830
我们曾说决不能再发生这种事
we said it would never come to this again.

203
00:08:47,830 --> 00:08:48,870
到底是怎么搞的
How the hell did it?

204
00:08:48,880 --> 00:08:51,340
因为我们的对手是查尔斯·傅滋曼
We stepped into the ring with Charles Forstman.

205
00:08:51,660 --> 00:08:53,330
我猜他昨晚没改变主意
I'm guessing he didn't budge last night.

206
00:08:53,330 --> 00:08:54,350
他没有
He didn't.

207
00:08:54,350 --> 00:08:55,400
他把尾巴藏得很深
He sheltered himself,

208
00:08:55,400 --> 00:08:56,800
宁愿冒着被证监会盯上的风险
and he'd rather laugh in my face

209
00:08:56,800 --> 00:08:59,630
也要当面嘲笑我
than be 100% protected against the S.E.C.

210
00:09:00,020 --> 00:09:01,090
你有备选方案吗
You have a plan "B"?

211
00:09:01,090 --> 00:09:03,040
他没有  但我有
He doesn't, but I do.

212
00:09:03,280 --> 00:09:04,460
那到底是什么
What the hell is it?

213
00:09:04,890 --> 00:09:06,630
如果你是卡荷尔你会怎么做
What would you do if you were Cahill?

214
00:09:06,840 --> 00:09:08,190
仔细调查这盒子里的每一个人
Go through every one of these boxes,

215
00:09:08,190 --> 00:09:09,440
然后找我们取证
and start deposing us.

216
00:09:09,440 --> 00:09:11,450
好  那如果他一开始行动
Okay, so what if while he's doing that,

217
00:09:11,900 --> 00:09:13,510
我们就开始找他取证呢
we start deposing him?

218
00:09:19,930 --> 00:09:21,930
你亲自来这里给我送文件吗
Did you come here to personally deliver my files?

219
00:09:21,930 --> 00:09:23,900
我亲自来这里送这个
I came here to personally deliver this.

220
00:09:23,900 --> 00:09:25,490
如果这是你生日会的邀请函
Well, if it's an invitation to your birthday party,

221
00:09:25,490 --> 00:09:26,710
我想那天我没空
I think I'm busy that day. 

222
00:09:26,710 --> 00:09:28,960
可惜  我答应了孩子们会有小丑的
That's too bad. I promised the children a clown.

223
00:09:28,960 --> 00:09:30,410
你这一定是在逗我
You've got to be kidding me.

224
00:09:30,470 --> 00:09:32,800
你得到霍普金斯法官准许
You got Judge Hopkins to let you start depositions

225
00:09:32,800 --> 00:09:34,710
针对你的狗屁诬告进行采证
on your malicious prosecution bullshit?

226
00:09:34,710 --> 00:09:35,820
他可不觉得这是狗屁
He didn't think it was bullshit,

227
00:09:35,820 --> 00:09:36,930
所以他才让我从你的小男友
which is why he's letting me start

228
00:09:36,930 --> 00:09:38,760
埃里克·伍德尔开始
with your boyfriend Eric Woodall.

229
00:09:38,760 --> 00:09:40,560
你是想分散我注意力  哈维
You trying to take my eye off the ball, Harvey?

230
00:09:40,560 --> 00:09:41,900
这就是事情关键  肖恩
This is the ball, Sean.

231
00:09:41,900 --> 00:09:44,970
而且是致命一击  准备接招吧
It's a wrecking ball, and it's headed your way.

232
00:09:53,820 --> 00:09:55,680
路易  你到底去哪了
Louis, where the hell have you been?

233
00:09:55,680 --> 00:09:57,310
那些文件要上交了
Those documents are on their way over.

234
00:09:57,310 --> 00:09:58,800
卡特里娜  放松
Katrina, relax.

235
00:09:59,280 --> 00:10:00,530
放松
Relax?

236
00:10:00,970 --> 00:10:02,560
上回我见你的时候  你还在担心
The last time I saw you, you were worried

237
00:10:02,560 --> 00:10:04,170
会不会进监狱
about going to prison.

238
00:10:04,380 --> 00:10:05,560
你打算怎么做
What did you decide to do?

239
00:10:05,560 --> 00:10:06,560
我去找了哈维和杰西卡
I went to Harvey and Jessica,

240
00:10:06,560 --> 00:10:09,030
-告诉了他们一切  -什么
- and I told them everything. - What?

241
00:10:09,040 --> 00:10:11,230
杰西卡说我犯了个错误
Jessica said that I made a mistake,

242
00:10:11,230 --> 00:10:12,880
而他们在想解决的办法
and they're working on a way out.

243
00:10:12,880 --> 00:10:16,440
路易  你看过黑手党电影吗
Louis, have you seen any mafia movie ever made?

244
00:10:16,440 --> 00:10:17,760
其实我不太喜欢那种电影
I'm not really a fan of the genre.

245
00:10:17,770 --> 00:10:19,910
我觉得这种电影有点冒犯意大利人
I find it to be a little offensive to Italians--

246
00:10:19,910 --> 00:10:21,060
闭嘴  听着
Shut up, and listen.

247
00:10:21,440 --> 00:10:24,250
她当着你的面  告诉你她会饶你一命
She's telling you to your face she'll let you live,

248
00:10:24,470 --> 00:10:27,580
但背地里  她在计划狠狠搞你
but behind your back, she's making plans to whack you.

249
00:10:27,580 --> 00:10:29,570
老天  我离死不远了
Holy shit, I'm living on borrowed time.

250
00:10:29,580 --> 00:10:32,150
除非你解决这事  因为如果你没做到
Unless you fix this, because if you don't,

251
00:10:32,150 --> 00:10:34,950
即使杰西卡保你免受牢狱之灾
even if Jessica manages to keep you out of prison,

252
00:10:35,190 --> 00:10:37,080
她也会炒了你
she'll be coming to fire you.

253
00:10:43,370 --> 00:10:46,340
杰西卡  我刚在想
Jessica, I was just thinking about 

254
00:10:46,340 --> 00:10:48,500
我们今晚吃什么  我想...
our dinner plans tonight, and I think that...

255
00:10:49,200 --> 00:10:51,480
-怎么了  -我们在调查埃里克·伍德尔
- What's wrong? - We're going after Eric Woodall.

256
00:10:52,010 --> 00:10:53,720
哈维加快了进度
Harvey moved up the time line.

257
00:10:55,180 --> 00:10:57,450
既然现在这是哈维的案子了
And since this is Harvey's case now...

258
00:10:58,090 --> 00:10:59,320
你和我说这个做什么
Why are you talking to me?

259
00:10:59,320 --> 00:11:02,900
因为我需要你查出所有埃里克·伍德尔
'Cause I need you to find out every dirty thing

260
00:11:02,900 --> 00:11:06,490
做过  知情或参与过的不法行为
Eric Woodall has ever done, condoned, or been part of.

261
00:11:07,540 --> 00:11:09,540
杰西卡  要我不明原因
Jessica, I really don't feel comfortable

262
00:11:09,540 --> 00:11:12,170
就参与勒索他人  我觉得不太舒服
participating in blackmail without knowing why.

263
00:11:12,170 --> 00:11:13,400
这不是勒索
It's not blackmail, 

264
00:11:13,470 --> 00:11:15,450
这是采证  我会告诉你原因
it's evidence, and I'll tell you why.

265
00:11:15,450 --> 00:11:18,080
因为在他有案底的情况下
Because malicious prosecution is easier to prove

266
00:11:18,080 --> 00:11:19,270
我们指控他们诬告更有胜算
when there's a track record.

267
00:11:19,270 --> 00:11:21,310
对  只是有一个问题
Yeah, there's only one problem with that.

268
00:11:21,320 --> 00:11:23,900
就在昨天  我们同意交出全部文件
You see, just yesterday, we agreed to hand over our files

269
00:11:23,900 --> 00:11:25,270
因为我们没什么好遮掩的
because we had nothing to hide,

270
00:11:25,270 --> 00:11:27,380
而现在  你要我去调查证监会
and now, you want me to go after the S.E.C.,

271
00:11:27,380 --> 00:11:28,660
-就意味着我们有不可告人的事  -杰夫
- which means we do. - Jeff--

272
00:11:28,660 --> 00:11:31,350
杰西卡  随你想怎么瞒他们  好吗
Jessica, hide it from them all you want, okay?

273
00:11:31,820 --> 00:11:33,290
但我们谈过这个问题  你说
But we talked about this, and you said

274
00:11:33,290 --> 00:11:35,590
我应该跟其他合伙人的待遇不同
that I shouldn't be treated like any other partner,

275
00:11:35,600 --> 00:11:37,970
所以别瞒我
so don't come in here hiding it from me.

276
00:11:37,970 --> 00:11:39,140
你要一个直接的答案
You want a straight answer.

277
00:11:39,140 --> 00:11:40,910
那我直接告诉你
I'll give you a straight answer.

278
00:11:41,580 --> 00:11:44,660
哈维和迈克·罗斯没有勾结
Harvey did not collude with Mike Ross,

279
00:11:44,660 --> 00:11:46,540
但肖恩·卡荷尔根本不在乎
but Sean Cahill doesn't give a shit about that.

280
00:11:46,540 --> 00:11:49,470
所以我需要你尽一切力量
So I need you to do whatever you have to

281
00:11:49,470 --> 00:11:52,180
给我从这些人身上找出点什么来
and get me something on these guys.

282
00:12:01,470 --> 00:12:04,040
卡荷尔对我们给他的惊喜有什么反应
Hey, how did Cahill handle our surprise?

283
00:12:04,040 --> 00:12:05,560
事实上  我亲自去给他的
Actually, I got to hand it to him.

284
00:12:05,560 --> 00:12:07,320
他的反应非常好
He handled it pretty damn well.

285
00:12:08,350 --> 00:12:09,910
-怎么  -你们上演了那么多
- What? - You guys had

286
00:12:09,910 --> 00:12:11,310
神奇双胞胎的桥段
your whole Wonder Twins riff,

287
00:12:10,310 --> 00:12:12,310
{\an8}神奇双胞胎  1977年诞生的著名卡通人物

288
00:12:11,320 --> 00:12:13,300
这时候却对他以礼相待了  接下来呢
and now you're giving him respect? What's next: 

289
00:12:13,300 --> 00:12:15,700
-和他去佛罗里达群岛度假吗  -别急  老虎
- a time share in the Florida Keys? - Easy, tiger.

290
00:12:15,700 --> 00:12:17,550
只想说  我送你们两个字
Just saying, I got two words for you:

291
00:12:17,580 --> 00:12:19,770
基  情
Bro-mance.

292
00:12:19,770 --> 00:12:21,940
在你给我们买结婚贺礼前
Before you order us a gift off our registry,

293
00:12:21,940 --> 00:12:23,620
让我告诉你他做了什么
let me tell you what he's been up to.

294
00:12:23,830 --> 00:12:26,080
他让霍普金斯法官同意他的取证
He had Judge Hopkins sign off on his depositions,

295
00:12:26,080 --> 00:12:27,050
也就是说
meaning

296
00:12:27,050 --> 00:12:29,390
我们调查他的同时  他也来调查我们了
he's coming at us the same time we go after him.

297
00:12:29,390 --> 00:12:31,850
-我们能解决  -瑞秋能吗
- We can handle it. - Can Rachel?

298
00:12:32,530 --> 00:12:33,560
什么
What?

299
00:12:33,560 --> 00:12:34,570
看看吧
Take a look.

300
00:12:34,750 --> 00:12:36,220
她在调查名单的首位
She's first on the list.

301
00:12:37,090 --> 00:12:38,640
你要我去告诉她这些事
And you want me to tell her it's coming.

302
00:12:38,640 --> 00:12:40,020
我要你做的远不仅如此
I want you to do more than that.

303
00:12:40,020 --> 00:12:41,450
我要你给她做取证预演
I want you to prep her.

304
00:12:41,800 --> 00:12:43,630
哈维  这不是个好主意
Harvey, that's not a good idea.

305
00:12:43,630 --> 00:12:45,240
不  这是好主意  你是这工作的最佳人选
Yes, it is--you're the best person for the job.

306
00:12:45,240 --> 00:12:47,020
我是最不适合做这件事的人了
I am the worst person for the job.

307
00:12:47,020 --> 00:12:47,800
你这么说
And you're only saying it

308
00:12:47,800 --> 00:12:49,600
只不过因为这会让你不舒服
because it makes you feel uncomfortable.

309
00:12:49,600 --> 00:12:51,540
你以为卡荷尔在取证时
How do you think Cahill's gonna make Rachel feel

310
00:12:51,540 --> 00:12:52,940
会让瑞秋好受吗
when he gets her under oath?

311
00:13:05,090 --> 00:13:07,740
通常大家谈正事不会从洗手开始
Usually, people don't start by washing their hands.

312
00:13:07,740 --> 00:13:09,900
通常人们不会在这谈路易的事情
Usually, people aren't here to talk about Louis.

313
00:13:10,510 --> 00:13:13,640
-唐娜  -杰西卡  他只是犯了错
- Donna. - Jessica, he made a mistake.

314
00:13:13,640 --> 00:13:16,700
犯错的意思是他不小心失误
"Mistake" implies that he did something by accident.

315
00:13:16,840 --> 00:13:18,220
路易做的是选择
Louis made a choice.

316
00:13:18,700 --> 00:13:20,450
而你选择在这一切结束以后
And you're making the choice to fire him

317
00:13:20,450 --> 00:13:21,640
炒了他
when this is over.

318
00:13:22,050 --> 00:13:24,170
这到底又关你什么事
And how the hell is that any of your business?

319
00:13:24,170 --> 00:13:27,490
我只是想如果路易能帮你摆脱困境
I just thought if Louis could help get you out of it--

320
00:13:27,490 --> 00:13:28,890
帮我摆脱困境
Help get me out of it?

321
00:13:28,890 --> 00:13:30,590
就是他让我陷入困境的
He's the one that got me into it.

322
00:13:30,590 --> 00:13:31,430
如果是哈维
And if this were Harvey,

323
00:13:31,430 --> 00:13:32,740
你一定会让他做出补救
you'd let him try to make up for it.

324
00:13:32,750 --> 00:13:33,550
如果是哈维
And if this were Harvey,

325
00:13:33,550 --> 00:13:35,810
我有信心他能补救
I'd have the confidence that he would.

326
00:13:37,030 --> 00:13:40,190
杰西卡  路易这么做
Jessica, Louis did all of this

327
00:13:40,190 --> 00:13:43,030
是因为他太想得到你的认可了
because he is dying for your approval.

328
00:13:43,040 --> 00:13:44,190
你对他从来没有信心
You never have confidence in him,

329
00:13:44,190 --> 00:13:46,060
也从不像对哈维一样对他
and you never treat him the way you treat Harvey.

330
00:13:46,060 --> 00:13:47,060
所以倒是我错了
So this is my fault?

331
00:13:47,060 --> 00:13:49,740
我只是说在哈维犯错的时候
I'm saying Harvey's made mistakes,

332
00:13:49,750 --> 00:13:51,160
你都原谅了他
and you've forgiven him.

333
00:13:51,450 --> 00:13:53,940
我也犯过错  你也原谅了我
I've made mistakes, and you've forgiven me.

334
00:13:54,390 --> 00:13:56,550
你说得对  唐娜  你犯了一次错
You're right, Donna, you did make a mistake once,

335
00:13:56,550 --> 00:14:00,700
我的确原谅了你  但首先我解雇了你
and I did forgive you, but first I fired you.

336
00:14:01,140 --> 00:14:02,760
现在如果你还不让开
And if you don't back off me right now,

337
00:14:02,760 --> 00:14:04,550
我会再炒你一次
I will do it again.

338
00:14:06,830 --> 00:14:09,310
现在  恕不奉陪  我还有取证会要开
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a deposition to get to.

339
00:14:14,030 --> 00:14:15,810
请陈述全名以供记录
Please state your full name for the record.

340
00:14:15,810 --> 00:14:18,510
-埃里克·伊格内修斯·伍德尔  -伊格内修斯
- Eric Ignatius Woodall. - Ignatius?

341
00:14:18,510 --> 00:14:21,330
-像圣徒的名字  -我可怀疑
- Like the saint. - I doubt that.

342
00:14:21,520 --> 00:14:23,330
你在美国证监会工作了多久
And how long have you worked for the S.E.C.?

343
00:14:23,330 --> 00:14:24,120
两个月
Two months.

344
00:14:24,120 --> 00:14:25,550
在那之前你是做什么工作的
And where were you before that?

345
00:14:25,550 --> 00:14:27,740
在美国检察院工作
I worked at the U.S. Attorneys' office.

346
00:14:27,750 --> 00:14:29,790
直到我起诉你诬告让你被解雇
Until I got you fired for malicious prosecution.

347
00:14:29,790 --> 00:14:31,090
不是你让我被解雇
You didn't get me fired.

348
00:14:31,090 --> 00:14:34,070
你向当权者诽谤我
You slandered me to a person in power,

349
00:14:34,070 --> 00:14:35,920
才让我离开了所爱的工作
which caused me to leave a job I loved.

350
00:14:35,920 --> 00:14:37,340
才得以免于被解雇
To avoid getting fired.

351
00:14:37,340 --> 00:14:39,640
这事你没证据  他也不知情
You have no proof of that, and he has no knowledge of that.

352
00:14:39,640 --> 00:14:42,720
他知道自己对我的感觉吗
Does he have any knowledge of his feelings towards me?

353
00:14:43,290 --> 00:14:46,000
我对你可没什么感觉  斯佩克特先生
I don't have any feelings for you, Mr. Specter,

354
00:14:46,010 --> 00:14:48,530
另外  跟你们说一声  我有了新饭碗
and for your information, I landed on my feet.

355
00:14:48,530 --> 00:14:50,350
对  我们知道  在证监会
Yes, we know, at the S.E.C.,

356
00:14:50,350 --> 00:14:52,050
但我们不想聊这个
but we don't want to talk about that.

357
00:14:52,050 --> 00:14:54,140
我们想说说吉姆·品波里
We want to talk about Jim Pembry.

358
00:14:55,320 --> 00:14:57,800
你看起来没那么自在了啊  埃里克
You don't seem too comfortable anymore, Eric.

359
00:14:58,700 --> 00:15:00,200
谁是吉姆·品波里
Who's Jim Pembry?

360
00:15:00,660 --> 00:15:03,000
我和吉姆在检察院一起工作过
I worked with Jim at the U.S. Attorneys' office.

361
00:15:03,000 --> 00:15:04,730
办亚瑟·科恩的案子吗
On the Arthur Cohen prosecution?

362
00:15:04,730 --> 00:15:06,230
我想他替我做了点事
I believe he did some work for me.

363
00:15:06,230 --> 00:15:08,690
你想  过去四年里就这案件
You believe? You sent him over 1,200 emails 

364
00:15:08,690 --> 00:15:11,010
你给他发了超过1200封邮件
on that case over four years.

365
00:15:11,010 --> 00:15:11,900
你说有就有吧
If you say so.

366
00:15:11,900 --> 00:15:13,840
其实是你的电脑记录告诉我们的
Actually, your computer records say so,

367
00:15:13,840 --> 00:15:15,250
我可以全部读给你听  但
and I could read them all, but 

368
00:15:15,270 --> 00:15:16,980
我想从我最喜欢的这封开始
I'd rather start with my favorite.

369
00:15:17,530 --> 00:15:19,950
"我不在乎以什么名义抓到亚瑟·科恩
"I don't care what we get Arthur Cohen on.

370
00:15:19,950 --> 00:15:22,880
"逃税  内部交易  甚至是乱穿马路
"Tax evasion, insider trading, jaywalking if we have to,

371
00:15:22,880 --> 00:15:24,860
"但我们一定要把他关起来"
but we're putting that piece of shit behind bars."

372
00:15:24,860 --> 00:15:25,790
你从哪里找来的邮件
Where the hell did you get that?

373
00:15:25,790 --> 00:15:27,190
我们从哪儿获得不重要
It's not important where we got it,

374
00:15:27,190 --> 00:15:28,140
关键是我们找到了
but that we got it.

375
00:15:28,140 --> 00:15:29,120
邮件的口气有点过火
Emails get heated.

376
00:15:29,120 --> 00:15:30,200
因为这个案子正进行到一半
It was the middle of a case.

377
00:15:30,200 --> 00:15:31,450
问题是  埃里克
The problem is, Eric,

378
00:15:31,450 --> 00:15:32,890
这是你开始办你那件大案
this was dated two years before

379
00:15:32,890 --> 00:15:34,180
两年之前的邮件
you even brought your big case.

380
00:15:34,180 --> 00:15:35,980
-你有问题吗  -当然
- Do you have a question? - I sure do.

381
00:15:35,980 --> 00:15:37,420
你先决定一个人有罪
You decide someone's guilty,

382
00:15:37,420 --> 00:15:39,150
然后才去找罪名抓他
then you find the crime to fit them.

383
00:15:39,150 --> 00:15:40,670
-是这样吗  -不
- Isn't that true? - No.

384
00:15:40,670 --> 00:15:42,920
你还要我告你做伪证吗
You want me to get you for perjury too?

385
00:15:42,930 --> 00:15:44,590
你本想用一个罪名抓亚瑟
You tried to get Arthur on one thing.

386
00:15:44,590 --> 00:15:46,760
结果却用了另外一个  不是吗
Instead, you got him on another, didn't you?

387
00:15:46,760 --> 00:15:47,670
-别回答  -是的
- Don't answer him. - Yes.

388
00:15:47,670 --> 00:15:50,170
这也恰恰是你对我所做的  不是吗
And that's exactly what you want to do with me, isn't it?

389
00:15:50,180 --> 00:15:52,420
够了  别打字了  到此为止
That's enough. Stop typing. We're done here.

390
00:15:52,420 --> 00:15:54,070
-给你个答案  -别
- To answer your question... - Don't--

391
00:15:54,070 --> 00:15:55,620
你说的没错
You're damn right it is.

392
00:15:56,500 --> 00:15:59,170
没关系  这或许没记下来
That's okay. It may not be on record, But 

393
00:15:59,170 --> 00:16:00,370
但我已经得到我想要的了
I got what I wanted.

394
00:16:10,610 --> 00:16:12,240
你可不是我平常的司机
You're not my usual guy.

395
00:16:12,470 --> 00:16:14,620
我从来不是平常人
I'm not a usual anything.

396
00:16:14,620 --> 00:16:15,800
确实
No, you're not.

397
00:16:17,080 --> 00:16:19,700
我们逮住他了  谢谢你
We got him, thanks to you.

398
00:16:20,490 --> 00:16:21,700
感谢吉姆·品波里
Thanks to Jim Pembry.

399
00:16:21,700 --> 00:16:24,130
我不是来和吉姆·品波里庆祝的
I'm not here to celebrate with Jim Pembry.

400
00:16:26,190 --> 00:16:27,800
杰西卡  或许我们第一拳打得不错
Jessica, we may have landed the first punch,

401
00:16:27,800 --> 00:16:29,020
但接下来还得小心
but we're next up.

402
00:16:29,800 --> 00:16:31,520
卡荷尔一定不会放过我们
And Cahill's gonna be brutal on us.

403
00:16:31,520 --> 00:16:33,420
-不一定  -什么意思
- No, he isn't. - What do you mean?

404
00:16:33,420 --> 00:16:34,980
我们明天上庭
We're going to court tomorrow,

405
00:16:34,980 --> 00:16:36,100
运气好的话
and with any luck, 

406
00:16:36,100 --> 00:16:37,670
我们能在他有机会向我们取证前
we're gonna get this whole thing tossed

407
00:16:37,670 --> 00:16:39,800
把这整件事摆平
before he even has a chance to depose us.

408
00:16:40,310 --> 00:16:41,610
那或许我们该去吃饭了
Well, then, maybe we should go to dinner.

409
00:16:41,610 --> 00:16:43,250
我有个更好的主意
I have a better idea.

410
00:16:44,020 --> 00:16:45,250
我们叫送餐服务
Let's order in.

411
00:16:55,600 --> 00:16:57,900
赞恩小姐  你和收购案另一方律师
Miss Zane, do you live with Michael Ross,

412
00:16:57,900 --> 00:17:00,310
迈克尔·罗斯同居是吗
the lawyer on the other side of this takeover?

413
00:17:00,780 --> 00:17:01,560
没错
Yes.

414
00:17:01,560 --> 00:17:04,020
那在案件期间
And, uh, and at any point during the takeover,

415
00:17:04,020 --> 00:17:05,590
你有没有和他谈过这个案子呢
did you discuss business with him?

416
00:17:05,590 --> 00:17:06,600
没有
No.

417
00:17:07,350 --> 00:17:08,550
你以为我会相信吗
You expect me to believe that?

418
00:17:08,550 --> 00:17:09,830
你相不相信都行
I don't care whether you believe it or not,

419
00:17:09,830 --> 00:17:11,100
因为我说的是真话
because it's the truth.

420
00:17:12,460 --> 00:17:13,540
真话
The truth.

421
00:17:16,240 --> 00:17:19,070
那你和罗斯先生讨论过洛根·桑德斯吗
Did you discuss Logan Sanders with Mr. Ross?

422
00:17:22,040 --> 00:17:23,060
讨论过
Yes. 

423
00:17:23,230 --> 00:17:24,320
我不懂了  你刚才说
I'm confused. You just said that 

424
00:17:24,320 --> 00:17:26,670
你没有和罗斯先生讨论过案件
you didn't discuss business with Mr. Ross,

425
00:17:26,720 --> 00:17:27,610
但你现在又说
yet now you're saying that 

426
00:17:27,610 --> 00:17:29,770
你们讨论过收购案的另一方
you discussed the man on the other side of the takeover.

427
00:17:29,770 --> 00:17:31,540
这两种说法怎么能同时成立呢
How can one of those be true and not the other?

428
00:17:31,540 --> 00:17:34,760
-那与案件无关  -那是关于什么
- That wasn't about business. - Then what was it about?

429
00:17:34,830 --> 00:17:36,460
我曾经和洛根·桑德斯
It was about the fact that 

430
00:17:36,460 --> 00:17:39,450
交往过一阵子
I used to be involved with Logan Sanders.

431
00:17:40,330 --> 00:17:41,800
你有没有向罗斯先生保证
And did you assure Mr. Ross

432
00:17:41,810 --> 00:17:43,250
你不会再和洛根·桑德斯
that you wouldn't become involved

433
00:17:43,250 --> 00:17:44,410
有所牵连
with Logan Sanders again?

434
00:17:44,410 --> 00:17:45,680
-这有什么关系  -回答我的问题
- What does that have to do with-- - Answer my question. 

435
00:17:46,640 --> 00:17:49,120
-我保证过  -然而在收购案期间
- Yes, I did. - And yet, over the course of the takeover,

436
00:17:49,120 --> 00:17:50,930
你确实和他又发生了一些事
you did become involved with him again, 

437
00:17:50,930 --> 00:17:51,990
-对吗  -没有
- Didn't you? - No, I didn't.

438
00:17:51,990 --> 00:17:54,320
你完全没有和他有任何性意味的身体接触
You had no physical contact of a sexual nature at all--

439
00:17:54,320 --> 00:17:55,260
迈克  拜托  我没有...  
Mike, please, I don't-- 

440
00:17:55,260 --> 00:17:56,650
回答我问题就好
Just answer my question.

441
00:17:57,120 --> 00:17:58,430
我们接吻过一次  仅此而已
We kissed once, and that was it.

442
00:17:58,430 --> 00:18:00,130
你和他上过床吗  
Did you sleep with him? 

443
00:18:00,130 --> 00:18:01,670
他不会问我...
He is not going to ask me--

444
00:18:01,670 --> 00:18:03,700
你说谎了  你之前说没有牵扯了
You just lied. You said you weren't involved,

445
00:18:03,700 --> 00:18:04,620
然后又说和他接过吻
and then you said you kissed him.

446
00:18:04,620 --> 00:18:05,560
所以我再问你一次
So I'm gonna ask you again:

447
00:18:05,560 --> 00:18:07,640
在你向你爱的人保证你
Did you sleep with Logan Sanders

448
00:18:07,640 --> 00:18:10,430
你和洛根·桑德斯不会有什么之后
after you assured the man that you supposedly love

449
00:18:10,430 --> 00:18:11,800
和他上过床没有
that you wouldn't become involved again?

450
00:18:11,800 --> 00:18:12,670
我不会回答这个问题
I'm not gonna answer that,

451
00:18:12,670 --> 00:18:15,300
因为这与合谋无关
because it doesn't have anything to do with collusion.

452
00:18:15,310 --> 00:18:16,730
这与可靠性有关  关系着
It goes to credibility. It goes to

453
00:18:16,740 --> 00:18:19,060
你能不能让陪审团信任你
what you're capable of, whether a jury should trust you.

454
00:18:19,060 --> 00:18:19,960
是陪审团还是你
A jury or you? 

455
00:18:19,960 --> 00:18:21,230
有什么区别吗
What difference does that make?

456
00:18:21,230 --> 00:18:22,360
区别在于你这么盘问我
The difference is you're the one that's doing it, 

457
00:18:22,360 --> 00:18:23,780
因为你不相信我
because you don't trust me.

458
00:18:23,780 --> 00:18:24,900
是哈维让我这么做的
Because Harvey needs me to. 

459
00:18:24,900 --> 00:18:25,980
这是不对的  太残忍了  
It is vicious, and it's cruel. 

460
00:18:25,980 --> 00:18:26,670
我只是做份内的事
I am doing my job.

461
00:18:26,670 --> 00:18:29,060
-迈克  我以为你放下了  -我没有
- Mike, I thought You were over this. - Well, I'm goddamn not!

462
00:18:38,530 --> 00:18:41,460
我没有和洛根上床
I didn't sleep with Logan.

463
00:18:45,990 --> 00:18:50,660
我吻了他  也为此恨自己
I kissed him, and I hate myself for it.

464
00:18:53,090 --> 00:18:54,860
迈克  我很抱歉
Mike, I'm so sorry.

465
00:18:56,190 --> 00:18:58,430
我可以在我的余生
And I can apologize to you 

466
00:18:58,820 --> 00:19:00,940
每天都向你道歉
every day for the rest of my life,

467
00:19:00,940 --> 00:19:02,150
但我...
but I-I...

468
00:19:04,150 --> 00:19:05,990
我不知道还能怎么做
I don't know what else to do,

469
00:19:06,640 --> 00:19:08,430
只能告诉你
other than to tell you that...

470
00:19:09,350 --> 00:19:12,000
对我而言  你比这个世界上任何东西都重要
You mean more to me than anything in the world,

471
00:19:12,000 --> 00:19:13,900
我需要你相信我
and I need you to believe me.

472
00:19:15,960 --> 00:19:18,320
我需要你相信我  这样我们才能继续
I need you to believe me so that we can move on

473
00:19:18,320 --> 00:19:19,910
好好过日子
and live our lives.

474
00:19:26,100 --> 00:19:28,630
我觉得今晚也问得差不多了
Think that's enough questions for tonight.

475
00:19:38,580 --> 00:19:40,110
路易  你在这里做什么
Louis, what the hell are you doing here?

476
00:19:40,300 --> 00:19:41,990
我读了埃里克·伍德尔的证词
I read the Eric Woodall deposition,

477
00:19:41,990 --> 00:19:43,870
-觉得或许能帮上忙  -帮什么忙
- and I thought I could help. - Help what?

478
00:19:44,040 --> 00:19:45,390
你来和肖恩·卡荷尔做了断
You're here to shut down Sean Cahill,

479
00:19:45,390 --> 00:19:46,670
可他不会善罢甘休的
and he's not gonna give up without a fight.

480
00:19:46,670 --> 00:19:48,380
路易  我没工夫和你说了
Louis, I don't have time for this.

481
00:19:48,380 --> 00:19:50,130
废话少说  赶紧离开
So take your arguments and get the hell out of here.

482
00:19:50,140 --> 00:19:51,400
拜托  杰西卡  我想帮忙
Please, Jessica, I want to help.

483
00:19:51,400 --> 00:19:52,750
我不需要你帮忙
I don't need your help.

484
00:19:52,750 --> 00:19:54,070
我们就要摆平这件事情了
We're about to put this thing to bed.

485
00:19:54,070 --> 00:19:56,880
-我觉得我有责任  -你确实有责任
- And I feel responsible. - You are responsible.

486
00:19:56,880 --> 00:19:59,170
就是因为你我们才陷入这种危机
You are the entire reason we are in jeopardy,

487
00:19:59,170 --> 00:20:02,140
你还想让你那张蠢脸出现在卡荷尔面前
and you want to sit your stupid face in front of Cahill?

488
00:20:02,470 --> 00:20:05,250
你还不如戴个"下次找我取证"的牌子
You may as well wear a sign that says "Depose me next."

489
00:20:05,250 --> 00:20:08,740
如果他找你  你会像纸牌屋般一触即溃
And if he does that, you will tumble like a house of cards,

490
00:20:08,740 --> 00:20:10,810
因为你的情感控制了理智
because you are ruled by your emotions,

491
00:20:10,810 --> 00:20:12,390
这也是我们为何
and that is the reason 

492
00:20:12,510 --> 00:20:15,300
走到这一步的原因
why we are in this situation in the first place.

493
00:20:16,910 --> 00:20:17,880
那我在旁听席坐着行吗
Can I at least sit in the gallery?

494
00:20:17,880 --> 00:20:19,510
我才不在乎你坐哪儿
I don't care where you sit,

495
00:20:19,640 --> 00:20:20,940
但卡荷尔再过30秒就进来了
but Cahill's gonna be here in 30 seconds,

496
00:20:20,940 --> 00:20:22,770
所以你赶紧给我滚
so it better be far away from me.

497
00:20:25,650 --> 00:20:26,690
他到这里来干什么
What the hell is he doing here?

498
00:20:26,690 --> 00:20:27,470
重要的是
The important thing is

499
00:20:27,470 --> 00:20:29,440
他再也不坐这里了
that he's not sitting here anymore.

500
00:20:33,100 --> 00:20:36,030
卡荷尔先生  这封邮件有力证明
Mr. Cahill, this email makes a strong case

501
00:20:36,030 --> 00:20:38,800
埃里克·伍德尔有诬告他人的倾向
that Eric Woodall has a propensity for malicious prosecution.

502
00:20:38,800 --> 00:20:40,070
没错  法官大人
Yes, it does, Your Honor,

503
00:20:40,180 --> 00:20:42,040
但负责这个案子的是我
but I'm the one pursuing this case,

504
00:20:42,040 --> 00:20:43,100
不是埃里克·伍德尔
not Eric Woodall,

505
00:20:43,100 --> 00:20:45,330
我起诉别人没有任何偏见
and I don't have a propensity for anything.

506
00:20:45,330 --> 00:20:47,260
只是一个想做好份内事的老实人
I'm a simple man trying to do my job.

507
00:20:47,330 --> 00:20:48,690
你希望我们相信
You expect us to believe that 

508
00:20:48,700 --> 00:20:51,150
一个司法部出身的人
the guy you came up with at the Department of Justice

509
00:20:51,150 --> 00:20:53,000
刚到证监局做事
comes over to the S.E.C.,

510
00:20:53,000 --> 00:20:55,520
就立马针对我们
and you immediately start coming after us,

511
00:20:55,520 --> 00:20:56,770
只是一桩巧合吗
and it's a coincidence?

512
00:20:56,770 --> 00:20:58,750
很容易就把这些联系起来  法官大人
Doesn't take much to connect the dots here, Your Honor.

513
00:20:58,760 --> 00:21:00,030
说到联系
Well, as long as we're connecting dots,

514
00:21:00,030 --> 00:21:01,540
我也能联系几件事
I can connect a few too.

515
00:21:01,760 --> 00:21:02,810
先说杰夫·马龙吧
Let's start with Jeff Malone.

516
00:21:02,810 --> 00:21:04,520
他曾在证监会工作
A man who used to work at the S.E.C.

517
00:21:04,520 --> 00:21:06,830
现在跳槽去了皮尔逊-斯佩克特
Now conveniently works at Pearson Specter.

518
00:21:06,830 --> 00:21:08,640
跳槽又不犯法
It's not against the law to change jobs.

519
00:21:08,640 --> 00:21:10,480
没错  但他为什么要跳槽呢
Yes, but why did he change jobs?

520
00:21:10,480 --> 00:21:12,750
因为有人让他代表证监会
Because he was instructed to come after us

521
00:21:12,750 --> 00:21:14,290
来对付我们
on behalf of the S.E.C.

522
00:21:14,290 --> 00:21:15,140
那是他的说法
So he says.

523
00:21:15,140 --> 00:21:17,510
我认为他跳槽是为了和他女朋友
I think it's because he wanted to work with his girlfriend

524
00:21:17,510 --> 00:21:19,190
杰西卡·皮尔逊一起工作
Jessica Pearson.

525
00:21:20,090 --> 00:21:20,990
你说什么
Excuse me?

526
00:21:20,990 --> 00:21:22,820
皮尔逊女士雇佣马龙先生
Ms. Pearson hired Mr. Malone,

527
00:21:22,820 --> 00:21:24,550
是因为一个人想犯法
because if you're planning to break some rules,

528
00:21:24,550 --> 00:21:26,150
总要有人来代劳
you need someone to navigate them for you.

529
00:21:26,150 --> 00:21:26,950
谁会比一个
Who better to do that

530
00:21:26,950 --> 00:21:29,040
在证监会工作的男友更合适呢
than your boyfriend who works at the S.E.C.?

531
00:21:29,040 --> 00:21:30,160
荒谬
That's ridiculous.

532
00:21:30,160 --> 00:21:32,030
你有证据支撑这一指控吗
Do you have any proof of this allegation?

533
00:21:32,030 --> 00:21:33,280
就在这里
Right here.

534
00:21:35,200 --> 00:21:38,100
我可以申请传唤你  或者现在就质证
I can call you up to the stand, or we can do this right now.

535
00:21:41,740 --> 00:21:43,870
杰夫·马龙在证监会工作期间
Were you seeing Jeff Malone

536
00:21:43,870 --> 00:21:46,160
你在跟他交往吗
during the time that he worked for the S.E.C.?

537
00:21:52,240 --> 00:21:55,200
请记下皮尔逊女士说"是"
Please let the record reflect Ms. Pearson said yes.

538
00:21:55,450 --> 00:21:58,610
恋爱关系并不能证明两人合谋
Well, a romantic relationship isn't proof of a conspiracy,

539
00:21:58,610 --> 00:22:00,050
但也并非毫无关联
but it's not irrelevant.

540
00:22:00,050 --> 00:22:02,790
我允许你开始进行取证
I'll allow you to move forward with depositions.

541
00:22:04,500 --> 00:22:06,370
我不管要做什么
I don't care what we have to do.

542
00:22:06,510 --> 00:22:08,720
我才不要输给那个混蛋
I'm not losing to that son of a bitch.

543
00:22:12,060 --> 00:22:14,390
不管我们刚证明了什么  但你不是输给他
Despite what we just proved, you're not losing to him,

544
00:22:14,390 --> 00:22:15,470
而是输给我
you're losing to me.

545
00:22:15,470 --> 00:22:17,580
到了取证阶段
And as far as depositions go,

546
00:22:18,080 --> 00:22:19,610
该我们出牌了
now it's our turn.

547
00:22:29,610 --> 00:22:30,870
路易
Louis.

548
00:22:31,650 --> 00:22:33,450
有什么我能帮得上的吗
Is there something I can help you with?

549
00:22:34,700 --> 00:22:36,210
我只是在想
I was just thinking

550
00:22:36,210 --> 00:22:38,390
我还在这间办公室的时候
things were so much simpler

551
00:22:38,390 --> 00:22:39,710
一切都单纯多了
when I was in here.

552
00:22:39,850 --> 00:22:41,060
是啊  路易
Yeah, Louis...

553
00:22:41,060 --> 00:22:42,880
我知道了你和杰西卡的事
I know about you and Jessica.

554
00:22:43,890 --> 00:22:45,140
什么
What?

555
00:22:45,190 --> 00:22:46,800
法庭上公开了
It came out in court.

556
00:22:47,750 --> 00:22:50,740
我以为你是想利用我往上爬
See, I thought you were using me to get ahead,

557
00:22:50,740 --> 00:22:54,360
原来你只是想和杰西卡多相处一会儿
when you really just wanted to spend more time with Jessica.

558
00:22:55,210 --> 00:22:56,890
你来这儿干什么  路易
What are you doin' in here, Louis?

559
00:22:56,890 --> 00:22:58,500
我是来道歉的
I'm here to apologize.

560
00:22:59,510 --> 00:23:01,510
你想和我做朋友  我却拒绝了你
You wanted to be my friend, and I rejected you

561
00:23:01,510 --> 00:23:03,780
只因为你想保护她
because you were trying to protect her.

562
00:23:06,030 --> 00:23:07,710
你一定很孤独
You must've felt so alone.

563
00:23:08,950 --> 00:23:09,790
相信我
And believe me,

564
00:23:09,790 --> 00:23:12,650
我知道孤独是什么滋味
I know what it's like to feel alone.

565
00:23:13,150 --> 00:23:15,110
-你不孤独  -我孤独
- You're not alone. - Oh, I am.

566
00:23:16,200 --> 00:23:16,930
杰西卡说
Jessica said that I'm responsible 

567
00:23:16,930 --> 00:23:18,730
我是这一切的罪魁祸首
for everything that's happening,

568
00:23:18,730 --> 00:23:20,310
她说得对
and she was right.

569
00:23:21,460 --> 00:23:24,080
没人逼我跟傅滋曼做非法交易
No one made me make that dirty deal with Forstman,

570
00:23:24,080 --> 00:23:25,660
现在她不会原谅我了
and now she won't forgive me.

571
00:23:25,700 --> 00:23:27,020
我孤立无援
I'm alone.

572
00:23:28,640 --> 00:23:31,110
你想让我帮你跟她说情
And you want me to talk to her for you.

573
00:23:31,110 --> 00:23:33,030
我只能找你了  杰夫
You're the only one I can go to, Jeff.

574
00:23:35,120 --> 00:23:37,510
你是她最亲近的人
And you're the closest person she has.

575
00:23:40,070 --> 00:23:41,490
没问题  路易
Sure, Louis.

576
00:23:42,230 --> 00:23:44,010
我会帮你说情的
I'll talk to Jessica for you.

577
00:23:53,900 --> 00:23:55,220
卡荷尔不会对付你了
You're off the hook with Cahill.

578
00:23:55,220 --> 00:23:57,840
他明早会先问询我和哈维
He's gonna start with me and Harvey in the morning.

579
00:23:58,460 --> 00:23:59,720
不会了吗
Am I?

580
00:24:00,000 --> 00:24:02,070
-不会什么  -来对付我
- Are you what? - Off the hook.

581
00:24:04,990 --> 00:24:06,240
瑞秋
Rachel...

582
00:24:06,610 --> 00:24:09,860
发生这种事  我也不愿意
I didn't mean for what happened to happen.

583
00:24:10,310 --> 00:24:12,330
-但还是发生了  -我知道
- But it did. - I know.

584
00:24:15,440 --> 00:24:16,890
-迈克  -你告诉我之后
- Mike-- - I still haven't gotten

585
00:24:16,890 --> 00:24:18,710
我还没睡过一晚安稳觉
a full night's sleep since you told me.

586
00:24:18,710 --> 00:24:22,380
我知道你心里还有芥蒂
I know that you're not completely over it.

587
00:24:24,780 --> 00:24:26,600
但以后还会有别的事情  我...
But things are gonna come up, and I--

588
00:24:27,020 --> 00:24:29,410
希望我别变得恶毒无情
Want me to not be vicious and cruel.

589
00:24:30,270 --> 00:24:31,920
你觉得这可能吗
Do you think that's possible?

590
00:24:32,780 --> 00:24:34,110
但愿吧
I hope so.

591
00:24:35,120 --> 00:24:36,530
我也这么希望
I hope so too.

592
00:24:40,680 --> 00:24:42,350
如果能让你好受点
If it means anything,

593
00:24:43,510 --> 00:24:45,070
这些事发生之后
I haven't gotten a good night's sleep

594
00:24:45,070 --> 00:24:47,330
我也没睡过好觉
since any of this happened either.

595
00:24:49,210 --> 00:24:51,410
也许我们今晚可以试着好好睡一觉
Maybe we can both give it a shot tonight.

596
00:25:00,990 --> 00:25:03,250
先从你开始吧  罗斯先生
Let's start with one for you, Mr. Ross.

597
00:25:03,290 --> 00:25:05,650
你离开律所时跟他关系很好  对吧
Were you on good terms with him when you left?

598
00:25:07,930 --> 00:25:09,540
-是的  -是吗
- Yes. - Oh.

599
00:25:09,930 --> 00:25:11,350
那在吉利斯工业收购案中
Well, then, why weren't you representing him

600
00:25:11,350 --> 00:25:12,980
你为什么没有代理他
on the Gillis Industries takeover?

601
00:25:12,980 --> 00:25:15,690
因为他当时严格来说不算我们的客户
Because he wasn't technically our client at the time.

602
00:25:16,040 --> 00:25:17,370
如果你俩关系那么好
Well, if you're on such good terms,

603
00:25:17,370 --> 00:25:18,710
他为什么不是你的客户
why wasn't he a client?

604
00:25:18,710 --> 00:25:20,750
兄弟偶尔也会闹别扭
Because sometimes brothers fight.

605
00:25:21,550 --> 00:25:24,440
有时他们会假装闹别扭
And sometimes they pretend to fight.

606
00:25:24,520 --> 00:25:25,640
你是什么意思
What are you getting at?

607
00:25:25,640 --> 00:25:27,590
我是说  收购案一开始
I'm getting at the fact that you supposedly

608
00:25:27,590 --> 00:25:29,050
你俩在闹别扭
were fighting when this thing started,

609
00:25:29,050 --> 00:25:31,660
可收购案结束时  你又说你们没闹别扭
yet you claim that you weren't fighting when it ended.

610
00:25:31,660 --> 00:25:33,500
谁说我们结束时没闹别扭了
Who says we weren't fighting when it ended?

611
00:25:33,500 --> 00:25:35,170
你  因为你重新雇佣了他
You did, when you hired him back.

612
00:25:35,170 --> 00:25:37,660
尽管是宿敌  达拉斯牛仔队还是
Yeah, and the Cowboys signed Deion Sanders,

613
00:25:37,660 --> 00:25:38,880
签下了迪昂·桑德斯[橄榄球星]
Even though they were rivals.

614
00:25:38,880 --> 00:25:40,040
你知道为什么吗
You want to know why?

615
00:25:40,040 --> 00:25:41,100
因为他是名出色的球员
'Cause he was awesome,

616
00:25:41,100 --> 00:25:43,670
牛仔队不想再让他断他们的球
and they were tired of him intercepting their passes.

617
00:25:43,670 --> 00:25:45,360
他可没帮你断球
He didn't intercept passes for you.

618
00:25:45,360 --> 00:25:46,450
他漏球了
He fumbled the ball.

619
00:25:46,450 --> 00:25:48,070
胡扯  他干得很出色[打出全垒打]
Bullshit. He hit it out of the park.

620
00:25:48,070 --> 00:25:49,520
你是在为谁工作
What park are you playing at?

621
00:25:49,520 --> 00:25:53,130
他力挺沃尔特·吉利斯  买了大量股份
He sides with Walter Gillis, buys a ton of shares,

622
00:25:53,130 --> 00:25:54,420
接着把可怜的沃尔特一脚踢开
then ditches poor Walter,

623
00:25:54,420 --> 00:25:55,930
然后从整件事里抽身而出
and then walks away from the whole thing.

624
00:25:55,930 --> 00:25:58,270
你怎么会想要雇佣这样的人
Why would you even want a guy like this on your team?

625
00:25:58,270 --> 00:25:59,170
我漏掉什么了吗
What am I missing?

626
00:25:59,170 --> 00:26:02,090
你漏掉了他第一次业务就非常出色
You're missing the fact that he kicked ass his first time out,

627
00:26:02,090 --> 00:26:03,540
能够拥有他是一种幸运
and anybody would be lucky to have him.

628
00:26:03,540 --> 00:26:05,560
那为什么没人要他
Then why didn't anybody take him?

629
00:26:06,440 --> 00:26:07,190
什么
What?

630
00:26:07,190 --> 00:26:09,730
我查过城里每家大律所
I checked with every major law firm in the city,

631
00:26:09,730 --> 00:26:11,850
没人收到过你的简历
and not one of them received a resume from you.

632
00:26:11,850 --> 00:26:14,750
为什么  因为显而易见
Why is that? Because it's clear as day.

633
00:26:14,750 --> 00:26:17,410
你在隐瞒什么  我告诉你是什么
You're hiding something, and I'll tell you what it is.

634
00:26:17,410 --> 00:26:19,460
你一直知道他会回来
It's because you always knew that he was coming back

635
00:26:19,460 --> 00:26:22,000
因为你俩一直在串通
because you and he were in this together the whole time.

636
00:26:22,000 --> 00:26:23,380
你这套理论的漏洞在于
The problem with your theory is

637
00:26:23,380 --> 00:26:25,090
我俩没有从这次所谓的合谋中
neither one of us got a nickel from this

638
00:26:25,090 --> 00:26:26,030
获利一分钱
alleged collusion,

639
00:26:26,030 --> 00:26:27,400
你没有证据
and you've got no proof we did.

640
00:26:27,400 --> 00:26:28,710
没错  你也永远找不到证据
Yeah, and you're never gonna find any,

641
00:26:28,710 --> 00:26:31,230
因为证据根本不存在
because it doesn't exist.

642
00:26:31,640 --> 00:26:33,910
这么说你俩都坚持没有从中
So you're both insisting that neither one of you

643
00:26:33,910 --> 00:26:34,980
获利一分钱
got any money?

644
00:26:34,980 --> 00:26:36,340
没错
Damn right.

645
00:26:36,340 --> 00:26:38,470
这说明获利的是别人
That tells me that someone else did.

646
00:26:42,380 --> 00:26:43,240
谢谢  先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.

647
00:26:43,240 --> 00:26:46,520
你们告诉了我该把火力集中到哪里
I believe you showed me where I should focus my manpower.

648
00:26:46,640 --> 00:26:48,410
那些文件中
Somewhere in those files

649
00:26:48,410 --> 00:26:50,710
有一笔从某处支付给某人的款项
there's a payment from somewhere to someone,

650
00:26:50,710 --> 00:26:51,920
我会找到它
and I'm gonna find it,

651
00:26:51,920 --> 00:26:54,470
别想在证监会眼皮底下藏钱
because you can't hide money from the S.E.C.

652
00:27:02,000 --> 00:27:03,640
混蛋
Son of a bitch.

653
00:27:06,120 --> 00:27:07,870
-你为什么不告诉我  -告诉你什么
- Why didn't you tell me? - Tell you what?

654
00:27:07,870 --> 00:27:10,430
路易跟傅滋曼做违法交易的事
About Louis making a dirty deal with Forstman.

655
00:27:10,430 --> 00:27:13,180
-他告诉你了  -他以为我早知道了
- He told you. - He thought I already knew.

656
00:27:13,330 --> 00:27:14,490
他知道了我们在交往
He found out we were together,

657
00:27:14,490 --> 00:27:17,780
和你不同  他认为情侣之间
and unlike you, he assumed that people in relationships

658
00:27:17,780 --> 00:27:19,000
不会隐瞒这种破事
share shit like that.

659
00:27:19,000 --> 00:27:20,660
那个该死的定时炸弹
Goddamn ticking time bomb.

660
00:27:20,660 --> 00:27:22,190
你知道自己在说什么吗
Do you hear yourself?

661
00:27:22,620 --> 00:27:25,670
我来这里是想谈咱俩的问题
I'm coming to you with a problem between you and me,

662
00:27:25,800 --> 00:27:27,110
可你却只关注路易
and you're focused on Louis.

663
00:27:27,110 --> 00:27:29,450
我关注他是因为他的行为
I'm focused on Louis because right now his actions

664
00:27:29,450 --> 00:27:30,620
正威胁到整个律所
threaten this entire firm.

665
00:27:30,620 --> 00:27:32,830
于是话题又回到一开始了
Which brings me right back to where we started.

666
00:27:32,830 --> 00:27:34,550
我问你为什么要抓伍德尔的把柄时
Why didn't you tell me about Louis

667
00:27:34,550 --> 00:27:37,830
你为什么不告诉我路易的事
when I asked you what the dirt on Woodall was for?

668
00:27:37,970 --> 00:27:39,240
我没告诉你
I didn't tell you

669
00:27:39,240 --> 00:27:40,720
是因为我不想让你
because I didn't want you in the position of

670
00:27:40,720 --> 00:27:42,950
在取证时为我撒谎
having to lie for me in a deposition.

671
00:27:44,310 --> 00:27:47,540
这够不够"关注咱俩的问题"
Is that "Focused on you and me" enough?

672
00:27:49,590 --> 00:27:50,880
杰西卡
Jessica...

673
00:27:52,140 --> 00:27:53,320
你什么时候才能明白
When are you gonna understand

674
00:27:53,320 --> 00:27:55,500
我能接受触犯法律
that I can handle crossing lines,

675
00:27:55,600 --> 00:27:58,050
但我不能接受你骗我
but I won't handle you lying to me?

676
00:27:59,780 --> 00:28:01,680
我们到底有多大麻烦
Now, how much trouble are we in?

677
00:28:01,830 --> 00:28:03,480
我也想知道
That's what I'm gonna find out.

678
00:28:10,020 --> 00:28:11,810
-路易  你看这个了吗  -没  什么东西
- Louis, did you see this? - No, what is it?

679
00:28:11,810 --> 00:28:14,080
卡荷尔对哈维和迈克的取证
It's Cahill's deposition with Harvey and Mike.

680
00:28:16,050 --> 00:28:17,620
直接看最后
Skip to the end.

681
00:28:20,360 --> 00:28:22,450
天啊  他鼻子跟猎犬一样灵
Jesus Christ, he's honing in like a bloodhound.

682
00:28:22,450 --> 00:28:24,120
查到我只是时间问题了
It's only a matter of time.

683
00:28:24,440 --> 00:28:25,610
肯定有办法把这个...
There's got to be a way we can get this filed--

684
00:28:25,610 --> 00:28:27,060
没办法了
There isn't.

685
00:28:27,060 --> 00:28:28,550
-路易  -我完了
- Louis. - I'm done.

686
00:28:32,990 --> 00:28:34,270
我完了
I'm done.

687
00:28:37,460 --> 00:28:38,880
而且如果我现在不做些什么
And if I don't do something now,

688
00:28:38,880 --> 00:28:40,530
哈维和迈克就也完了
So are Harvey and Mike.

689
00:28:41,290 --> 00:28:43,560
-你去哪  -去收拾我制造的残局
- Where are you going? - To finish what I started.

690
00:28:44,920 --> 00:28:46,290
-知道我在想什么吗  -什么
- You know what I think? - What?

691
00:28:46,290 --> 00:28:47,890
我在想  出庭作证时
I think we both could've used a better lawyer

692
00:28:47,890 --> 00:28:49,090
我们俩可以用更好点的律师
in that deposition.

693
00:28:49,090 --> 00:28:51,120
-你觉得很好玩吗  -不  不觉得
- You think this is funny? - No, I don't.

694
00:28:51,120 --> 00:28:52,840
那就帮我想办法
Then help me figure a way out,

695
00:28:52,840 --> 00:28:55,630
如果不那么做  他们就会发现路易的事
because if we don't, they're gonna find out about Louis,

696
00:28:55,630 --> 00:28:58,120
而卡荷尔给我们扣的帽子
and everything Cahill's been saying about us

697
00:28:58,120 --> 00:28:59,540
也会感觉越来越真
is gonna start looking true.

698
00:28:59,540 --> 00:29:01,780
我们不能让卡荷尔看那些文件了
We have to stop Cahill from going through those files.

699
00:29:01,780 --> 00:29:03,490
-我们已经试过了  -还得再试试
- We tried that. - we have to try again.

700
00:29:03,490 --> 00:29:06,190
我们得证明卡荷尔只调查这一个案子
We have to prove that Cahill is only on this investigation

701
00:29:06,190 --> 00:29:07,540
就因为伍德尔很讨厌你
because Woodall hates you.

702
00:29:07,540 --> 00:29:10,360
问题是我们不能证明他们之间有联系
The problem is we don't have a link between them.

703
00:29:10,360 --> 00:29:12,420
可他们却能证明杰西卡和马龙有联系
And they have a link between Jessica and Malone.

704
00:29:12,420 --> 00:29:15,130
所以我们必须让霍普金斯法官相信
So we'd have to convince Judge Hopkins

705
00:29:15,130 --> 00:29:18,080
他俩的恋情跟整件事毫无关系
Their relationship has nothing to do with this whole thing,

706
00:29:18,080 --> 00:29:21,120
而我们根本做不到
which... we'll never be able to do.

707
00:29:21,730 --> 00:29:23,480
他们怎么可能知道杰西卡和马龙的事呢
How do they even know about Jessica and Malone?

708
00:29:23,480 --> 00:29:25,000
不知道  肯定是马龙还在那工作的时候
I don't know. Someone at the S.E.C. 

709
00:29:25,000 --> 00:29:26,920
证监会的什么人看到他们在一起了
must've seen them together while Malone was still working there.

710
00:29:26,920 --> 00:29:28,190
看到他们牵手了吗
You think they were holding hands?

711
00:29:28,190 --> 00:29:30,380
拜托  哈维  我们说的可是杰西卡啊
Come on, Harvey, this is Jessica we're talking about.

712
00:29:30,380 --> 00:29:31,860
说我什么
Talking about me, what?

713
00:29:32,390 --> 00:29:33,940
我去  你说得对
Holy shit, you're right.

714
00:29:33,940 --> 00:29:35,810
她过结婚我都不知道
She was married, and I didn't even know it.

715
00:29:35,810 --> 00:29:37,800
卡荷尔没有授权却一直纠缠我们
Cahill had us followed without authorization.

716
00:29:37,800 --> 00:29:39,820
那么他追查政府公职人员
And there's no way he had authorization

717
00:29:39,820 --> 00:29:41,680
肯定也没有授权
to follow a government official.

718
00:29:42,140 --> 00:29:43,610
你得去见见他
You need to pay that man a visit.

719
00:29:43,610 --> 00:29:46,370
要去见他的人是我
I need to pay that man a visit.

720
00:29:49,750 --> 00:29:51,020
请进
Yep.

721
00:29:52,190 --> 00:29:54,130
抱歉  你可能还没听说
Oh, sorry, maybe you didn't hear the news.

722
00:29:54,130 --> 00:29:55,710
杰夫·马龙已经不在这工作了
Jeff Malone doesn't work here anymore.

723
00:29:55,710 --> 00:29:57,300
那么我猜你知道他在哪
And I'm guessing you know exactly where he is,

724
00:29:57,300 --> 00:29:58,840
因为你已经跟踪他好几个月了
since you've been following him for months.

725
00:29:58,840 --> 00:30:00,640
我从没跟踪过他
I haven't been following him at all.

726
00:30:00,660 --> 00:30:01,730
我追查的是你们
I've been following you.

727
00:30:01,730 --> 00:30:03,670
你查谁无关紧要
Well, it doesn't really matter who you followed,

728
00:30:03,670 --> 00:30:05,830
因为你不可能得到授权
since there's no way you got authorization.

729
00:30:05,830 --> 00:30:07,890
你认为霍普金斯法官
You think Judge Hopkins is going to look into

730
00:30:07,890 --> 00:30:09,480
会看着你迷离的棕色眼睛
those dreamy brown eyes of yours

731
00:30:09,480 --> 00:30:10,810
而因着迷放弃这个案子吗
and drop the case because of that?

732
00:30:10,810 --> 00:30:13,270
不  我认为你会放弃它
No, I think you're gonna drop it.

733
00:30:13,270 --> 00:30:15,240
因为否则
'Cause if you don't,

734
00:30:15,240 --> 00:30:17,250
那就不再是诬告那么简单了
it's no longer malicious prosecution.

735
00:30:17,250 --> 00:30:19,120
那是滥用职权
it's abuse of power.

736
00:30:19,120 --> 00:30:21,190
你对迈克·罗斯这么干过  也对我这么干过
You did it to Mike Ross, you did it to me.

737
00:30:21,190 --> 00:30:23,310
而我们会查出你还对谁这么干过
And we're gonna find out who else you did it to.

738
00:30:23,310 --> 00:30:24,440
你试试看吧
Take a shot.

739
00:30:24,440 --> 00:30:26,020
那么做会让你一个案子耗费两年时间
It'll take you two years to make a case.

740
00:30:26,020 --> 00:30:28,670
就算案子成立  我也只会得到轻微处罚
And even if it sticks, I'll get a slap on the wrist,

741
00:30:28,670 --> 00:30:31,030
而哈维·斯佩克特那时已经在坐牢了
but Harvey Specter will already be in prison.

742
00:30:31,030 --> 00:30:32,950
你这个下流的混账
You dirty son of a bitch.

743
00:30:33,400 --> 00:30:34,660
下流
Dirty?

744
00:30:34,940 --> 00:30:37,520
我也许违规了  但我那么做是因为你有罪
I may bend the rules, but I'm doing it because you are guilty.

745
00:30:37,520 --> 00:30:39,310
我们让他屁滚尿流之前
That's exactly what Eric Woodall said

746
00:30:39,310 --> 00:30:41,170
埃里克·伍德尔也说过一样的话
before we got his ass fired.

747
00:30:41,170 --> 00:30:42,520
跟哈维说过的话  我再跟你说一遍
Well, I'll tell you what I told Harvey.

748
00:30:42,520 --> 00:30:43,820
我不是埃里克·伍德尔
I'm not Eric Woodall,

749
00:30:43,820 --> 00:30:45,560
派那个叫路易·利特的人
and sending some guy named Louis Litt

750
00:30:45,560 --> 00:30:48,180
来承认一些编造出来的屁话
to confess to some fabricated bullshit

751
00:30:48,180 --> 00:30:49,780
是不会让我住手的
isn't gonna make me stop.

752
00:30:49,900 --> 00:30:51,790
反而会让我更努力地追查下去
It's gonna make me come at you harder.

753
00:30:59,460 --> 00:31:01,510
也许没消息就是好消息
Maybe no news is good news.

754
00:31:02,940 --> 00:31:05,470
好吧  没消息也有可能是坏消息
All right, maybe no news means bad news.

755
00:31:05,990 --> 00:31:09,090
发生在杰西卡身上  没消息就是没消息
When it comes to Jessica, no news is no news.

756
00:31:09,500 --> 00:31:10,960
哈维  有空吗
Harvey, you have a minute?

757
00:31:10,960 --> 00:31:12,460
你想干嘛  路易
What do you want, Louis?

758
00:31:12,800 --> 00:31:14,610
我想跟你单独说
I'd prefer to tell you alone.

759
00:31:14,610 --> 00:31:16,940
迈克什么都知道  尽管说吧
Mike knows everything, so spit it out.

760
00:31:16,940 --> 00:31:19,300
好吧  我觉得你俩应该明白
Okay, um, but I think you both should know

761
00:31:19,300 --> 00:31:21,160
不管我身上发生了什么事
that whatever happens to me,

762
00:31:21,320 --> 00:31:23,730
我都是很有尊严地来这  像个男人一样说出来
I had the dignity to come to you and tell you like a man.

763
00:31:23,730 --> 00:31:24,520
你干了什么
What did you do? 

764
00:31:24,520 --> 00:31:26,290
他干了我明确告诉他不可以做的事
He did exactly what I told him not to do.

765
00:31:26,290 --> 00:31:28,890
他去了证监会  供认了一切
He went to the S.E.C., and he confessed.

766
00:31:28,890 --> 00:31:30,020
杰西卡  等等  拜托
Wait, Jessica, please.

767
00:31:30,020 --> 00:31:31,860
拜托什么  别杀你吗
Please what? Don't kill you?

768
00:31:31,860 --> 00:31:33,540
因为有一件事是板上定钉的
Because one thing is for sure.

769
00:31:33,540 --> 00:31:36,500
当一切结束之后  我会把你炒掉
When all this is over, I'm gonna fire the shit out of you.

770
00:31:36,500 --> 00:31:37,800
炒我
Fire me?

771
00:31:38,470 --> 00:31:40,220
你应该感谢我
You should be thanking me.

772
00:31:40,220 --> 00:31:41,710
我读了文录
I read the transcript.

773
00:31:41,710 --> 00:31:44,100
卡荷尔知道被隐匿的交易
Cahill knows about the hidden payment.

774
00:31:44,100 --> 00:31:46,060
我去把你们都救下来了
I went there to save all of you!

775
00:31:46,060 --> 00:31:48,670
我也告诉过你  如果你那么做
And I told you the second you did that,

776
00:31:48,670 --> 00:31:51,020
他们俩就从或许无罪
these two go from being probably innocent

777
00:31:51,020 --> 00:31:52,660
变成绝对有罪
to definitely guilty.

778
00:31:52,660 --> 00:31:53,830
天大的傻瓜
Goddamn idiot. 

779
00:31:53,830 --> 00:31:55,270
等一下  我们...
Wait a second. We--

780
00:31:55,820 --> 00:31:57,970
路易  你去认罪了  为什么还能站在这
Louis, if you confessed, then why are you here?

781
00:31:57,970 --> 00:31:58,930
他们让我回家了
They sent me home. 

782
00:31:58,930 --> 00:31:59,780
什么
What?

783
00:31:59,780 --> 00:32:01,210
你到底跟卡荷尔说了什么
What exactly did you say to Cahill?

784
00:32:01,210 --> 00:32:02,420
我没跟卡荷尔谈
I didn't talk to Cahill.

785
00:32:02,420 --> 00:32:03,680
我去了他的办公室
I mean, I was in his office,

786
00:32:03,680 --> 00:32:06,210
可埃里克·伍德尔进来了  带我去了大厅
but then Eric Woodall comes in, takes me down the hall.

787
00:32:06,210 --> 00:32:07,390
我跟他坦白的
I confessed to him.

788
00:32:07,390 --> 00:32:09,150
你跟证监会的头头承认
You told the head of the S.E.C.

789
00:32:09,150 --> 00:32:11,770
自己犯了罪  他居然让你走了
you committed a federal crime, and he sent you on your way?

790
00:32:11,770 --> 00:32:13,990
-是的  -他没要你把哈维牵连进来吗
- Yes. - And he didn't try to get you to implicate Harvey?

791
00:32:13,990 --> 00:32:15,050
其实  没有
No, in fact,

792
00:32:15,050 --> 00:32:16,200
他好像一点也不在乎
he didn't seem to care at all.

793
00:32:16,200 --> 00:32:18,790
你跟他明确说了跟傅滋曼的交易吗
And you specifically told him about your deal with Forstman?

794
00:32:18,790 --> 00:32:21,300
是的  他说他们对我这样的小鱼小虾没兴趣
Yeah. He said they're not interested in little fish like me.

795
00:32:21,300 --> 00:32:23,000
对他来说也许你是小鱼小虾
You might be a little fish to him,

796
00:32:23,000 --> 00:32:25,120
但傅滋曼对他绝对是头巨鲸
but Forstman is a goddamn whale.

797
00:32:25,120 --> 00:32:25,950
都不重要
It doesn't matter.

798
00:32:25,950 --> 00:32:27,710
伍德尔恨我  我才是他想要的
Woodall hates me: I'm the one he wants.

799
00:32:27,710 --> 00:32:30,190
可为什么不用傅滋曼来钓你
But why not use Forstman to reel you in

800
00:32:30,190 --> 00:32:32,170
达到一箭双雕的效果呢
and get two for the price of one?

801
00:32:32,510 --> 00:32:33,490
除非是有什么
Unless for some reason

802
00:32:33,490 --> 00:32:36,050
伍德尔不愿拖傅滋曼下水的理由
Woodall doesn't want to drag Forstman into this.

803
00:32:36,980 --> 00:32:38,620
因为他们同穿一条裤子
Because they're in bed together.

804
00:32:39,300 --> 00:32:40,430
这可是很大的飞跃
That's a big leap.

805
00:32:40,430 --> 00:32:41,860
哈维  你说你跟傅滋曼说
Harvey, you said you told Forstman

806
00:32:41,860 --> 00:32:43,170
证监会在追究他
the S.E.C. was on his ass, 

807
00:32:43,170 --> 00:32:45,310
他却表现出一副金刚护体的样子
and he acted like he was wearing a teflon suit.

808
00:32:45,310 --> 00:32:47,020
他对我也是那幅德性
He acted the same way with me.

809
00:32:47,020 --> 00:32:48,850
而一个混混之所以表现出一副无敌的样子
And when assholes act invincible,

810
00:32:48,850 --> 00:32:50,430
是因为他们认为自己确实无敌
it's because they think they are.

811
00:32:50,430 --> 00:32:52,270
这是唯一说得通的解释
It's the only thing that makes sense.

812
00:32:52,410 --> 00:32:54,560
你们俩去找证据证明他们之间有联系
You two find the link between those two,

813
00:32:54,560 --> 00:32:56,390
今晚就要找到
and find it tonight.

814
00:33:10,540 --> 00:33:11,890
这个可能有用
This could be something.

815
00:33:12,630 --> 00:33:13,890
看
Look.

816
00:33:14,350 --> 00:33:16,260
去年四月
In April of last year,

817
00:33:16,260 --> 00:33:20,410
查尔斯·傅滋曼给这三个参议员捐了一大笔钱
Charles Forstman made huge contributions to these three senators.

818
00:33:21,820 --> 00:33:23,250
那又怎么样  他有的是钱可烧
So what? He's got money to burn.

819
00:33:23,250 --> 00:33:24,340
没错  但四周之后
Yeah, but four weeks later,

820
00:33:24,340 --> 00:33:26,530
这三个参议员指名埃里克·伍德尔
these same senators helped appoint Eric Woodall

821
00:33:26,530 --> 00:33:28,620
当上了证监会纽约办公室的一把手
to head the New York office of the S.E.C.

822
00:33:28,620 --> 00:33:29,980
这不能证明傅滋曼和伍德尔
That doesn't prove a direct link

823
00:33:29,980 --> 00:33:31,240
有直接联系
between Forstman and Woodall.

824
00:33:31,240 --> 00:33:32,890
但还是有联系啊  哈维  
It's still a link, Harvey. 

825
00:33:32,890 --> 00:33:34,070
这种事情就是这样
And it's how this shit works.

826
00:33:34,070 --> 00:33:36,270
完全合法  对我们没有帮助
It's totally legal, and it's not gonna do a thing for us.

827
00:33:36,270 --> 00:33:37,160
那你想要什么
Well, what do you want?

828
00:33:37,160 --> 00:33:39,330
他递了一袋子钱给伍德尔的照片吗
A picture of him handing Woodall a bag of money?

829
00:33:39,330 --> 00:33:40,680
我们永远也搞不到的
Because we're never gonna get that.

830
00:33:40,680 --> 00:33:42,030
也许不需要
Maybe we don't need it.

831
00:33:43,340 --> 00:33:45,430
你最好有什么好消息
You better be here with something good.

832
00:33:49,660 --> 00:33:50,940
我有
I am.

833
00:33:52,150 --> 00:33:54,380
查尔斯·傅滋曼硬塞给我一百万美金
Charles Forstman made me take a million dollars

834
00:33:54,380 --> 00:33:56,040
以防我背叛他
to keep from turning on him.

835
00:33:56,040 --> 00:33:58,180
如果他对伍德尔也用过这招呢
What if he made Woodall take a taste too?

836
00:33:58,580 --> 00:33:59,710
你认为我们想不到吗
You think we don't know that?

837
00:33:59,710 --> 00:34:01,280
又回到一袋子钱的问题上了
That's the "Bag of money" Problem.

838
00:34:01,280 --> 00:34:02,520
不会是一袋子钱
It wouldn't be a bag of money,

839
00:34:02,520 --> 00:34:03,520
因为如果那笔钱无从追踪
because if it's untraceable,

840
00:34:03,520 --> 00:34:04,890
他就无法要挟伍德尔了
he wouldn't have leverage over Woodall.

841
00:34:04,890 --> 00:34:07,140
说得对  但是我们是不可能
That's great, but we can't get access

842
00:34:07,140 --> 00:34:08,220
查看伍德尔的银行账户的
to Woodall's bank accounts.

843
00:34:08,220 --> 00:34:09,490
我们确实不能
We can't.

844
00:34:09,990 --> 00:34:11,040
但卡荷尔可以
But Cahill can.

845
00:34:11,040 --> 00:34:12,690
好吧  那又有什么用呢
Okay, what good does that do us, huh?

846
00:34:12,690 --> 00:34:14,710
-他们是一伙的  -如果不是呢
- They're together. - What if they're not?

847
00:34:17,550 --> 00:34:19,350
我告诉过你  我去见卡荷尔
I told you, I went to see Cahill.

848
00:34:19,350 --> 00:34:20,570
他不在
He wasn't there.

849
00:34:20,570 --> 00:34:22,360
五分钟之后埃里克·伍德尔来了
Five minutes later, Eric Woodall shows up.

850
00:34:22,360 --> 00:34:24,090
我只说了一句  "查尔斯·傅滋曼"
I say two words: "Charles Forstman".

851
00:34:24,090 --> 00:34:26,030
他就催着我出去  好像我是他的情妇
He hustles me outta there like I'm his mistress

852
00:34:26,030 --> 00:34:27,870
而他老婆正开车进门似的
with his wife coming up the driveway.

853
00:34:27,870 --> 00:34:30,950
他为什么不等卡荷尔呢
Why would he not wait for Cahill?

854
00:34:31,150 --> 00:34:33,620
你想让我们说服卡荷尔把矛头指向伍德尔
You want us to get Cahill to turn on Woodall.

855
00:34:33,620 --> 00:34:34,960
说得没错
Damn right I do.

856
00:34:34,960 --> 00:34:36,150
也许路易说得对
Maybe Louis is right.

857
00:34:36,150 --> 00:34:38,320
也许伍德尔越过了一条卡荷尔不愿意
Maybe there are lines that Woodall's willing to cross

858
00:34:38,320 --> 00:34:39,500
越过的底线
that Cahill won't.

859
00:34:39,500 --> 00:34:40,850
这"也许"得太大胆了
That's a big "Maybe."

860
00:34:41,530 --> 00:34:42,990
你有更好的办法吗
You have a better idea?

861
00:34:43,570 --> 00:34:44,990
没有
No, I don't.

862
00:34:45,600 --> 00:34:49,340
你们也知道这事之后杰西卡就会炒了我
Look, guys, we all know that Jessica's gonna fire me after this.

863
00:34:51,250 --> 00:34:52,710
我只是想帮点忙
I just want to help,

864
00:34:53,180 --> 00:34:54,570
纠正错误
make things right.

865
00:34:58,250 --> 00:34:59,640
去穿外套
Get your coat.

866
00:35:07,450 --> 00:35:10,090
你真的都是自己看这些文件的吗
You really looking through those all by yourself?

867
00:35:10,490 --> 00:35:12,110
各位东镇女巫是来教我
Are the witches of Eastwick here to tell me

868
00:35:12,110 --> 00:35:13,450
如何管理我的部门吗
how to run my department?

869
00:35:13,450 --> 00:35:15,650
我们是来帮你减轻负担的
We're here to make things easier for you.

870
00:35:15,920 --> 00:35:19,610
这些盒子里头有一份这个文件的副本
Buried in one of these boxes is a copy of this.

871
00:35:20,090 --> 00:35:21,480
能证明有合谋罪
It proves collusion.

872
00:35:21,480 --> 00:35:23,170
不是我和迈克
Not between me and Mike.

873
00:35:23,490 --> 00:35:26,340
是他和查尔斯·傅滋曼勾结
Between him and Charles Forstman.

874
00:35:26,340 --> 00:35:27,730
你就直接送给我了  是吗
And you're just gonna give this to me?

875
00:35:27,730 --> 00:35:28,610
对
Yup.

876
00:35:28,610 --> 00:35:29,760
你还要给伍德尔
And you're gonna give it to Woodall,

877
00:35:29,760 --> 00:35:31,020
看看他会说什么
and we're gonna see what he says.

878
00:35:31,020 --> 00:35:33,330
他会说他根本不在乎什么
And what he's gonna say is that he doesn't give a shit

879
00:35:33,330 --> 00:35:34,460
查尔斯·傅滋曼
about Charles Forstman,

880
00:35:34,460 --> 00:35:36,240
就跟我向他认罪时  他说的一样
just like he told me when I confessed to him.

881
00:35:36,240 --> 00:35:37,440
你们到底在暗示什么
What exactly are you implying?

882
00:35:37,440 --> 00:35:38,450
我们没暗示什么
We're not implying anything.

883
00:35:38,450 --> 00:35:40,880
我们在告诉你  伍德尔失去工作后
We're telling you that after Woodall lost his job,

884
00:35:40,880 --> 00:35:43,200
傅滋曼把他安排到了证监会
Forstman got him installed at the S.E.C.,

885
00:35:43,200 --> 00:35:46,380
作为回报  他只需保护傅滋曼
and all he had to do in return was protect Forstman.

886
00:35:46,380 --> 00:35:47,400
证据在哪里
Where's the proof?

887
00:35:47,400 --> 00:35:48,980
在埃里克·伍德尔的银行账户里
In Eric Woodall's bank accounts.

888
00:35:48,980 --> 00:35:50,960
所以你是要我根据你的说法
Oh, so you want me to go through his bank accounts

889
00:35:50,960 --> 00:35:52,230
去查他的银行账户
based on your word.

890
00:35:52,230 --> 00:35:54,230
你听了他的鬼话  就来查我们了啊
You followed us based on his bullshit.

891
00:35:54,230 --> 00:35:55,620
那是我朋友的要求
Based on the word of my friend.

892
00:35:55,620 --> 00:35:57,550
你为什么不问问你朋友  他肯不肯
Why don't you ask your friend if he has a problem

893
00:35:57,550 --> 00:35:59,120
让你查他的账户
giving you access to his accounts?

894
00:35:59,120 --> 00:36:00,480
如果他不肯  那我们就错了
If he doesn't, then we're wrong,

895
00:36:00,480 --> 00:36:02,320
我们刚把铁证交给你
and we've just handed you the smoking gun.

896
00:36:02,320 --> 00:36:04,410
如果你们是对的  你们想让我
And if you're right, you want me to let him

897
00:36:04,410 --> 00:36:05,740
让他免受惩罚
off the hook for what he did.

898
00:36:05,740 --> 00:36:07,940
伍德尔已经说了他只是条小鱼
Woodall already said he's a little fish.

899
00:36:07,940 --> 00:36:10,500
我们只是想请你把他丢回水里去
We're asking you to throw him back in the water.

900
00:36:10,880 --> 00:36:12,050
这里在干什么
What the hell's going on in here?

901
00:36:12,050 --> 00:36:13,010
埃里克
Hey, Eric.

902
00:36:13,010 --> 00:36:14,030
很高兴又见到你
It's good to see you again.

903
00:36:14,030 --> 00:36:15,800
肖恩  这下我们人齐了不是很好嘛
Sean, isn't this great that we're all together?

904
00:36:15,800 --> 00:36:17,080
你看到我进来了吗
Did you see me come in?

905
00:36:17,600 --> 00:36:18,950
担心我会说什么吗
Afraid of what I'd say?

906
00:36:18,950 --> 00:36:20,960
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.

907
00:36:20,960 --> 00:36:22,650
埃里克  这几位先生们过来
Eric, these gentlemen came in here

908
00:36:22,650 --> 00:36:24,120
提出了疯狂的指控
with these wild accusations

909
00:36:24,120 --> 00:36:26,310
说你和查尔斯·傅滋曼串通一气
that you and Charles Forstman are in bed together.

910
00:36:26,310 --> 00:36:28,810
掉在傅滋曼的钱窝里了
A bed filled with Forstman's money.

911
00:36:29,930 --> 00:36:32,740
没错  查尔斯·傅滋曼给了我几百万美元
Yes, Charles Forstman gave me millions of dollars.

912
00:36:32,740 --> 00:36:34,490
所以我才会只开着一辆斯巴鲁
That's why I drive a Subaru.

913
00:36:34,490 --> 00:36:36,400
是啊  我也没花他给我的钱
Yeah, I didn't spend the money he gave me either.

914
00:36:36,400 --> 00:36:37,860
但那不意味着他没逼我拿钱
That doesn't mean he didn't make me take it.

915
00:36:37,860 --> 00:36:39,830
我才不管呢  我又不是你
I don't give a shit. I'm not you.

916
00:36:39,830 --> 00:36:42,360
埃里克  这些指控太不可理喻了
Eric, obviously these allegations are crazy.

917
00:36:42,360 --> 00:36:43,670
当然
Of course they are.

918
00:36:43,670 --> 00:36:45,100
那就...
So just...

919
00:36:46,500 --> 00:36:48,600
向他们证明你光明磊落  无需隐藏
prove it to 'em you've got nothing to hide.

920
00:36:53,280 --> 00:36:54,780
太可笑了
This is ridiculous.

921
00:36:55,000 --> 00:36:57,960
我  不会给他们面子...
I...am not gonna dignify...

922
00:37:02,790 --> 00:37:04,250
我是你上司
I'm your boss.

923
00:37:06,480 --> 00:37:07,900
先生们  给我一分钟
Gentlemen, give me a minute.

924
00:37:07,900 --> 00:37:09,160
好
Yep.

925
00:37:10,940 --> 00:37:13,720
他的一分钟  指的是10到15年
And by a minute, he means 10 to 15 years.

926
00:37:15,570 --> 00:37:17,300
半小时后  你将需要一位
In about a half an hour, you're gonna need

927
00:37:17,300 --> 00:37:19,100
非常厉害的律师
a really good lawyer.

928
00:37:19,310 --> 00:37:20,890
到那时候
And when that happens,

929
00:37:21,200 --> 00:37:22,550
可别找我
don't call me.

930
00:37:35,190 --> 00:37:36,770
你觉得伍德尔会找哪个律师
Which lawyer do you think Woodall called?

931
00:37:36,770 --> 00:37:39,250
如果他够聪明  他应该找丹尼尔·哈德曼
Well, if he was smart, he would call Daniel Hardman.

932
00:37:39,250 --> 00:37:41,570
最适合为罪犯辩护的人  是另一个罪犯
The best person to defend a criminal is a criminal.

933
00:37:41,570 --> 00:37:43,540
哈德曼是一位比你优秀得多的律师
And Hardman's a much better lawyer than you anyways.

934
00:37:43,540 --> 00:37:45,370
真好笑
Oh, very funny.

935
00:37:46,640 --> 00:37:47,900
谢谢
Thank you.

936
00:37:48,090 --> 00:37:49,560
谢谢  路易
Thank you, Louis.

937
00:38:00,880 --> 00:38:02,230
拜托了
Please.

938
00:38:02,620 --> 00:38:03,930
我会尽力的
I'll try.

939
00:38:11,520 --> 00:38:13,250
唐娜说她已经跟你说过了
Donna told me she already said this to you,

940
00:38:13,250 --> 00:38:14,870
但我还是想亲口跟你说
but I want you to hear it from me.

941
00:38:16,370 --> 00:38:18,720
如果不是路易  我不可能回来
I wouldn't be back here if it wasn't for Louis.

942
00:38:21,210 --> 00:38:22,660
我来解决
I'll take care of it.

943
00:38:30,530 --> 00:38:33,850
搞定伍德尔了  其他事也都解决了
Woodall's taken care of, and so is everything else.

944
00:38:33,850 --> 00:38:35,820
-不是所有事  -杰西卡
- Not everything. - Jessica--

945
00:38:35,820 --> 00:38:38,860
哈维  我已经决定了
Harvey, I've already made up my mind.

946
00:38:38,860 --> 00:38:41,650
你不在场  他帮我们摆脱了困境
You weren't there. He helped get us out of this.

947
00:38:41,650 --> 00:38:43,110
是他把我们拖入泥潭的
After he put us goddamn in it.

948
00:38:43,110 --> 00:38:45,160
我也曾害我们深陷泥潭
And I put us in it just as much,

949
00:38:45,160 --> 00:38:47,300
我雇用迈克·罗斯那天就是
the day I hired Mike Ross.

950
00:38:47,360 --> 00:38:48,980
你是想救路易
Are you looking to save Louis,

951
00:38:48,980 --> 00:38:50,800
还是也想被炒了
or to get yourself fired too?

952
00:38:50,800 --> 00:38:52,910
我是说他确实捅了篓子
I'm saying he did some bad shit,

953
00:38:52,910 --> 00:38:55,290
但我也有过  你也有过
but so have I, and so have you.

954
00:38:55,290 --> 00:38:57,780
但你我可没有搞砸
You and I don't mess shit up.

955
00:38:57,780 --> 00:38:58,770
我们都及时补救了
We fix it.

956
00:38:58,770 --> 00:39:00,190
他今天也是这样做的
Which is what he did today.

957
00:39:00,190 --> 00:39:02,000
你想聊聊他做了什么吗
You want to talk about what he did?

958
00:39:02,200 --> 00:39:04,800
我让他别去认罪  他却直接跑到证监会
I told him not to confess, and he went straight down

959
00:39:04,800 --> 00:39:07,280
像个告密的小婊子
to the S.E.C., and he sang like a canary,

960
00:39:07,280 --> 00:39:09,440
之前他也是那样去找杰夫·马龙的
after he did the same thing with Jeff Malone.

961
00:39:09,440 --> 00:39:11,120
-那不...  -不什么
- That doesn't-- - Doesn't what?

962
00:39:11,120 --> 00:39:13,110
那还只是冰山一角
That's just the tip of the iceberg.

963
00:39:13,380 --> 00:39:15,230
再来说说他的辉煌历史
Let's talk about his greatest hits.

964
00:39:16,160 --> 00:39:19,640
去年  他毁了我们的合并谈判
Last year, he blew up our merger negotiations

965
00:39:19,640 --> 00:39:21,580
就因为一只猫
because of a cat.

966
00:39:21,580 --> 00:39:25,130
今年  他指引迈克·罗斯去找查尔斯·傅滋曼
This year, he led Mike Ross straight to Charles Forstman.

967
00:39:25,130 --> 00:39:26,710
在我明确叮嘱他不准之后
He unwound the Wexler shares

968
00:39:26,720 --> 00:39:28,730
他还是放出了韦克斯勒股份
after I specifically told him not to,

969
00:39:28,730 --> 00:39:30,460
最厉害的是
and to top it all off,

970
00:39:30,460 --> 00:39:33,400
他拿了一百万美元回扣  进行了税务欺诈
He took a million-dollar payout to commit tax fraud

971
00:39:33,400 --> 00:39:36,060
那可能会让你吃十年牢饭
that could've landed you ten years in jail.

972
00:39:36,060 --> 00:39:38,410
直到一切都太晚之后他才告诉我们
And he didn't tell us about that until it was too late,

973
00:39:38,410 --> 00:39:40,750
他那样做只是因为不得不这样做
and he only did that because he had to.

974
00:39:40,950 --> 00:39:42,180
我还是不愿意
I'm still not doin' it.

975
00:39:42,180 --> 00:39:43,400
我让他做什么事
I tell him to do something,

976
00:39:43,400 --> 00:39:45,790
他就是不照办
and he never goddamn does it.

977
00:39:47,710 --> 00:39:49,970
现在我告诉自己要做一件事
Now, I told myself I'm gonna do something.

978
00:39:50,560 --> 00:39:52,320
我就一定要做
and I'm gonna goddamn do it.

979
00:39:57,300 --> 00:39:58,810
那就让我来吧
Then let me do it.

980
00:40:03,720 --> 00:40:05,320
为什么要让你去而不是我
Why you and not me?

981
00:40:05,320 --> 00:40:07,630
因为你想表达的是
Because you want to deliver the message

982
00:40:07,640 --> 00:40:09,910
"我们不再需要他了"
"His services are no longer needed,"

983
00:40:10,800 --> 00:40:12,560
而我要跟他说的是"再见"
and I want to tell him "Good-bye."

984
00:40:13,120 --> 00:40:14,820
你真打算去说吗
You're really going to do this?

985
00:40:29,210 --> 00:40:31,330
哈维  这里是他仅有的一切
Harvey, this place is all he has.

986
00:40:31,940 --> 00:40:33,230
我知道
I know.

987
00:40:36,130 --> 00:40:37,580
我跟你一起去
I'm coming with you.

988
00:40:47,070 --> 00:40:48,750
亲爱的哈维和杰西卡
Dear Harvey and Jessica,

989
00:40:49,700 --> 00:40:50,800
作为男人
there comes a time

990
00:40:50,800 --> 00:40:53,170
都有照照镜子  审视自我
when a man must look at himself in the mirror,

991
00:40:53,610 --> 00:40:56,970
而不是等别人来评判自己的时刻
to judge himself instead of waiting to be judged by others.

992
00:40:57,490 --> 00:40:59,720
对我而言  这个时刻到了
And for me, that time is now.

993
00:41:01,110 --> 00:41:02,920
你们都知道  我刚从法学院毕业
You both know I came to Pearson Specter

994
00:41:02,920 --> 00:41:05,780
就来到皮尔逊-斯佩克特  但你们也许不知道的是
right out of law school, but what you may not know is

995
00:41:06,320 --> 00:41:08,480
这是我唯一工作过的地方
this is the only place I've ever worked.

996
00:41:09,510 --> 00:41:12,030
也是我唯一想工作的地方
It's the only place I've ever wanted to work.

997
00:41:13,350 --> 00:41:14,790
这里是我的生活
It is my life...

998
00:41:15,920 --> 00:41:17,390
是我的家
It is my home...

999
00:41:18,610 --> 00:41:21,500
在这里工作的人  是我的家人
And the people that work here are my family.

1000
00:41:22,130 --> 00:41:23,810
你们就像我的父母
You're like my parents.

1001
00:41:24,160 --> 00:41:26,140
而合伙人们就像我的兄弟
And the partners, they're like my brothers,

1002
00:41:26,140 --> 00:41:29,500
我手下的律师们  就像我的孩子
and associates under my care are like my children.

1003
00:41:29,500 --> 00:41:31,370
我很愧于承认  但是
And I'm ashamed to admit it, but...

1004
00:41:31,560 --> 00:41:34,620
我确实为了个人利益  害你们身陷危急
I put all of you in jeopardy for my own personal gain.

1005
00:41:35,310 --> 00:41:36,970
我告诉自己那是为了更大的利益
I told myself it was for the greater good,

1006
00:41:36,970 --> 00:41:38,910
但实际上  我只是想
but the truth is I just wanted to feel

1007
00:41:38,910 --> 00:41:41,300
与你们平起平坐  我...
on the same level as both of you, I...

1008
00:41:42,660 --> 00:41:44,730
我再也不能否认这点
I can deny that no longer.

1009
00:41:44,730 --> 00:41:47,500
也不能再原谅我的行为
I can excuse my actions no longer.

1010
00:41:47,810 --> 00:41:49,640
尽管我们过去几年一直有分歧
Although we've had our differences over the years,

1011
00:41:49,640 --> 00:41:53,230
但你们依然是我最尊敬的两个人
there are no two people I respect more.

1012
00:41:53,550 --> 00:41:55,870
你们能做命名合伙人是有原因的
Your names are on the wall for a reason,

1013
00:41:56,310 --> 00:41:58,620
而我不能做  也是有原因的
and mine is not for a reason.

1014
00:41:59,410 --> 00:42:01,750
我不愿让你们任何一人
And I refuse to put either one of you 

1015
00:42:01,750 --> 00:42:03,850
承受开除员工的痛苦
through the pain of having a fire.

1016
00:42:03,920 --> 00:42:05,970
所以  立刻生效
So ... effective immediately,

1017
00:42:06,360 --> 00:42:08,630
我  路易·利特
I, Louis Litt,

1018
00:42:09,370 --> 00:42:11,700
从皮尔逊-斯佩克特辞职
am resigning from Pearson Specter.

1019
00:42:12,430 --> 00:42:14,300
请照看好我的家
Please take care of my home.

