1
00:05:41,790 --> 00:05:46,790
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:05:41,790 --> 00:05:46,790
{\an2}{\pos(70,258)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:05:41,790 --> 00:05:46,790
{\an2}{\pos(60,248)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:05:41,790 --> 00:05:46,790
{\an2}{\pos(86,258)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:05:41,790 --> 00:05:46,790
{\an5}{\pos(240,242)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为

6
00:05:46,790 --> 00:05:51,790
{\an8}翻译：草草   潇湘月影   某豚   王大可   香茗小焙   某羽   CS漫画家小明   

7
00:05:51,790 --> 00:05:56,790
{\an8}翻译：CiciXT   鱼小姐啦   校对：油炸电风扇    贺天天    潇湘月影

8
00:05:56,790 --> 00:06:01,790
{\an8}时间轴：凭陵新月   今    阿丹   小式

9
00:06:01,790 --> 00:06:06,790
{\an8}后期：斯人爱死小西装  加森      总监&精校：某羽

10
00:06:07,610 --> 00:06:09,790
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,73.91)}诉 讼 双 雄

11
00:06:07,610 --> 00:06:09,790
{\an8}{\pos(186.305,179.043)}第四季   第二集

12
00:00:01,030 --> 00:00:02,450
{\pos(189,213)}《诉讼双雄》前情提要

13
00:00:02,450 --> 00:00:04,730
我想要的就是在皮尔逊-斯佩克特工作
What I want is to work at Pearson Specter

14
00:00:04,730 --> 00:00:05,670
而且和你在一起
and to keep seeing you.

15
00:00:05,670 --> 00:00:07,360
这两者不能兼得
Those two things are not both gonna happen.

16
00:00:07,360 --> 00:00:08,480
你来这里三个月了
You've been here for three months.

17
00:00:08,480 --> 00:00:10,930
你所做的都只是安打而已  我需要全垒打
All you've done is hit singles, and I need a goddamn home run.

18
00:00:10,930 --> 00:00:11,990
-乔纳森  听我说  -我不想听
- Jonathan, listen. - I don't want to hear it.

19
00:00:11,990 --> 00:00:13,520
好好赚点大钱吧
Start making us some real money.

20
00:00:13,520 --> 00:00:15,210
沃尔特·吉利斯那样的人
A man like Walter Gillis

21
00:00:15,210 --> 00:00:16,900
才不会听你的这样的人
isn't gonna listen to a guy like you

22
00:00:16,900 --> 00:00:19,650
用阳光彩虹来挽救他
offering to save him with sunshine and rainbows.

23
00:00:19,710 --> 00:00:20,230
沃尔特
Walter...

24
00:00:20,230 --> 00:00:21,820
我不能保证我们会赢
I can't guarantee you we'll win,

25
00:00:22,270 --> 00:00:25,330
但我能保证我永远不会出卖你
but I can guarantee you that I will never sell you out.

26
00:00:25,820 --> 00:00:26,970
好的  我加入
All right, I'm in.

27
00:00:27,000 --> 00:00:28,510
你想进行恶意收购
You're talking hostile takeover.

28
00:00:28,510 --> 00:00:29,650
吉利斯工业
Gillis Industries.

29
00:00:29,650 --> 00:00:30,820
洛根  我们有冲突
Logan, we have a conflict.

30
00:00:30,820 --> 00:00:32,270
你我要么为敌  要么为友
You're either with me or against me.

31
00:00:32,270 --> 00:00:34,690
这还算上我十亿美元的生意
That includes all $1 billion of my business.

32
00:00:34,690 --> 00:00:37,870
为洛根·桑德斯起草一份投标报价书
Get moving on drawing up a tender offer for Logan Sanders.

33
00:00:37,900 --> 00:00:39,580
你记得我告诉过你  我...
Do you remember when I told you that I...

34
00:00:39,720 --> 00:00:41,750
我曾经跟一个有妇之夫偷情吗
that I once had an affair with a married man?

35
00:00:42,680 --> 00:00:43,880
就是他
It was him.

36
00:00:48,550 --> 00:00:49,740
你起得好早啊
You're up early.

37
00:00:50,430 --> 00:00:51,420
你也是
So are you.

38
00:00:51,590 --> 00:00:54,220
我是没办法  你不用啊
Well, I have to be. You don't.

39
00:00:54,220 --> 00:00:57,730
我本来就醒了  在想事
I was already awake. Thinking.

40
00:00:57,730 --> 00:00:59,400
昨晚的事吗  迈克...
About last night? Look, Mike, I--

41
00:00:59,400 --> 00:01:01,970
没事  我不介意
It's okay. I'm good.

42
00:01:02,930 --> 00:01:05,260
你不介意我跟洛根在收购项目上合作吗
You're good with me working on the takeover with Logan?

43
00:01:05,260 --> 00:01:06,760
你为什么不相信我呢
Why do you not seem to believe me?

44
00:01:06,760 --> 00:01:08,340
因为你昨晚介意来着
Because you weren't good last night.

45
00:01:08,340 --> 00:01:09,760
那是今早之前的事
Which was before this morning

46
00:01:09,760 --> 00:01:11,970
我想明白了那是公事
when I realized that that's work.

47
00:01:13,590 --> 00:01:15,070
而我们之间是私事
This isn't.

48
00:01:16,740 --> 00:01:20,880
只要我们不让公事影响到私事
So as long as we don't let that affect this...

49
00:01:21,190 --> 00:01:22,360
不会的
We won't.

50
00:01:23,300 --> 00:01:26,260
这样的话  我们设立一些家里的规矩吧
In that case, let's set some in-home ground rules.

51
00:01:26,260 --> 00:01:27,470
不用说  第一条
Obviously, the first--

52
00:01:27,470 --> 00:01:29,590
尊重彼此的隐私
Uh, respecting each other's privacy.

53
00:01:29,590 --> 00:01:30,750
没错
Exactly.

54
00:01:30,820 --> 00:01:32,080
桌子左侧
The left-hand side of the desk

55
00:01:32,080 --> 00:01:34,290
属于罗斯合众国
belongs to the United Nation of Ross.

56
00:01:34,720 --> 00:01:37,460
-你才不是国呢  -我能竖小旗
- You're not a nation. - I have a flag.

57
00:01:37,970 --> 00:01:38,740
好吧
Fine.

58
00:01:38,900 --> 00:01:42,080
但我们要说好  看我的电话
As long as we agree that any perusal of my phone

59
00:01:42,080 --> 00:01:43,800
即是犯我边境
is considered a breach of my borders.

60
00:01:45,080 --> 00:01:48,110
你不是喜欢我侵犯你的边境吗
I thought you liked it when I breached your borders.

61
00:01:48,250 --> 00:01:51,880
不是一种边境嘛
Mm, well, those are different kind of borders.

62
00:01:52,350 --> 00:01:54,000
那种情况下的侵犯我允许
In that case, a breach is allowed.

63
00:01:54,000 --> 00:01:56,060
-允许  -鼓励
- Allowed? - Encouraged.

64
00:01:57,360 --> 00:01:59,000
-是请求吧  -是命令
- Requested. - Demanded.

65
00:02:02,030 --> 00:02:03,650
我们去做点让你迟到的事吧
Let's go make you late for work.

66
00:02:06,980 --> 00:02:08,620
杰西卡  听我说
Jessica, I am telling you.

67
00:02:08,630 --> 00:02:10,950
证监会会派杰夫·马龙来找我们麻烦
The S.E.C. is gonna send Jeff Malone after us,

68
00:02:10,950 --> 00:02:13,060
要打败他  最合适人选莫过于...
and nobody is better suited to beat him down than--

69
00:02:13,220 --> 00:02:14,750
猜对了
you guessed it

70
00:02:13,950 --> 00:02:16,170
{\an8}利特

71
00:02:14,960 --> 00:02:17,160
因为我们都知道
Because we all know that

72
00:02:17,080 --> 00:02:20,850
{\an8}路易·利特>证监会

73
00:02:17,550 --> 00:02:20,430
这边比这边强
this is better than this,

74
00:02:20,630 --> 00:02:23,020
最终结果就是这样
which will result in this,

75
00:02:24,290 --> 00:02:27,210
和这样
which will also result in this

76
00:02:28,020 --> 00:02:29,230
这样
and this

77
00:02:30,300 --> 00:02:32,230
这样
and this.

78
00:02:34,540 --> 00:02:36,060
我想要什么回报呢
And what do I want in return?

79
00:02:36,890 --> 00:02:38,950
你知道的
Oh, you know what I want.

80
00:02:40,350 --> 00:02:41,650
你一直知道的
You've always known.

81
00:02:42,220 --> 00:02:43,520
等我赢了
And after I win,

82
00:02:44,050 --> 00:02:45,880
你不仅会愿意给我
you'll not only be willing to give it to me.

83
00:02:48,110 --> 00:02:49,880
你会求着塞给我
You're gonna be begging to give it to me.

84
00:02:53,160 --> 00:02:55,470
{\an8}皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特

85
00:02:58,280 --> 00:03:00,030
-路易  -没空
- Louis. - B--not now.

86
00:03:00,030 --> 00:03:01,180
-路易  -没空
- Louis, - B--not now.

87
00:03:01,180 --> 00:03:02,220
我得跟你谈谈 
I have to talk to you.

88
00:03:02,220 --> 00:03:03,270
我说多少遍了
How many times have I told you?

89
00:03:03,270 --> 00:03:05,160
除非你成功把我的头PS到了龙身上
Unless you have photoshopped my head onto a dragon,

90
00:03:05,160 --> 00:03:07,030
否则别打扰我练习演讲
do not interrupt me while I'm perfecting my pitch.

91
00:03:07,030 --> 00:03:08,480
你的演讲不用完美
Your pitch doesn't need to be perfect.

92
00:03:08,480 --> 00:03:09,700
但必须立刻去做
It needs to be now.

93
00:03:09,700 --> 00:03:11,050
-为什么  -马龙来了
- Why? - Malone is here.

94
00:03:11,120 --> 00:03:13,260
-他来了  -在大堂
- He's here? - In the lobby.

95
00:03:13,740 --> 00:03:15,280
杰西卡叫你过去
And Jessica just asked to see you.

96
00:03:15,280 --> 00:03:16,880
别挡路
Oh, out of my way.

97
00:03:17,330 --> 00:03:18,900
你不带上画架了吗
Aren't--aren't you going to bring your easel?

98
00:03:19,760 --> 00:03:21,950
我不需要画架也能打得他满地找牙
Oh, I don't need an easel to kick this sucker's ass.

99
00:03:25,220 --> 00:03:26,130
杰西卡
Jessica.

100
00:03:27,590 --> 00:03:30,040
杰西卡  我收到你的信儿了  我想...
Jessica, I got your message, and I just wanted to--

101
00:03:30,290 --> 00:03:32,570
路易  这是杰夫·马龙
Louis, this is Jeff Malone.

102
00:03:32,710 --> 00:03:35,780
嗯  我知道他  他是证监会的
Yeah, I know who he is. He's with the S.E.C.

103
00:03:35,780 --> 00:03:37,910
今早之后就不是了
He was until this morning.

104
00:03:38,250 --> 00:03:38,940
我们把他请进了公司
We brought him over 

105
00:03:38,940 --> 00:03:41,440
因为我们有理由认为证监会要找我们麻烦
because we have reason to believe they'll be coming after us.

106
00:03:41,440 --> 00:03:42,480
慢着  什么
Wait, what?

107
00:03:42,580 --> 00:03:45,090
杰夫是我们最新的高级合伙人了
Jeff is our newest senior partner.

108
00:03:45,480 --> 00:03:47,410
他会负责应付证监会
He's going to be taking on the S.E.C.

109
00:03:50,680 --> 00:03:51,960
因为你糟透了
Because you suck.

110
00:03:51,960 --> 00:03:54,650
我想先把他介绍给你
And I wanted to introduce him to you first

111
00:03:55,000 --> 00:03:57,110
因为你就是个废物
because you're a loser.

112
00:03:57,440 --> 00:04:00,930
因为你能帮他尽快熟悉富顿证券的事宜
Who can get him up to speed on Felton Securities.

113
00:04:00,930 --> 00:04:04,750
因为你永远别想当上冠名合伙人了
Because you're never going to be name partner.

114
00:04:06,480 --> 00:04:08,660
而且你俩都是金融方面的专家
And you're both experts in finance.

115
00:04:09,290 --> 00:04:10,530
路易  我十分期待
Louis, I'm really looking forward to 

116
00:04:10,530 --> 00:04:12,500
跟你在富顿证券上合作
working with you on Felton Securities.

117
00:04:15,380 --> 00:04:16,600
我也是
Yeah, me too.

118
00:04:18,760 --> 00:04:21,640
你糟透了  你是个废物
You suck. You're a loser.

119
00:04:22,040 --> 00:04:23,060
路易
Louis?

120
00:04:25,570 --> 00:04:26,970
还有事吗
Is there something else?

121
00:04:28,360 --> 00:04:29,360
没事
No.

122
00:04:30,370 --> 00:04:31,450
没什么
Nothing.

123
00:04:47,010 --> 00:04:48,280
你干多久了
How long you been working on that?

124
00:04:48,420 --> 00:04:49,150
两小时
Two hours.

125
00:04:49,150 --> 00:04:50,500
你知道那东西应该是"简"报吧
You know it's called a brief, right?

126
00:04:50,500 --> 00:04:51,940
你知道是给哈维的吧
You know his name's Harvey, right?

127
00:04:51,940 --> 00:04:53,580
有理有据  令人信服
You make a compelling argument.

128
00:04:54,320 --> 00:04:55,480
我收到你的字条了
So I got your note.

129
00:04:55,850 --> 00:04:56,800
想找我说什么
What do you wanna talk about? 

130
00:04:59,200 --> 00:05:00,600
洛根·桑德斯
Logan Sanders.

131
00:05:00,760 --> 00:05:01,660
怎么了
What about him?

132
00:05:01,790 --> 00:05:04,390
我们几年前算是约过会
We sort of dated a few years ago.

133
00:05:05,100 --> 00:05:08,490
慢着  什么叫"算是"
Wait, hang on. Define "sort of."

134
00:05:08,490 --> 00:05:10,360
-就是绝对是  -"约会"呢
- Definitely. - Define "dated."

135
00:05:11,570 --> 00:05:13,170
他有老婆时我们偷过情
We had an affair while he was married.

136
00:05:13,170 --> 00:05:14,080
老天啊
Holy shit.

137
00:05:14,080 --> 00:05:15,330
我知道  而且
I know. And I--

138
00:05:15,330 --> 00:05:17,160
是的  你得告诉哈维
Yes, you have to tell Harvey.

139
00:05:17,540 --> 00:05:19,590
因为瑞秋  哈维最讨厌的两件事
Because, Rachel, if there's two things that Harvey hates,

140
00:05:19,590 --> 00:05:22,810
就是被人瞒着  和被人瞒着
it's things being kept from him and things being kept from him.

141
00:05:22,810 --> 00:05:25,150
-我知道  -那你还找我来干什么
- I know. - Then what am I doing here?

142
00:05:25,150 --> 00:05:26,140
我不知道要怎么说
I don't know how to tell him.

143
00:05:26,140 --> 00:05:26,980
快去说
Quickly, 

144
00:05:27,140 --> 00:05:29,020
-洛根过一小时就要到了  -什么
- because Logan's gonna be here in an hour. - What?

145
00:05:29,020 --> 00:05:32,010
瑞秋  你怎么告诉哈维并不重要
and, Rach, it's less important how you tell Harvey

146
00:05:32,030 --> 00:05:33,700
重要的是你要告诉他
than that you tell Harvey.

147
00:05:33,940 --> 00:05:34,870
快去
Go.

148
00:05:36,570 --> 00:05:37,620
好的
okay.

149
00:05:39,620 --> 00:05:42,030
花不错
Hmm. These are nice.

150
00:06:19,740 --> 00:06:21,270
我想了一整天你到底会不会来
I was wondering all day if you would be here

151
00:06:21,270 --> 00:06:22,590
我不能这么做
I can't do this.

152
00:06:22,590 --> 00:06:23,900
怎么了  瑞秋
What? Rachel--

153
00:06:23,900 --> 00:06:24,880
这样不对
It's wrong.

154
00:06:25,860 --> 00:06:28,100
不对  是你先亲的我
Wrong? You're the one who kissed me.

155
00:06:28,100 --> 00:06:29,860
所以我错了
And I was wrong.

156
00:06:30,040 --> 00:06:31,570
不  你没有
No, you weren't.

157
00:06:31,850 --> 00:06:32,950
我的整个人生都在做一些
My whole life I've done everything

158
00:06:32,950 --> 00:06:34,050
别人认为我该做的事
that I was supposed to do,

159
00:06:34,070 --> 00:06:36,370
所有那些事都让我变得痛不欲生
and all it did was make me miserable.

160
00:06:36,430 --> 00:06:38,080
直到我遇见你
Ever since I met you...

161
00:06:39,810 --> 00:06:42,280
我一直在想你  我脑子里只有
I can't stop thinking about you, and all I want to do--

162
00:06:42,280 --> 00:06:44,910
洛根  我们这么做
Logan Logan, if we do this,

163
00:06:45,050 --> 00:06:47,330
早晚会被发现  到时怎么办
Someone's gonna find out at some point and then what?

164
00:06:47,840 --> 00:06:49,160
我不在乎
I don't care.

165
00:07:06,300 --> 00:07:07,120
好吧
Okay.

166
00:07:07,580 --> 00:07:09,270
哈维  我需要告诉你
Harvey, I need to tell you--

167
00:07:10,030 --> 00:07:11,100
瑞秋
Rachel?

168
00:07:13,160 --> 00:07:14,220
洛根
Logan.

169
00:07:16,740 --> 00:07:17,560
哈维去哪里了
Where's Harvey?

170
00:07:17,560 --> 00:07:19,230
我不知道  我来早了
I don't know. I'm early.

171
00:07:20,070 --> 00:07:20,840
他不喜欢别人
He doesn't like it when people--

172
00:07:20,840 --> 00:07:23,570
-你怎么在这  -我是哈维的初级律师
- What are you doing here? - I'm Harvey's associate.

173
00:07:24,900 --> 00:07:26,560
你成功了  你上了法学院
You did it. You went to law school.

174
00:07:27,130 --> 00:07:28,780
不完全对  我正在上法学院
Not exactly. I'm in law school.

175
00:07:28,870 --> 00:07:29,670
瑞秋  这太好了
Rachel, that's great.

176
00:07:29,670 --> 00:07:31,560
我真为你骄傲
I'm really proud of you.

177
00:07:32,170 --> 00:07:33,250
我一会儿再来
I'm just gonna come back.

178
00:07:33,250 --> 00:07:35,370
你是来告诉他我们的事的  对吧
You came in here to tell him about us, didn't you?

179
00:07:37,070 --> 00:07:38,150
你怎么知道
How'd you know?

180
00:07:39,230 --> 00:07:40,480
都写在你脸上了
It's all over your face.

181
00:07:40,530 --> 00:07:41,480
-洛根  -请别告诉他
- Logan-- - Please don't tell him.

182
00:07:41,480 --> 00:07:42,610
我必须告诉他
I have to tell him.

183
00:07:44,430 --> 00:07:45,430
瑞秋
Rachel...

184
00:07:47,540 --> 00:07:49,130
你知道当人们看到
Do you know what people think

185
00:07:49,220 --> 00:07:51,330
儿子接管父亲公司时会怎么想吗
when a son takes over his father's company?

186
00:07:51,330 --> 00:07:52,890
认为他父亲很为他自豪吗
That his father's proud of him?

187
00:07:52,890 --> 00:07:54,160
会认为他不够格
That he didn't earn it.

188
00:07:55,010 --> 00:07:57,440
所以我才不想昭告天下
Which is why I'm not looking to advertise the fact

189
00:07:57,440 --> 00:07:58,460
我曾经有过婚外情
that I once had an affair.

190
00:07:58,460 --> 00:08:00,850
这不是昭告天下  是向律师披露重要信息
You're not advertising it. You're disclosing it to counsel.

191
00:08:00,850 --> 00:08:03,280
好吧  你想听实话
Okay, look, you want the truth?

192
00:08:04,100 --> 00:08:06,030
我并不为当时的做法自豪
I'm not proud of the way I was back then.

193
00:08:06,570 --> 00:08:09,960
包括对待艾莉森的方式  对待你的方式
The way I treated Allison, the way I treated you.

194
00:08:10,710 --> 00:08:12,070
但我已经改变了
But I'm not that person anymore,

195
00:08:12,070 --> 00:08:13,970
我不想别人还像以前一样看我
and I don't want people to think that I am.

196
00:08:14,260 --> 00:08:16,600
我理解  但是我为哈维工作
And I understand that, but I work for Harvey,

197
00:08:16,910 --> 00:08:19,170
我不能不告诉他这些重要信息
and I can't keep things from him that he needs to know.

198
00:08:19,170 --> 00:08:20,780
-他不需要知道这些  -他需要
- He doesn't need to know this. - Yes, he does.

199
00:08:20,780 --> 00:08:21,680
为什么
Why is that?

200
00:08:22,980 --> 00:08:25,210
因为我恰巧在和收购战的另一方
Because I happen to live with the man on the other side

201
00:08:25,210 --> 00:08:26,600
一起生活
of the takeover battle.

202
00:08:35,110 --> 00:08:37,740
不是吧  你已经开始需要独处了
Oh, no. You need some me time already?

203
00:08:38,290 --> 00:08:39,590
这不是独处
It's not me time.

204
00:08:39,600 --> 00:08:41,390
这是我会打得你屁滚尿流的意思
It's "I'm gonna kick your ass" time.

205
00:08:41,460 --> 00:08:44,080
我想我们都知道你只有吃了热狗才会那样
I think we both know you only kick ass after eating a hot dog.

206
00:08:44,240 --> 00:08:46,920
我就算喝果汁也能有那种状态
I could be drinking a juice box and still kick your ass.

207
00:08:46,920 --> 00:08:49,100
我可不这么认为  因为我有这个
I don't think so, because I have this.

208
00:08:49,600 --> 00:08:50,800
直接念吧
Just read it to me.

209
00:08:52,270 --> 00:08:54,550
哈维·斯佩克特  你被传召出席
"Harvey Specter, you are summoned to"--

210
00:08:54,550 --> 00:08:57,250
你开玩笑吗  你给我发了传票
You gotta be kidding me. You're subpoenaing me?

211
00:08:57,250 --> 00:08:59,460
是的  我申请了临时禁令
Oh, yeah. I filed a T.R.O.

212
00:08:59,460 --> 00:09:00,760
我要拒绝你温柔的邀请了
I'm gonna block your tender offer.

213
00:09:00,760 --> 00:09:01,700
废话  你当然会了
Bullshit, you are.

214
00:09:01,700 --> 00:09:03,660
那就看看法官怎么说吧
Well, we'll see what the judge has to say.

215
00:09:03,660 --> 00:09:05,230
对了  你腾不出手来
Oh, right. You got your hands full.

216
00:09:05,230 --> 00:09:07,020
我来帮你  好了
Here, let me get that for you. There you go.

217
00:09:07,130 --> 00:09:08,750
听证会两点开始  到时见
Hearing's at 2:00. I'll see you then.

218
00:09:08,760 --> 00:09:10,490
哈维  这套西装
Oh, Harvey, the suit--

219
00:09:10,490 --> 00:09:12,760
你不觉得穿着上庭有点过时了吗
It's a little dated for court, don't you think?

220
00:09:15,170 --> 00:09:17,120
和人力资源部都交接好了吗
Did you get everything settled with HR?

221
00:09:17,350 --> 00:09:18,220
好了
Yeah.

222
00:09:19,470 --> 00:09:22,740
拐角办公室啊  你一定很喜欢我
Corner office. You really must like me.

223
00:09:23,810 --> 00:09:25,320
别高兴太早
Don't get too excited.

224
00:09:25,540 --> 00:09:27,510
你知道吗  这间办公室之前的两任主人
You know, the last two partners that had this office

225
00:09:27,510 --> 00:09:28,530
连一年都没熬过去
didn't survive the year.

226
00:09:28,530 --> 00:09:30,310
那幸好我比他们都强
Then it's a good thing I'm much better than they were.

227
00:09:30,430 --> 00:09:31,510
你都不知道他们是谁
You don't even know who they were.

228
00:09:31,640 --> 00:09:33,300
那不重要  杰西卡  我知道我是谁
That doesn't matter, Jessica. I know who I am.

229
00:09:33,300 --> 00:09:36,680
我也知道  一个还没为我办过事情的
Me too, cocky lawyer in a corner office

230
00:09:36,840 --> 00:09:38,730
拐角办公室里的嚣张律师
who hasn't done a thing for me yet.

231
00:09:39,290 --> 00:09:40,370
没来得及而已
Yet.

232
00:09:41,400 --> 00:09:43,690
顺便说一句  我听说冠名合伙人依照传统
By the way, I understand it's tradition for the name partner

233
00:09:43,690 --> 00:09:45,480
是要和新晋合伙人吃欢迎午餐的
to welcome a new partner with lunch.

234
00:09:46,010 --> 00:09:48,630
杰夫  我说我们的关系
Jeff, when I told you that our relationship

235
00:09:48,630 --> 00:09:50,980
仅限于工作  我是认真的
is now purely professional, I was serious.

236
00:09:50,980 --> 00:09:53,540
杰西卡  午餐怎么不是限于工作了
Jessica, what's not purely professional about lunch?

237
00:09:53,830 --> 00:09:56,300
除非你说的是饭后的亲热
Unless you mean the sex that will be following lunch?

238
00:09:56,850 --> 00:09:57,920
你没听懂我的话
Oh, you're not hearing me.

239
00:09:57,920 --> 00:10:00,050
我懂  只是在无视它们
Oh, I'm hearing you. I'm just ignoring you.

240
00:10:00,050 --> 00:10:02,450
但我保证午餐时不无视你的话
But I promise I won't be ignoring you at lunch.

241
00:10:03,790 --> 00:10:05,110
嚣张
Cocky.

242
00:10:12,690 --> 00:10:14,820
哈维  哈维  能跟你说两句话吗
Harvey. Harvey, can I talk to you for a minute?

243
00:10:14,820 --> 00:10:15,650
当然可以  进来吧
Yeah, sure, come on in.

244
00:10:15,650 --> 00:10:16,870
我希望能去我办公室谈
I was actually hoping that we could talk in my office.

245
00:10:16,870 --> 00:10:19,020
什么...  你来早了
What's the-- you're early.

246
00:10:19,020 --> 00:10:21,690
-你知道...  -你们俩还没见过面吧
- Did you... - Oh, you two haven't met.

247
00:10:21,690 --> 00:10:23,350
瑞秋  这位是洛根  洛根  这位是瑞秋
Rachel, Logan. Logan, Rachel.

248
00:10:23,350 --> 00:10:24,830
-看来你不知道  -不知道什么
- I guess you didn't. - Didn't what?

249
00:10:24,830 --> 00:10:26,260
其实我们以前见过面
We actually have met before.

250
00:10:26,260 --> 00:10:28,030
所以我才想去找你
That's why I was trying to find you.

251
00:10:28,390 --> 00:10:30,060
-告诉我你见过我们的客户吗  -不
- To tell me you met our client? - No.

252
00:10:30,060 --> 00:10:33,890
告诉你我们曾经交往过
To tell you that we used to be in a relationship together.

253
00:10:36,480 --> 00:10:38,100
你俩想复合吗
You looking to get back together?

254
00:10:38,100 --> 00:10:39,030
不想
No.

255
00:10:39,030 --> 00:10:40,940
-那我不在乎  -很好
- Then I don't give a shit. - Good.

256
00:10:40,940 --> 00:10:42,620
那该你解释了  你为什么没告诉我
Then we can move on to why you didn't tell me that the guy

257
00:10:42,620 --> 00:10:44,930
我们的竞争对手曾经是你的初级律师
on the other side of this fight used to be your associate.

258
00:10:44,930 --> 00:10:46,270
-我本打算说的  -什么时候
- I was going to. - When?

259
00:10:46,270 --> 00:10:48,380
二十分后  约你来这里的时间
In 20 minutes, when you were scheduled to be here.

260
00:10:48,380 --> 00:10:49,950
不巧的是  会面得改期了
Unfortunately, I have to reschedule.

261
00:10:49,950 --> 00:10:51,740
-为什么  -我要出庭
- Why? - I have court.

262
00:10:51,740 --> 00:10:53,410
迈克指控我违反保密特权
Mike's alleging I broke privilege.

263
00:10:53,410 --> 00:10:55,470
-你违反了吗  -严格来说  是的
- Did you? - Yes, technically,

264
00:10:55,470 --> 00:10:57,060
因为我告诉你要加快速度
when I told you to move up our timeline.

265
00:10:57,060 --> 00:10:58,820
恕我失陪
Now, if you'll excuse me.

266
00:10:59,000 --> 00:11:01,670
等等  如果你违反了保密特权
W-wait a minute. If you--if you broke privilege,

267
00:11:01,670 --> 00:11:02,950
要怎么跟法官说
what are you gonna tell the judge?

268
00:11:02,950 --> 00:11:04,700
不知道  在我想出办法前
I don't know, but until I think of something,

269
00:11:04,700 --> 00:11:06,890
我要把这潭水搅浑
I'm going to confuse the shit out of everyone I can.

270
00:11:06,890 --> 00:11:08,420
这毫无意义
That doesn't make any sense.

271
00:11:08,420 --> 00:11:09,320
非常有意义  
It makes total sense. 

272
00:11:09,320 --> 00:11:10,770
不  没意义  法官大人
No, it doesn't, Your Honor.

273
00:11:10,770 --> 00:11:12,430
好吧  等等  让我理清思路
All right, hold on. Let me get this straight.

274
00:11:12,430 --> 00:11:13,200
你为他工作  
You work for him? 

275
00:11:13,200 --> 00:11:14,640
工作过  我曾是他的初级律师
Worked. I was his associate.

276
00:11:14,640 --> 00:11:16,260
不是最好的那个  法官大人
Not the best associate, Your Honor.

277
00:11:16,260 --> 00:11:16,890
有关系吗
Is that relevant?

278
00:11:16,890 --> 00:11:18,290
没有  但我希望这句话记录在案
No, but I'd like it on the record.

279
00:11:18,290 --> 00:11:20,190
无论如何都已经记录下来了
Well, it's on there now whether we want it there or not.

280
00:11:20,190 --> 00:11:23,330
我想说的是  律师之间没有保密特权
And all I'm saying is, there's no attorney-attorney privilege.

281
00:11:23,330 --> 00:11:24,380
终于说点靠谱的了
Finally, a fact.

282
00:11:24,380 --> 00:11:25,310
但与本案无关
An irrelevant fact,

283
00:11:25,310 --> 00:11:26,790
因为发生利益冲突时
because at the time of the conflict,

284
00:11:26,790 --> 00:11:28,930
-我是他的客户  -也不是最好的客户
- I was his client. - Not the best client either.

285
00:11:28,930 --> 00:11:31,090
你闭嘴  斯佩克特先生  你是他的客户
Mr. Specter, shut up. Now you're his client?

286
00:11:31,090 --> 00:11:33,270
不  我曾是他的客户  好吧
No, I was his client-- okay.

287
00:11:33,330 --> 00:11:35,190
我曾在皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所当初级律师
I was an associate at Pearson Specter,

288
00:11:35,190 --> 00:11:37,010
后来我离开律所去做投资银行家了
and then I left to become an investment banker.

289
00:11:37,010 --> 00:11:38,000
乱得很
It's very confusing.

290
00:11:38,000 --> 00:11:39,390
我建议撤销动议  法官大人
I'd dismiss the whole motion, Your Honor.

291
00:11:39,390 --> 00:11:41,580
我让你闭嘴
I said, "Shut up."

292
00:11:41,990 --> 00:11:43,780
你到底是律师还是投资银行家
Are you an attorney or an investment banker?

293
00:11:43,780 --> 00:11:44,780
我是投资银行家
I'm an investment banker.

294
00:11:44,780 --> 00:11:46,130
那你来我办公室干什么
Then what the hell are you doing in my chambers?

295
00:11:46,130 --> 00:11:47,410
为我自己辩护
Acting as my own attorney.

296
00:11:47,410 --> 00:11:50,450
无论他多想把事情复杂化  都不能让他得逞
And no matter how much he tries to confuse the issue, he can't.

297
00:11:50,450 --> 00:11:52,790
我告诉过他我要收购同一家公司
I told him I was going after the same company he was,

298
00:11:52,790 --> 00:11:55,100
他利用我告诉他的消息迅速起草了投标报价书
and he used that knowledge to move up his tender offer.

299
00:11:55,100 --> 00:11:56,250
他签了利益冲突弃权书
He waived conflict.

300
00:11:56,250 --> 00:11:57,840
那可不适用于保密特权
That doesn't apply to privilege.

301
00:11:57,840 --> 00:12:00,180
总之  他什么证据都没有
Bottom line is, he doesn't have proof of anything.

302
00:12:00,180 --> 00:12:01,800
我没有  但他有
I don't, but he does.

303
00:12:02,080 --> 00:12:04,190
不幸的是  他不能强迫我作证
Unfortunately, he can't force me to testify.

304
00:12:04,190 --> 00:12:05,030
没有先例
There's no precedent.

305
00:12:05,030 --> 00:12:07,460
不巧  还真有
Fortunately, there is.

306
00:12:07,550 --> 00:12:10,110
请继续  问他是否做了我说的事
So go ahead, ask him if he did what I'm saying.

307
00:12:13,410 --> 00:12:15,700
斯佩克特先生  我需要让你宣誓吗
Mr. Specter, do I need to swear you in?

308
00:12:16,710 --> 00:12:18,100
发给他暂时禁令
Give him the T.R.O.

309
00:12:18,100 --> 00:12:19,990
我不仅要签发禁令
You know, I'll do more than that.

310
00:12:20,120 --> 00:12:22,540
你的客户在六十天内不能进行投标报价
Not only can't your client make a tender offer for 60 days,

311
00:12:22,540 --> 00:12:25,050
在此期间也不能购买更多股份
they can't purchase any more stock until then either.

312
00:12:29,990 --> 00:12:32,860
我说了  我们得跟他谈判
I'm telling you, we need to negotiate with him.

313
00:12:32,860 --> 00:12:33,710
你是说给他钱
You mean pay him off?

314
00:12:33,710 --> 00:12:35,850
没错  就是这样
Yes, that's exactly what I mean.

315
00:12:35,850 --> 00:12:39,020
每拖一天  你就会损失几百万
Every day this drags on, it's millions out of your pocket.

316
00:12:39,020 --> 00:12:41,800
在我眼里  我只看到一个
Well, from where I'm sitting, all I can see is a lawyer

317
00:12:41,800 --> 00:12:42,870
搞砸了整件事
trying to distract me 

318
00:12:42,870 --> 00:12:44,470
却想推卸责任的律师
from the fact that this whole thing is his fault.

319
00:12:44,470 --> 00:12:45,670
如果我不违反保密特权
If I didn't break privilege,

320
00:12:45,670 --> 00:12:46,920
他会把整件事捂得密不透风
he might have locked this whole thing up

321
00:12:46,920 --> 00:12:48,720
你要到栽了跟头才明白
before you knew what hit you.

322
00:12:48,790 --> 00:12:49,790
好吧  我们谈判
Fine. We'll negotiate.

323
00:12:49,790 --> 00:12:52,260
不  我去谈判
No, I'll negotiate.

324
00:12:53,250 --> 00:12:55,260
不行  我要参与
No, not without me.

325
00:12:55,260 --> 00:12:56,650
需要我给你把形势画出来吗
Do I need to draw you a picture?

326
00:12:56,650 --> 00:12:58,450
你  迈克  瑞秋
You, Mike, Rachel.

327
00:12:58,450 --> 00:13:00,390
哈维  感谢你的关心
Harvey, I appreciate your concern,

328
00:13:00,390 --> 00:13:01,690
但这是我的第一笔生意
but this is my first deal,

329
00:13:01,690 --> 00:13:03,510
除非你要自己出钱给他
so unless you're gonna pay him off with your money, 

330
00:13:03,510 --> 00:13:05,600
否则我就要参加会议
I'm gonna be at that meeting.

331
00:13:10,630 --> 00:13:11,940
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?

332
00:13:12,740 --> 00:13:14,210
写日记
I'm writing in my diary.

333
00:13:14,950 --> 00:13:16,910
你不是用录音笔记日记吗
Isn't that what your dictaphone is for?

334
00:13:16,910 --> 00:13:19,470
不  录音笔是记录胜利的
No, my dictaphone is for my singular triumphs,

335
00:13:19,470 --> 00:13:22,540
比如说  哈维告诉我我碉堡了
like when Harvey told me I was the man,

336
00:13:22,540 --> 00:13:26,010
我的日记记录最痛苦的失败
and my diary is for my most agonizing defeats,

337
00:13:26,010 --> 00:13:27,490
比如杰西卡告诉我
such as when Jessica just told me

338
00:13:27,490 --> 00:13:28,840
我永远当不了冠名合伙人
I'll never make name partner.

339
00:13:28,840 --> 00:13:30,990
路易  她没这么说  
Louis, she didn't say that. 

340
00:13:30,990 --> 00:13:32,420
她还不如直说呢
Well, she might as well have.

341
00:13:32,420 --> 00:13:34,280
她把拐角办公室给马龙了
She just gave Malone the corner office.

342
00:13:35,070 --> 00:13:36,150
天啊
Oh, my God.

343
00:13:36,150 --> 00:13:37,500
是啊
Yeah.

344
00:13:37,970 --> 00:13:38,840
而且
And what's more

345
00:13:38,840 --> 00:13:41,620
我想我答应把富顿证券交给他了
is I think I agreed to give him Felton Securities.

346
00:13:42,090 --> 00:13:43,890
那就反悔啊
Well, un-agree to it.

347
00:13:43,890 --> 00:13:45,190
不行
I can't.

348
00:13:45,300 --> 00:13:47,160
我跟他握手了  木已成舟
I shook his hand. The die is cast.

349
00:13:47,160 --> 00:13:48,880
该死  路易
God damn it, Louis.

350
00:13:48,880 --> 00:13:50,020
你知道这样下去会怎么样
You know how this works.

351
00:13:50,020 --> 00:13:51,890
先是案子  然后是客户
First it's a case. Then it's a client.

352
00:13:51,890 --> 00:13:54,840
很快你就会去38楼陪泰德了
Before you know it, you're on the 38th floor with Ted.

353
00:13:54,840 --> 00:13:56,670
-泰德是谁  -问得好
- Who's Ted? - Exactly.

354
00:13:57,850 --> 00:14:01,310
天啊  我都干了什么
Holy shit. What did I just do?

355
00:14:01,310 --> 00:14:02,550
我告诉你该怎么做
I'll tell you what you're gonna do.

356
00:14:02,550 --> 00:14:04,900
别再写什么破日记了
You're gonna stop writing in that pussy diary,

357
00:14:04,900 --> 00:14:06,780
给杰西卡看看  你才是应该
and you're gonna show Jessica you're the one

358
00:14:06,780 --> 00:14:08,800
坐在拐角办公室的那个人
who should be sitting in that corner office.

359
00:14:08,800 --> 00:14:10,080
好了
All right.

360
00:14:11,550 --> 00:14:13,610
准备好录音笔  要派上用场了
Ready the dictaphone. We're gonna need it.

361
00:14:21,560 --> 00:14:23,020
和洛根·桑德斯谈得怎样
How are things going with Logan Sanders?

362
00:14:23,020 --> 00:14:25,410
-简直超乎想象  -有什么值得听的吗
- You have no idea. - Do I want to have an idea?

363
00:14:25,410 --> 00:14:26,620
除非你想听听
Not unless you want to hear about

364
00:14:26,620 --> 00:14:29,010
迈克·罗斯是怎么继续给我们找麻烦的
how Mike Ross is still causing us trouble. 

365
00:14:29,010 --> 00:14:30,370
不想
Nope.

366
00:14:30,900 --> 00:14:33,620
你一点都不在乎洛根·桑德斯  是吧
You don't care about Logan Sanders at all, do you? 

367
00:14:33,630 --> 00:14:35,160
不在乎
No.

368
00:14:35,630 --> 00:14:38,800
我俩不是什么巧遇  对吧
This isn't a coincidental encounter, is it? 

369
00:14:38,800 --> 00:14:40,760
当然不是
No, it is not.

370
00:14:40,760 --> 00:14:43,140
今天你得和杰夫·马龙一起吃午餐
You are having lunch with Jeff Malone today.

371
00:14:43,200 --> 00:14:44,670
得啦  杰西卡  你上了他
Come on, Jessica. You banged him.

372
00:14:44,670 --> 00:14:47,260
-至少该带他吃顿午饭  -这话不好笑
- The least you could do is take him to lunch. - That is not funny.

373
00:14:47,540 --> 00:14:49,770
等等  你想让我带他去吃午餐
Wait a second, you want me to take him to lunch

374
00:14:49,770 --> 00:14:51,430
正是因为你上了他
because you banged him.

375
00:14:51,430 --> 00:14:52,720
哈维
Harvey...

376
00:14:53,610 --> 00:14:54,840
你再当着我的面
I want you to go ahead 

377
00:14:54,840 --> 00:14:59,030
说一次"上"这个字
and say "banged" to my face one more time.

378
00:15:00,140 --> 00:15:03,430
我才不说  但不是因为我怕你
I'm not going to but not because I'm scared of you.

379
00:15:03,690 --> 00:15:06,430
随便你怎么安抚自己  白人少年
Whatever lets you sleep at night, white boy.

380
00:15:10,290 --> 00:15:12,920
唐娜  告诉保罗·波特准备中午和我吃饭
Donna, tell Paul Porter he's meeting me for lunch.

381
00:15:12,920 --> 00:15:15,800
他到了餐厅后  让他和杰夫·马龙坐一起
When he gets there, tell them to seat him with Jeff Malone.

382
00:15:15,800 --> 00:15:17,010
谁不想和他吃午饭
Who's he not having lunch with?

383
00:15:17,010 --> 00:15:18,780
-杰西卡  -知道了
- Jessica. - Oh, done.

384
00:15:18,780 --> 00:15:20,220
不问问我为什么吗
Aren't you gonna ask me why?

385
00:15:21,100 --> 00:15:23,000
她让你去  因为她不想去
She asked you to go because she didn't want to.

386
00:15:23,000 --> 00:15:24,640
你让波特去  因为你不想去
You're sending Porter because you don't want to,

387
00:15:24,640 --> 00:15:27,100
但你又没种当面拒绝她
but you didn't have the balls to say no to her face.

388
00:15:27,880 --> 00:15:29,010
是这么回事吧
Is that it?

389
00:15:29,010 --> 00:15:30,190
有种没种有待商榷
The balls are debatable. 

390
00:15:30,200 --> 00:15:31,900
种的问题从来不用商榷
Balls are never debatable.

391
00:15:37,270 --> 00:15:39,450
-你好  -你好
- Ah, hey there. - Hey.

392
00:15:39,560 --> 00:15:41,180
路易  我只...
Louis, listen, I just, um,

393
00:15:41,180 --> 00:15:42,680
只想再说一遍
I just wanted to say one more time

394
00:15:42,680 --> 00:15:44,820
我很期望和你共事
how much I'm really looking forward to working with you.

395
00:15:44,820 --> 00:15:47,030
那我也想头一回说
Aww, well, I would just like to say for the first time

396
00:15:47,030 --> 00:15:48,280
你不会和我共事
that you will not be working with me,

397
00:15:48,280 --> 00:15:49,710
因为我话都不想跟你说
because I will not be giving you my jock, 

398
00:15:49,710 --> 00:15:51,420
一起解决案子就更不想
let alone my case.

399
00:15:51,420 --> 00:15:52,680
这样
Yeah.

400
00:15:53,190 --> 00:15:55,050
行  我懂了
Okay, I get it.

401
00:15:55,950 --> 00:15:57,190
你就是那个人吗
So you're the guy? 

402
00:15:57,200 --> 00:15:59,060
对  我就是那个人
Yeah, I am the guy.

403
00:15:59,060 --> 00:16:01,700
不  不是你说那个  你绝对不是那个
No, not that guy, Louis. Definitely not that guy.

404
00:16:01,700 --> 00:16:02,800
你是办公室里
You're the guy in every office 

405
00:16:02,800 --> 00:16:04,680
喜欢往新人身上撒尿
who wants to piss on the new guy,

406
00:16:04,680 --> 00:16:06,800
来标记自己领地的那种人
you know, to mark your territory.

407
00:16:06,800 --> 00:16:09,040
不如我带你去我办公室
So why don't I just walk you on down to my office?

408
00:16:09,040 --> 00:16:11,070
让你在角落里撒泡尿
I'm gonna let you get your little piss on in my corner,

409
00:16:11,070 --> 00:16:12,470
然后继续工作
and then we can move on.

410
00:16:12,470 --> 00:16:13,670
我已经继续工作了
Oh, I've moved on.

411
00:16:13,670 --> 00:16:15,630
我安排了陶德·史密斯明天取证
I've set the deposition for Todd Smith tomorrow.

412
00:16:15,630 --> 00:16:16,670
你以为我不知道吗
You don't think I know about that?

413
00:16:16,670 --> 00:16:18,290
我不管你知不知道
I don't give a shit whether you know it or not.

414
00:16:18,290 --> 00:16:20,840
判定陶德·史密斯有没有罪是我的工作
It's my job to determine whether Todd Smith is guilty.

415
00:16:20,840 --> 00:16:22,890
你觉得谁更擅长判断
And who do you actually think is better at determining

416
00:16:22,890 --> 00:16:25,680
某人是不是犯内幕交易罪  路易
whether a guy is guilty of insider trading, Louis?

417
00:16:25,680 --> 00:16:27,700
证监会的职业检察官
A career prosecutor for the S.E.C. 

418
00:16:27,700 --> 00:16:29,770
还是穿意大利西装的猴子
or a monkey in some Italian suit?

419
00:16:29,770 --> 00:16:30,930
-猴子  -对  猴子
- a Monkey? - Monkey.

420
00:16:30,930 --> 00:16:32,870
你不过是个自鸣得意的屌人
Well, you're nothing but a crowing cock.

421
00:16:32,960 --> 00:16:34,720
上一个走进我办公室的屌人
And the last cock that walked into my office

422
00:16:34,720 --> 00:16:36,670
可学到了万年不变的真理
learned what all the other cocks learned,

423
00:16:36,670 --> 00:16:39,050
我每餐都把屌炖了吃
that I eat cock for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.

424
00:16:39,050 --> 00:16:40,270
路易  无论你愿不愿意
Louis, you're gonna let me 

425
00:16:40,270 --> 00:16:42,350
明天都得让我参与取证
in that deposition tomorrow whether you like it or not.

426
00:16:42,350 --> 00:16:43,670
为什么  因为你打算向杰西卡汇报吗
Why, because you're gonna run to Jessica?

427
00:16:43,670 --> 00:16:46,160
不  就因为我会告诉办公室里的每个人
No, simply because I'm gonna tell everyone here in the office

428
00:16:46,160 --> 00:16:49,040
你说  你每餐都把屌炖了吃
that you said you eat cock for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.

429
00:16:49,040 --> 00:16:52,190
就是这样  美味得很
Yeah, that's right. It's goddamn delicious.

430
00:16:58,250 --> 00:17:00,750
怎么  你觉得你对付陶德·史密斯比我强
So what, you think you can handle Todd Smith better than me?

431
00:17:01,000 --> 00:17:04,150
我们就看看  看看你有什么本事
Well, let's just see. Let's just see what you got.

432
00:17:06,670 --> 00:17:08,710
我看你安排了跟迈克见面
Saw you scheduled a meeting with Mike.

433
00:17:08,790 --> 00:17:10,920
我想这意味着你打算给他开个条件
I assume that means you're going to offer him a deal.

434
00:17:10,920 --> 00:17:13,400
也可能是我打算请他去迪斯尼玩一圈
It could mean I'm going to offer him a trip to Disneyland.

435
00:17:13,400 --> 00:17:14,370
但不是这样
But it doesn't.

436
00:17:14,370 --> 00:17:16,390
当然不是  他估计会想戴米老鼠耳朵
Of course not, he'd probably want to wear mouse ears,

437
00:17:16,390 --> 00:17:17,860
那样谁都不会开心
and then nobody wins.

438
00:17:18,360 --> 00:17:19,240
不用谢
You're welcome.

439
00:17:19,240 --> 00:17:21,010
我可没谢你
I didn't thank you.

440
00:17:21,010 --> 00:17:23,090
因为你趁我在上课时安排会议
Since you scheduled the meeting when I'm at law school,

441
00:17:23,090 --> 00:17:25,020
就是为了把我排除在外
which you did to cut me out.

442
00:17:25,050 --> 00:17:27,420
一个午餐的时间  你成命名合伙人了
Did you get your name on the wall since lunch?

443
00:17:27,630 --> 00:17:29,430
-没有  -那我们就把话说明白了
- No. - Then let's get something straight.

444
00:17:29,430 --> 00:17:31,400
我没安排会议  唐娜安排的
I didn't set that meeting. Donna did.

445
00:17:31,400 --> 00:17:34,480
如果我不想让你在场  我会当面告诉你
And if I didn't want you there, I'd just tell you to your face.

446
00:17:34,480 --> 00:17:37,210
那我现在告诉你  你不能参加会议
So let me tell you now, you're not going to that meeting.

447
00:17:37,210 --> 00:17:39,170
因为你觉得我处理不来吗
Because you think I can't handle it?

448
00:17:39,170 --> 00:17:41,820
因为我不打算火上浇油
Because I'm not throwing gasoline on a pile of matches

449
00:17:41,820 --> 00:17:43,120
就为看个热闹
just to see what happens.

450
00:17:43,120 --> 00:17:45,520
浪费够我时间了就走吧
Now, if you're done wasting my time,

451
00:17:45,520 --> 00:17:47,110
你刚让我想到了个点子
you just gave me an idea.

452
00:17:49,250 --> 00:17:50,590
不用谢
You're welcome.

453
00:17:57,170 --> 00:17:59,560
-哈维  你来干什么  -你自己说的
- Harvey, what are you doing here? - You said it yourself.

454
00:17:59,560 --> 00:18:02,040
你搬进来的时候我没给你礼物
I never brought you a gift when you moved in.

455
00:18:02,070 --> 00:18:04,640
-但我没看见兰花  -花会死的
- Still don't see an orchid. - Flowers die.

456
00:18:04,690 --> 00:18:06,550
我觉得该带更好的东西来
I thought I'd bring something better.

457
00:18:07,290 --> 00:18:08,580
我自己
Me...

458
00:18:08,810 --> 00:18:10,460
来跟你谈判
across the table from you.

459
00:18:11,860 --> 00:18:13,520
-你的客户呢  -他不用到场
- Where's your client? - He doesn't need to be here.

460
00:18:13,520 --> 00:18:15,690
这场争斗由你我开始
This fight started with you and me.

461
00:18:15,690 --> 00:18:17,530
就在你我之间解决吧
So let's you and me settle it right now.

462
00:18:17,530 --> 00:18:18,500
你是说  你不想让他来
You mean you don't want him here

463
00:18:18,510 --> 00:18:20,110
因为你觉得洛根和我
because you don't think Logan Sanders and I

464
00:18:20,110 --> 00:18:21,150
没法共处一室
can be in the same room.

465
00:18:21,150 --> 00:18:22,490
不用觉得  这是事实
I don't think. I know.

466
00:18:22,490 --> 00:18:24,070
哈维  我又不是小孩
Harvey, I'm a grown man.

467
00:18:24,070 --> 00:18:25,860
我能跟和瑞秋有情史的人
I can sit across the table from somebody

468
00:18:25,860 --> 00:18:26,980
坐下来谈正事
who had a history with Rachel.

469
00:18:26,980 --> 00:18:28,960
没准可以  但你们都长了脑子和老二
Maybe, but you both have a brain and a dick,

470
00:18:28,960 --> 00:18:30,400
让你俩共处一室
and if you get in that room together,

471
00:18:30,400 --> 00:18:32,520
想问题的就不是脑子了
the brains aren't gonna be leading that conversation.

472
00:18:32,520 --> 00:18:36,250
行  你敢说他授权你跟我谈条件了
Fine, you tell me that you have the authority to negotiate a deal, 

473
00:18:36,250 --> 00:18:37,810
我就跟你谈
and I'll negotiate.

474
00:18:38,700 --> 00:18:41,520
但你不行  因为做决定的不是你
But you can't 'cause you don't.

475
00:18:41,860 --> 00:18:43,780
我今天跟你谈什么
And I'm not gonna agree to something here today

476
00:18:43,780 --> 00:18:45,740
明天都得被洛根拒绝  有什么用
just to have Logan reject it tomorrow.

477
00:18:45,740 --> 00:18:47,390
所以回家好好睡一觉吧
So go home, get some sleep,

478
00:18:47,390 --> 00:18:50,090
明早我们三个再继续
and then the three of us will do this again in the morning.

479
00:18:57,310 --> 00:19:01,390
听着  陶德  我们真正的客户不是你
Look, here's the thing, Todd. You're not actually our client.

480
00:19:01,390 --> 00:19:02,620
是富顿证券
Felton Security is.

481
00:19:02,620 --> 00:19:04,840
我的任务就是搞清楚你是不是在撒谎
And it's my job to find out if you're telling the truth.

482
00:19:04,840 --> 00:19:06,360
胡扯  是我的任务
Bullshit. It's my job.

483
00:19:06,360 --> 00:19:08,970
-路易  我能搞定  -不  你搞不定
- Louis, I'm handling this. - No, you're not.

484
00:19:08,970 --> 00:19:10,820
要是他再继续撒谎  我就放弃他
If he doesn't stop lying to me, I'm gonna cut him looser

485
00:19:10,820 --> 00:19:12,910
放得比杰拉德减肥后的腰带还松
than Jared's pants after a Subway diet.

486
00:19:10,820 --> 00:19:12,910
{\an8}杰拉德·福戈尔  赛百味代言人  因食用赛百味三明治成功减掉111公斤

487
00:19:12,910 --> 00:19:14,930
-我没骗你  -你收到了消息
- I'm not lying to you. - You took a tip.

488
00:19:14,930 --> 00:19:17,340
陶德  你听到消息就趁机帮客户
All right, Todd, you took a tip, used it for your client--

489
00:19:17,340 --> 00:19:18,960
没错  你现在还打算
Yes, and now you're trying--

490
00:19:18,960 --> 00:19:20,540
该死  路易
God damn it, Louis!

491
00:19:20,820 --> 00:19:23,300
你要是再继续搀和我的审问
Listen, if you don't back the hell off my interrogation,

492
00:19:23,300 --> 00:19:24,950
我就把他那一把皮包骨头
I'm gonna pick his scrawny ass up

493
00:19:24,950 --> 00:19:27,150
拎起来打死你
and use him to beat the shit out of you!

494
00:19:27,150 --> 00:19:28,020
够了
Stop it!

495
00:19:28,020 --> 00:19:29,070
你们以为我看不懂吗
You think I don't know what you're doing?

496
00:19:29,070 --> 00:19:30,550
你们这是想吓唬我
You're trying to rattle me.

497
00:19:32,480 --> 00:19:33,720
怎么了
What?

498
00:19:33,720 --> 00:19:35,450
你的青筋
Your vein.

499
00:19:35,450 --> 00:19:36,540
-这里吗  -都凸出来了
- Here? - It's bulging.

500
00:19:36,540 --> 00:19:38,130
跟我心脏病发作前一样
Just like mine did, right before my heart attack.

501
00:19:38,130 --> 00:19:40,190
-路易  他不会  -不会心脏病发作吗
- Louis, he's not gonna-- - What? Have a heart attack?

502
00:19:40,190 --> 00:19:42,330
我在法庭一头栽倒前的十秒钟
That was exactly my thought ten seconds before I was slumped

503
00:19:42,330 --> 00:19:43,490
也是这么想的
on the courtroom floor.

504
00:19:43,490 --> 00:19:45,380
跟詹金斯一样
Oh, wow, it's just like Jenkins.

505
00:19:45,380 --> 00:19:47,620
-詹金斯吗  -詹金斯也是吗
- Jenkins? - No shit, Jenkins too?

506
00:19:47,620 --> 00:19:49,310
我发誓  他就坐我旁边
He was sitting right next to me, hand to God.

507
00:19:49,310 --> 00:19:50,910
路易  你真该看他老婆孩子在葬礼上
And, Louis, you should have seen his wife and kids

508
00:19:50,910 --> 00:19:52,490
-那副样子  -葬礼
- at the funeral. - Funeral?

509
00:19:52,700 --> 00:19:55,420
-没错  你也有孩子吧陶德  -有两个
- Yeah, you have kids, todd? - Yeah, I have two kids.

510
00:19:55,420 --> 00:19:57,910
你要是继续撒谎  等着你就两条路  
Yeah, well, whether it's a heart attack or prison time,

511
00:19:57,910 --> 00:19:59,720
心脏病或是监狱
if you do not stop lying to us,

512
00:19:59,720 --> 00:20:01,540
他们再也见不到爸爸了
They're never going to see their father again.

513
00:20:01,540 --> 00:20:02,940
听懂了吗
Do you understand what I just said?

514
00:20:02,940 --> 00:20:05,150
-你再也不能和他们踢球了  -好了
- You are never going to play soccer with them-- - Okay. Okay, 

515
00:20:05,150 --> 00:20:06,560
我是骗人了
I am lying to you.

516
00:20:07,460 --> 00:20:08,590
但你们得帮帮我
But please, you gotta help me.

517
00:20:08,590 --> 00:20:09,730
我们是想帮你
Well, we want to.

518
00:20:09,820 --> 00:20:12,540
但陶陶  要想让自家人罩着你
But, t-dog, you gotta be straight up with your homies

519
00:20:12,540 --> 00:20:14,080
就得老实说实话  懂吗
if you want us to have your back.

520
00:20:14,080 --> 00:20:16,780
实话是  我有细菌恐惧症
The truth is, I'm germaphobic.

521
00:20:17,010 --> 00:20:19,130
一天到晚总在洗手
I have to wash my hands throughout the day.

522
00:20:19,130 --> 00:20:21,660
手上皮肤特别  特别干
And they get dry, I mean really dry.

523
00:20:21,660 --> 00:20:23,850
就得抹好多护肤油
So I have to put on a lot of lotion.

524
00:20:23,960 --> 00:20:25,720
我知道这听着很不可思议
And I know this sounds ridiculous,

525
00:20:25,720 --> 00:20:28,120
但我就是按键盘的时候手滑了
but my finger must have slipped on the keyboard, and I,

526
00:20:28,300 --> 00:20:29,950
买错股了
I hit the wrong stock.

527
00:20:29,970 --> 00:20:32,380
你本来没想买那只股票吗
You're saying that you didn't even mean to buy that stock?

528
00:20:32,380 --> 00:20:33,860
没  但那支股开始狂涨
Nope, but then it skyrocketed,

529
00:20:33,870 --> 00:20:35,780
我也不能跟大家说我投了这支股票
and I wasn't gonna tell everybody that I only bought it

530
00:20:35,780 --> 00:20:38,460
只因为我皮肤太干
because I suffer from dry skin.

531
00:20:38,460 --> 00:20:40,070
求你们了  一定不能抛弃我
Please, you can't cut me loose.

532
00:20:40,070 --> 00:20:41,840
我不能进监狱
I mean, I-I can't go to prison.

533
00:20:43,670 --> 00:20:45,190
那里太不干净了
Unsanitary.

534
00:20:51,530 --> 00:20:52,600
我不该管闲事
Not that it's any of my business,

535
00:20:52,600 --> 00:20:54,290
但你领带本来不歪的
but it was straight before.

536
00:20:54,720 --> 00:20:55,760
我知道
I know.

537
00:20:55,840 --> 00:20:57,180
我懂了
Oh, I get it.

538
00:20:57,580 --> 00:21:00,450
仪表不整  别人就会低估你
Look less together. Get underestimated.

539
00:21:03,210 --> 00:21:05,400
你得慢点挥手
You gotta wave your hand slower.

540
00:21:08,370 --> 00:21:09,890
-多谢  -不客气
- Thanks. - No problem.

541
00:21:09,890 --> 00:21:12,490
想要肥皂  磕三下脚跟就行
If you want soap, you just click your heels together three times.

542
00:21:12,500 --> 00:21:15,120
那我该怎么启动干手器呢
How do you think I'm planning on getting that dryer to work?

543
00:21:15,120 --> 00:21:16,560
你们收费这么高
You know, you think you wouldn't have these problems,

544
00:21:16,560 --> 00:21:18,060
还以为不会有这些问题
considering what you guys charge.

545
00:21:18,060 --> 00:21:19,730
我不是这里的员工
Oh, no, I don't work here.

546
00:21:19,730 --> 00:21:21,570
-但你  -原来是
- But you, uh-- - I used to.

547
00:21:24,190 --> 00:21:25,790
你是迈克·罗斯
You're Mike Ross.

548
00:21:28,510 --> 00:21:30,330
而你就是洛根·桑德斯了
And you're Logan Sanders.

549
00:21:33,000 --> 00:21:34,060
要纸巾吗
Paper towel?

550
00:21:34,900 --> 00:21:36,200
何不呢
Don't mind if I do.

551
00:21:38,720 --> 00:21:39,650
你先请
After you.

552
00:21:39,650 --> 00:21:42,030
-何不呢  -看来你们见过面了
- Don't mind if I do. - I see you two have met.

553
00:21:42,040 --> 00:21:43,200
没错
We have.

554
00:21:43,220 --> 00:21:45,710
别因为他领带不整就低估他
And don't underestimate him because of his tie.

555
00:21:45,710 --> 00:21:48,640
我一直知道他领带怎么回事
I have always estimated that tie correctly.

556
00:21:49,100 --> 00:21:52,000
能谈正事了吗
Now, can we talk about business?

557
00:21:52,000 --> 00:21:54,510
看你开什么条件了
Depends on what you're proposing.

558
00:21:54,600 --> 00:21:56,040
条件是你放手
That you walk away.

559
00:21:56,160 --> 00:21:57,660
这听着不像是要谈事啊
That doesn't sound like much of a deal.

560
00:21:57,660 --> 00:21:58,660
他忘记说了
Well, he forgot to add the part 

561
00:21:58,660 --> 00:22:00,740
你会带着两千万走人
where you walk away $20 million richer.

562
00:22:01,190 --> 00:22:03,520
纯利润  无风险
Pure profit. No risk.

563
00:22:03,600 --> 00:22:05,280
双赢
Win-win.

564
00:22:06,470 --> 00:22:07,420
好吧
All right.

565
00:22:10,760 --> 00:22:11,840
听着不错
Sounds good.

566
00:22:12,800 --> 00:22:14,630
我只有一个问题
Guess I just have one question.

567
00:22:15,150 --> 00:22:17,110
你收购这家公司后打算怎么办
What exactly are you going to do with this company?

568
00:22:17,110 --> 00:22:19,980
恕我直言  但我觉得这不归你管
All due respect, I don't see how that's any of your concern.

569
00:22:19,980 --> 00:22:21,990
恕我直言  但你是提条件的一方
All due respect, you're the one coming to me with an offer.

570
00:22:21,990 --> 00:22:23,950
所以我说归我管  就归我管
So if I say it's my concern, it is.

571
00:22:23,950 --> 00:22:26,870
麦克  你是要竞争对手透露商业计划吗
Mike, you're asking about a competitor's business plan.

572
00:22:26,870 --> 00:22:28,450
他要是不想继续做竞争对手
And if he wants to not be competitors,

573
00:22:28,450 --> 00:22:30,120
就该回答我的问题
then he needs to answer my question.

574
00:22:30,120 --> 00:22:31,610
那就告诉你
Okay, I'll tell you.

575
00:22:31,610 --> 00:22:34,180
当然是分拆出售  谁都会如此
I'm gonna do what anyone would and sell it for parts.

576
00:22:37,810 --> 00:22:38,750
不行
No deal.

577
00:22:39,320 --> 00:22:40,710
好吧  迈克
Okay, Mike.

578
00:22:41,150 --> 00:22:42,220
你赢了
You win.

579
00:22:43,120 --> 00:22:45,580
三千万怎么样
Let's, uh, make it 30 million.

580
00:22:46,270 --> 00:22:47,440
洛根  即使你愿意出十亿
You could make it a billion, Logan,

581
00:22:47,440 --> 00:22:49,710
我还是会拒绝
and the answer is still gonna be the same.

582
00:22:49,910 --> 00:22:51,410
因为我向沃尔特·吉利斯承诺过
'Cause I made a promise to Walter Gillis

583
00:22:51,410 --> 00:22:53,930
我要为他公司的生存而战
that I would fight to keep his company alive.

584
00:22:53,930 --> 00:22:56,210
然而我觉得签一个出卖他员工的协议
And I don't think he's gonna believe that cutting a deal

585
00:22:56,210 --> 00:22:59,260
可不能算遵守诺言
to sell his workers out is keeping that promise.

586
00:22:59,260 --> 00:23:00,660
你不是说他挺聪明的吗
I thought you said he was smart.

587
00:23:00,670 --> 00:23:02,990
没错  所以我很清楚这里的局面
I am, which I why I know what's going on here.

588
00:23:03,370 --> 00:23:04,860
这里什么局面
What exactly is that?

589
00:23:04,860 --> 00:23:06,690
从没有人对你说过"不"
No one ever tells you no.

590
00:23:07,960 --> 00:23:09,840
你已经习惯要风得风  要雨得雨了
You're used to getting what you want.

591
00:23:10,470 --> 00:23:12,610
可惜到此为止了
But that's gonna stop right now.

592
00:23:12,610 --> 00:23:13,830
你说得没错
You're right. 

593
00:23:13,830 --> 00:23:15,860
我确实要风得风  要雨得雨
I do always get what I want.

594
00:23:15,860 --> 00:23:17,610
这次又有什么不同呢
I don't see how this time's gonna be any different.

595
00:23:17,610 --> 00:23:18,990
我会告诉你有什么不同
I'll tell you how it's gonna be different.

596
00:23:18,990 --> 00:23:21,150
这次谈的  是我关心的事情
This time you're talking about something that I care about.

597
00:23:21,160 --> 00:23:22,710
所以你要是觉得我会袖手旁观
So if you think I'm gonna step aside and let you do--

598
00:23:22,720 --> 00:23:25,200
我才不管你要不要袖手旁观
Yeah, I don't care if you step aside or not.

599
00:23:25,410 --> 00:23:27,250
我看到想要的东西  就弄到手
When I see something I want, I take it,

600
00:23:27,250 --> 00:23:28,710
然后它就随我摆布了
and then I do whatever the hell I want with it.

601
00:23:28,720 --> 00:23:32,040
而对这个公司  我就想把它解体
And what I wanna do with this company is strip it down,

602
00:23:32,040 --> 00:23:33,200
-翻个底朝天  -好了  别说了
- flip it over-- - Okay, that's enough.

603
00:23:33,200 --> 00:23:33,950
不不不  让他说
No, no, no, let him talk.

604
00:23:33,950 --> 00:23:35,130
我很想听  继续说吧  桑德斯
I wanna hear this. Keep going, Sanders.

605
00:23:35,130 --> 00:23:37,310
不用我多说  因为你对结果心知肚明
No, I don't need to because you know how this ends.

606
00:23:37,310 --> 00:23:39,450
对  我知道我会和沃尔特·吉利斯一个阵营
Yeah, I do, with me and Walter Gillis on one side

607
00:23:39,450 --> 00:23:41,550
而你在另一个阵营跟爸爸哭天抹泪
and you crying to your daddy on the other.

608
00:23:41,550 --> 00:23:42,360
到此为止
We're done.

609
00:23:42,360 --> 00:23:43,450
是的
You're right.

610
00:23:44,060 --> 00:23:45,090
到此为止
We are.

611
00:23:47,030 --> 00:23:49,910
听着  下次我说"不要参加会面"时
Listen to me, the next time I say "Don't come to a meeting",

612
00:23:49,910 --> 00:23:50,880
就不要参加会面
don't come to a meeting.

613
00:23:50,880 --> 00:23:51,980
他那么凶狠地攻击我
He came at me just as hard as--

614
00:23:51,990 --> 00:23:53,440
我才不管他做了什么
I don't give a shit what he did.

615
00:23:53,440 --> 00:23:55,220
我要失陪一下
Now, if you'll excuse me.

616
00:23:55,220 --> 00:23:57,770
-你去哪  -去为你夺回这个公司
- Where are you going? - To get you this company.

617
00:23:57,770 --> 00:23:59,570
-你说什么  -你没听他说话吗
- What are you talking about? - Weren't you listening?

618
00:23:59,570 --> 00:24:01,350
他暴露了弱点
He just gave up his weak spot.

619
00:24:04,710 --> 00:24:06,280
詹金斯的事是真的吗
Was that true about Jenkins?

620
00:24:06,670 --> 00:24:08,380
詹金斯是谁我都不知道
I don't even know a Jenkins.

621
00:24:08,380 --> 00:24:11,020
但我知道陶德并没有青筋暴出
But I do know Todd's vein wasn't bulging.

622
00:24:12,170 --> 00:24:13,970
路易  你在会议室表现得很好
And, Louis, you were actually pretty good in there.

623
00:24:13,970 --> 00:24:16,630
我知道  你表现得也不错
Yeah, I was. And so were you.

624
00:24:16,630 --> 00:24:17,480
所以我们意见统一了
So we're in agreement.

625
00:24:17,480 --> 00:24:18,680
是的  你也不是一无是处
Yeah, you don't completely suck.

626
00:24:18,680 --> 00:24:21,430
我是说  我们应该坚持帮陶德·史密斯
I just meant that we should stick by Todd Smith.

627
00:24:21,710 --> 00:24:23,910
他说的太荒唐了  只是有可能真实
That story was so ridiculous, it just might be true.

628
00:24:23,920 --> 00:24:26,340
很好  那我给富顿证券打电话提建议了
Great, I'll call Felton and make the recommendation.

629
00:24:26,340 --> 00:24:28,290
等一下  你要去干什么
Well, hold up. You're gonna do what now?

630
00:24:28,450 --> 00:24:30,650
-打电话给我的客户  -路易
- Call my client? - Louis.

631
00:24:30,720 --> 00:24:32,440
它也许是你的客户  但也是我的案子
It may be your client, but it's still my case.

632
00:24:32,440 --> 00:24:34,050
见鬼  杰夫
Like hell it is, Jeff.

633
00:24:34,050 --> 00:24:37,050
-好吧  那你打  -我是要打
- Okay. Okay, you call. - Oh, I plan to.

634
00:24:37,050 --> 00:24:37,950
我会告诉他们
And when I do, I'll be telling them

635
00:24:37,950 --> 00:24:40,520
那位手滑先生已经不成问题了
that Mr. Slippery Fingers is no longer our problem.

636
00:24:40,520 --> 00:24:42,750
一秒钟之前你还说你相信他
Just one second ago, you said you believed him.

637
00:24:42,750 --> 00:24:45,250
是  我也说了他说得太荒唐
Yeah, I also told you that his story was so ridiculous

638
00:24:45,250 --> 00:24:46,330
没人会相信
and nobody would believe it.

639
00:24:46,340 --> 00:24:48,320
那我们的工作就是让人们相信它  路易
Well, then it's our job to make them believe it, Louis,

640
00:24:48,320 --> 00:24:49,760
否则他可能就要坐牢了
Or this guy could wind up in prison.

641
00:24:49,760 --> 00:24:51,830
我不管他  杰夫
He is not my concern, Jeff.

642
00:24:51,840 --> 00:24:53,990
我管的是富顿证券
Felton Securities is.

643
00:25:03,960 --> 00:25:05,460
沃尔特·吉利斯知道他在干什么
Walter Gillis knows what he's doing.

644
00:25:05,460 --> 00:25:06,270
我也知道
Yeah, so do I.

645
00:25:06,270 --> 00:25:08,210
他是要让你赔上养老金
He's letting your pension go unfunded,

646
00:25:08,210 --> 00:25:09,570
这样他自己就可以囤下十亿美元
So he can hoard $1 billion.

647
00:25:09,580 --> 00:25:13,570
不  那笔钱是要用于发展亚洲业务的
No, that money is earmarked for expansion into Asia.

648
00:25:13,570 --> 00:25:15,440
而且我相信沃尔特的构想
And I believe in Walter's vision.

649
00:25:15,440 --> 00:25:18,310
你相信  可你的员工相信吗
You might, but do the workers you represent?

650
00:25:18,310 --> 00:25:20,390
你说得好像我们已经没有资金了似的
You're acting as if our fund is empty.

651
00:25:20,390 --> 00:25:22,890
我说得是你们只剩40%的资金了
I'm acting as if it's 40% full.

652
00:25:22,890 --> 00:25:25,630
让我猜猜  你是要补上剩下的部分吗
And let me guess, you're gonna fill up the rest.

653
00:25:25,630 --> 00:25:28,530
在我们能出价之前
Someone else wants to acquire Gillis' company

654
00:25:28,530 --> 00:25:30,350
就有其他人想要吉利斯的公司
before we can make an offer.

655
00:25:30,490 --> 00:25:32,060
如果你投反对票
If you vote to block it,

656
00:25:32,080 --> 00:25:35,650
我们一接手公司  就会补上你的养老金
we will fully fund your pension the day we take over.

657
00:25:38,120 --> 00:25:39,980
你是要我出卖朋友
You're talking about me selling out my friend.

658
00:25:39,980 --> 00:25:42,810
我是在跟你谈五亿美元的资金
I'm talking about $500 million.

659
00:25:42,810 --> 00:25:44,530
他们弄不来钱  你们怎么就能
And why can you fund it and they can't?

660
00:25:44,530 --> 00:25:46,530
他们用那五亿可以做到  可他们不愿意
Well, they can with half that billion, but they won't.

661
00:25:46,530 --> 00:25:49,760
就像我说的  他正在为那个白日梦囤积资金
Because like I said, he's hoarding it for that pipe dream.

662
00:25:49,760 --> 00:25:52,300
你会把那十亿美元收入自己腰包
You're gonna take that billion for yourselves.

663
00:25:52,300 --> 00:25:53,340
五亿
Half.

664
00:25:53,540 --> 00:25:55,750
另外五亿给你和你的组织
The other half goes to you and your union--

665
00:25:55,750 --> 00:25:58,710
给那些沃尔特·吉利斯本该关心的人
the men Walter Gillis supposedly cares about.

666
00:25:58,830 --> 00:26:02,180
皮特  换做是别人  事情也会是这样
Pete, this is gonna happen whether it's me or someone else.

667
00:26:02,180 --> 00:26:04,180
而且别人可能不会给你机会
And someone else may not give you the chance to do

668
00:26:04,180 --> 00:26:05,770
去做你应该做的事
what you were elected to do:

669
00:26:07,190 --> 00:26:08,810
保护你的员工
Protect your people.

670
00:26:18,410 --> 00:26:20,260
今天跟哈维会面怎么样
How'd your meeting with Harvey go today?

671
00:26:22,590 --> 00:26:25,230
我们不是说过吗  谈工作是犯规
I thought talking about work was against the rules.

672
00:26:25,350 --> 00:26:27,950
谈工作犯规  但是谈今天过得如何不犯规
Talking about work is. Talking about our day isn't.

673
00:26:27,950 --> 00:26:30,290
如果我们什么都不能谈  那么案子
I mean, if we can't do that, then we're letting the case

674
00:26:30,290 --> 00:26:31,860
就使我们有隔阂了  对吗
come between us, right?

675
00:26:34,580 --> 00:26:36,300
我跟哈维的会面挺好的
My meeting with Harvey went fine.

676
00:26:37,450 --> 00:26:38,970
但你没接受协议
But you didn't take the deal.

677
00:26:40,280 --> 00:26:41,960
因为那个协议不怎么样
Because it wasn't a good deal.

678
00:26:45,030 --> 00:26:46,130
好吧
Fine.

679
00:26:48,770 --> 00:26:50,610
好吧  到底怎么了
Okay, what's the matter with you?

680
00:26:50,610 --> 00:26:54,100
事实是  我都听说了
What's the matter is that I heard what happened.

681
00:26:54,530 --> 00:26:56,260
-听哈维说了  -不  听唐娜说的
- From him? - No, from donna.

682
00:26:56,260 --> 00:26:58,560
但也有可能是听看到你们大吵一架的
But it could have been from any of the 50 people

683
00:26:58,560 --> 00:26:59,900
另外五十个人说的
who saw the two of you going at it.

684
00:26:59,900 --> 00:27:01,110
-瑞秋  -告诉我
- Rachel -- - Just tell me this.

685
00:27:01,120 --> 00:27:03,830
你拒绝协议是因为它不够好
Did you refuse the deal because it wasn't good enough

686
00:27:03,830 --> 00:27:04,910
还是因为那是洛根提的
or because it came from Logan?

687
00:27:04,910 --> 00:27:06,310
你觉得我拒绝这个交易
You think I didn't take this deal

688
00:27:06,310 --> 00:27:08,140
是因为你和这混蛋的那段过去吗
because of your history with this asshole?

689
00:27:08,140 --> 00:27:09,360
你确实叫他混蛋了
Well, you did just call him an asshole.

690
00:27:09,360 --> 00:27:11,670
那是因为他为了赚钱
He's an asshole because he's willing to decimate a company

691
00:27:11,670 --> 00:27:13,570
可以把一家公司大肆拆分
just to put some money in his pocket.

692
00:27:13,570 --> 00:27:16,080
我向沃尔特·吉利斯保证过
Look, I gave my word to Walter Gillis.

693
00:27:16,080 --> 00:27:18,220
我跟哈维和洛根也是这么说的
That's what I told harvey and what I told Logan

694
00:27:18,220 --> 00:27:20,090
我还以为不用再跟你说了
and what I didn't think I'd have to tell you.

695
00:27:20,090 --> 00:27:24,890
我只想说  这一切原本可以在今天结束
I'm just saying, all of this could have been over today.

696
00:27:24,890 --> 00:27:26,700
你以为我不想了结吗
You think I don't want this to be over?

697
00:27:26,700 --> 00:27:27,660
我也想
I do.

698
00:27:27,820 --> 00:27:29,280
但我不能接受那个提议
But I can't take that deal.

699
00:27:29,280 --> 00:27:31,610
而且我们说好不会让工作影响我俩的
And we said we wouldn't let this come between us.

700
00:27:31,610 --> 00:27:32,880
所以别谈了
So don't.

701
00:27:37,210 --> 00:27:38,870
-嗨  唐娜  -嗨  路易
- Hi, Donna. - Hey, Louis.

702
00:27:38,870 --> 00:27:39,880
有什么需要我帮忙的吗
What can I do for you?

703
00:27:39,880 --> 00:27:42,240
我就是过来
Oh, well, I just came in 

704
00:27:42,240 --> 00:27:45,530
把这个和这个
to bring you this and this

705
00:27:45,600 --> 00:27:47,320
还有
and 

706
00:27:47,550 --> 00:27:51,110
这些东西给你
all of these.

707
00:27:51,460 --> 00:27:53,980
你之前评估过的七个同类案件的当事人
Those are the last seven Todd Smiths you evaluated.

708
00:27:53,980 --> 00:27:54,980
-唐娜  -七个
- Donna-- - Seven.

709
00:27:54,980 --> 00:27:56,570
你一个都没有弃之不顾
And you didn't cut one of them loose.

710
00:27:56,570 --> 00:27:58,650
-你听到我和马龙的谈话了  -对
- You heard me and Malone. - I did.

711
00:27:58,650 --> 00:28:00,490
你这次撒手不管是为了刁难他
And you're cutting this guy loose just to spite him.

712
00:28:00,490 --> 00:28:01,540
太可笑了
That's ridiculous.

713
00:28:01,550 --> 00:28:03,800
好  那这次和马龙无关咯
Okay, so this has nothing to do with Malone?

714
00:28:03,800 --> 00:28:04,810
无关
Nothing.

715
00:28:06,360 --> 00:28:07,980
{\an8}皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特

716
00:28:09,320 --> 00:28:09,900
你从哪里弄到的
Where'd you get that?

717
00:28:09,900 --> 00:28:11,690
拜托  你心知肚明
Come on. You know where I got it.

718
00:28:12,010 --> 00:28:13,000
路易
Louis...

719
00:28:16,980 --> 00:28:18,910
我知道他夺走了你的梦想
I know he took your dream.

720
00:28:22,240 --> 00:28:23,880
她想都没考虑过我
I mean, she didn't even consider me.

721
00:28:24,470 --> 00:28:26,410
就把他招进公司  让我训练他
Just brings him in, had me train him,

722
00:28:26,410 --> 00:28:28,230
还把拐角办公室给他
and gives him the corner office.

723
00:28:30,670 --> 00:28:32,930
我告诉过你我在大学时试镜
Hey, did I ever tell you about the time that I auditioned

724
00:28:32,930 --> 00:28:34,760
《哈姆雷特》里的角色吗
for Hamlet in college?

725
00:28:35,790 --> 00:28:37,200
你肯定演得是奥菲利亚[女主角]
Obviously, you played Ophelia.

726
00:28:37,200 --> 00:28:39,390
不  克丽丝·吉福得到了那个角色
No, Chrissy Kiff did.

727
00:28:39,390 --> 00:28:40,960
我是她的替角
I was her understudy,

728
00:28:41,060 --> 00:28:42,720
我当时太嫉妒她了
and I was so jealous.

729
00:28:43,410 --> 00:28:46,200
我发现自己竟然期盼她会出什么事
I found myself wishing that something would happen to her,

730
00:28:46,210 --> 00:28:49,810
比如生个病或者扭到脚
that she would get sick or she would twist an ankle.

731
00:28:50,000 --> 00:28:53,260
后来  就在我们要演出的前一天
And then, the day before we closed...

732
00:28:55,880 --> 00:28:57,520
她父亲去世了
Her father died.

733
00:28:59,730 --> 00:29:01,070
唐娜  这不是你的错
Donna, that wasn't your fault.

734
00:29:01,070 --> 00:29:02,650
但我还是感觉很糟
But I still felt horrible

735
00:29:03,790 --> 00:29:04,950
还很羞愧
and ashamed

736
00:29:06,370 --> 00:29:09,210
因为我的嫉妒引出了我内心的丑陋
'cause my jealousy had brought out something really ugly in me.

737
00:29:11,990 --> 00:29:15,290
你也看得出来  我至今还在后悔
And as you can tell, I still regret that.

738
00:29:17,550 --> 00:29:20,680
你以前从没跟我聊过这类事情
You know you've never told me a story about yourself like that before.

739
00:29:21,770 --> 00:29:24,100
我没跟任何人说过这件事
I've never told anyone that story before.

740
00:29:25,100 --> 00:29:28,910
路易  我知道你很想得到那个位子
Louis, I know how badly you wanted this.

741
00:29:31,040 --> 00:29:32,880
但那关乎一个人的性命
But this is a man's life.

742
00:29:34,100 --> 00:29:35,030
我们不会不管他
We won't cut him loose.

743
00:29:35,030 --> 00:29:36,930
我会告诉马龙
I'll tell Malone.

744
00:29:40,370 --> 00:29:41,870
我为你骄傲  路易
I'm proud of you, Louis.

745
00:29:46,880 --> 00:29:49,940
有人开价让你放弃这次收购吗
Did you get an offer to walk away from your takeover?

746
00:29:49,940 --> 00:29:50,870
有
I did.

747
00:29:50,870 --> 00:29:52,140
什么样的条件
What was the offer?

748
00:29:52,730 --> 00:29:53,580
3000万
$30 million.

749
00:29:53,580 --> 00:29:55,770
而你拒绝了  你脑子有问题吗
And you turned it down? What the hell is wrong with you?

750
00:29:55,770 --> 00:29:57,340
他们会把这个公司分解
They're gonna rip the company apart.

751
00:29:57,340 --> 00:29:59,280
就算他们想用沃尔特·吉利斯的头作镇纸
I don't care if they wanna use Walter Gillis' head

752
00:29:59,280 --> 00:30:00,130
我也不在乎
as a paperweight.

753
00:30:00,130 --> 00:30:01,480
你说你要一次全垒打
You said you wanted a grand slam.

754
00:30:01,480 --> 00:30:02,670
那个只是二垒打
That offer is a double.

755
00:30:02,670 --> 00:30:04,180
那总比什么都没有的强
Well, I'd rather have a double than nothing.

756
00:30:04,180 --> 00:30:05,780
我清楚我现在在做的事
Look, I know what I am doing here.

757
00:30:05,780 --> 00:30:06,750
是吗
Do you?

758
00:30:06,800 --> 00:30:08,320
因为他们刚争取到了工会主席
Because they just flipped the head of the union.

759
00:30:08,320 --> 00:30:10,430
少了他那一票  我们什么都没有
And without his vote, we don't have shit.

760
00:30:10,510 --> 00:30:12,170
-什么  -这些人是动真格的
- What? - These guys play to win.

761
00:30:12,170 --> 00:30:15,240
他们刚保证将五亿美金捐给退休基金
They just promised $1/2-billion donation to their pension fund.

762
00:30:15,240 --> 00:30:17,110
除非沃尔特·吉利斯也能出那么多
And unless Walter Gillis is gonna match it,

763
00:30:17,110 --> 00:30:18,110
否则就玩完了
we're done.

764
00:30:19,160 --> 00:30:20,010
是
Yeah.

765
00:30:20,300 --> 00:30:21,450
我是这么想的
That's what I thought.

766
00:30:22,900 --> 00:30:24,790
要么接受3000万的开价
You get that $30 million,

767
00:30:24,820 --> 00:30:26,550
要么你另谋高就吧
or you find yourself another job.

768
00:30:31,880 --> 00:30:34,370
唐娜  你有什么需要吗
Donna, did you need something?

769
00:30:34,370 --> 00:30:37,080
不  但路易有
No, but Louis does.

770
00:30:38,380 --> 00:30:40,750
在你和哈维见杰夫·马龙之前
He was planning to pitch you that he take on Jeff Malone

771
00:30:40,750 --> 00:30:42,170
他就想向你毛遂自荐
before you and Harvey even met him.

772
00:30:42,170 --> 00:30:43,930
他先我们一步预见到伍德尔想对付我们吗
He saw Woodall coming before we did?

773
00:30:43,930 --> 00:30:44,720
如果他赢了
And if he won,

774
00:30:44,720 --> 00:30:47,500
他本以为能成为冠名合伙人
he was hoping that that would mean name partner.

775
00:30:48,440 --> 00:30:50,690
我理解  唐娜  真的
I empathize with that, Donna. I do.

776
00:30:50,690 --> 00:30:53,290
但我得从律所的利益出发  作出决策
But I have to make decisions based on what's best for the firm.

777
00:30:53,290 --> 00:30:54,900
我不是来劝你改变心意
And I'm not here to change your mind,

778
00:30:54,900 --> 00:30:56,840
但你可以为路易做点别的
but maybe if you did something else for Louis--

779
00:30:56,990 --> 00:30:58,160
比如
Such as?

780
00:30:58,530 --> 00:30:59,880
给他拐角办公室
Giving him the corner office.

781
00:30:59,880 --> 00:31:01,440
你是指杰夫·马龙的办公室
You mean Jeff Malone's office?

782
00:31:01,440 --> 00:31:03,290
他可以搬到路易那间去
He could move to Louis'.

783
00:31:04,110 --> 00:31:06,740
感谢你提醒我路易的事
I appreciate you letting me know about Louis,

784
00:31:06,980 --> 00:31:08,080
但我不会那么做的
but I'm not going to do that.

785
00:31:08,080 --> 00:31:09,600
为什么  杰夫·马龙才刚进律所
Well, why not? Jeff Malone just got here.

786
00:31:09,600 --> 00:31:11,690
因为我说了算  如果你没有别的事...
Because I said so. Now if you'll excuse me--

787
00:31:11,690 --> 00:31:13,040
你跟他睡了
You're sleeping with him.

788
00:31:13,620 --> 00:31:14,890
-什么  -显然
- What? - Of course.

789
00:31:14,900 --> 00:31:17,890
那气色  晨会  让哈维替你赴约
That glow, the morning meetings, you had Harvey take your lunch.

790
00:31:17,900 --> 00:31:19,900
我怎么没注意到呢  我没以前敏锐了
How could I miss it? I'm losing my edge.

791
00:31:19,900 --> 00:31:24,110
唐娜  我和马龙之间没有...
Donna, there is nothing going on between--

792
00:31:26,970 --> 00:31:28,570
你还是跟以往一样敏锐
You're not losing your edge.

793
00:31:28,640 --> 00:31:31,400
但我雇佣杰夫·马龙的当天
But I ended my relationship with Jeff Malone

794
00:31:31,400 --> 00:31:33,050
就跟他分手了
the day that I hired him.

795
00:31:33,480 --> 00:31:34,870
值得尊敬
And I respect that.

796
00:31:35,100 --> 00:31:36,420
但你说你做决策
But you said you make decisions

797
00:31:36,420 --> 00:31:38,350
是考虑到律所的利益
based on what's best for the firm.

798
00:31:39,240 --> 00:31:42,310
把路易的尊严还给他难道对律所不好吗
Isn't giving Louis his dignity back good for the firm?

799
00:31:47,220 --> 00:31:48,590
我收到你的信息了
Hey, I got your message.

800
00:31:48,590 --> 00:31:50,300
一般有人想谈生意...
Usually when someone wants to talk business--

801
00:31:50,310 --> 00:31:51,870
我想接受你们的提议
I want to take your offer.

802
00:31:54,060 --> 00:31:56,870
迈克  那交易已经过时了
Mike, that offer's gone.

803
00:31:56,960 --> 00:31:58,810
如果我要少点呢
And what if I told you I'd take less?

804
00:31:58,970 --> 00:32:00,430
少点也给不了
I'd say I can't give you less.

805
00:32:00,430 --> 00:32:02,110
拜托  是你们要和解
Come on, you're the guy who settles.

806
00:32:02,110 --> 00:32:04,940
我现在告诉你我想和解了
I'm telling you I wanna settle.

807
00:32:04,940 --> 00:32:07,290
你是说你必须得和解了
You're telling me you have to settle.

808
00:32:07,290 --> 00:32:09,120
我知道你能拿回那份要约
And I know that you can get that offer back.

809
00:32:09,120 --> 00:32:10,340
但那不是我的工作
It's not my job to get it back.

810
00:32:10,340 --> 00:32:12,200
就算是  你觉得你说了那些话后
And even if it was, you think he's gonna give you a nickel

811
00:32:12,200 --> 00:32:13,280
他还会给你一分钱吗
after what you said to him?

812
00:32:13,280 --> 00:32:14,970
我说的话  那他说的话怎么算
What I said to him?What about what he said to me?

813
00:32:14,970 --> 00:32:16,530
我不关心他说了什么
I don't care what he said to you.

814
00:32:16,530 --> 00:32:17,560
我给了你一条出路
I gave you a way out,

815
00:32:17,560 --> 00:32:19,270
但你非得去开会
and you insisted on going to that meeting.

816
00:32:19,270 --> 00:32:21,380
你那不是为我  是为了你的客户
You didn't do that for me. You did that for your client.

817
00:32:21,380 --> 00:32:24,180
有什么区别  那计划是双赢
What difference does it make? It was a win-goddamn-win.

818
00:32:24,180 --> 00:32:25,740
而你把它当狗屎了
And you shit all over it.

819
00:32:25,740 --> 00:32:27,270
现在我说  我接受
Now I'm saying, I'll take it.

820
00:32:27,270 --> 00:32:28,990
可事情不会顺你心了
Yeah, well, it doesn't work that way.

821
00:32:29,000 --> 00:32:30,240
我是出于礼节才来的
I'm here as a courtesy.

822
00:32:30,240 --> 00:32:32,320
你来是因为你要输了
You're only here because you lost.

823
00:32:32,320 --> 00:32:33,830
-哈维  我...  -够了
- Harvey, I'm-- - Enough.

824
00:32:34,640 --> 00:32:37,670
那家公司命运已定  早就定了
That company's fate is sealed. It always has been.

825
00:32:37,670 --> 00:32:40,640
下次你离开谈判桌时
And the next time you walk away from the table,

826
00:32:40,640 --> 00:32:43,190
准备好承担后果
be prepared to walk away from the table.

827
00:32:59,750 --> 00:33:00,950
能给我倒一杯吗
Wanna pour me one of those?

828
00:33:00,950 --> 00:33:02,090
请自便吧
Help yourself.

829
00:33:04,710 --> 00:33:07,630
迈克·罗斯怎么了
So what's going on with Mike Ross?

830
00:33:07,630 --> 00:33:09,460
你怎么知道我在想迈克·罗斯的事
How do you know I'm thinking about mike ross?

831
00:33:09,460 --> 00:33:10,810
还能是谁呢
Who else would it be?

832
00:33:10,810 --> 00:33:12,220
他把你逼入绝境了
He got you on the ropes?

833
00:33:13,250 --> 00:33:14,550
是我把他逼入绝境了
No, I got him.

834
00:33:15,480 --> 00:33:16,620
他要完了
And he's about to go down.

835
00:33:16,620 --> 00:33:17,700
你怎么知道
How do you know?

836
00:33:17,700 --> 00:33:19,210
因为他要还想玩下去
'Cause the only way to stay in the game

837
00:33:19,210 --> 00:33:22,180
只能让沃尔特·吉利斯放弃梦想
is to get Walter Gillis to give up his dream.

838
00:33:23,280 --> 00:33:25,300
而你觉得他不愿意
And you don't think he has the stomach

839
00:33:25,400 --> 00:33:27,100
断臂求生
to rip off the arm to save the body.

840
00:33:27,100 --> 00:33:28,530
对  他不愿意
No, he doesn't.

841
00:33:29,520 --> 00:33:31,290
你好像赢了也不太高兴
You don't seem to feel good about that.

842
00:33:31,460 --> 00:33:32,630
是不高兴
No, I don't.

843
00:33:33,610 --> 00:33:34,870
哈维
Harvey.

844
00:33:36,580 --> 00:33:38,960
你记得我把柯林斯的案子给你的时候吗
Do you remember when I gave you the Collins case?

845
00:33:39,040 --> 00:33:39,770
记得
Yeah.

846
00:33:39,770 --> 00:33:42,190
很残忍  但我们必须做
It was brutal, what we had to do.

847
00:33:42,830 --> 00:33:44,950
那是我第一次遇到那样的事
It was my first taste of that kind of thing.

848
00:33:44,950 --> 00:33:46,410
而你喜欢那感觉
And you loved it.

849
00:33:46,590 --> 00:33:47,700
你想说什么
What's your point?

850
00:33:47,700 --> 00:33:50,550
有些人就是喜欢血腥味
Some people love the taste of blood.

851
00:33:50,900 --> 00:33:53,220
有些人就...
Other people, hmm.

852
00:33:54,020 --> 00:33:56,930
早点认清自己总是好的
Better to find out who you are sooner than later.

853
00:33:56,930 --> 00:33:58,850
你说我在帮他
You saying I'm doing him a favor?

854
00:33:58,860 --> 00:34:02,370
我是说  你在做自己
I'm saying, you're being who you are

855
00:34:02,380 --> 00:34:04,640
同时也在让他做自己
and letting him be who he is.

856
00:34:18,650 --> 00:34:19,940
你在做什么
What are you doing?

857
00:34:22,350 --> 00:34:23,460
只是在想
I'm just thinking about how much

858
00:34:23,460 --> 00:34:25,440
以后会多想念自己的办公室
I'm going to miss having my own office.

859
00:34:25,440 --> 00:34:28,210
把自尊心放一放  你还可以去找哈维
Put your pride away, okay? You can still go back to Harvey.

860
00:34:28,210 --> 00:34:29,660
我去找过他
I went back to Harvey.

861
00:34:30,510 --> 00:34:32,620
交易已经作废了
The money's off the table.

862
00:34:34,630 --> 00:34:36,570
那你必须改变投票结果
Then you have to flip that vote.

863
00:34:36,580 --> 00:34:39,090
唯一的办法是让沃尔特·吉利斯
The only way to do that is to get Walter Gillis

864
00:34:39,090 --> 00:34:43,060
往养老基金里投5亿美元
to put $500 million into that pension fund.

865
00:34:43,060 --> 00:34:45,550
如果他那么做  就会失去扩张能力
And if he does that, he loses his expansion.

866
00:34:45,550 --> 00:34:46,530
迈克  那就去做
Mike, then do it.

867
00:34:46,530 --> 00:34:50,260
艾米  他儿子死后  这公司就是他的家
Amy, when his son died, this company became his family.

868
00:34:50,260 --> 00:34:52,730
如果他不扩张  他的公司也会死
If he doesn't expand, then his company's gonna die too.

869
00:34:52,730 --> 00:34:54,860
我要求他那么做  就比洛根好不到哪去
I ask him to do that, then I'm no better than Logan.

870
00:34:54,860 --> 00:34:56,670
不  你比他好  因为做完这事
No, you are better, because after you do this,

871
00:34:56,670 --> 00:34:58,240
你还会拼尽全力让他们活下去
you're still gonna fight to keep them alive.

872
00:34:58,240 --> 00:35:00,040
吉利斯不会那么看问题
Gillis is not gonna see it that way.

873
00:35:00,040 --> 00:35:01,750
他只会看到狡猾的银行家
He's just gonna see some slick banker

874
00:35:01,750 --> 00:35:03,940
给了他美好愿景  却做了跟别人一样的事
who sold him a bill of goods just to end up doing

875
00:35:03,940 --> 00:35:06,450
至少别人还来得直截了当
what everybody else was at least up front about.

876
00:35:09,250 --> 00:35:11,070
那你干嘛不卷卷你的破铺盖
Then why don't you just pack up your shit

877
00:35:11,080 --> 00:35:13,070
夹着尾巴爬出去呢
and crawl out of here with your tail between your legs?

878
00:35:13,070 --> 00:35:15,740
如果你搞不定这事
Because if you don't have the stomach to handle this,

879
00:35:15,740 --> 00:35:17,390
就没资格待在这里
then you don't belong here.

880
00:35:21,520 --> 00:35:23,670
我收到你信息了
Hey, uh, got your message.

881
00:35:23,680 --> 00:35:25,420
富顿证券出什么问题了吗
Is there something wrong with Felton Securities?

882
00:35:25,420 --> 00:35:26,190
完全没有
Not at all.

883
00:35:26,190 --> 00:35:27,270
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.

884
00:35:27,270 --> 00:35:30,550
我以为要在马龙办公室见是因为那个
I just assumed since you wanted to meet here in Malone's office.

885
00:35:30,830 --> 00:35:32,510
这不是他的办公室了
Oh, this isn't his office anymore.

886
00:35:32,780 --> 00:35:34,030
他被开了吗
Oh, did he get fired?

887
00:35:34,110 --> 00:35:36,160
不  但他要搬出去了
No, but he is moving.

888
00:35:36,880 --> 00:35:40,030
路易  我知道对你而言
Louis, I know it hasn't always been easy for you

889
00:35:40,030 --> 00:35:41,830
接受新合伙人一直不容易
to embrace new partners,

890
00:35:42,610 --> 00:35:45,760
你确实努力接受了杰夫
but you've made a great effort with Jeff.

891
00:35:46,080 --> 00:35:47,100
一天的工作而已
All in a day's work.

892
00:35:47,100 --> 00:35:50,600
你这一天可以让律所受益几年
And your day's work has benefited this firm for years.

893
00:35:51,170 --> 00:35:53,210
所以我觉得该给你
So we thought it was time to show you

894
00:35:53,210 --> 00:35:55,140
一点迟到的奖赏了
a little overdue appreciation.

895
00:36:06,180 --> 00:36:07,490
这间办公室
This office?

896
00:36:11,960 --> 00:36:13,170
我把这件办公室给杰夫
I gave this office to Jeff

897
00:36:13,170 --> 00:36:15,400
是因为我想让他感觉受到了重视
because I wanted him to feel valued here.

898
00:36:16,260 --> 00:36:20,690
但实际上  我应该把它给你
But the truth is, I-- I should have given it to you.

899
00:36:26,900 --> 00:36:28,330
我不知道该说什么好
I don't know what to say.

900
00:36:29,510 --> 00:36:30,640
好吧
Oh, okay.

901
00:36:30,700 --> 00:36:32,250
好了  哭出来吧
All right, let it out.

902
00:36:33,830 --> 00:36:34,440
不可能
No way.

903
00:36:34,440 --> 00:36:36,140
皮特·科瑞林永远不会支持他们
Pete Kreeling would never side with them.

904
00:36:36,140 --> 00:36:37,730
他会  他已经这样做了
He would, and he has,

905
00:36:37,730 --> 00:36:39,510
因为他们给了他你给不了的东西
because they offered what you couldn't--

906
00:36:39,510 --> 00:36:40,910
给他的工人们的保障
security for his workers.

907
00:36:40,920 --> 00:36:41,850
他们是我的工人
They're my goddamn workers.

908
00:36:41,850 --> 00:36:43,840
那就让他们知道你在乎他们
Then show them that you care about them.

909
00:36:44,170 --> 00:36:46,010
拨款给养老金  现在就拨款
Fund the pension, and fund it now.

910
00:36:46,010 --> 00:36:47,710
你说过你会尽力阻止这种事情发生
You told me you'd fight to keep this from happening.

911
00:36:47,710 --> 00:36:49,540
我告诉你我会尽力保护你的公司
I told you I would fight to protect your company.

912
00:36:49,540 --> 00:36:51,770
而现在  这是实现这个目标的最好方法
And right now, this is the best way of doing that.

913
00:36:51,770 --> 00:36:54,250
这需要动用我本想用来扩张的钱
You're talking about using my expansion money.

914
00:36:54,250 --> 00:36:55,400
如果你现在不用那笔钱
If you don't use it now,

915
00:36:55,400 --> 00:36:57,130
就没有公司可以让你扩张了
there's gonna be nothing to expand.

916
00:36:57,130 --> 00:36:58,940
你个混蛋  你利用了我
You son of a bitch, you manipulated me.

917
00:36:58,940 --> 00:37:00,760
不  我告诉你战争即将打响
No, I told you a war was coming

918
00:37:00,760 --> 00:37:02,070
而你需要战争基金
and that you needed a war chest.

919
00:37:02,070 --> 00:37:03,640
现在是这笔钱派上用场的时候了
Well, now is the time to crack it open.

920
00:37:03,650 --> 00:37:07,190
你告诉我我想听的  让我和你站在一边
You told me what I wanted to hear to get me on your side.

921
00:37:07,320 --> 00:37:08,010
你和他们一个德行
You're the same as them.

922
00:37:08,010 --> 00:37:09,740
你错了  我当着你的面
You're wrong. I looked you in the eye,

923
00:37:09,740 --> 00:37:11,940
告诉你我想保住你的公司
and I told you that I wanted to save your company.

924
00:37:11,940 --> 00:37:13,150
他们却当着我的面
They looked me in the eye

925
00:37:13,150 --> 00:37:14,570
告诉我他们想把它拆得七零八落
and told me they wanted to rip it apart.

926
00:37:14,570 --> 00:37:15,850
你和他们一个德行
You're the same as them!

927
00:37:15,850 --> 00:37:18,100
而你是一个幼稚的老头
And you're an naive old man having a tantrum

928
00:37:18,100 --> 00:37:19,730
稍不如意就乱发脾气
because he's not getting his way!

929
00:37:35,600 --> 00:37:37,760
这次扩张是我的梦想
That expansion was my dream.

930
00:37:39,260 --> 00:37:40,150
我理解
I know.

931
00:37:47,300 --> 00:37:49,100
但现在是梦醒的时候了
But now it's time to wake up.

932
00:37:51,570 --> 00:37:53,290
拨款给养老基金吧  沃尔特
Fund the pension, Walter.

933
00:37:54,480 --> 00:37:57,470
皮特·科瑞林会把票投给我们
Pete Kreeling's vote stays in our favor, and...

934
00:37:59,990 --> 00:38:02,050
我们还有资本卷土重来
we live to fight another day.

935
00:38:08,500 --> 00:38:09,090
{\an8}《彗星美人》

936
00:38:12,330 --> 00:38:12,920
不行
No.

937
00:38:12,920 --> 00:38:15,500
我只是想感谢你  给我新办公室
I just wanted to thank you, you know, for the new office.

938
00:38:15,500 --> 00:38:16,670
那是降级
It's a downgrade.

939
00:38:16,670 --> 00:38:17,610
对我来说不是
Not to me.

940
00:38:17,960 --> 00:38:19,980
我还想因为午饭感谢你
I also wanted to thank you for lunch.

941
00:38:19,980 --> 00:38:21,330
午饭我没有出现
I didn't show up for lunch.

942
00:38:21,330 --> 00:38:23,610
我知道  你以为你借此传达了一种讯息
I know.You thought you were sending me a message.

943
00:38:23,610 --> 00:38:25,270
我就是在向你传达讯息
I was sending you a message.

944
00:38:25,270 --> 00:38:27,110
并不是你想的那种讯息  杰西卡
Not the one you wanted, Jessica.

945
00:38:27,110 --> 00:38:28,480
因为从我的角度看
You see, because what I heard is that

946
00:38:28,480 --> 00:38:30,760
你没有信心在接近我的时候克制自己
you don't trust yourself around me.

947
00:38:31,580 --> 00:38:32,860
如果我没有
If I didn't,

948
00:38:34,300 --> 00:38:36,240
我就不会把你安排在我隔壁
I wouldn't have put you right next door.

949
00:38:36,290 --> 00:38:37,810
杰西卡  随便你怎么说
Jessica, say what you will,

950
00:38:37,870 --> 00:38:40,050
但你我都知道结局会是
but we both know where this is headed--

951
00:38:40,470 --> 00:38:43,300
你和我一起看这部电影
you and me watching these.

952
00:38:43,510 --> 00:38:45,510
你以为自己非常了解我
You think you know me that well?

953
00:38:45,510 --> 00:38:46,710
就算不了解
Well, if I don't,

954
00:38:47,100 --> 00:38:48,380
也快了
I'm about to.

955
00:38:51,220 --> 00:38:52,170
邻居
Neighbor.

956
00:38:57,990 --> 00:39:01,040
再过来一点  过来一点  好了
More. More. More. Ah, ah.

957
00:39:02,990 --> 00:39:03,960
谢谢
Thank you.

958
00:39:10,140 --> 00:39:11,670
乔迁贺礼
Happy corner office.

959
00:39:13,770 --> 00:39:14,680
打开啊
Open it.

960
00:39:18,300 --> 00:39:19,940
-这是...  -我
- Is this... - Me.

961
00:39:20,770 --> 00:39:22,210
扮演奥菲丽娅
As Ophelia.

962
00:39:23,650 --> 00:39:24,680
但我以为你...
But I thought you--

963
00:39:24,680 --> 00:39:26,300
是的  不过
Yeah, well,

964
00:39:27,520 --> 00:39:29,510
有时候苦涩的回忆
sometimes bitter memories

965
00:39:30,790 --> 00:39:32,410
会变得甘苦参半
become bittersweet

966
00:39:35,320 --> 00:39:36,940
当你和朋友分享
when you share them with a friend.

967
00:40:14,510 --> 00:40:15,990
你是来接瑞秋的吗
You here to pick up Rachel?

968
00:40:16,160 --> 00:40:17,030
不是
No.

969
00:40:17,070 --> 00:40:19,840
不  我是顺道过来感谢你的
No, I just came by to say thanks.

970
00:40:20,020 --> 00:40:21,000
为了什么
For what?

971
00:40:21,490 --> 00:40:23,230
为你没有给我退路
For not giving me a way out.

972
00:40:25,610 --> 00:40:27,060
你们给养老金拨款了
You funded the pension.

973
00:40:27,330 --> 00:40:28,660
没错
100%.

974
00:40:29,750 --> 00:40:31,890
你刚刚花掉了你一半的战争基金
You just got rid of half your war chest.

975
00:40:31,890 --> 00:40:32,750
可能吧
Maybe,

976
00:40:32,750 --> 00:40:36,170
但我也做到了你以为我做不到的事
but I also did what you thought I couldn't do.

977
00:40:38,000 --> 00:40:39,210
我把投票争取回来了
I got the vote back.

978
00:40:40,180 --> 00:40:43,510
现在你大概能明白我的决心了吧
Maybe now you'll realize that I'm willing to go the distance.

979
00:40:44,820 --> 00:40:46,550
你不过是坚持到了第二轮
All you did was make it to round two.

980
00:40:46,550 --> 00:40:47,520
你以为
Oh, so you thought

981
00:40:47,520 --> 00:40:50,240
这会像泰森前期的比赛
this was gonna be like one of those early Tyson fights,

982
00:40:50,330 --> 00:40:52,840
只需45秒就一边倒结束吗
the ones that only lasted 45 seconds.

983
00:40:53,910 --> 00:40:55,050
还记得第一次有人坚持过第一轮时
Remember what happened the first time

984
00:40:55,050 --> 00:40:56,720
发生了什么事吗
someone made it out of round one?

985
00:40:57,640 --> 00:41:00,080
{\an8}詹姆斯·道格拉斯
第一个打败泰森的拳手  但只昙花一现

986
00:40:57,640 --> 00:41:00,080
但道格拉斯最后又怎样了呢
And what ever did happen to Buster Douglas?

987
00:41:00,160 --> 00:41:02,630
我不知道  但无论后来如何
I don't know, but wherever he is,

988
00:41:02,880 --> 00:41:04,950
胜利永远摆在那里
they can't take that title away from him.

989
00:41:19,570 --> 00:41:20,680
你在做什么呢
What you working on?

990
00:41:21,140 --> 00:41:23,040
你知道我在做什么
You know what I'm working on.

991
00:41:24,240 --> 00:41:25,310
想回家吗
You wanna go home?

992
00:41:29,180 --> 00:41:30,070
哈维
Harvey.

993
00:41:31,710 --> 00:41:34,000
我猜这意味着你要加班了
Guess that means you're gonna be working late, huh?

994
00:41:39,960 --> 00:41:42,010
这要归功于我们的对手
Thanks to the guy we're up against.

995
00:41:42,010 --> 00:41:46,180
事实证明他比所有人预想的要更强
He is proving to be much tougher than everyone expected.

996
00:41:46,180 --> 00:41:47,280
所有人
Everyone?

997
00:41:47,470 --> 00:41:48,760
不是所有人
Not everyone.

998
00:41:53,580 --> 00:41:55,800
听起来这人是个十足的混蛋
He sounds like a real douche bag.

999
00:42:00,140 --> 00:42:02,020
其实他也没那么强
You know, he's not that tough.

1000
00:42:04,580 --> 00:42:06,370
我可以明天接着干
I can work on this tomorrow.

1001
00:42:06,860 --> 00:42:08,070
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.

1002
00:42:14,930 --> 00:42:18,370
你真的要明天再工作吗
You really gonna work on that tomorrow?

1003
00:42:18,370 --> 00:42:20,320
不  我一会儿要继续
No, I'm going to work on it later tonight,

1004
00:42:20,320 --> 00:42:22,170
但至少是会家工作
but at least I'll be home.

1005
00:42:23,560 --> 00:42:25,010
你做完后能给我看一眼吗
Think I can take a look at it when you're done?

1006
00:42:25,010 --> 00:42:25,940
不可以
I think not.

1007
00:42:25,940 --> 00:42:27,360
只是帮你校对一下
Just a proofread?

1008
00:42:27,360 --> 00:42:28,540
还是不行
Ah, still no.

